[pleasant music]
[bells tolling]
Oh, man. Late again.
[bell tolling,
and groaning]
(man)
Later. Oh! Gotta go!
Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you have
the time?.
No, I don't, I'm so sorry.
Okay.
[man whistles]
Hey, there, Rainy.
Come here, boy. Good boy.
[groaning and panting]
Good boy. Have a good day.
Hey. Hi Rainy. Hey.
Hey, boy.
Come on, Rainy.
Good boy.
(man)
Hey, Rainy.
Come here.
Hey, boy. Good dog.
Hey, Rainy. Come to Mama.
Let me give you a big hug.
(man)
Hey, Rainy, have a treat.
Hey! Cool dog!
[groaning]
Good boy.
[clapping]
[music continues]
[panting]
[rings bell]
Hey, there, Rainy.
Deliver this for me?.
Sweet.
Thanks.
Morning, folks.
Morning.
[whimpers]
[romantic music]
[twinkle sound]
Look at that!
[both chuckle]
[groans]
[romantic music continues]
[humming]
[honks]
Hey, Rainy!
Hey, there.
[alarm clock]
[panting]
[turns alarm off]
I'm tired.
[groaning]
[chuckling]
No, Rainy.
No! Just one more minute.
[groaning]
[chuckling]
Oh, man! I'm late.
[whining]
Let me go brush my teeth.
[groaning]
What would I do
without you, boy?.
[whine and twinkle]
Good morning.
Jimmy, sit
down and eat some
breakfast, please.
But I'm
late, Laura.
Sit down,
young man.
All my friends
are waiting
for me. Dad?.
Son, you gotta
figure out a way
to get to bed earlier.
But it's a holiday.
Do you have
money for lunch?.
Yeah. Bye.
Come here, Rainy.
(Laura)
That's no breakfast
for a grown boy, Dean.
I know I 'm not his mother,
but you have to be firmer
with him sometimes.
He'll be fine, doll.
Have you told him yet?.
No.
Honey, it's gonna
be difficult enough
knowing he has to move.
Even more difficult
because of Rainy.
You need to speak to him.
I know. It's just--
It's gonna break his heart.
[train horn and rap music]
Did you eat
your breakfast, boy?.
[whimpers]
Okay then. I got your
favorite snack right here.
But remember,
Dad doesn't think
it's good for your teeth.
[rap music continues to play
on their earphones]
[groans]
What's wrong boy?.
What's the matter?.
(girl)
Help!
Help me, please!
I can't hold on!
Help me! Help me!
[sobbing]
[suspense music]
Sharon!
We have to do something, boy.
[groans]
(Sharon)
Help me! Help me!
[screaming]
Hang on, I'll go get help.
Jimmy, help!
[barking]
Help me!
[sobbing]
[barking]
That's it, Rainy!
Please, please help me.
[groaning]
Please Rainy,
help me.
Help me. Please.
Please, Rainy.
Grab Rainy's collar!
[groaning]
(Jimmy)
Reach, Sharon! Reach!
[groaning]
(Jimmy)
Closer!
Pull her, Rainy!
Good boy. Good boy.
[groaning]
[triumphant music]
(man)
Sharon! Over here!
Daddy! Daddy!
Dad. Rainy saved me.
(Jimmy)
Good job, Rainy.
Dad.
Sharon. Oh.
Sweetheart, are
you okay?.
What happened?.
I lost control
of my bicycle.
He saved me.
Well, he
sure did.
He's a heck
of a dog.
He's a hero.
I love you, Rainy.
Did you
hear that boy?.
You're a hero.
Now what
can we do
for Rainy?.
How about
a big juicy bone?.
(father)
You got it!
I love you, too.
[cheering]
(man)
That dog's a hero!
Yee-ha!
Hey, Rainy.
Look over there.
(Jimmy)
Did you see that?
Hey, can I have one?.
(announcer)
Jefferson High
marching band!
Whoo!
You're a hero.
[several animals howling]
[groaning]
[whining]
[all, meowing]
[groaning]
[roaring]
Dad!
Hey, sport.
How was your
day today, huh?.
It was so much fun.
Rainy is a star.
Hey, Rainy,
did you get your
errands all done?.
[barking]
(Laura)
Dinner!
Come on, boy.
Let's go.
(Laura)
Would you like
to say grace this
evening, Jimmy?
Sure. Thank you
Lord for this food,
for rest and home
and all things good,
but most of all,
for those we love.
Specially, Rainy. Amen.
[Rainy groans]
Amen.
Well, it sure
smells good, honey.
You know, Jimmy,
we have some exciting
news to tell you.
We're going on vacation?.
Not exactly. But we are
going somewhere this
coming weekend.
Where?.
Well, your father
got a big promotion.
He's gonna be
the general manager
of a new insurance office
in New York City.
Isn't that great news?.
Does this mean
we have to move?.
Well, yes it does, sport.
You'll love it, Jimmy.
It's so much more
exciting than here.
None of this small town
thinking there.
But I like Eagle Rock.
And what about my friends?.
Well, you'll
make new friends.
Sport, we'll be able
to come back and visit
from time to time.
Well, you boys can.
Well, I suppose
that'll be okay.
Rainy and l
are pretty good
at making friends.
[sighs]
[melancholy music]
Jimmy, we can't take Rainy.
What do you mean?.
(Laura)
The apartment
the company's paying for
doesn't allow pets
But Rainy's part
of the family. Right Dad?.
Yes, he is.
Then we have to take him.
We can hide him,
and he'll be quiet
and nobody will know.
Jimmy, this is very
important to your father.
We've all made sacrifices
so he can get this promotion.
Now I don't think
we can be selfish
about it now, can we?
But it's Rainy.
We can't leave him alone.
Jimmy, we talked to Charlie.
He's a security guard
at the Fairgrounds
and he's agreed to look
after Rainy until we find
an apartment that allows pets.
You called him,
didn't you, honey?
Y es. And Charlie told me
he loves animals.
And he promised to take very
good care of Rainy until we
find another apartment.
He promised.
No! I won't go!
I 'm staying here
with Rainy.
Come on, boy.
Jimmy!
I told you!
Laura, the boy lost
his mother five years ago,
And now he feels
like he's gonna lose
his best friend.
It's not so easy for him.
[melancholy music]
Hi, Mommy.
I miss you
so much.
I have some
really bad news.
We're movin'
to New York City
so I don't think I'll be
seeing you as much
[sniffs]
I'm sorry.
And the worst thing is,
is that Rainy
can't come with us.
[whining]
I wish you could hold me
just one more time.
Can you please ask God
if he can take care of Rainy?
I mean, he's
a really good dog
and I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Come on, boy.
[horses neighing]
[several animal noises]
It doesn't look
like he'll have
many friends here.
He'll have plenty of room
to run around, Jimmy.
It's only temporary.
Dad, can we
please take him?.
I'm sorry, son.
It's just not
possible now.
But I promise,
I'll find another apartment
as soon as we can, okay?.
Come on, sport.
[funny horn honking]
[animal bleating]
Well, hello.
What can I do for you?.
Hi, I'm Laura Warner.
I called you a couple
days ago about our dog.
Oh, yeah.
So, where's the animal?.
His name
is Rainy.
Of course it is.
Hey, and don't worry.
I'll take real good
care of him.
I got a real nice place
for him right inside.
Can I come say goodbye?.
Well, uh, parish regulations--
Please! He's
my best friend
in the whole world.
All right.
You gonna get him?.
(Jimmy)
Promise to give him
leftovers? He especially
loves chicken.
Sure. Fine.
Stay there.
Okay.
[whimpering]
Come on, Rainy.
Come on. Let's go.
All right, now,
put him in there.
Could I have
a minute with him?.
[sighs]
Make it quick!
Guess this is where
you'll be staying
for now, boy.
[sighs]
[whimpering]
[melancholy music]
I'm so sorry, Rainy.
I'll miss you so much.
[whimpering]
But, I'll check in, okay?.
Here.
This is where we're going.
It's New York City.
Here's our address.
In case you ever
wanna come to visit
us. Okay?.
And I'm also
leaving this with you.
So, you can play
your favorite song
and never forget me.
[whimpering]
Well, I guess that's it.
I'll see you again soon.
[whimpering]
I love you, Rainy.
Bye.
[whimpering]
You okay, sport?.
[melancholy music]
(Dad)
Off we go.
(announcer over speakers)
All passengers
to New York City
the train will leave
from Platform Five
in ten minutes.
All passengers
to New York City,
ten minutes.
[train horn]
[lively music]
(Laura)
Look at this. Park A venue,
Rockefeller Center,
Grand T erminal shopping.
This is really
so exciting,
isn't it, boys?.
Well, our lives
are about to change
for the better.
Hey. I got
a surprise for you.
Season tickets
for the Yankees.
I love you, Jimmy.
You're gonna have
to trust me on this.
Come on.
Try and cheer up, son.
I thought we were
near TriBeCa.
Laura's right, Dad.
It looks terrible.
Maybe we should
find a new place.
One that
allows dogs.
Well, it's probably
nice inside.
Come on, let's
check it out.
(Laura)
I thought all
New York apartments
had elevators.
Apparently not, dear.
Maybe we should
go back home.
[angry]
This is home
now, Jimmy!
[door creaking]
Who are you?.
We're the Warners.
We're moving in
to apartment 12.
Oh, yeah.
[crunch]
This is
my wife, Laura.
I'm Muriel.
This is Reuben.
[playful music]
Hm. Pleasure.
This is
our son, Jimmy.
We didn't
know there would
be children.
Well, it is
in the paperwork.
(Muriel)
Oh?
Hey.
So it is.
What'd you say
your name was again?.
Jimmy.
(Muriel)
Jimmy, are you
a good boy?
Yeah.
You'd better be.
(Muriel)
Reuben will show
you the apartment.
(Jimmy)
Excuse me.
I was just wondering
if you allow pets.
(Muriel)
Pets?
Absolutely not.
Why?.
Have you got a pet?.
Y eah. A dog. Rainy.
That lease clearly
states, in red ink--
We didn't bring him
with us.
Well good. 'Cause we
don't permit 'em.
Dogs is
filthy animals. Mm-hm.
And dangerous.
Yeah.
Well, Rainy's really clean.
And he won't bite anybody.
He's the best dog
in the whole world.
He really is a good dog.
(Muriel)
Listen to me.
The only
thing worse than dogs
is precocious little kids.
Unfortunately, the law
forbids me from keepin'
them out.
Reuben, show them
the unit!
Right this way.
Come on, come on.
Oh, I gotta fix that.
Wow.
Hey, boy.
I got my eye
on you, boy.
[suspense music]
I'm watching!
I better not
see no animals
on these premises.
[several animal noises]
[whimpering]
[gasps and chuckles]
[cackling]
[Rainy groaning
to the rap]
Wait, what do we
have here?.
[rap music on earphones]
[whimpering]
Hey, hey.
Now, you won't
be needing this
now, will you?.
[barking]
[lively, playful music]
Let me outta here! hey!
[shouting]
Hey, man. Hey.
[barking]
Stop. Over here,
you mangy mutt. Ugh.
[playful music]
You can't
protect him, horse.
Move outta my way.
[trumpets]
[train horn sound]
[mooing and pounding sounds]
[loud mooing]
Holy cow.
Holy cow, man.
[mooing]
You don't wanna hurt,
no, you don't wanna
hurt nobody
Come on, you,
you're a loving animal.
Peaceful by nature, peaceful.
Ugh!
[bull mooing]
Oh!
[loud thump]
[farting]
[Charlie coughing]
Oh, yuck.
What did you eat,
you stupid bull?.
[playful music]
Come on.
No funny business.
Just give me my hat.
I'm just needing--
[spitting]
Ugh!
[bleating]
Come on. Ugh.
[suspense music]
[spitting]
[shouting]
What?.
Why me?.
No, nobody makes
a fool 'a me.
Now come back here,
you slow down.
It's not fair.
[crowing]
[several animal noises
echoing with circus music]
[shouting]
Oh, little puppy.
Here, puppy.
Here, scoundrel.
Come here, nice dog.
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
Ugh!
[chirping]
Stop laughing.
[barking]
[laughing hysterically]
You think you can get away
from me that easy, do you?.
You got nowhere
to go. I'm gonna
teach you a lesson
you won't soon forget.
[barking]
Ah!
[burps]
[Rainy, groaning]
No, no.
Stay away from--
Yeah, that's right. Run.
Run like the scared
little animal you are.
Oh. Oh.
[lively music]
[man whistling]
[whistling]
[starts engine]
[whimpering]
[groaning]
What-- Oh!
[train horn]
Hey. You can't
come in here.
T ake it easy, boy.
(policeman)
He's heading
for the train yard, let's go!
(policeman 2)
Come back here!
[blowing whistle]
[panting and huffing]
[train horn]
Hey, look
what we
have here.
Looks like we got
another one of us
on board, boys.
Hey, I'm Derek.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome aboard.
This here is Jojo.
Hello.
This is Clive.
[whimpering]
(Derek)
Glad to be on board.
[train horn]
Gotcha now, Derek.
[playful music]
It's been a long time.
It don't look good.
That's for sure. I'm
in a corner, old boy.
What do you think?.
[Rainy, whimpering]
Hey, what's goin' on?.
He's giving me
some ideas.
That mutt?.
[chuckles]
If you figure a way
to get outta this,
I'll give him my dinner.
[chuckles]
[whimpering]
[Derek, laughing]
What a move!
(Clive)
That can't be.
Looks like we got
another guest for dinner.
(homeless men)
# Well, I come from Alabama
With a banjo on my knee #
# I'm going to Louisiana
My true love for to see #
# It rained all day
The night I left
The weather it was dry #
# The sun so hot
I froze to death #
# Suzanna don't
You cry, whoo #
# Oh, Suzanna
Don't you cry for me #
# I come from Alabama
With a banjo on my knee #
# I had a dream
The other night
When everything was still #
# I thought I saw Suzanna
Coming up the hill #
# The buckwheat cake
Was in her mouth
The tear was in her eye #
# Says I'm coming
From the South
Suzanna don't you cry #
# Oh, Suzanna
Don't you cry for me #
[school bell]
Hey, you're
the new guy. Right?.
I'm Billy and these
are the Koolz,
with a K and a Z.
Hi. I'm Jimmy.
So where are
you from, Jimmy?.
Eagle Rock, Louisiana.
Hm. Of course,
small town.
So let me fill you in
on how things work
around here.
You need to pay
not to get hurt.
What?.
Got any
lunch money left?.
No.
That's too bad.
Ow!
[suspense music]
See what I mean?.
No money, big hurt.
Better have some lunch
money for us tomorrow, Jimmy.
(girl)
Hey, guys.
Leave him alone.
You are all bullies.
Ain't that cute?
Jimmy's girlfriend
is protecting him.
I 'm not his girlfriend.
But I am telling on you
if you don't leave.
Boo!
Come on guys. Let's leave
the lovebirds alone.
T omorrow, Jimmy.
All right, guys.
Are you okay?.
Yeah.
But, I could have
handled myself.
Yeah. I can see that.
Well, thanks.
No problem.
I'm Amy.
Nice to meet you.
Don't think
about them. They're
just dumb bullies.
Like to pick on kids
smaller than they are.
They wouldn't do this
if Rainy was here.
Who's Rainy?.
My dog.
He always came
to school with me.
Where is he now?.
I had to leave him
in Eagle Rock.
See, we're from Louisiana,
but my landlords here
don't allow pets
That's too bad.
He sounds pretty cool.
Can he do tricks?.
Absolutely. He can
roll over, play dead.
Even ride a skateboard.
Wow.
And we love
the same music too.
I left him my iPod.
[lively music]
[Jimmy, echoing]
This is where we're going.
It's New York City.
[ship horn]
[lively music continues]
Hey, Amy.
Thanks again
for today.
You're welcome.
But, if it
happens tomorrow,
maybe let me
take care of it.
[dog barking]
Hey.
[dog barking,
man grunting]
That's my landlord.
He's the one
who won't let
Rainy live with us.
[dog, growling]
Oh. That hurts!
Oh, pup, pup.
[suspense music]
That's strange.
I thought no pets
were allowed.
That's what they said.
Well maybe they changed
their minds. I'll check.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
[lively music]
(girl)
Somebody lost a dog.
(woman)
He's so cute.
(man)
Hey, watch where
you're walkin', you.
(man)
Hey, hey, come here, buddy.
[pleasant music]
[chuckling]
(girl)
What a cute doggie.
[suspense music]
[gasps]
[barking]
Help! help!
(lady)
Somebody stop him!
Get outta the way.
[barking]
Police comin' through!
Get outta my way.
Ugh.
(thief)
Hey, get him off me.
(policeman)
You're under
arrest, pal.
(policeman 2)
Come on. Get up.
Stealin' purses
from little old
ladies, huh?
Mangy mutt!
Thank you, officers.
My whole life
is in this bag.
Don't thank us.
The dog caught
the thief.
Mangy mutt.
(policeman)
You're a mangy mutt.
Come on.
Oh, what a good
dog you are.
Who's your owner?.
Let's see your collar.
[groaning]
Oh, my, you're
halfway uptown.
That's a long
way home.
Come. I'll
take you back.
Come on.
[whistling]
Let's go.
[whimpering]
(Reuben)
'Cause I don't wanna
get rabies. I, I'm not thi-
How many
times do I have
to tell you?.
don't look
the animals
right in the eye.
It' makes them mad.
Well, the damn thing
bit me, Muriel.
Oh, it nipped you.
It didn't even break
the skin.
Uh, Ms. Ledger?.
Somethin' wrong, kid?.
Well, I just wanted
to ask you about
my dog again.
I told you,
no pets allowed.
Well, I saw Mr. Reuben
bringing in a cage
with an animal in it
I thought maybe you
just changed the rules.
Why are you nosing
around, kid?.
Are you one
of those troublemakers?.
No, I just thought maybe--
No pets!
Now get outta
here before I talk
to your parents.
I'm always careful
not to be seen.
You idiot.
Now get up
here and make
me a sandwich.
I think we're outta
Miracle Whip.
(Muriel)
Well, you better make
a miracle and get some.
[sirens wailing]
Come on.
It's your building.
[horns honking]
Young man!
(man)
Let's go,
I ain't got all day.
Young man!
[horns honking]
[shouting]
Do you live
around here?.
Do you live around here?.
Uh, yeah.
Well, I am trying
to get this nice
doggie home.
And his collar says
that this is his building.
Here?. No way.
Why not?.
You see, I know the landlords
of this building, the Ledgers.
They're as mean
as snakes.
They don't like kids
and they hate animals.
They do?.
Oh yeah. There's no way
they're gonna let a dog,
even a cool dog
like this one stay here.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Well, it seems like we're
not having any luck.
And I have to go.
Maybe your owners
are keeping you
secret. Sh.
[whimpering]
Can you stay here and wait
for them to come home?.
[whimpering]
You are such a good doggie.
Thank you very much.
[whimpering]
(Dean)
Hey guys.
(Laura)
Hi, honey.
Hi, Dad.
How was your first
day in the new
school, sport?.
Nothing special.
(Laura)
You see,
I told it would be
just like Eagle Rock.
Just like.
Hey, did you
make any new
friends today?.
Just one.
Great. What's his name?.
How come the landlords
are allowed to have pets,
but we can't?.
Well, I wasn't aware
that he had any.
I saw Mr. Reuben bring in
a cage with an animal in it.
It even bit him.
Jimmy.
I was in their
apartment today,
and I didn't see
any dogs.
But I saw him.
And I asked them too.
And what did he say?.
No pets allowed.
And what else?.
Stop being nosy.
You see?
There you have it.
We must stop
all this talk about dogs.
We're in New York now
and it's not gonna change.
[melancholy music]
Wish you could be here, Rainy.
It's not much fun
without my best friend.
[sniffs]
God. If you could
only find a way.
[melancholy music continues]
[all chuckling]
(punk 1)
Hey, look at this guy.
Hey, what
you got there,
old man?. Huh?.
Hey, hey, stop.
Come on, man.
What is this, trash?
(homeless man)
That's my stuff. Hey.
Whoa. Look
at old man crazy.
Hey. There's nothin'
in there you want.
Oh, a free hat.
Come on, guys.
Look. Ain't nothin'
in there for you.
(punk 1)
Check it out.
Whoa!
That wasn't necessary,
you punks.
What'd you call us?.
I called you a punk.
Throwin' my stuff all down--
I don't even know
what's wrong with you
young folks today,
I wasn't botherin' nobody.
[barking]
Ugh!
[growling]
You go, dog.
All right.
[growling]
He tried to bite me.
Yeah, well,
he'll do it again
if you don't git.
Go! Get outta here!
Oh, good boy. Get him boy.
Go on, get him, boy. Get him,
get him. Get him.
[laughing]
Mommy!
Thanks, man.
Boy, them punks don't
respect nobody these days.
They just throwin'
stuff all on the ground.
Shoot. Boy, you know,
you a clever pup, too.
You know that?.
I sure wish I had
somethin' to give you.
Man, l, l, I'm flat broke.
I ain't got a dime.
[barks]
I'll tell you
what. We'll go
eat us somethin'. Okay?.
[barks]
Yeah, all right.
Okay. All right,
let's go.
(man)
There you go, buddy.
(woman)
Look at that sweet dog.
Baby, you're so cute.
[whimpering]
(woman)
You have a lovely dog.
Well, we gonna eat us
some dinner now, boy.
[chuckles]
Here it is, guys.
[whimpering]
Don't tell me.
You here for a hot dog?.
[groaning]
You got money?.
Okay. How many?.
[barks twice]
Two dogs. Coming up.
You want mustard?.
[whimpering]
Mustard, oh,
all right. Mayo?.
No mayo. Ketchup?
Nope. Uh, pickles?.
[groaning]
That'll be three bucks.
Enjoy.
One 'a the best
hot dogs I ever ate.
I mean, all of 'em
are good. Mm, mm, mm.
Well, guess it's time
for me to settle down
for the night.
[grunts]
Good night, boy.
[groaning]
Here are the keys.
[engine starting]
Hey!
What are you doing?.
[engine roars]
No, no, no!
[barking]
(valet)
You can't drive that car!
[brakes screeching]
Come back here!
[lively music]
[horns honking]
[cheering]
[lively music]
[brakes screeching]
(man)
It's a dog.
[lively music]
Rainy?.
[melancholy music]
Just a dream.
Now listen, sport.
You can't miss the bus
everyday. You understand?.
[Dean, whistling]
Taxi!
T axi!
[whimpering]
[continues whimpering]
[suspense music]
[horn honking]
[brakes screeching]
Okay, hey. Have
a great day, Jimmy.
You too, Dad.
[grunting]
Love you.
[school bell rings]
[suspense music]
Jimmy, boy.
Where's our money?.
I brought my own
lunch today. Maybe l
could give you a cookie.
You tryin' to be funny?.
No.
(Billy)
You tryin'
to make fun of me?
No.
Then you
must be stupid.
Stop!
Hey, let her go!
Leave her alone.
I'm gonna
teach you a lesson.
First just--
Let her go.
You gonna cry
like a baby?.
Rainy!
(Jimmy)
I can't believe it.
(all)
Ow! Ah!
Oh!
Ow!
[cheering]
[barking]
Please. Please.
Get him off me.
[barking]
Get him off me!
[groaning]
[cheering]
Now look who's
crying like a baby.
[cheering]
I can't believe you
came back, boy.
[whimpering]
I missed you so much.
[both laughing]
Rainy, this is Amy.
Amy, Rainy.
(Amy)
Pleased to meet
you, Rainy.
Come on. Or we'll
miss the bus.
[both chuckling]
(Jimmy)
I think he likes you.
He's very
cool, Jimmy.
Yeah, but,
I don't know
what to do with him.
You should
tell your parents.
I can't. My
stepmother will freak
She doesn't want
to lose our apartment.
(Amy)
He sure is
a great dog, Jimmy.
I can't lose
Rainy again.
(boy)
He's so cute.
We'll figure
something out,
boy. I promise.
(Amy)
See you tomorrow.
(Jimmy)
Bye, Amy.
Thanks again.
She's a good friend.
I can't take you
upstairs, boy.
What can we do?.
[groaning]
Come on.
Let's go, boy.
[pleasant music]
Hey. This might
lead inside.
[kicking]
Ugh.
[groaning]
We'll have to keep you
here for now, boy.
Come here, boy.
Lie down.
[groaning]
Here. Eat this.
I'll come back with more
food and water later.
You have to be
very quiet. Okay?.
[groaning]
Sh.
Well, have sweet dreams.
[door opens]
(Muriel)
Now don't mess
this up, Reuben.
I want to get
rid of one of these
birds. You hear me?
They stink to high heaven,
flappin' their little wings
all the time.
And that one
is a vicious gossip.
Chit-chattin' all the time.
Don't mess this up, Reuben.
[birds chirping
and playful music]
This is gonna make
my client very happy.
Y eah. What'll
he fetch?.
Two thousand.
Nonsense. More.
Maybe. Maybe,
twenty-five hundred.
I won't accept a penny
less than three thousand.
[squawks]
Don't be cheap,
don't be cheap.
Okay. It's a deal.
I'll come back tomorrow
and pick up the bird.
Ah, ah. Payment first.
And three.
Beautiful.
[squawks]
Take a hike.
Shut up, dummy, shut up.
No, you shut up.
I'll fry you up
and serve you on toast.
I feel sorry for such
a wonderful creature.
Don't be
an idiot, Reuben.
We're gonna be rich.
Come on.
Let's go upstairs
and roll around in it.
(parrot)
Reuben, get me
a cheeseburger.
With fries.
[squawks]
[playful music]
Don't leave me hanging.
[squawks]
A doggie.
Prison break.
[parrot squawks]
Freedom, baby. Freedom.
[squawks]
[playful music continues]
Hasta la vista, baby.
[squawks]
[barking]
I'll be right down.
Where's the bird?.
He was here
last night.
Where's my bird?.
He's not here now.
No, it's not.
Reuben, go check
the other cages.
Right, sweetheart.
I'll look everywhere.
They're here.
I think they're
all here.
So what?.
So I find it hard to believe
that someone broke in here,
last night
with all these other
animals here and only
your bird got stolen.
What are you saying?.
I think you know
what I'm sayin'.
This is ridiculous, huh?.
I want my money,
and I'm not doin'
anymore business
with the two's 'a you.
Reuben, call the police.
Right.
But sweetness--
If I call the police,
they're, they're gonna
lock us all up.
Admit what you did.
No!
Admit it!
This whole
time you--
(Muriel)
What in the world
is this?
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
These don't look
like little kid prints.
These look like
the kind of prints
of some kind of dog.
(Seagal)
You hear me?.
I want my bird.
(Muriel)
When I find--
Oh, it even chewed a hole.
I can't believe this!
[growling]
I knew it.
That Warner
kid has a dog.
Come on, go get it.
Go get it.
Good, yeah.
Come here.
But pets
aren't allowed.
That mutt
must'a done this.
I'm gonna go
have a little chat
with his parents.
(Dean)
It's a little hard
to believe.
I mean,
I know Rainy
is a very smart dog.
But I can't imagine
him travelin' 2000 miles
to this city to find Jimmy.
Sounds like a movie.
I am warning you. Your
lease specifically
states, no pets.
If I find a dog
hiding in here,
you are out!
(Laura)
Please, Mrs. Ledger.
We don't want any
trouble here.
Well, it's too late for that!
(Dean)
Now wait a minute.
Now, there's no evidence
that we have any animal
in this apartment at all.
So, until you can produce
such evidence, I'll thank you
not to threaten my family.
Oh!
[roars]
[crunching]
It's okay.
I guess I should go.
Sweetness.
(Amy)
What did you bring?.
For what?.
Uh-oh.
You forgot?.
That's not good.
Mr. Newman said
anyone who didn't bring
a show and tell gets an F.
Maybe he won't
call on me.
Here, take mine.
No way. You'll get an F.
[clears throat]
Mr. Warner.
Is there something
you'd like to share today?.
Uh-- Uh-- l--
Mr. Warner.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
[rattling drums]
[children exclaim]
What is the meaning of this?.
Who does he belong to?.
(Jimmy)
Uh, he's my show
and tell, Mr. Newman.
Well, this is
a bit irregular,
but go ahead.
[pleasant music]
(girl)
He's talented.
Rainy. Come on.
[groaning]
[children chuckle]
Just in time, boy.
[groaning]
T oday, I wanna
tell you about
the German Shepherd dog,
one of the bravest,
and smartest breeds
there is.
Looks like a stupid
animal to me
You would know.
[Rainy growls,
children laugh]
Gentlemen. Continue Jimmy.
In fact, Rainy's so smart,
he got invited to train
for a search and rescue team
in the great Smoky
Mountains of Tennessee.
Once, he even saved
a pilot's life.
Oh, so now he can fly?.
[children chuckle]
Billy. Let him finish.
So about a year ago
there was
this pilot flying
over the Smoky Mountains.
[pleasant music]
[alarm sets off]
(Jimmy)
Suddenly, he started
to have engine trouble.
[suspense music]
Mayday. Mayday.
(pilot)
Losing oil pressure.
Rapidly losing altitude.
Mayday. Mayday.
(Jimmy)
It was gonna
be a real dangerous
emergency landing.
H is wheels touched down,
and the plane landed
in the ice and snow.
And Rainy was there
[groaning]
(Jimmy)
The pilot set the plane
down safely, but passed out.
[barking]
(Jimmy)
Rainy pulled him out
just in the nick of time.
[pleasant music]
[groaning]
He won a medal
for that too. The end.
Now that was
an A-plus presentation.
Good job, Mr. Warner.
(girl)
He's so cute.
(girl 2)
I wanna pet him.
Thanks, boy.
I'll see you
after school.
He's a German
Shepherd dog,
a very dangerous,
unruly animal
I fear
for the neighborhood.
Don't worry.
I'll get him.
Know why?.
Check it out.
The latest
tracking devices.
Pinpoint GPS services.
Satellite imagery.
Heat signature detection.
And the latest,
audio sensing equipment.
Hell. With this,
I can hear an elephant
fart in Africa.
[fart and elephant calling]
It's why they call me
Big-Game Gostavo.
[whimpers]
What, what you
gonna do with him
when you catch him?.
Let's just say
[suspense music]
it won't be PG Thirteen.
[startled]
Ah, Chihuahua.
[laughing viciously]
[ominous music]
[vicious laughter
continues, echoing]
[groaning]
[mechanical noises]
[electronic swooshing sound]
Where are you,
you mangy mutt?.
[meow]
[suspense music]
[growling]
[deep growl]
What do you think
you're doing?
[roars]
It was the dog.
The dog did this!
Ah!
(big cook)
Next time watch
where you're going.
[groaning]
[electronic sounds
and cow mooing]
[bird squawking
[birds chirping]
Where the heck--
[groaning]
[shouting]
You varmint!
[guys laughing]
[sobbing]
I 'm gonna get you,
you dirty animal.
[barking and groaning]
Come here, you varmint!
Oh, I'll get you.
Come here, you
hairy beast!
Get ready
for the shock
ofyour life.
[laughing viciously]
[growling and barking]
[buzzing]
Ah!
Oh!
[coughing]
[flies buzzing]
But we paid you,
Gostavo. You promised
to take care 'a him.
Yeah, whatever
happened to that
not PG Thirteen?.
Are you not
listening to me?.
(Gostavo)
This is the first time ever
I couldn't catch a dog.
Oh!
Reuben, if we don't
take care 'a this dog
it's gonna be the end
of the business.
It sounded like he was
inside a dumpster
or somethin'.
[sniffs]
Ugh.
Say hello
to my meaty friend.
[laughs viciously]
[chewing loudly]
Hey, guys. No. Hey!
No, no--
Don't shut it. Wait.
(Gostavo)
I'm in here! Help!
[engine sound]
Please. Somebody!
Ow. I'm a dog
catcher in here.
[laughing]
[Rainy groaning]
How was your day?.
[barking]
What is it, boy?.
[engine starts]
Hey. It's Mr. Ledger.
Let's go see what he's
up to. Come on.
[suspense music]
M r. Reuben!
M r. Reuben, wait!
[eerie music]
(Reuben)
Yeah, we got it all.
We have, uh, uh, birds,
bats, marsupials.
[various animal noises]
(Reuben)
I got your
bird right here.
Uh-huh. What?
What?. Well, you're gonna
have to talk to M uriel
about the price.
I, l, I don't
know anything
about that.
What's that
all about?.
[various animal noises]
[groaning]
Oh my gosh.
They're selling
these poor animals.
Rainy we need
to call the police.
Or at least tell Dad.
You ain't
gonna tell nobody,
you nosy little kid.
Mrs. Ledger,
this is against the law.
Only if the law
catches me.
And I'm gonna
make sure it don't.
What are you doing?.
[Rainy, barking]
Oh, no.
(Muriel)
Gotcha.
[whimpering]
You're hurting him!
You didn't think
I could lasso, did you?
I 'm gonna sell you
to the highest bidder.
I'm gonna get
a good price
for ya, too.
Let him go!
Oh, I will.
Right after I take care
'a you, you little brat.
[barking]
[bleating]
Don't you make me
run after you.
[barking]
(Muriel)
Oh, stop opening
these cages.
These animals are worth
thousands of dollars.
Oh!
[neighing]
I 'm gonna find ya.
There's no way out.
[thump]
Oh!
[crash]
[suspense music]
(Muriel)
Jimmy!
[barking]
I've got a nice piece
'a candy for ya.
(both)
Ugh!
(Muriel)
Reuben!
I'm gonna find this kid.
I am gonna get you, kid.
Reuben!
[barking]
(Muriel)
I hear him, Reuben.
He's over here.
Just follow
the sound of my sweet
voice and you'll be there.
I got him. I got him.
[growling]
[barking]
[laughing viciously]
There you are, mutt.
[Jimmy, growling]
[laughing]
Time to take a nap,
pup. Ready, aim--
No!
Shut up, kid!
Ah!
[groaning]
[both growling]
[shot]
No!
Oh. Sleepy.
Run Rainy,
get help!
[groaning]
Reuben, get that dog!
[snoring]
[lullaby music]
Reuben! Reuben,
come on, come on.
Come on.
Get up.
You gotta
get that dog.
(Reuben)
Dog. Yeah.
[groaning]
[moaning in pain]
[various animal noises]
Hi, hi, Mr. Goat.
I gotcha.
Let me go!
Ow, let me go.
Stop it, stop it.
You're hurting me
I got him, Muriel!
(Amy)
Rainy?.
[Rainy barking]
What's the matter?.
[barking]
Where's Jimmy?.
Something's wrong.
I need to find help.
(Seagal)
What you gonna do
with the kid?
I'll send him
to Mexico for
a couple 'a years.
By the time he
gets back he won't
remember anything.
I have a very
good memory.
You zip it.
You were warned
to stay away and you still
nosed your way in here.
I'm not scared.
[mocking]
(Reuben)
You know, Muriel.
He's not such a bad kid.
Maybe he could
keep a secret.
Oh.
What are you, stupid?.
Who's callin'
who stupid?.
I'm callin'
you stupid.
Yeah, well,
you're a dummy.
S-T-O-O-P-l-D.
Will you two knock it off?
In case you haven't noticed,
we're about to lose our very
profitable business
because of a kid
and a dog.
I think we should go
with your idea.
Yeah?.
How are you gonna
get him to Mexico?.
I got a friend
in the shipping business.
He goes down there
quite often. Reuben.
Reuben, give
me the phone!
Oh. Here.
[dialing]
Somebody oughtta
congestigate to you
how important
and serious
the situation is.
'Cause I don't appreciate
the way you been
goofin' around.
G-O-O-F, hoovin'.
[groaning]
Officers. Officers.
Hi there.
What's wrong?.
I'm Amy.
This is Rainy,
my friend Jimmy's dog.
He's never
without him.
Well, maybe
the dog got out.
No, you don't understand.
See, Jimmy has this
really mean landlord,
who hates Rainy.
Jimmy, too.
[sighs]
Please. I know
something's wrong.
[barking]
Okay. Let's
take Rainy back. You
know where he lives?.
I'll show you.
[suspense music]
(Amy)
Rainy, go find Jimmy.
[groaning]
Captain Nelson
is in town.
And he's
leavin' for Mexico
this afternoon.
(Reuben)
But that means
you're gonna
send him away?
From his family?.
Well, yeah, from his family,
you dunce. That's
the whole point.
And when I'm done
with you
I'm goin'
after your nosy dog.
Please. He'll be quiet.
Rainy's a good boy.
He won't say a thing
to anybody.
Oh, I'm gonna make sure
'a that. Let's go.
[suspense music]
Reuben, put him
in the van. Oh!
Not for nothin',
but I'm startin'
to think
I should send
all three of these
mutts to Mexico.
(Jimmy)
Let me go!
Who has
the keys?. Oh.
[Rainy barking]
Is this where
the dog lives?.
Yeah, and that's where
Jimmy was hiding Rainy.
I bet he's in there.
Check out
the door.
Whoa. It's locked.
He's trying to tell us
that Jimmy's inside.
All right. Bust it down.
Step to the side.
(both)
Ugh.
[thump]
[suspense music]
Stop right there!
Rainy!
(Muriel)
Close that door
and let's get outta here.
They've got Jimmy.
(policeman 1)
Go, go, go.
[brakes screeching
and barking]
and horn honking]
(Muriel)
We don't have time
for traffic.
(Muriel)
Hey, Reuben. Reuben!
Wake up!
We're goin' to jail.
(Muriel)
Drive!
[brakes screeching]
(Amy)
Good boy, Rainy.
[groaning]
They have Jimmy!
Good boy!
Central, this Four Adam Twelve,
callin' in an Amber alert.
[suspense music]
[siren wailing]
[brakes screeching]
(Muriel)
Stop whimpering.
No one is going to jail.
Just shut up and drive.
(Muriel)
Can't you make
this go any faster?
[horns honking]
(Muriel)
Come on.
[brakes screeching]
Captain Nelson?.
It's Muriel.
Muriel, darling.
(Nelson)
Do you have the package?
Oh, we got him
all right.
Don't touch me.
I don't like bein'
incarcerated. Drive.
I don't like
being touched.
bein' dead.
(Muriel)
There will be
a hefty fee for it,
don't you worry.
I'm just
pullin' into the old
naval shipyard now.
I'll meet you
at the warehouse.
(Muriel)
Well, it sounds like
somebody's gonna be
headin' off to Mexico
with old Captain Nelson.
[laughing viciously]
Suspect van entering
the naval shipyard.
Copy. Four Adam
Twelve en route.
Don't worry.
We'll find your friend.
(Muriel)
Okay. Why are you
driving like a maniac?
(Reuben)
Muriel, I love you,
but you've gotta be
quiet. I can't concentrate.
What are you, no,
l, it's not right.
It's not right.
Nelson, so nice
to see you.
Aw, good to see
you, Muriel.
[chuckling]
It's good
to have friends
you can rely on.
Mm-hm. Especially
if friends have money.
[both laughing]
Give him the money.
What are you
lookin' at me for?.
Either we pay
our Captain here,
or we pay
for lawyers down
at the police station.
Comprende?
[mumbling]
[both mouthing silently]
I could go to Mexico
myself for that money.
[chuckles]
Gracias.
Now, where
is this package?.
[car door opens]
Yow. Ugh.
Oh, come on,
come on, kid.
Get out, get, get out.
(Muriel)
Take a look
at our nosy little
friend, Jimmy Warner.
And my husband Reuben.
Please.
Can't you just
take me home?.
I won't say anything.
[chuckling]
Let's box him up.
[siren wailing]
(policeman 1)
They've gotta be
around here somewhere.
Rainy, find Jimmy.
[helicopter]
[suspense music]
(Muriel)
And don't you
worry, Jimmy
We're sendin' you
to Mexico with some
first class accommodations.
(M uriel)
Oh, yes.
N ice and roomy
for you.
Hey. Quit movin'
around, kid.
Boom.
Ugh.
What?. You let him
get away.
Ow. He stepped
on my bunion.
Oh! We gotta
get that kid.
Go. Reuben, go.
(Reuben)
Yes, sweetheart.
I'll get him.
(Muriel)
Go. Run like
the wind, boys.
Reuben!
Pull me up.
Help me up.
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on.
We're losing him.
(Reuben)
Where'd he go?
Oh, Charlie.
(Seagal)
I'll g- get you.
Jimmy.
I'm gonna--
I'm gonna murdelize you.
[laughing viciously]
Where are you
going now, kid?.
[shouting]
(Muriel)
Get off of me!
Wait!
I got him.
Oh. I don't got him.
[growling]
Oh!
(Muriel)
Get him!
[suspense music]
[all laughing]
Now we got you.
(Muriel)
Now let's get
this kid in the box
and get him to Mexico.
[Seagal coughing]
(radio dispatch)
Suspect van inside
Romati Warehouse.
(Muriel)
Nelson. I'm gonna let you
go ahead and ship this
rotten little kid.
Hasta la vista, J immy.
Ugh.
Reuben, come on.
Adios.
You're goin'
for a long ride, kid.
Uh, Mister,
do you like dogs?.
Why?.
[growling]
[sirens wailing]
It's the cops.
(policeman 2)
I got him right
here, Mike.
You okay?.
They didn't hurt
you, did they?.
No.
(Muriel)
Let go 'a me. I didn't
do nothin' wrong.
(policeman 1)
You're under arrest.
For kidnapping,
and running
an illegal animal
selling operation.
No. We didn't
kidnap him. We was
just havin' fun.
Ain't that
right, Jimmy?
As for the animals,
we run a shelter.
You do not.
But we do!
We love animals,
don't we, Jimmy?.
We love them, tell 'em.
(Seagal)
Hey, hey, kid.
Tell 'em how I'm
your fun, rich friend
who was helpin' you
catch the bad guys.
Can Rainy stay with us?.
Of course he can,
he can even stay
at our place,
ain't that right, honey?.
[snoring]
Reuben!
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
he can come over
the house for weeks.
Yeah.
Uh, that's
very nice.
Only you'll have
to wait till you
get outta jail.
Take them away!
Oh! I'm gonna
get you, kid.
You're messin' up my hair.
This is a very expensive
shirt from--
You did
a good job.
[walla]
Kid, your dog's
a hero.
Rainy.
Where is Rainy?.
Rainy. Come here.
Rainy.
[suspense music]
(policeman)
Hey, come on,
let's look for the dog.
Oh, no.
Rainy!
[melancholy music]
[weeping]
God. Please help Rainy.
[sobbing]
Rainy. Oh, God,
please help him.
Don't let him die.
He saved me.
Jimmy!
Are you all right,
are you hurt?.
(policeman 1)
The dog's a hero.
He saved your boy.
Daddy. Please help him.
Don't let Rainy die.
Jimmy, he's in God's
hands. All we can do
is pray now.
Please. Rainy, don't die.
You're my best friend
in the whole world.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry, son.
There's nothin'
we could do.
[melancholy music continues]
Why would God take away
my best friend, Daddy?.
Jimmy.
That's somethin'
only God could answer.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Do you think
Rainy will be
with Mommy now?.
Yeah, Rainy's
in heaven with Mommy.
And, Mommy'll take
care 'a Rainy now.
Come on, son,
let's just go home.
Let me
say goodbye
to him, Daddy.
Okay.
(Jimmy)
I know how much
you love to eat this.
And I'll ask Mommy
to give you some more
in heaven.
Bye, Rainy.
I love you.
(Jimmy)
I'll see you
again someday.
[groans]
Jimmy, look!
[softly groaning]
[lively music]
He's alive! Rainy.
[whimpering]
It's a miracle.
Oh, Rainy.
I'm so happy you're alive.
I thought
that mean old Captain--
Hey. Where is
he anyway?.
[suspense music]
[groaning]
Follow Rainy.
(policeman 2)
Come on, let's go!
[groaning and growling]
Get that dog off me!
[barking]
Boys.
Put him
in the prison deck.
Thanks, Rainy.
[groaning]
Hey, three cheers
for Rainy.
[all cheer and applaud]
(mayor)
Ladies and gentlemen,
We are here
today to honor
a new breed of hero.
No pun intended.
[all laugh]
Rainy exemplifies
everything that we
all strive for.
Courage, determination,
loyalty, and kindness.
Rainy, with the help
of this courageous
young man here,
broke up a nefarious
animal smuggling ring.
Amy helped too.
(Amy)
Here I am.
(mayor)
Well done, Amy.
And so
it is, without
further ado,
I present
the Golden Key
of our fair city,
to Rainy.
[groaning]
[all cheering and applauding]
Does this mean Rainy
could stay with us,
Mr. Mayor?.
As far as I am
concerned he is now
a citizen of New York.
That's my
boy, Rainy.
[groaning]