Happy holiday
- Merry Christmas, bud.
- Thank you. Merry Christmas to you.
Okay. Hi, Chief.
Come in.
Hello, honey.
Well, this is our last
night in show business.
Some feeling, huh?
Some feeling.
I got the ring and the license.
- Honey, we're ready.
- Oh.
Say, there's a hook
leftover at the top here.
Should that be?
Never mind, I'll take care of it.
- Jim?
- Huh?
Well, I think that tie's terrible.
Well, who cares?
Tomorrow I'm a farmer.
You'd better go change it.
Listen, honey, when you're
flipping those twinkle toes
who's gonna be looking at my tie?
You only have five minutes. Hurry.
Okay, I'm on my way.
What'd he say?
I didn't tell him.
Why not? We love each other.
You wanna continue dancing.
I know, but he gets a look.
Oh, he's always had that look.
It doesn't mean anything emotionally.
It has something to
do with his liver.
Simply tell him you
had made a mistake.
You don't wanna give up your
career and live on a farm.
But he's already bought the farm.
And the license, and the ring.
Oh, I can't tell him.
All right, I will.
Right after our number.
Listen, darling, don't weaken.
Think of our life together.
Think of diamonds, of sables,
of your own little penthouse.
Is that a promise?
Well, just think about
them for the time being.
Ready, Miss Dixon.
Well, thank you.
Say, this thing didn't come out even.
Oh, I'll fix it. We have to hurry.
I love you.
I love you...
and Jim.
I love Jim, too. But after all,
I mean, let's not be too chummy.
Here she comes down the street
My, oh my, ain't she sweet?
Why, here comes my hot toddy
Over my dead body
I'll capture her heart singing
Just wait until she gets
a load of my dancing
Just wait till I start singing
I'll take her strolling down
the road with my dancing
I can't go wrong, a tender song
And she'll discover my charms
Some fancy taps and she'll collapse
And fall right into my arms
I'll capture her heart singing
Oh, no, you haven't a chance
When I go into my dance
I'll take you through life singing
I'll make you my wife dancing
If you could dance instead of sing
I'd learn to love you somehow
If you could sing instead of dance
I'd take you home with me now
The way you sing don't mean a thing
You'd better stick to your dance
And as for you, your dance won't do
You'll have to sing for romance
I'll capture her heart...
- Singing
- Dancing
Not much of a Christmas
present for you, is it?
I mean, both of us
walking out on you.
Don't worry about me, kid.
I'll do all right.
Whata chum.
Can't you see what we're
walking out on? The grind.
365 days a year.
When's the last time
you had as day off?
I don't know. Maybe last year?
Do you ever hear of Thanksgiving
or Labor Day or the Fourth of July?
- Vaguely.
- You know what they are, don't you?
They're holidays.
Days of rest. There's lots of 'em.
They mark 'em in red on the calendar
so you can't miss 'em.
What happens in show business
when a holiday comes along?
You give an extra performance.
Not for me, brother.
Lila and I are going up to
that farm in Connecticut
and we're gonna live by the calendar.
- Say, Jim?
- Mmm?
There's something you should know.
Oh, I know, Ted. I feel
the same way about you.
You know, we've had
our ups and our downs
and we fought a little over the women
we swiped from each other, but...
- I know, but...
- Sorry, Jimmy boy, but that's life.
Ted, if I'm not the best
manager in the business
I'll eat a garage mechanic's shirt.
Fifteen weeks at the Park Club,
sight unseen, for you and Lila.
$200 a week more than you were
getting with the farmer thrown in.
What's the matter?
I haven't told him.
- You haven't told him?
Haven't told me what? What...
What's this? What's the news?
Well, don't be upset, Jim, dear.
It isn't that I don't love you. I do.
I love everybody,
but when Ted explained how
much he loved me and...
All at once, we both realized
that we belong together.
The two of us, dedicating our lives
to making people happy with our feet.
The two of you, huh?
Dedicating your lives to making
people happy with your feet.
That's sweet.
Well, I guess that kick I just
got was a good start, huh?
Sorry, Jimmy boy, but that's life.
Yeah, it's best that you
found out now, Jim.
You wouldn't wanna make Lila unhappy.
Oh, no. No, I... I wouldn't
want to make Lila unhappy.
Not now, now that I really know her.
What a narrow squeak that was.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, nothing. Nothing, honey.
I'm just happy that you're happy.
That little speech sounds like the
crack of a confederate money.
Well, kids, I'm still gonna
rejoin the human race.
I hope you get a lot of work,
holidays included,
dance yourselves into
beautiful nervous breakdowns.
You ever want to look me up,
you know where to find me,
Midville, Connecticut,
under a large shady tree,
just being lazy.
Lazy, I want to be lazy
I long to be out in the sun
With no work to be done
Under that awning
They call the sky
Stretching and yawning
And let the world go drifting by
I want to peep
Through the deep
Tangled wildwood
Counting sheep till I sleep
Like a child would
With a great big valise full
Of books to read where it's peaceful
While I'm killing time
Being lazy
So Lazy Acres was a snare
and a delusion, huh?
Oh, brother, there's the
hardest work in the world.
Maybe you'd be happier
back in town, Jim.
Of course, if you get that
agricultural urge again,
you can always raise a geranium.
Oh, no. Wait till you hear.
I think I've dreamed up the
greatest idea I ever had.
And you've had some pips.
Oh, but this can't miss.
I'm turning the farm into
an inn, but what an inn.
Here, read up, brother.
"Holiday Inn, Midville Connecticut."
- Open holidays only?
- Mmm-hmm.
Say, how many of those are there?
There's about 15.
That gives me 350 days
a year to kick around in.
He would think of that.
Did you get your discharge
papers from that sanitarium?
Oh, don't you worry,
this is gonna work.
I'm having auditions out
at the farm every day.
Say, if you run into any talent
that's willing to work for
a share of the table,
will you send them out?
Sure, soon as I get back.
I'm flying down to
Miami Beach tonight
to set an engagement
for Ted and Lila.
Lila.
You forgot to order the flowers.
Now, don't get excited, there's
a flower shop out at the airport.
I guarantee to have orchids in her
dressing room before her first number.
Oh, boy, you better.
As I remember, this kid even
expects presents on Father's Day.
Yeah.
Well, good luck, Jim.
So long, Ted. Have a nice trip.
I mean, yeah, thanks, I will.
That reminds me,
I forgot to give him a little
Christmas remembrance
I brought along.
Got one here for each of you.
Say, this is swell.
What is it?
It's homemade peach preserves.
I put them up myself, just before
I went into the sanitarium.
Boy, do I go for those.
Why, they're great on...
Or even plain.
They're non-fattening, too.
Well, it's a long trip back to
the farm, I think I'll get along.
Will you say hello to Lila for me?
But you gotta wait and catch the act.
We got some new routines
and then after the show...
I don't think they like
this nightclub air.
Wait. Wait. You better
wait for Lila's.
I think Danny's was the loudest.
Well, different tone.
Dawn patrol, huh?
Hello! Am I too late?
You would have been
in another minute.
Danny Reed.
Listen, I have to wait on that man.
- But...
- I'll work five nights for you. Anything.
Just leave me alone
and don't butt in.
What would you like?
Orchids, the finest you've got.
Corsage?
No. No. A dozen.
Loose, looking like they don't care.
All right.
There, "Lila, love, Ted."
Have them delivered
to Miss Lila Dixon
at the Club Pierre
before 11:00 tonight.
Oh, I'm sorry, but our delivery
truck is on its last trip
and won't be back until after 11:00.
How about a messenger boy?
Oh, it's impossible to guarantee
delivery this late on Christmas Eve.
But to help you out, I'll take them.
Oh, there you are.
A dozen orchids, please.
Lady, you're a lifesaver.
Here. Here's $5. Take your boyfriend
out and show him a good time.
Oh, thank you, but let's
consider this a personal favor.
Well, I can't leave town
indebted to a stranger.
Would you like to see the
floor show at the club tonight?
Oh, I'd like to very much, but...
All right, now you just
give this card to Francois
and he'll seat you at
the entertainer's table.
Why, you're Mr. Reed.
Uh-oh.
I'm Linda Mason. Well,
this is just a part-time job.
Actually, I sing and dance.
Mr. Reed, I want...
I know. I know, you've studied
dancing since you were a little child.
You spent long weary hours in every
theatrical agency in Broadway.
But just now I happen to
be catching a plane to...
Of course, once you
told me I was no good,
I could probably get a job at a
bargain basement and like it.
Now look, honestly,
as soon as I get...
Oh, of course. Sure, you worked
hard, you want a chance.
So what? So I'm gonna give it to you.
- A job?
- Uh-huh.
A friend of mine is opening a place
in Connecticut, Holiday Inn.
You take that card
out there tomorrow,
tell him I sent you
and you'll be all set.
Mr. Reed, how could
I possibly thank you?
Don't. Just deliver those orchids
and let me catch my plane.
This table's reserved for the band.
Excuse me!
Fussy, isn't he?
I think I'll have
a bowl of coffee, huh?
- And the lady?
- Coffee.
We seem to be on the
40-cent tour here.
It is embarrassing.
I'm Jim Hardy.
Linda Mason.
Got a friend in the show?
Well, I'm here at
Mr. Reed's invitation.
Oh, Danny.
Then you know Ted Hanover.
What?
Yes, naturally.
Oh, my.
He's quite a man with
the ladies, that Ted.
Well, after all, he's a
very attractive man.
Do you know him?
Oh, yes. Yes.
Matter of fact,
I've been considering Ted
and his partner for my new club.
Oh, you have a place.
Oh, yes. Yes.
I don't know, though.
His act might not go
so well at a place as large as mine.
Oh.
Well, I've found that the size
of a place doesn't matter,
if one has sufficient personality.
That's what you found, huh?
You in show business?
I'm Linda Mason.
Oh, Linda Mason.
I could dance nightly
Just holding you tightly
My sweet
I could keep right on
Because you're so light on your feet
You're easy to dance with
There is no doubt in
The way we stand out in the crowd
Though it's called dancing
To me it's romancing out loud
You're easy to dance with
Loving you the way I do
Makes you easy to dance with
That is why I'm always
right on the beat
All those charms in one man's arms
Make you easy to dance with
I can hardly keep my mind on my feet
Let's dance forever
Come on, say we'll never be through
It's so easy to dance with you
You're easy to dance with
It's so easy to dance
With you
That was wonderful.
Oh, it's a great act,
isn't it? Here they come.
- Who?
- Ted and Lila.
Hey, what's the matter?
- Hello, Lila.
- Jimmy boy.
- How are you?
- I'm so glad to see you.
It's good to see you.
I thought you were alone, Jim.
Who's your friend,
and what's her hurry?
Don't ask me, she's your friend.
- Mine?
- Yeah.
What is she afraid of? Facing me?
Darling, I swear, I never...
"Darling, I swear."
You lie...
You're on.
So this is Holiday Inn.
Yeah. Will be if it ever opens up.
Well, why shouldn't it open?
Well, I ain't one to talk,
but you could probably
buy a half interest
in this place for a barrel of apples.
Next train for New York's at
7:43, if I can flag her down.
Say, I'm looking for a job.
Where's the boss?
Right here, I'll be down in a second.
So, you're the big shot
that didn't know whether
Hanover and Dixon
were good enough for your place.
Well, that wasn't exactly hay
you were throwing, either.
"I'm Linda Mason."
Merry Christmas.
All right, you're a
fake and I'm a phony.
And we're both soaked.
- Are you hurt?
- I'll check later.
Come on, let's get out of
this before you catch cold.
All right. Ooh.
Well, here's what cooks.
Oh.
Well, this is darling.
Was it as large as this
when it was a farmhouse?
Yeah, it was built by a fellow
who felt cramped in New York.
He finally ran out of lumber, though.
Oh, Mamie.
Coming.
Is your names Mamie?
- No.
Get back in the kitchen.
My, my. What's happened?
Oh, we had a little accident.
- Mamie, this is Miss Linda Mason.
- How do you do?
Please to know you, Miss Linda.
And these are her children.
That's Daphne, and that's Vanderbilt.
How do you do?
Mamie, will you take Miss
Mason up to the guest room
and change her into
anything that'll fit her
while we get her clothes dry, huh?
Sure thing, Mr. Jimmy.
Come on, honey.
I'll see about getting the
fire ready in the living room.
Is your names Miss Linda?
- No.
I don't know, it sounds like
something you dream about at night
and it would be wonderful,
then you'd wake up in the morning
and realize it couldn't work.
Oh, it'll work, if I can sell
the idea to some performers.
They seem to think
that profit sharing
means taking bows on
an empty stomach.
So that's why you're
not open tonight.
Well, I'm also, sort of, particular
about the kind of
talent I'm gonna use.
Fifteen holidays a year.
Mmm-hmm.
You're a lazy fellow.
No, not especially.
Just have my own ideas about living.
My father was like you.
Just a man with a family.
Never amounted to much, didn't care.
But as long as he was alive
we always had plenty to eat
and clothes to keep us warm.
- Were you happy?
- Yes.
Then your father was a very
successful man. Hope I can do as well.
Say, I came out here for
a job. Could you use me?
Well, I might find a spot for you
in my first show. What can you do?
I sing a little and dance.
Couldn't guarantee
any salary at first,
right now I've got the
ledger and an iron lung.
I don't care if you pay off in
eggs, just give me a chance.
Well, let's see what you can do.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You know, I've written
special music for each holiday.
This sort of gives me a chance to
keep a little promise I made to myself.
I said I was gonna sing
this song at the inn tonight.
I'm dreaming
Of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the treetops glisten
And children listen
To hear sleigh bells in the snow
I'm dreaming
Of a white Christmas
With every Christmas card I write
May your days be merry and bright
And may all your Christmases
Be white
I'm dreaming
Of a white Christmas
Just like...
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the treetops glisten.
Where the treetops glisten
And children listen.
And children listen
To hear
Sleigh bells in the snow
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
With every Christmas card I write
May your days be merry
And bright
And may all your
Christmases
Be white
Happy holiday
While the merry bells keep ringing
May your every wish come true
Happy holiday
May the calendar keep bringing
Happy holidays to you
If you're burdened down with trouble
If your nerves are wearing thin
Park your load down the road
And come to Holiday Inn
If the traffic noise affects you
Like a squeaky violin
Kick your cares down the stairs
And come to Holiday Inn
If you can't find somebody who
Would set your heart a-whirl
Get in your car and motor to
The home of boy meets girl
If you're laid-up with a breakdown
Throw away your vitamin
Don't get worse
Grab your nurse
And come to Holiday Inn
Happy holiday
May the calendar keep bringing
Happy holidays to you
Happy New Year, Ted.
No!
Francois, have you seen Mr. Hanover?
Twice, sir.
What happened?
The first time, sir,
he came from his dressing room
with a telegram in his hand.
He ordered Scotch and soda,
a bottle of each.
I know, I know. What then?
The second time he came
from his dressing room
he asked which way is Connecticut.
- Connecticut?
- Connecticut.
He said he has a friend there
who knows about women, too.
Why didn't you stop him?
How could I stop him,
sir, when I don't know
which way is Connecticut.
Who said Holiday Inn wouldn't work?
Well, we're gonna divvy up a stack
of important money tonight, huh?
Man, man.
I've got a landlady who's gonna
ask for your autographed picture.
No.
Everybody get something?
All right, come on, now.
Go to bed, now, it's getting late.
- Good night.
Look, it's almost time.
Say, it's practically
straight up, isn't it?
One minute to midnight
One minute to go
One minute to say good-bye
Before we say hello
Let's start the new year right
Twelve o'clock tonight
When they dim the light
Let's begin
Kissing the old year out
Kissing the new year in
Let's watch the old year die
With a fond good-bye
And our hopes as high
As a kite
How can our love go wrong if
We start the new year right?
That's it. That's midnight.
I'll see you out on
the floor, all right?
All right.
Come on, everybody. Happy New Year.
Happy holiday.
Happy New Year.
I forgot my check.
You won't need that, but I
think you'll need your coat.
Happy New Year.
Same to you.
You got to dance.
Oh, you got to dance.
Come on, you got to...
Why, Mr. Hanover.
Mr. Hanover.
That's Mr. Hanover.
Wait a minute, I got to go.
Oh, no, I don't want Ted Hanover,
I want you. This is New Years, kid.
I know.
Ted!
He wasn't drunk, it's a gag.
What happened?
Ted Hanover with his new partner.
They were great.
New partner?
You better get back.
Well, I am sorry, if I'd
have known how he was...
Oh, he'll be all right in a week
or 10 days. You better hurry.
Ted!
Oh.
How is he?
He's out cold.
Hot or cold, he can keep his
dancing shoes in my office.
Did you hear that applause?
Yeah, it went pretty good.
And I was worried
about his losing Lila.
- Losing Lila?
- Yeah.
Yeah, she eloped tonight
with some Texan from Texas,
with Ted's engagement
ring on her finger.
But who cares?
You lose one girl,
you find another. That's life.
That's good, huh?
Here we go again.
Come in.
- Good morning, Ted.
- Oh. Good morning.
Got a little head?
Where am I?
You're at Holiday Inn.
Well, how did I get here?
Who brought me?
You were clinging to the
undercarriage of a jeep, I think.
Here, have a slug out of the mug.
- You mean you don't remember anything?
- Uh...
Let's see. I had a wire from Lila
telling me she's going to marry
some millionaire or something.
- I remember that all right.
- Mmm-hmm.
Then I had a drink.
A drink?
Boy, you were fractured.
And then I decided I had
to talk to my old pal, Jim.
You don't remember anything else?
No. That's all, except that
I must have been killed on the
way out here or something.
You really come up empty, huh?
Too bad about Lila.
I think you're better
off doing a single.
You're a born soloist, you know.
Oh, no, no, Jim, I've
got to have a partner.
And when I find her...
Yeah, I know,
you'll fall in love with her.
- You haven't missed yet.
- Happy New Year!
Oh, don't do that.
Why didn't you tell me?
Letting me beat my brains out
worrying about his losing Lila
and all the time, he's got
this girl on the leash.
What girl?
Boy, you must have been high.
Doing a complete dance routine
with your new partner and you...
You don't know who she is?
I danced with a new partner?
When? Where?
Here. Last night.
Think, Ted. Remember?
Wait a minute. I remember.
I got here just about midnight.
There was a girl.
We danced.
What she look like?
I... I don't know. All I
saw was a vague outline.
Can't you remember
anything about her?
I remember dancing with her.
If I ever dance with her again,
I'd probably recognize her.
Great, that takes care of
everything but finding her.
You were here, why ask
me how she looked?
I only saw her from
the back. She was...
About this...
She had a...
If I ever saw her from the
back again, I'd recognize her.
Well, that's fine.
After I've danced with her,
I'll just turn her
around for your okay.
This should be a cinch.
You saw her, describe her.
Who, me? Well, I wasn't
watching very closely.
She was a medium...
Medium-built sort of a girl,
with a medium face. She had
a nice evening gown on
with a belt in the back.
See, she was built just
like a girl friend of mine.
A girl you don't know but her
name was Consuela Stupkis.
She used to play the pinball machine
a lot down at the corner drugstore.
I remember one time she was
high man. Three weeks in a row.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
That's nothing at all,
happy to do it.
See, I got a hunch, fellas.
I've got a hunch we're going
to find this girl eventually.
And when we do we'll be
glad we waited for her.
Listen, I'm not interested in getting
any other partner, understand?
A chance meeting
in the night. Destiny.
She'll be back.
Here's where we will find
her on the next holiday.
- Here?
- Here.
I've got to go turn the roast.
Now don't worry, we'll find her.
If I see her from the back again,
I'll recognize her.
It's kind of a roundabout way
to go at it, but let's try it.
Are you decent?
Yes, come in.
What's that?
Well, I thought it over
and I believe that our number'll
go a little better in blackface.
Oh. I thought we were
going to do it like this.
Well, that's before...
Before I thought it over.
- I look terrible in the stuff.
- No.
I don't even know how to put it on.
I'll put it on for you.
I broke in as a bootblack, you know.
Here we go.
Oh.
For a month and a half
I've been dreaming
of how pretty I was
going to look tonight.
Well, here's my punishment
for thinking so well of myself.
Oh, you'll have plenty
of times to be pretty.
I was just going to
ask you if you'd like
to be in the rest of
the shows out here.
You were?
- Will you?
- Will I?
Fifteen nights a year Cinderella
steps into her pumpkin coach
and becomes queen of Holiday Inn.
Well, what's the matter?
I wish I didn't have to work
all the other days in the year
to make these few possible.
Maybe a little later on
when we start doing better
you could stay out here all the time.
Did you hear what you just said?
Yeah.
Was it a proposal?
It will be when I get a
few bucks in the bank.
You're a strange duck.
You don't even give me
a chance to say darling
and throw my arms around you.
Better save that till
you see the bankbook.
Well, I guess I'm sort of engaged.
Say, what is this? A daisy chain?
Well, we were just looking for
the back of a girl we don't know.
Upon a February morn
A tiny baby boy was born
Abraham
When he growed up, this tiny babe
Folks all called him Honest Abe
Abraham
In 1860, he became
The sixteenth president
And now he's in the hall of fame
A most respected gent
That's why we celebrate
This blessed February date
Abraham
When black folks lived in slavery
Who was it set the darkie free?
Abraham
That's right, child.
When troubles come
down from the shelf
Who's heart was bigger than hisself?
Abraham
Yeah, ma'am!
The country's going to the dogs
They shouted loud and strong
Then from a cabin made out of logs
The right man came along
And that is why we celebrate
This blessed February date
Abraham
The U.S.A.'s united thanks
Yeah
To one whose name was Nancy Hanks
Tell me!
Abraham
She gave this land the finest son
That's what she did.
Who ever went to Washington
Who dat?
Abraham
When someone told him General Grant
Was drinking every night
He answered, "Go see if you can't
"Get all my generals tight"
That's why we celebrate
This blessed February date
Abraham
Good night.
I give up. She's not here tonight.
You wait here, I'll go up
and see if Jim's seen her.
Gus is waiting to take
you to the station.
Remember now, day after tomorrow,
St. Valentine's Day.
Someone's coming, we better
use the other stairway.
- Who is it?
- Bill-collector.
- Good night.
- Good night, Jim.
You better get inside before you
catch cold. You haven't got a coat.
- Well, I...
- Go on.
I don't need a coat now.
Hey, Ted. Did you find the girl?
This is terrible, I wish we could
recognize her from the front.
I feel like a wolf.
Why, Ted.
Ted!
- She's here!
- Who?
- I saw her!
- This way.
Let go of my coat.
This way, shortcut,
shortcut. Come on.
Giddyap.
It's locked, it's never
been locked before.
Let's try the other stairwell.
Let go of me, let go.
Go ahead.
Well, we've lost her again.
Did you get a look at
her face this time?
No, we're still working
from the rear.
How do you know it was her?
After all, she had an overcoat on.
I don't care if she had...
How do you know she
had an overcoat on?
Well, she... If she didn't,
look for a girl with pneumonia.
Come on. Let's get inside.
Say, Jim, when's your next show?
Next show? St. Valentine's
Day, I think.
- Day after tomorrow, huh?
- Is it?
That's our break.
We'll get here bright and early
and stay until we find her.
We'll make an announcement
asking her to identify herself.
- We won't miss next time.
- No.
Say, fellas, how did
you like the show?
Well, we were so busy we didn't
see much of it, Jim. Why?
I thought the people seemed
to like the blackface routine.
Yeah, they did.
Don't you think a blackface number
on St. Valentine's
Day would be novel?
- A what?
- It's no good, eh?
Just an idea I had.
Well, good-bye.
- Good-bye, Ted.
- So long, Jim.
Bye, Dan.
- Hey, lady.
- Yes.
You know we open in an hour.
You haven't even had a rehearsal.
Coming.
Oh, very smart.
You'll have to talk Gus into
buying a horseless carriage.
I spend half my life between
here and the station.
I think Gus will have to face the
machine age sooner or later, won't he?
Did you escape those
bill-collectors the other night?
Bill-collectors?
Oh, yes, temporarily.
Say, that reminds me,
I have a surprise for you downstairs.
Well, thanks. What reminds you?
Nothing, it's just... I mean,
I want you to remember the surprise
when those doggone
bill-collectors move in.
You sound sweet,
but you don't make sense.
The inn is so romantic looking.
Nice? I posed for
those cupids myself.
Hello, boys.
Hi. How are you?
Paid-up cards here tonight.
Where's the surprise?
Aha! Right here, a little
home cooking I whipped up.
Beautiful.
"Be Careful, It's My Heart."
And I ain't kidding, either.
I wrote this just for you, honey.
Be careful, it's my heart
It's not my watch you're
holding, it's my heart
It's not the note I sent you
That you quickly burned
It's not the book I lent you
That you never returned
Remember, it's my heart
The heart with which
so willingly I part
It's yours to take, to keep or break
But please, before you start
Be careful, it's my heart
It's not my watch you're
holding, it's my heart
It's not the note I sent you
That you quickly burned
It's not the book I lent you
That you never returned
Remember, it's my heart
The heart with which
so willingly I part
It's yours to take, to keep or break
But please, before you start
Be careful, it's my heart
I'm sorry, Jim, I couldn't resist it.
Wonderful, she's prefect,
light as a feather.
You found her, Jim. You're a pal.
Yeah.
Young lady, do you realize
that we've been searching
for you for weeks?
- For me?
- Yes, ever since...
The girl in the flower shop.
Yes, Mr. Reed.
Where have you been working
since New Year's Eve?
Here.
Would you mind letting
me in on your secret?
Oh, it's no secret.
Ted Hanover is looking for
a new dancing partner
and we've decided
to give you the job.
Oh, here now. Wait, just a minute.
Oh, no hard feelings, Jim,
I don't blame you for trying.
She is wonderful.
I feel as if I've
known her for months.
Oh. Same old feeling, huh?
Let's see, Washington's
Birthday is the next show.
That will give us a week of rehearsals.
We can open the act here.
I'll take care of the invitations.
Strictly formal.
I'll get all the newspaper
boys from New York.
Now hold everything. This is my inn,
and I am not running it for
a bunch of stuffed shirts.
What would you like,
the dungaree set?
Well, that would be better than the
bunch of chowder heads you drag in.
Maybe I can't use the act.
Not use Ted Hanover?
Well, the show is pretty well set.
You're in, but he's out.
But you could change the show
for a special occasion like this.
Of course he could. He's just
trying to hide his gratitude.
Jim, you better think
up a number for us.
Well, just what do
you visualize, Ziggy?
Ah, let's see.
For Washington's birthday I see,
sort of, a romantic costume thing.
- Naturally.
- Something that just reeks
- with grace and charm, you know?
- Mmm-hmm.
I think the music should
be sweet and gentle to...
Well, to create the mood, each time
I take her into my arms and kiss her.
That's it.
Don't you think it's getting
a little stuffy in here?
I could say that you're homely
Just as homely as pie
But this is Washington's birthday
And I've got to say you're beautiful
'Cause I can't tell a lie
I could say that you're stupid
Nothing up in your crown
But this is Washington's birthday
And the truthful he
Of the cherry tree
Would look down on me and frown
I could say that I hate you if I try
But I've got to say I love you
'Cause it's February
the twenty-second
And I can't tell a lie
Hit it.
Come in.
Well, honey, in spite of what
good old Jim tried to do to us,
your future starts as of tonight.
Now where would you
like to go from here?
- From here?
- Yes.
New York, Havana, Rio? We have
our pick of engagements, you know.
But I can't be your partner
if you leave the inn.
Of course you can. There's no reason
for you to remain buried here.
There's a very good reason.
I promised to be in Jim's holiday
shows for the rest of the year.
Ah, but he tricked you into that
while he was hiding you from me.
No matter how he
did it, I've promised.
Besides, well,
we're going to be married.
Married? Now wait a minute,
let's be fair.
He didn't give me a chance.
After all, I love you, too.
Linda, from the very first
moment we danced together,
I knew you were to be
the one girl in my life.
You didn't even know my name.
Please. All right,
forget about me, then.
Forget about Jim, think of yourself.
Here's your chance to do
the one thing you like best.
Not only for 15 days
a year, but always.
Sorry, but I promised.
Well?
I guess I should apologize for
hooking up your number, huh?
Oh, forget it. I'm the one
that should apologize to you.
Here I've been trying to
take Linda away from you
not knowing you two
were going to be married.
Married?
Yeah, aren't you?
Yes, sure.
I mean, naturally,
we're sort of engaged.
Oh.
Well, anyway, I've decided to
bow out of here. Linda's all yours.
Well, you're a pretty game
guy to take it this way.
Well, it's happened so often I'm
getting used to it, that's all.
Good-bye, kid.
A lot of luck, Ted.
Thanks.
How are we doing?
Two minutes ago, I would have
sold my chances for a tired dime.
But when a man is surprised to
hear that he's going to be married,
brother, that's when I go to
work with a clear conscience.
- Everything's good, huh?
- Everything is perfect.
In your Easter bonnet
With all the frills upon it
You'll be the grandest lady
In the Easter parade
I'll be all in clover
And when they look you over
I'll be the proudest fellow
In the Easter parade
On the Avenue
Fifth Avenue
The photographers will snap us
And you'll find that you're
In the rotogravure
Oh, I could write a sonnet
About your Easter bonnet
And of the girl I'm taking
To the Easter parade
On the Avenue
Fifth Avenue
The photographers will snap us
And you'll find that you're
In the rotogravure
Oh, I could write a sonnet
About your Easter bonnet
And of the girl I'm taking
To the Easter parade
Hello!
I didn't exactly expect
the welcome mat,
but I thought somebody
might say hello.
- Hello.
- Thanks.
What brings you here on this
bright and uninviting day?
I've discovered something,
my friends, about life.
Meaning what?
Well, I don't want success,
I want the true happiness you
people have found here at the inn.
You're not gonna stay in the inn?
Not just stay, I want to
be part of your shows,
help you in your work,
share your simple pleasures.
I asked you once not
to interfere, Ted.
Please believe me, I am a tired,
lonely and unhappy man.
But I could be happy here, helping
the two people I like the best.
Will you take me in?
My motherly intuition
tells me to throw him out.
Well, at least give him
the benefit of the doubt.
I've given him plenty of doubt.
Are you kidding with that "sharing
life's simple pleasures"?
May I go inside with you?
Why, of course.
My... My trunks will
arrive this afternoon.
What do I do?
Move in the broom closet?
Jim, that's no way to talk to
a man who's here to help you.
The world doesn't change.
A gentle smile often breeds
a kick in the pants.
But for your sake,
Linda, I'll be big.
I'll give you a tip about
these things, Gus.
They'll go up and back,
but not sideways.
Yeah, well, I keep forgetting
this blind thing can't
see where it's going.
Yeah, well, unload the rest of
this stuff in the back, huh?
Hey! What did you do,
get up before breakfast?
Why, every morning.
I trust you slept well.
When I found out how late you got in,
I told Mamie to let you sleep.
- Life on a farm!
- Can't beat it, huh?
Jim, you've made me very happy!
That's fine.
Now, how about you making me happy?
You sound like a landlord
with eviction papers.
Oh. This is good news,
Lila's back in New York.
I got a letter from her yesterday.
What happened to her millionaire?
Slight mistake there.
He didn't own millions, he owed them.
Poor girl, always straying to greener
pastures and finding spinach.
Say, she was wondering if you'd
be interested in taking
her back as a partner.
I think it'd be a great idea.
Naturally, you would.
But I like it here
with you and Linda.
Yes, and we love having you, too.
Uh, when are you leaving?
- Why didn't you say something?
- You look so silly.
- Where's Jim?
- Inside.
Good. I've fixed it. Here's the news
in one luscious word: Hollywood!
Now, I told you, I'm not leaving
here until Linda goes with me.
But this is the setup you needed
to get her away from Jim.
Now, there are going to be two
Hollywood men here tonight
to see the show.
One's an important director.
If they like your dancing,
you and Linda
will be on a westbound
train tomorrow.
We better find out
if Linda's interested.
We let her know when there's a
contract staring her in the face.
- Look...
- Now I know you're in love with the girl
but forget her until we
get her away from here.
This is no time to be honest.
Well, what should I do?
All we have to do is to convince Jim
that he'd be a heel if he stood
in the way of a chance like this.
Oh, that'll be easy,
like peeling a turtle.
Mamie says these go up here!
Yes, set them right down.
Say, Gus, how would you
like to earn a slow $10?
Well, I don't care
how slow, but sure.
It's sure, all right,
here's the wrinkle,
I want you to go down to the station
pick up a party and
start for Holiday Inn
but never get here.
Could you handle that?
Wouldn't be surprised!
Hello, long distance.
That's what I want you
to do with Linda Mason.
Miss Mason? Our friend?
You're not supposed
to understand it, Gus.
For that kind of money you ought to
be able to go by way of Medicine Hat.
Hello, yeah. Just a minute.
Long distance, I want
to get Parkway Hotel,
New York City, Miss Lila Dixon.
Didn't Linda say she'd be
here for final rehearsal?
Oh, relax, our audiences
aren't professional critics.
Gus, you made a wrong turn.
Shortcut.
Gus!
Shortcut, another shortcut.
How could you possibly expect
to drive through this?
Well, I never had no
trouble with a horse.
Oh, you'd better carry me to shore,
and I'll walk back to the highway.
Well, I think you'd be better
off waiting right here.
Gus, will you please do as I say?
Oh, all right.
- The other way.
- Huh?
Turn around. Gus, turn around!
Oh!
Gus!
- My hat!
- You pushed me.
Get my hat!
I swear the show will
start any minute now.
You said that an hour ago.
Yeah, but this time
I'm sincere. Excuse me.
Who started the show?
I did. You're on.
But what about Ted's partner?
You've kept this crowd waiting long
enough, he can go on without her.
Have you gone nuts?
I've rehearsed a double dance.
Let's say it with firecrackers
and banners held high
Let's have a real old-fashioned
noisy Fourth of July
Let's say it with firecrackers
They'll jump at up North
Let's have the kind we used
to call a glorious Fourth
Let's salute our native land
Roman candles in each hand
While a Yankee Doodle band
Gets hotter than a firecracker
Don't need any long speeches
Or shouts of "Hooray!"
No words can say as much
as firecrackers can say
Freedom! Freedom!
Here comes the Freedom Man
On this day of independence
On this Independence Day
Listen to an American
troubadour from the U. S.A.
I'm singing a song of freedom
For all people who cry out to be free
Free to sail the seven seas
Free to worship as we please
If the birds up in the trees
Can be free
Why can't we?
I'm bringing a song of freedom
To all people wherever they may be
Free to speak and free to hear
Free from want and free from fear
Sons of freedom far and near
Who agree
Sing with me
That all God's people shall be free
I'm singing a song of freedom
For all people who cry out to be free
Free to sail the seven seas
Free to worship as we please
If the birds up in the trees
Can be free
Why can't we?
I'm bringing a song of freedom
To all people wherever they may be
Free to speak and free to hear
Free from want and free from fear
Sons of freedom far and near
Who agree
Sing with me
That all God's people shall be free
Will you give me a lift?
Sure, hop in.
Aren't you Ted Hanover's
former dancing partner?
Yes, although I wouldn't
exactly say former.
I'm dancing with him
at the inn tonight.
But I... Doesn't he
have a new partner?
Oh, she won't be there tonight.
I didn't know that!
I work at the inn.
Oh?
Waitress?
Yes.
I know your boss, Jim Hardy,
quite well. Quite well.
Then he's responsible for
your rejoining Mr. Hanover.
Uh-huh.
By the way, if I were you,
I'd look my prettiest tonight
when I'm waiting on tables.
Jim says there will be a
couple of men from Hollywood
to consider Ted and me for pictures.
And Mr. Hanover's other partner
will be missing this chance
to go to Hollywood.
Yes, although she can't
be very talented
or they wouldn't be
working at the inn.
Ted and I played
only the best places.
Listen, you're late
for the show already,
if you'd care to let me drive
I know a shortcut that'll get
us there 15 minutes sooner.
There's a farmhouse near here
and I'll have us towed out
in a couple of minutes.
Oh, for the love of mud, hurry!
Wait right here!
What else can I do?
- You're on now.
- But Linda isn't here yet.
You've got to save the pieces,
keep those men interested now
and do a number with Linda later.
What can I do?
Well, fake something.
Fake something, okay.
There's your cue.
Don't fail me, keep them flying.
I'll keep them flying.
Linda! What happened to you?
A bad job of sabotage.
Excuse me!
Well, Jim, you deliberately kept me
from working at the inn
tonight, didn't you?
- Yeah.
- You knew there would be men here
from Hollywood who might
offer me a chance in pictures.
You've decided I shouldn't
have that opportunity.
Not even the opportunity to refuse.
I was afraid the offer might
be too important for
you to turn down.
The point is you don't trust
me to make my own decisions
because they might interfere
with your own selfish plans.
I've had about enough of that, Jim.
Ted, Linda!
Mr. Parker, Mr. Dunbar,
I want you to meet the
greatest dance team
in show business, Hanover and Mason.
And the owner Jim Hardy.
Glad to know you, Hardy.
Nice little place you've got here.
Gentlemen, even though
you haven't seen
Miss Mason dance, I can assure you...
Hardy, Hollywood is always interested
in new ideas and we
think this is a honey.
Frankly, we'd like to do a picture
based on the Holiday Inn.
The idea behind it, how it works,
the special holiday songs.
Of course, it's purely a speculative
thing, far from foolproof
and we can't afford to pay too much.
You don't have to
start talking it down
because the idea is not for sale.
Well, maybe I haven't
explained enough.
We expect to use Mr. Hanover
and his partner in the picture.
Well, I don't know
how the others feel
but I'd like to keep this little
setup just the way it is.
Jim, would you be decent just once
and let somebody else
around here have a chance?
Wait a minute, Danny, after
all, the place belongs to him
he can do as he wants.
I guess it was just
too good to last, huh?
A simple little layout,
where we could do our best
at the work we know without
having any illusions of glory.
I can see now that I'm the only
one who could be happy here.
Go ahead, take the idea,
take the music,
take Linda, take the
whole darn thing.
But what about you? We'll need you
in Hollywood to write
the rest of the music.
Oh, no, I work right here.
I'll send you the music
when it's written.
And don't bother me before, huh?
Guess maybe I was
a little selfish, huh?
Is that the deal you wanted or
should I have thrown in my shirt?
Chummy sort of a fellow, isn't he?
Listen, Linda, if you
really want to stay here...
Don't talk that way. This is the
chance you wanted, isn't it?
Of course. Boy, are we happy!
Happy Thanksgiving, Mr. Jim.
Same to you, Mamie. And staff.
Didn't I tell you children
to stay in the kitchen?
Those wings ain't going
to fly away. Now shoo!
Everything's ready and hot, Mr. Jim.
Thank you, Mamie.
I've got plenty to be thankful for
Are you kidding?
I haven't got a great big yacht
To sail from shore to shore
Still I've got plenty
to be thankful for
You're loaded, Dan.
I've got plenty to be thankful for
Like what?
No private car
No caviar
No carpet on my floor
Still I've got plenty
to be thankful for
You know you're better off than I am.
I've got eyes to see with
You need glasses.
Ears to hear with
Or fly with.
Arms to hug with
Lips to kiss with
Someone to adore
You're a little flat, too.
How could anybody ask for more?
My needs are small I buy them all
At the five and ten cent store
Sing it!
Sing it pretty.
Oh, I've got plenty
to be thankful for
Why, you ain't ate a bite.
I'm pouting, Mamie.
Who is this?
That's Mr. Jones.
Jonesey! I'm sorry,
I knew him too well.
But you got to eat.
The trouble ain't with that
turkey, Mr. Jim, it's you!
I feel all right.
I'm riding high, Mamie.
Well, why you close
the inn and sit around
like a jellyfish with the misery?
'Cause a slicker stole your gal
and you ain't got fight
enough to get her back.
Excuse me, Mr. Jim.
I tried to keep her here!
What kind of keeping is that?
Nothing but tricks.
If you went to Hollywood
and told Miss Linda how
much you loves her,
and misses her, and told her that
the way a lady likes to hear it told,
I'll bet you she'd be the quickest
ex-movie star that ever exed.
You're crazy, Mamie
I'm crazy? I knows Miss Linda.
I knows her like I knows my own kids.
Why, she ain't the fancy
type no more than you are.
What she wants is what
you got right here.
But women has to have them
things told to them the right way.
You could melt her heart
right down to butter,
if you'd only turn on the heat.
Mamie, you don't try
to take a fellow's gal
away from him after
he's bought the ring.
Or as I recall, do you?
Now you're talking!
Oh, sure, women has to be
told things the right way.
Yes, sir!
At last, the night I've been
dreaming about actually here.
This is still my wedding, you know.
You make me feel like a kibitzer.
Now don't misunderstand me,
I'm happy because this marriage means
that we can all settle
down and stop worrying.
I wish I had your confidence
without your viewpoint.
My fingers are crossed
until Linda and I
are on that plane bound for Yuma.
Now what's worrying you?
I don't know, except I've been
this close to marriage before
only to wake up next morning
and find myself with no
bride and a hangover.
Look, the girl said yes,
the picture finishes tonight,
there's a judge waiting in Yuma.
Come in!
Everything is all set and ready.
What could possibly happen to...
Hi, fellows!
Jim, what brought you here?
Train. Chug chug chug chug.
The wedding, when is it?
- Wedding?
- Yeah.
Well, we hadn't set any exact time.
Have you seen Linda?
No, no, not yet. But, say,
I saw your director,
he told me he was shooting
the finale tonight,
thought I'd like to see
how you make pictures.
He wouldn't... You wouldn't
like what they're doing tonight.
Why not?
Oh, no, that's dull, technical stuff.
Well, I'm a dull,
technical sort of a fellow.
Perhaps if you'd wait
and see Linda tomorrow.
Oh, no, I want to see the finish.
The success of you and Linda
means a lot to me, pal.
Say, why don't you be yourself.
What are you up to?
Well, I'm a son of a gun.
This is a beautiful hunk of welcome
for a guy who comes coast to coast
just to wish you a merry
Christmas and a happy wedding.
You remember how I suspected you
when you came to live at
the inn on Easter morning?
Silly, wasn't it?
Now I know he's up to something.
Oh, wait a minute
now let's not be unfair.
No?
No, we're treating Jim
like a poor country cousin.
- He doesn't mean any harm!
- No!
No, he just wants to see Linda.
So let's show him Linda.
Goodwill on earth toward men.
This... Where we going? What's this?
Hey, Ted! What is this?
I was afraid you'd gone crazy.
I'll keep him in here till
you get Linda on that plane.
I better hurry and get my clothes on.
Yeah, in the meantime
I'll go down to the set
and see how near ready they are.
Wait a minute,
my clothes are in there.
Merry Christmas!
Jim, pal! Wait!
Stop! We were only fooling!
Only you could think
of a thing like that.
Who you calling?
Nobody, the operator's gone.
Take it easy. Don't break your neck.
It's one of the most authentic
reproduction jobs we've ever done.
Is it?
And all worked out
from those photographs
we took of your place in Connecticut.
Uh-huh.
Well, Mamie and the kids ought to
see this. They'd never believe it!
Anything wrong?
Well, that Christmas tree's
a little out of place.
I'd guess nobody would
notice that but me or Linda.
We're going to start rolling
in a couple of minutes.
Come along with me where
you can see everything.
No, I'll just sort of
stay in the background.
I don't want to get in your way.
Well, suit yourself.
I'll see you later.
Right.
All right, darling,
we're going to follow you
on the boom from here inside the inn.
And when you get in the
other set, do your song.
Let's see, I think you have the mood,
your Hollywood success was empty,
you've lost the one man you love.
You know, the usual hope.
Just make me cry and you
can get to that wedding.
All ready for rehearsal!
Please! Let's shoot it.
Okay, it's a take!
All right, everybody,
quiet on the stage, it's a take.
Close them up. Come on, over there,
quiet down, let's get
settled, everybody.
Come on, everybody, let's get
settled now. This is the picture.
Hit the snow!
All right, roll 'em!
Sorry, Mr. Hanover,
but when the red light's on
you couldn't get in even
if you owned the studio.
Oh, but, pop, this is important.
I know, so is the light.
Hit the playback. Music!
All right, action!
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the treetops glisten
And children listen
To hear sleigh bells in the snow
...dreaming of a white
Christmas
With every Christmas card I write
May your days be merry and bright
Jim!
Cut it! Cut it!
That's it!
All right, gentlemen!
How could he get that
far in five minutes?
The lady must have been willing.
But the world can't do this to us.
Here she comes down the street
I'll admit my defeat
I've won my hot toddy
Over my scarred body
I knew that I'd win singing
But wait until she gets
a load of your dancing
We'll stay at the inn singing
All by myself I'll have
to stick to my dancing
Oh, no, my friend, I'm here to end
Your dancing trouble and strife
This will be fun, Miss Hit-and-Run
Has come back into my life
We'll stay at the inn...
We'll have to begin...
Singing!
Dancing!
We've each other to cling to
You'll be easy to sing to
And you're easy to dance with
So let the old year die
with a fond good-bye
And our hopes as high as a kite
How can our love go wrong
If we start the new year right?