He steps on the floor
Without making a sound
And then he starts feeling the beat
You would think the floor was greased
By the way he's moving his feet
He's a champion, he's the best
Impossible to tame
Go back! Stay! Stay!
Don't follow me to school. Stay! Stay!
Some kids have dogs
that follow them to school.
I think it's a head, ma'am.
Shall I throw it in the wastebasket?
Maybe you'd like to see it up close?
I can take it up to your desk, ma'am.
It's pretty heavy.
It feels like it's full of lead.
There you are, ma'am.
Now you can get a close look at it.
You missed it, sir.
We've been studying the human head.
Somehow I feel I should get you
for something, Marcie.
But I don't know what.
Put away that history book, Marcie.
Art is next.
I love art class.
How's this, ma'am?
Twenty-four cows standing in a pasture,
each one rendered in exquisite detail.
Maybe I'll add some sheep
and rabbits and squirrels.
A gorgeous pastoral setting.
Now I'll color the sky blue
and the grass green.
And I'll put in some yellow flowers.
Wow. What a picture!
What an artistic triumph.
Marcie, you haven't drawn a thing!
Some of us
are just patrons of the arts, sir.
What did you put down
for the fourth question?
Six times 12 is 72.
Seventy-two? I put down green.
Green? Why did you put down green?
I thought it was a trick question.
Marcie, this is hard work.
Boy, I sure could use
a little break right now.
Sorry, ma'am.
My nose is caught in my binder.
I'm trying not to scream.
It's very painful.
May I have permission
to see the school nurse?
Or maybe the custodian?
We may need a pair of pliers.
Sorry, ma'am.
I'm having trouble seeing where I'm going.
Ouch!
My report? I'm sorry, ma'am.
It's in my binder,
and my binder's caught in my hair.
I've tried whipping it
backward and forward.
But nothing seems to help.
Anyway, my report was called:
"Does education have to be painful?"
I think maybe it does.
No, ma'am.
I really can't take it off because--
Yikes!
Because my hair
is still caught in the binder.
Yikes!
She got it off. Marcie got it off.
What a relief.
My report? It's right here in my binder.
Don't sigh like that, ma'am.
It breaks my heart.
Gym is my favorite class.
I'm so dumb I wish all classes were gym.
I sure look forward to gym.
You know, Chuck? I may not be
as cute as that little red-haired girl,
and I may not have
naturally curly hair like Frieda,
and I may not be as smart as Lucy,
but I've got one thing none of them has.
I'm in shape!
I run five miles every morning
I do a hundred push-ups every day
I pedal every night
Take a swim, take a hike
I'm in shape
I'm in shape, I'm in shape
She's practicing
Peppermint Patty's PE program
She's in shape
She's in shape, she's in shape
When other kids
Are fading at the finish
When all the others fail
To break the tape
I saunter 'round the track
And wave to Daddy
I'm in shape
I'm in shape, I'm in shape
She's practicing
Peppermint Patty's PE program
She's in shape
She's in shape, she's in shape
Hey, Linus, get in shape
Pretty soon it'll be too late
Hey, Linus! Hey, Linus!
Hey, Chuck, you know how
Get in shape, do it now
-Hey, Chuck
Everybody get fit
Stop thinking about it, this is it
Lucy, Linus, Schroeder, Sally
Everybody work
So if you want to follow my example
You're gonna have to work
There's no escape
You gotta get
With Peppermint Patty's PE program
Get in shape
Get in shape, get in shape
She's practicing
Peppermint Patty's PE program
-She's in shape
-I'm in shape
-I'm in shape, I'm in shape
-She's in shape
-I'm in shape
In shape, in shape
Okay, Chuck. Lift those legs.
Lift them higher.
Oh, good grief.
Are you ready for the party tonight,
Sally?
I remember the last time
I went to a party.
Linus called up and asked me if I would
like to go to a party.
And I said, "Yes."
And then when we got there,
Linus asked me if I would like to dance.
And I said, "Yes."
Then after we danced, Linus said,
"Would you like a glass of punch?"
And I said, "Yes.
That would be very nice.
I would like to have a glass of punch."
I don't believe that ever happened.
Well, it should have!
Okay, gang, we're gonna play Simon Says.
I'll start it.
Simon says, "Raise your arms."
Simon says, "Turn around."
Simon says, "Clap your hands."
Simon says--
Okay, it's my turn now.
Lucy is the boss, Lucy is the boss
So you got to listen to Lucy
Listen to Lucy
Lucy's the boss, Lucy is the boss
So you gotta listen to Lucy
Listen to Lucy
And here's what Lucy says
Lucy says,
"Put your hands on your head"
Listen to Lucy, listen to Lucy
Lucy says, "Now turn around"
Put your hands by your side
Ah-ah, I didn't say "Lucy says"
Lucy's the boss, so listen to Lucy
And here's what Lucy says
Lucy says,
"Take your hands off your head"
Listen to Lucy, listen to Lucy
Lucy says, "Put them on your hips now"
Now jump up and down
Ah-ah, I didn't say "Lucy says"
Lucy's the boss, so listen to Lucy
And here's what Lucy says
Lucy says, "I wanna be
The queen of the world, yes, I do"
Lucy says, "I want everything my way"
Hey-hey-hey
Lucy says "I'm gonna be
A beautiful girl, yes, I am"
Lucy says
"I'm gonna marry Schroeder someday"
Oh, good grief!
Lucy says, "Pick up your right foot"
Listen to Lucy, listen to Lucy
Lucy says, "Now hop on your left foot"
Now start running in place
Ah-ah, I didn't say "Lucy says"
Lucy is the boss, so listen to Lucy
And that's what Lucy says
What are you doing, Sally?
I'm waiting for my Sweet Babboo.
I am not your Sweet Babboo!
I'm waiting here because
my Sweet Babboo asked me
to have the next dance with him.
I did not!
Well, you should have!
Oh, brother.
I'll have a cup, please.
I'm glad to see
you're not only having a good time,
but you're also
helping out with the party.
I'll have a cup of punch, please.
You know, Charlie Brown,
you have to do something about your face.
It's impossible to talk to someone
when they're making such sour faces.
Okay, everybody, gather 'round
It's time for the Pigpen Hoedown
Kick up your heels, jump up and down
Shut your eyes and whirl around
Reach out your hand
And if no one's there
Grab your own hand
Dance 'round in a square
When you're doing the Pigpen Hoedown
Gotta have a caller you can trust
'Cause when Pigpen does a hoedown
He really kicks up some dust
Hey, Chuck, we're all bumping
into each other.
Let me give it a try.
Bow to your left, bow to your right
And if you find no one in sight
Just bow to your toes
And bow to your knees
And dance around just as you please
When you're doing the Pigpen Hoedown
Gotta have a caller you can trust
'Cause when Pigpen does a hoedown
He really kicks up some dust
-I can hardly see.
-It's getting worse.
Hey, Patty, we're still bumping
into each other. Let me be the caller.
We don't need a caller, Lucy.
We need a vacuum cleaner.
If we really wanna dance
And we stay here we got no chance
So nod to the ceiling
And bow to the floor
Leave Pigpen here
And head for the door
When you're doing the Pigpen Hoedown
Gotta have a caller you can trust
'Cause when Pigpen does a hoedown
He really kicks up some dust
Do you realize what you're becoming?
I don't know what you're becoming,
but I do know what you're not becoming.
You don't do any of the things
that a dog is supposed to do.
You don't bark at strangers.
You don't bring in the morning paper.
You don't even bring me
my slippers at night.
In the old days,
dogs used to round up sheep
and guard them in case wolves attacked.
I never see you rounding up sheep.
I'll bet you don't even know
what one looks like.
You don't try to follow me to school,
and you don't meet me when I come home.
There's nothing worse than owning a dog
who isn't a dog.
Who can fly a doghouse
Up in the bright blue sky?
It's Snoopy, it's got to be him
Who can wind up his ears
Lift up his head and fly?
It's not a Rover, not a Fido
No, no, not him
It's not a Lassie, not a Benji
Not Rin Tin Tin
Well, it's Snoopy
Who's in the bathroom? Open up.
He can do anything
Snoopy makes everyone smile
Who doesn't need a glove
To be the best shortstop around?
It's Snoopy, it's got to be him
Who can put on his shades
And be the coolest dog in town?
It's not a Rover, not a Fido
No, no, not him
It's not a Lassie, not a Benji
Not Rin Tin Tin
Well, it's Snoopy, Snoopy
-Talkin' 'bout Snoopy
He can do anything
Snoopy makes everyone smile
He steps on the floor
Without making a sound
Then he starts feeling the beat
You would think the floor was greased
By the way he's moving his feet
He's a champion, he's the best
Impossible to tame
People say that he's obsessed
Listen to the sound of his name
They call him Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he moves around
The whole room starts to reel
You know he's Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he jumps up high
He glides like a wild eagle
Lightning flashes when he leaps up
He's got everybody shouting for more
Thunder crashes
When he hits the ground
He's burnin' up the dancin' floor
He's a champion, he's the best
Impossible to tame
People say that he's obsessed
Listen to the sound of his name
They call him Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he moves around
The whole room starts to reel
You know he's Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he jumps up high
He glides like a wild eagle
Flashbeagle?
I can't stand it.
I need something for show-and-tell.
I pick you
because you're a first-round draft pick.
Yes, sir. You're going to get me an "A"
for show-and-tell.
A real, live dog.
For show-and-tell, I brought
my pet chameleon. His name is George.
And George changes colors
with every shirt I wear.
George eats flies and bugs. Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
Heel, Snoopy.
For show-and-tell today,
I have brought a dog.
What's so great about that?
He doesn't do anything.
He just stands there.
He looks like he's asleep.
A dog is not only man's best friend,
but he's also a protector, a defender,
a ferocious friend in need-- indeed.
From the fur on his feet
To the tip of his nose
He's got rhythm
Pumping all through his veins
Oh, he spins like a top
That'll never stop
With the power of a hurricane
He's a champion, he's the best
Impossible to tame
People say that he's obsessed
Listen to the sound of his name
They call him Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he moves around
The whole room starts to reel
You know he's Flash, Flash
Flash, Flash, Flashbeagle
When he jumps up high
He glides like a wild eagle
A wild eagle
I don't know what to do about Snoopy.
I should give him a good lecture,
the way he carries on.
You just leave him alone.
That's the first time
I ever got an "A" in show-and-tell.