Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Chelsea
- Happy birthday. Good night.
- Good night.
Chelsea!
Chelsea, come on. We have no time.
My painting! Where's my painting?
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Bob!
Daddy! Daddy!
Bob, get the hell out of there,
for God's sake!
Jesus!
This was
the scene 18 years ago,
as millions of dollars' worth of Sebastian
Deardon paintings literally went up in smoke.
Deardon perished in the flames.
Surviving the inferno was his
eight-year-old daughter, Chelsea Deardon.
Last night,
that same Chelsea Deardon, now 26,
was arrested for attempting to steal
one of her father's valuable paintings
from the Manhattan penthouse
of Robert Forrester. Police...
Hey. I was watching that.
- Sorry! The news is so boring.
- Yeah.
Did you do your homework?
I'm just finishing it.
Your mother always tells me
to make sure you do your homework.
And you tell me that you have no homework,
until it's time to leave.
Why is that?
I only have to write one paragraph
on an emotion. It's easy.
Easy? You think things are easy?
- Can we go out for breakfast?
- No, we can't go out for breakfast.
We ate out last night.
When you stay with me, we're a family.
We eat in,
occasionally.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
- You didn't sleep again, did you?
- Huh?
- You didn't sleep again.
- I slept.
I woke up and I heard these strange sounds.
And...
Were you dancing in the bathroom?
Dancing in the bathroom?
Mom says whenever you can't sleep,
you tap dance in the bathroom.
Oh, she did, huh? Do you believe that?
Well, so I danced once or twice,
but I don't tap dance.
Uh-huh?
Dad!
Oh!
Get back. Hold on.
I got it. I can handle it.
Got it.
Don't tell Mom about the toast.
See you in a few days.
- Bye.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, it's, um...
- Good morning.
- Hey. Good morning, Tom.
- You're going to court.
- Court? This morning?
Howard Marchek, receiving stolen property.
Slumber party?
Marchek. This isn't my case.
This is Henning's.
Yours now. Henning's got laryngitis.
Tom, thanks.
You were right about the landlady.
I put her on the stand
and she cracked like an egg.
Oh, yeah?
I cracked her like a walnut.
She crumbled like blue cheese.
- He ought to open a restaurant.
- How'd you get oatmeal on your shirt?
Oh, damn it.
Do me a favor, will you?
Help me with this shirt.
What do I got here?
What's wrong here?
Oh, great.
I hate to break up your aerobics class,
Logan, but this is important.
- What do you got, Blanchard?
- Logan, I need that 750 form.
- Of course you do. What is it?
- 750?
The monthly composite of trials
and verdicts.
- Do you have it?
- No. No, I don't.
- Okay.
- I filed an 822 instead.
Logan, I'm familiar with every form
used in every division of the DA's office.
I assure you there's no 822,
and I do know that.
You got me.
Okay. I'd like to see this form, 750,
on my desk by the end of the day.
- Okay? Thank you.
- Yes.
- You've got lunch with the chief today.
- Yeah, I know. 12:30, his office.
1:00 at Le Zinc.
Right, 1:00. Le Zinc.
Hey. Marchek,
- who's the defense on that case? Yeah?
- Laura J. Kelly.
She once tried to put a dog
on the witness stand.
Under oath?
Mr. Marchek is a beloved member
of a very large and tight-knit family.
We've brought forth over two dozen
cousins, aunts, uncles, in-laws,
each of whom has testified under oath
that the alleged stolen property
was given to Mr. Marchek
as birthday gifts by them.
Now, 14 of them chose to give him
a television set.
An unlikely coincidence?
Under normal circumstances, perhaps.
But we all heard Mr. Marchek's
sworn testimony
that all he really wanted
was a sort of a media room,
not unlike that of
the President of the United States.
Now, then. The prosecution has made
a rather big issue out of the fact
that none of these relatives could
produce a receipt for the merchandise.
Oh, that's a very lovely watch, sir.
Do you have a receipt?
No.
- Clerk, arrest this man.
- Objection, Your Honor.
Defense is fondling one of the jurors.
Sustained.
You're not a thief.
Neither is Howard Marchek.
Receipts come, and receipts go.
He did what any compassionate human being
would've done in a situation like this.
He offered a fellow citizen a fair deal.
Are we to reward that kindness
with a jail term?
For all our sakes, I hope not.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
please look into your hearts,
place yourselves in Mr. Marchek's position,
and return a verdict of "not guilty."
Thank you.
Before I begin my closing remarks,
I'd like to congratulate Miss Kelly
on a defense which has been
so entertaining and imaginative.
I must confess to you, I...
I didn't know whether to refute it
or to simply give it a round of applause.
But we're not in a theater here.
We're in a court of law.
And in court we have to deal with the facts.
Now, the defense says
this was a birthday party.
Well, we've all been to birthday parties.
We've had our share of birthday presents.
But all known generosity pales
when compared to the attention
lavished on Mr. Howard Marchek
by his adoring relatives.
This must have been some birthday party.
Detectives said they found TV sets,
stereos, microwaves, typewriters.
Not exactly the kind of variety
you find at Sears,
but definitely selling
at much better prices.
What about the Obitser arraignment?
- I'll set the date.
- Mr. Logan. Slow down.
Twenty-seven relatives, birthday presents.
Were you serious?
It was all I had.
It was the best possible defense.
That case never should have gone
to court.
You should have pleaded him
guilty at the arraignment.
Think of it this way, every person,
guilty or innocent, deserves a defense.
- It's in the Constitution. You could look it up.
- Why are you following me?
I'd like you to talk to one of my clients,
Chelsea Deardon.
I plan to talk to Chelsea Deardon, in court.
I'm not talking about court.
There are special circumstances
surrounding this case. I'd like to brief you...
- If the evidence is compelling enough...
- It is.
Well, then I'm sure the jury will agree
with you. Now, excuse me.
I'm trying to prevent
a miscarriage of justice.
I'm talking about evidence
a jury may never have a chance to hear.
You have a reputation for fairness.
Chelsea Deardon is important to me.
- She's a client I can believe in.
- Like Howard Marchek?
That's it?
- That's the entire extent of your curiosity?
- Oh, no, on the contrary.
Twenty-seven relatives, a talking dog?
I can't wait to see what you're gonna
come up with next. See you in court.
Clients of yours?
Listen, you got to get that done this
afternoon because of the banquet. All right?
Got it. Right.
Watch it!
Tom.
- Tom.
- Yeah.
You got a handkerchief?
Yeah, sure. God.
That is my table.
I sit there every day of the week.
- Just a minute.
- You know it is.
- Please, sir.
- I always have reservations.
I'm sorry.
- Tom, I need your legal opinion.
- Not now, I gotta see Bowers.
I'll make it short.
My client slams his truck
through the window of a 7-Eleven.
He breaks a customer's leg,
bangs up the clerk with bruises.
You got a problem.
Okay, look, my client is driving,
but he is also with a woman
who's resting her head in his lap actively.
What are you talking about?
Speak English, Ed.
Resting her head with affection.
Naturally, this breaks his concentration
on driving, and...
I can build a case on this.
Ultimately, the accident is her fault
and not his.
- What do you think?
- I'd sell the screen rights.
Chief.
- A drink for you, sir?
- Um...
- Yeah. No. Sorry.
- You're late. Cause me stress.
Doctor says I'm supposed to
cut down on stress.
These pills kill the acid in the coffee
before the acid in the coffee kills me.
Now let's get to the point here.
You know, Tom, I always had
the highest personal regard for you,
both as a lawyer and a human being.
I appreciate that.
That's why I picked you to give the keynote
at the banquet tonight.
Every year some poor son of a bitch
has to get in front of the crowd
and spout comforting nonsense.
This year, I want to hear it
from someone with style and charm.
I want to hear it from someone
who's my choice
for the next district attorney.
You.
Me?
This is finally it, folks,
my last year as your district attorney.
Too late.
Appeal denied.
Now then, the big question is,
who'll replace me?
Well, perhaps someone
like our keynote speaker here tonight.
For the past 12 years,
I've given this man
the toughest assignments
and the heaviest case loads,
and for one simple reason.
He gets the job done!
Ladies and gentlemen,
a man whose past performance
guarantees him a brilliant future,
Tom Logan.
Chelsea, wait.
Let's do something.
I think this is better.
Yeah. Much better.
An attorney has to know the truth.
Whether he attacks it or defends it,
the truth is the touchstone of his trade.
That's the tricky part,
because clients often lie to him.
I don't know what it is about us,
but it seems to be human nature
to lie to a lawyer.
Is that him?
If your client was five miles away
from the scene of a crime,
he'd probably tell you he was 10 miles away.
Nobody seems to trust a lawyer enough
to tell the truth.
Because we are
what we are,
and tend to...
Because we... We, uh...
Because people lie so often to lawyers,
a prosecuting attorney in particular
has to develop that instinct
when it comes to determining the truth,
even when it turns out to be
against his best interests.
He has to expose the truth.
Now, that's justice.
And that's why I'm an attorney.
Thank you.
We'll back you all the way.
Kelly wants to file a cross-complaint
on the Deardon case. I told her no.
What?
She's threatened to call
a press conference right on the spot.
What did you tell her?
I told her that you'd
examine the cross-complaint.
A quick investigation.
We don't need this kind of press.
- Well, I'm not gonna do it.
- Come on, Chelsea.
No.
Moments ago, Laura J. Kelly,
a Manhattan attorney
told us she plans to file charges
against the district attorney's office.
Miss Kelly, can you tell us
what this is all about?
Well, first, I'd like to apologize
for my conduct this evening.
She's doing it. She's doing it.
...left open to us.
This young lady, Chelsea Deardon,
has been victimized
by some very unscrupulous people.
We've been trying to get cooperation
from the DA's office,
but so far they've been stonewalling us.
We have no choice
but to file a cross-complaint
against the district attorney's office
in this matter.
Oh! Here is Tom Logan
from the district attorney's office.
Mr. Logan, what can you tell us
about this situation?
Well, this is a total surprise to me.
I can assure you that
if there's any implication of impropriety
on the part of our office,
why, it's unfounded.
I'd like to also say that I personally will
be taking charge of this case from now on.
Well, I'd like to add that I had no doubt
that when a man of Tom Logan's
character and reputation
found out about the predicament
of my client,
he would take quick and decisive action.
Thank you so much, Mr. Logan.
Okay. For the record,
and so there's no misunderstandings,
you're entitled to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be held against you.
If you're not exactly thrilled with your
attorney, one will be provided.
- Oh, no, I like her.
- Thanks.
Did you steal the painting?
- No.
- Yes.
Yes, but no.
- Which is it?
- Both.
This is going to be a waste of my time.
I can feel it.
I did try to take the painting,
but it already belonged to me.
Can you prove that?
My father gave me that painting
when I was eight years old.
He even dedicated it to me
on the back in writing.
All anyone has to do is look.
Is there any other proof
that that painting once belonged to you?
My father kept a journal.
Chelsea, you never told me about that.
There were sketches
of that painting in the journal.
Beside one of them, he wrote
"For Chelsea's eighth birthday."
I'd like to see the journal.
It's in my apartment.
You can come by any time.
I'll be up there soon.
What... Who did you steal
this painting from?
She didn't steal the painting.
She allegedly stole the painting.
From one Robert Forrester,
major developer.
Robert Forrester?
What were you doing at his place?
His wife throws parties for young artists.
That way people think she knows art.
She's bored. She likes to wear earrings.
- And what is the painting worth?
- $200,000.
- Your father must've made a lot of money.
- I guess.
- How much inheritance did you get?
- None.
The estate was bankrupt.
All the unsold paintings
were destroyed in the fire,
including the one that
Chelsea allegedly stole from Forrester's.
Okay.
We'll look at the painting tomorrow,
and if there's an inscription on the back,
I'll consider dropping the charges.
Great.
- Mr. Forrester.
- Come in.
I'm afraid I can't show the Deardon to you,
Mr. Logan.
You see, I no longer own it.
- I don't understand.
- I traded it just yesterday.
- Traded it to whom?
- To a gallery.
Which gallery?
Taft Gallery.
Mr. Forrester, that painting is
material evidence in a felony proceeding.
Not anymore.
You see, I've decided to drop
all charges against Chelsea.
- What?
- Why?
Her father and I were very good friends.
Chelsea's had a rather difficult childhood.
It's obvious to me she acted on impulse.
There was no harm done.
Well, forgive me for asking, Mr. Forrester,
but what did you receive
in return for the Deardon?
A Picasso for a Deardon?
Yes, I thought it was
a rather good trade as well.
Mmm. This is good.
So Taft traded a Picasso for a Deardon.
That's not a good trade?
Not for a gallery owner that attempts
to stay in business.
No offense, Logan,
but since I know something about art,
- why don't you let me do the talking?
- Sure.
Can I help you?
Yes. Mr. Logan, Miss Kelly.
We're here to see Mr. Taft.
- Oh, yes.
- He's expecting us.
- Yes. Wait here just one moment.
- Okay.
Dubuffet.
de Kooning.
Calder.
How about that?
- Mr. Logan?
- Yes.
I'm Victor Taft.
Thanks for calling in advance.
I have a rather busy schedule,
as I'm sure you can appreciate.
I do. We'll be brief. This is Miss Kelly.
- Pleasure.
- Magnificent gallery.
I was wondering if you have any Picassos
around here at this present time?
Well, yes. Matter of fact,
you're standing right in front of one.
Right.
Right. That's expensive?
Oh...
Value is a relative thing, is it not?
Come. Let me show you around.
Picasso is one of the true masters
of this century.
And yet you traded a Picasso
for a Deardon,
which couldn't possibly be worth as much.
That particular Deardon was one of his last.
A work of total confidence and maturity.
Deardon was my discovery,
so I feel proprietary about his work.
I pestered Robert Forrester
to part with it for years.
Frankly, I was thrilled
when he finally agreed.
Let's set it on the stand.
It's a Bertolini. Startling, isn't it?
It was his model for a larger version,
which stands at Southern Square Park.
I bet the price's equally startling.
It's not for sale.
It was given to me personally by the artist.
It has great sentimental value.
If you don't mind me asking, Mr. Taft,
what exactly was or is
your relationship with Chelsea Deardon?
Her father and I were very close.
I watched little Chelsea grow up.
Mr. Logan, you're leaning.
Sorry.
Recently, Chelsea and I have lost touch.
I have followed her career,
but her sensibility in art doesn't interest me.
She's... She's a performance artist.
- Happenings, very ephemeral experiences.
- She's what?
- A performance artist.
- I hear she's quite talented.
Ah. Thank you, Roger.
It's very powerful.
It is.
I'd like to see the other side,
if you don't mind.
How refreshing.
Most of my clients prefer to see the front.
That was one of the shiftiest
performances I've ever seen.
I don't know.
I thought he was pretty straightforward.
Logan, whatever happened to that sixth sense
you're supposed to be so famous for?
- Doesn't it feel too neatly tied up to you?
- Kelly, it's dead.
There's no signature.
The charges are dropped. It's done.
- Can I get you a cab?
- I can get my own cab, thanks.
God, give me a break.
Okay.
That's it.
No.
- I couldn't let you do it.
- Why not?
You wouldn't be seen.
You'd be throwing away your own career.
It has nothing to do with my career.
...feeling
I'm happy again
I'm laughing at clouds
Come on with the rain
I've a smile on my face
- Someone's following me.
- What?
- I'm scared. Can I come in?
- Who... How did you...
Sure. How did you know where I live?
- I was afraid he'd follow me home.
- Who? Who'd follow you home?
- The man.
- What man?
I don't know what man.
I've seen him at three different times
and three different places today.
Where is he now? Do you know?
Probably right out front.
I'm sorry. I don't see anybody.
He's hiding.
Chelsea, you can't stay here.
Maybe a friend's house?
I don't have a friend.
Okay. I'll run you home.
Hang on. I'll get dressed.
Did you talk to Kelly?
Earlier.
So then you know there's no signature
on the back of that painting?
You're sure Victor Taft showed you
the right painting?
I suppose you think you're familiar enough
with my father's work
to tell one from another?
Won't you come in?
Okay.
- Lot of room.
- Yes.
What's all this?
Something I'm working on.
Let me show you.
Sit down.
Heart's desire, heart's desire
Never, never play with fire
Piece of cake.
Old flame.
I was driving down the highway
I saw a car burning on the side of the road
A woman was slumped over the wheel
Her shoulders were shaking,
like she was crying
Brush.
Brush fire.
Through the windshield,
on the hood of the car, there was a stack.
Maybe it was a small child.
As I drove by,
I noticed that nobody stopped.
Nobody stopped.
Neither did I.
Put out the fire.
Fire! Fire!
Fire.
Put out the fire.
Put out, put out.
Fire!
Fire! Fire!
What did you think?
I...
Think...
Fine.
What did you think?
I think...
I think I'm uncomfortable.
- Good.
- Good?
Yeah, good.
That's what I'm trying to do,
challenge your perspective.
Make you uncomfortable.
Still uncomfortable?
You bet.
There was a journal?
You said your father had a journal?
Mmm-hmm.
Can I see it?
Hmm?
- Yeah.
- Now?
Oh, I'd have to find it.
Well, it shouldn't take too long.
Maybe it's in the storeroom. I forget.
When was the last time you saw it?
- Two weeks ago.
- There's no journal, is there?
- There is a journal.
- But you don't have it?
- Do you always cross-examine people?
- Only when they lie.
I don't have anything
from when my father was alive.
There was a journal. There were paintings.
There was a fire.
I need your help.
I lied to you before because
I didn't think the truth was good enough.
He's there.
- What?
- He's there.
- No. There's no one there.
- No, he is. I can feel it.
- I gotta get some sleep.
- You can sleep here.
If there's any real trouble, call the police.
911, emergency.
Thanks for taking me home.
Something interesting up there?
Hi. This is Laura Kelly.
I can't come to the phone right now,
but if you leave your message at the tone...
Get me the police.
Miss Kelly, I need to talk to you.
Office hours are 9:00 to 5:00.
My number's in the book.
I'm with the police department, Miss Kelly.
My name is Cavanaugh, C.J. Cavanaugh.
I'm a detective. Manhattan South.
Just a minute.
- You have any ID?
- Yes, mam.
Show it.
Yeah, that's ID.
Come on in.
- What's this about?
- The Deardon case.
There is no Deardon case.
The charges were dropped yesterday.
Wrong Deardon case.
- Do you mind if I sit down?
- No. I'll sit with you.
Seventeen years ago,
I headed up an investigation
into the murder of Sebastian Deardon.
- Murder?
- Murder.
I... Could you excuse me?
Are you all right?
Fine.
- Can I get you something?
- No, no! No!
I read the record on that case.
There was nothing about a murder.
No. You read the whitewash, Miss Kelly.
My report got filed in somebody's
wastebasket down at City Hall.
Seventeen years ago,
I pushed on that case a little too hard
with the captain in charge.
All of a sudden, I'm busting winos
out in Staten Island.
So, what do you want me to do about this?
I want you to read this.
You're the Deardon girl's lawyer.
I hear you're curious.
Just read it.
If you need some more, I'll get it for you.
Wait a minute. Is this stolen material?
If it's stolen, you didn't get it from me,
because we never met, right?
- Try some tomato juice.
- Right.
Watson, have you seen Tom Logan?
Not since he buried me in court last week.
And I'm not looking for him either.
Okay.
- Thompson, where's Logan?
- I'm late, unprepared, and doomed!
- I need Logan, Thompson!
- He's in courtroom seven or six.
I don't know. One of those.
But you were having sexual relations
with the defendant.
No.
- I see.
- We have to talk.
- Then you don't deny it?
- On the contrary. I just did deny it.
- Oh, uh...
- Miss Kelly.
Today is my birthday
and things are going so well.
- Are you going to spoil my birthday?
- Happy birthday, Your Honor.
Begging the court's indulgence, could I
just confer with Mr. Logan for one moment?
- Mr. Rustavlov?
- No objection, Your Honor.
Get on with it.
I tried to call you last night.
The most incredible happened.
I'll say. I made a huge discovery that...
You tried to call me?
Yeah. What discovery?
The Deardon case. Major fraud.
I've got hard evidence.
Okay.
Your Honor, an important matter has just
come up that requires my urgent attention.
My learned assistant, Miss Freeman
will continue cross-examination
in my absence.
What? Me?
What about this hard evidence?
This.
It's a complete collection
of Sebastian Deardon's paintings.
Wait a minute.
This is a confidential insurance file.
Where'd you get this?
I have my sources.
Notice the red stamps
near most of the paintings?
These were the ones destroyed in the fire.
Look at 122.
Look familiar?
Yeah. This looks like the painting
that Taft showed us at the gallery.
Not looks like, Logan. Is.
Notice the red stamp next to it?
This painting was supposedly
destroyed in the fire.
I say we squeeze him and see what comes out.
Squeeze? No, no.
We're gonna go slow with this guy.
And I don't want to hear the word fraud
come out of your mouth,
'cause we don't know what we've got.
The whole thing could be a clerical error.
Right. A $20 million clerical error?
- I'm here with no authority whatsoever.
- Look.
You're in possession of insurance files
of a totally dubious origin.
Inside, I'll do the talking.
Stay behind me
and try to look like an attorney.
Yes, Your Holiness.
At $2,700,000 on the right side.
Now at $2,700,000. Now say 8.
$2,800,000 on the aisle here now.
At $2,800,000. Now say 9.
At $2,800,000 on the left aisle,
and fair warning
at $2,800,000.
Sold for $2,800,000.
That's for number 176.
Your next lot is number 12.
Lot 12, the Renoir.
Mr. Taft, I'd like to ask you a few more
questions about the Deardon painting.
Actually, I'm in the middle of pursuing
a rather elusive painting...
I'm sorry to bother you. Excuse me.
A colleague of mine
received some documents
related to art underwriting from
the Seaboard Fidelity Company.
- Please, I'm busy.
- We have evidence indicating
not as many Deardons
were destroyed in the fire
as was previously thought.
$1,300,000 now, in the left aisle,
a gentleman's bid at $1,300,000.
- I have $1,300,000 on the left.
- Go to $1.8.
$1,400,000. I have $1,400,000.
I have $1,400,000. Now 5. I have $1,400,000.
Five, $1,500,000. The gentleman at the back.
$1,500,000. Now 6.
I carried little Chelsea out
through the flames. I saved her life.
Everything else, everything,
burned to the ground.
And the Deardon you showed us yesterday?
Somehow that managed to survive.
Right. That's it. Get out, both of you,
before I have you thrown out.
- We're not making specific allegations...
- We know those paintings exist.
And we think you have them.
If you repeat that allegation anywhere,
publicly or privately,
I'll see to it you never practice law
in any court in this country.
That won't be necessary. Look,
I apologize for Miss Kelly's allegations
but as you know, I do represent
the district attorney's office.
And I would like to look
at your business records.
So if you'll just cooperate, I'm sure
we can avoid any further unpleasantness.
You seem an intelligent man, Mr. Logan.
Far too intelligent
to risk a profitable career
by meddling into legitimate matters
which are none of your concern.
Am I making myself clear?
Perfectly.
I'll have a grand jury issue you
a subpoena in the morning.
And I want to look at all of your records
for the past five years.
Shipping orders, inventories,
bills of sale, the works.
And if you fail to comply, I'll have a federal
marshal will confiscate those records,
and you'll be subject to arrest.
Is that clear?
- 'Bye.
- Good-bye, Mr. Taft.
"Oh, we know those paintings exist,
and we believe you have them."
Didn't you learn anything in law school?
Yeah, but, Logan,
we really shook him up in there.
Oh, yeah.
- That look in your eyes at the end.
- What?
Pure blue steel.
- What are you talking about?
- I'd like to develop a look like that.
You don't develop looks. You just look.
Not me. I practice looks in the mirror.
- I got one I picked up from you.
- What?
I'm cross-examining someone
and they give me an answer I just don't buy,
this is what you do.
- I don't do that.
- Yes, you do.
- All the time.
- Just like that.
- Come on.
You stand by the jury,
and you sort of give a quarter-turn,
and then you give that exact look.
I saw it, you totally discredited
Van Dyke with it.
Van Dyke? You were in the courtroom?
Yeah. Some people go to ballgames.
I go to court.
Do you have the keys?
Yeah.
Hang on. Hang on.
I'll be right back.
Where did you learn how to do this?
I used to... Never mind.
You can't always get it at first.
Well, you're closer.
- Much closer. There, you got it.
- Ah!
It's Taft.
- Sure seems to be in a hurry.
- Yeah.
- Logan. Logan, don't lose him, all right?
- I'm not gonna lose him. Where did he go?
He's... He's Right up there. See?
See? Just up ahead.
No, no. Not that car.
It's the gray Mercedes.
The idea is not to get too close,
so don't get too close.
- Oh, is that the idea?
- Hurry, but don't get too close.
Just ease back a little bit.
That's it. All right.
Good. You're doing good.
Okay.
Pull over to the right
so we can make a right-hand turn.
Can you do that? Can you do that?
What are you doing? Logan.
Logan, get back in.
- You drive.
- I don't want to drive.
You seem to have a pretty clear idea
about how to do all this.
I thought you were doing great.
Get back in the car.
- It's your turn, really. Drive.
- I can't.
- What?
- I can't drive.
Oh.
The light's changing.
- Let's...
- Don't. Don't even say it. Don't even think it.
Look, I know you've got
a lot of energy and enthusiasm,
and maybe that's not all bad,
but if we go through that door,
it's called breaking and entering.
Oh, it's not breaking, it's just entering.
There's no law against entering.
There are hundreds of laws against entering.
Not for a government official
in pursuit of a felon.
No. Not a felon. He's not a felon.
In pursuit of a probable felon.
- Probable felon.
- Uh-huh.
"Boston vs. Cavalero, 1967.
"If a certified public official
is in pursuit of a probable felon,
"he or she may enter an unlocked business
or storage area without a warrant
"is he has reasonable suspicion that
there are unlawful activities therein."
Boston vs...
Hey. Come here.
Come here.
- Hey!
- I'm just taking a peek.
An open door is practically an invitation.
I actually can cite cases where an implied
invitation is a valid reason to enter.
- In a building with a security...
- Do you hear something?
It's Taft. Coming, Victor.
He invited you, too.
Jesus.
I don't want to blur your concentration
or anything, but we're locked in here.
- What's all this flammable stuff?
- Look at this.
Look at this.
Here's the business records we wanted.
Letters of incorporation dated 1962.
Three-man partnership.
Triad Enterprises.
Victor Taft, counseling.
Victor Taft, Robert Forrester, Joseph Brock.
- Joseph Brock?
- Taft and Forrester were business partners.
No wonder they traded
that painting so quickly.
Look. Deardon's name is everywhere.
Joseph Brock.
What the hell happened to him?
His name disappeared in 1962.
Okay. Here's the insurance payoffs
on the Deardon paintings.
What's that sound, is that your watch?
It's driving me nuts.
No. No.
Robert Forrester. Victor Taft and
Robert Forrester were co-beneficiaries.
- Hey!
- Do something.
Hey. Hold it. Move. Let's go.
Here. Down here!
- Jump!
- Jump?
Are you all right?
- You all right?
- I'm okay.
You all right?
I don't ever want to do this again.
Never again.
Make out a warrant
for the arrest of Victor Taft for arson.
I think you should know
the chief is totally crazed.
He's scarfing down
those little pink pills like they were M&Ms.
He almost let the police charge you
and Kelly with breaking and entering.
He's probably never heard of Boston vs...
- Cavalero.
- Right.
Make sure the detective squad hires
some art experts
to sift through the wreckage
of that warehouse.
- Art experts.
- Yeah.
How'd the trial go? Did you win it?
I don't want to talk about it.
- Hey, Miss Kelly.
- Cavanaugh.
Just coming down to see you.
Are you okay? I heard all about it.
Jesus. Must have been a hell of a bang.
- I'm talking to the lady here.
- I can see that.
I'm listening to you talk to the lady.
- Who is this guy?
C.J. Cavanaugh, detective.
This is Tom Logan,
Assistant District Attorney.
Excuse me.
I said not to tell the DA's office.
- This is supposed to be between you and me.
- No, Cavanaugh. We're doing this together.
- Doing what together?
- It's just an expression.
This is Detective Cavanaugh, and he
investigated the original Deardon fire.
Oh, yeah?
You know something about the case?
Yeah, I know something about this case.
What about this partnership
between Taft and Forrester and...
- Brock.
- Brock, yeah.
Well, there's not much to tell.
The three partners were cooking the books.
Phony tax records.
The IRS starts sniffing around.
Taft and Forrester set up Joe Brock
to take the fall for them.
Brock was sitting in the can at Green Haven
when Deardon was murdered.
- Murdered?
- That's the way I see it, yeah.
What happened to Brock?
Joe Brock was not a lucky man.
He got the big C
the year he was released from prison.
Dead and buried in Kansas City, 1972.
That's it?
Yeah, that's it, for now.
Look, I do something for you,
you do something for me.
That's my home phone number on the bottom.
If you come up with anything, you call me.
Oh.
Snow. That's...
Uh...
Listen, I'm having dinner with my daughter.
Do you want to join us? You hungry?
- I have a date.
- A what?
A date.
You know, where a man invites
a woman out and they have a very nice...
No, I know what... I'm just wondering.
Are you any...
- Are you in any kind of condition to...
- Pardon me?
Well, I mean it's...
You look a little... Forget it.
Logan,
if there's anything at all
about me that you like,
could you tell me what that is right now?
I like your eyes.
Yeah?
They're very warm eyes.
Thank you.
- Cold ears.
- Very cold.
- Can I give you a lift?
- Yes.
May I come in?
Don't ever be a lawyer.
Everybody hates lawyers.
Dad, when you get to be district attorney,
does that mean you have to go into politics?
Oh... I already am in politics.
Princess, politics is
more than just running for elections.
Politics...
Politics should be the wise exercise,
distribution, and maintenance of power.
Then what's sexual politics?
Sexual politics?
Well, that's when you have... Uh...
Sex is...
If two...
Dad.
Is it like when... When you call a boy,
but he won't call you
because he's too cool,
so you call him to tell him he's cool.
So then he can tell everyone you like him,
but he doesn't have to say he likes you.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Right.
Well then, politics is
just getting what you want, right?
Wait a minute. What have we got here?
- I did something really crazy.
- Chelsea, this is not a good time.
- I went to see Victor Taft. I had a gun.
- A gun?
- Yeah.
- Come in.
I was trying to force him to tell me
where my father's paintings were.
With a gun?
He knocked me around. He took the gun away.
I got all panicky. He hit me.
I managed to break free and run out.
- Did you call Kelly?
- I called Kelly. Her machine was on.
Logan, Victor said he was gonna
call the police. I'm really scared.
We've got to get you dry. Uh...
You can use the bathroom.
It's in there. Okay?
- This is my daughter, Jennifer.
- Hi.
It's okay.
She looks guilty to me, Dad.
A juror's not supposed
to make a determination
until they have all the evidence. Okay?
Is this someone I'm gonna
get to know her really well?
No, you're not gonna
get to know her very well,
but that doesn't mean you shouldn't
be on your best behavior.
Yeah.
You, too. Right, Dad?
What in the hell... Hold it.
Hold it. It might be the police.
Police?
Why are you protecting her?
She's your girlfriend, isn't she?
No, she's not my girlfriend.
She's just someone... Oh!
Well, look who's here. What a surprise.
- Hi, Mom. We thought you were the cops.
- What?
Uh, well, there we are.
- She's ready. She's ready. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
What's the matter with you guys?
You're acting...
There you go.
- Oh. Uh...
- In front of the kid?
Nothing happened in front of the child.
Mom, Dad didn't hit her in the face.
It was just some guy
she was trying to rob with a gun.
- Thanks.
- Oh.
Congratulations. This seems like a perfect
environment for my daughter to be raised in.
- She's our daughter. You seem to forget that.
- Right now, I'm trying real hard to forget that.
Dad. Dad, I'll make sure she knows
you didn't do anything. Okay?
Yeah.
- 'Bye.
- Be good.
What do you want, Ed?
It's none of your business.
- I guess I screwed things up for you, didn't I?
- Oh, forget it.
- I'm always doing that.
- Forget it.
- Mind if I make myself some tea?
- No, I'll make... I'll call Kelly.
Hi. This is Laura Kelly.
I can't come to the phone right now,
but if you leave your message...
First thing you're gonna do
in the morning is to call Kelly.
Then you're gonna go down
to the police station and file a report.
Why can't you come with me?
Why? Why? Because...
Because she's your attorney. I'm not.
- Personal question?
- Huh?
What do you think of me?
Interesting.
The other night when I kissed you,
what did you think of that?
Dangerous.
That's a carefully chosen word.
Well, carefully chosen words are the tools
of my profession.
I think you've got everything here.
This has been such a complicated day. I'm...
Let's hope everything's fine. Here, I'm...
See you in the morning.
Freeze! Hold it right there! Don't move!
- You have the right to remain silent...
- I know what my rights are.
- Who the hell are you?
- Freeze! Don't move again.
Hey, wise guys! What the hell's happening?
Chelsea Deardon, you're under arrest
for the murder of Victor Taft.
Murder! It's not true!
Anything you say can be held against you.
- You have the right to an attorney.
- Looks like she's already had her attorney.
- Hey!
- Get your clothes on, pal.
Is it true you were found
in bed with the suspect?
They're calling you the darling DA.
What do you think of the name?
Our clairvoyant at World's People says
Chelsea Deardon's carrying your child.
Police report says you were both naked.
Do you usually examine suspects this way?
Whoa!
One year!
I had one more year. Now what do you
think they're gonna remember?
The 67,000 convictions I got?
No, they're going to remember
one horny bastard
who made my office the laughingstock
of the city.
Damn it, Logan, when we service
this community,
we do it with our pants on!
Who sent the cops to my place?
Who knew Chelsea was there?
An anonymous caller.
Most anonymous calls end up
in the wastebasket.
Most anonymous calls don't involve
an assistant district attorney.
I get shot at, my suspect blows up
a building and then gets killed.
Somebody's setting me up.
Well, I got no alternative
but to suspend you
for 90 days pending investigation.
What?
Suspend me?
You... What kind of a cheap
political dodge is that?
When I need your help and support
the most, suspend me?
No.
You're right. I'm not going to suspend you.
- No. Don't say it. Don't say it.
- You're fired.
No. What, fired? No.
You can't do that. I won't accept it.
- You're fired!
- I quit!
- You what? You what?
- 'Bye.
You what?
You're Logan.
I saw your picture in the paper.
Yeah? What about it?
Nothing. I just think
you got a raw deal from the press.
This is a subpoena for you
to appear in court to show cause
why you're inhibiting the proper
education of your daughter.
Your former wife has brought charges before
Judge Lloyd Solomon of district court.
You may bring legal counsel to this hearing
if you so desire. Give 'em hell.
You want to play rough?
Want to find out how good a goddamn
lawyer I am? Well, you got it, sweetheart.
By the time I finish with you,
I'll cut you into so many legal pieces,
they'll have to put you in a bag.
Huh? Oh!
Jennifer. Hi, sweetie.
Uh... Oh, no. No, I'm fine. I'm good.
I'm angry, that's all. Is Mom there?
Ah-ha.
Well, when she gets out of the tub,
would you just tell her I called?
Great. Okay. Fine.
I love you, too. 'Bye.
- Sorry, boss. Elliott Blanchard...
- Oh, not you.
Not now.
I was just checking out the office.
This is my damned office until I clean out
my damned desk.
Wouldn't listen, would you?
Everything had to be done your way.
Well, you're history.
I'll talk to you later, Doreen.
What?
What happened?
I really can't discuss it right now.
There's an excellent account
available in the Post.
Bit lurid, but highly provocative reading.
I read the Post.
So you know, or think you know.
You tell me otherwise, Logan.
Tell me you didn't sleep with my client.
- Damn it.
- Damn it? Damn it?
Is that what you said? Damn it?
Yes, damn it, Logan.
Why did you have to sleep with her?
She didn't have enough trouble as it was?
You had to make your conquest public?
Absolutely right. It is my mistake.
I should have kicked her out
the door and right out onto the street.
But I made the mistake and I'm the one
who's gonna pay for it.
Me, no one else, Tom Logan.
Ex-Assistant District Attorney.
- What are you doing?
- I'm helping you.
Well, don't.
Don't ever help me again. Please.
I think it's obvious
that you're being set up.
We both know that Chelsea was framed.
I think this trumped up murder charge
is just more of the same.
Well, a person is entitled
to his or her own opinion.
Lawyers have to prove theirs in court.
- I can prove it.
- Oh, yeah?
I could prove it.
Especially if I had someone working
on the case with me
that knew as much about it as I did.
- What are you... What are you saying?
- Someone...
Someone that would benefit a great deal
by Chelsea's acquittal.
No.
- No.
- Just for this one case, Logan.
You'd get your job back,
and I'd be on my way.
You get one side of the desk.
I get the other.
You have three drawers on your side.
I have three drawers on my side.
We can share the drawer in the center.
I'll just put the phone right in the middle.
My side of the desk will tend
to be very messy.
And I like it like that way,
so don't try to straighten anything up.
All right.
Can we discuss Chelsea's defense?
Well, in my opinion we have
to cloud the issues in this trial.
We have to get the focus off Chelsea.
We've got two witnesses.
How can we discredit them?
Do they have criminal records?
Do they pay their bills,
what do their neighbors think of them,
do they have parking tickets,
they have bounced checks?
You know, what kind of people are they?
Any old trick, huh,
to get the client off?
You're a defense attorney now, Logan.
You're supposed to get the client off.
I'm gonna need more room here.
I've got to have room to pace.
I'm a pacer.
All right. Can we get down to basics now
in the case?
Is she guilty? Do we think she killed Taft?
- I think she's capable of killing someone.
- I don't think she killed Taft.
The whole case is based
on circumstantial evidence.
Absolutely. That's why
we don't have to disprove anything.
- We just have to cast some doubt on it.
- Right.
Right.
There's one more important issue here.
What?
Are you going to sleep
with our client again?
What has that got to do with the trial?
It has everything to do
with our working relationship.
- She's a very attractive young girl.
- Extremely attractive.
I didn't say extremely,
I said just attractive.
Extremely.
- She has a nice body.
- A sensational body.
I'll pick the adjectives. A good body.
Big eyes.
- Hypnotic.
- Big eyes.
Unforgettable.
Logan, are you going to
sleep with her again or not?
No.
Good.
That's all I wanted to know.
All rise.
The Supreme Court
for the County and State of New York
is now in session. Draw near
and ye shall be heard.
The honorable judge John Dawkins presiding.
Please be seated.
Your Honor, the case for
The People of New York
vs. Chelsea Elizabeth Deardon
is ready to proceed for arraignment.
Counsel is present.
The defendant is present.
With respect to this matter
of change of venue,
does defense wish
to engage in oral argument?
- We don't, Your Honor.
- Yes, we do.
- We don't.
Which is it?
- No, we don't. No, we don't.
- Of course.
We move for a change of venue
due to unreasonable and misleading
exposure in the press, Your Honor.
- I object.
- You object to your own co-counsel?
I do, yes.
I see.
Would counsel approach the bench
for a moment, please?
Well, boys and girls,
is this the way things are going to be?
Your Honor, everyone in New York
has read about this case.
You think you can find a place
looser morally than New York?
I happen to be talking to His Honor,
Mr. Logan.
Maybe you guys should flip a coin to decide
who's going to be your spokesperson.
Enough already. Motion is denied.
Does defense wish to enter a plea
at this time?
Yes, Chelsea Deardon pleads "not guilty."
The court will note for the record
your plea of not guilty. Call the next case.
The State of New York
vs. Christian Clemenson...
You're a good typist.
Thanks. I thought I'd need something
to fall back on
in case I didn't make it through law school.
- My dad's a terrible typist.
- I've noticed.
- But he has his good points.
- Yeah.
You guys like each other, don't you?
Yeah.
I see the way you look at each other.
I like the way he moves.
Yeah, until he trips over something, right?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Are there any calls?
- Just Mom. She's on her way over.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
I, uh... I had a long talk with Mom
and I got her to cancel the subpoena.
How did you get her to do that?
Well, I told her it would be all right
with you if I went to California.
What?
But... But you get to pick me up on June 1,
in LA and keep me for 60 consecutive...
Ninety consecutive days.
What do you know about this?
Uh...
Did you do this?
You did this.
And you thought I'd buy a deal like that?
Right now, you have her four days a month,
that's 48 days a year.
- I got you 42 more days.
- Yeah. That's... That's almost double, Dad.
I can add.
That's Mom.
- You got everything?
- Yeah. I think so.
- Here, take this, this time.
- Yeah.
Dad?
So what do I tell her?
Tell her she's got a deal.
- Okay. 'Bye.
- 'Bye.
You guys are really a great team.
You have a lot in common.
What's she mean we have "a lot in common"?
I don't know.
Earlier, she said you liked me.
What does she know? She's just a kid.
She's a pretty bright kid.
Okay, so you have the case load.
- You're going to bring that. Yeah, trial notes.
- You have the trial notes?
Bring them over tomorrow.
- All right.
- Good night.
All right.
- That was nice.
- Yes, it was.
- See you tomorrow, okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we, the people, are prepared
to prove beyond a reasonable doubt
that on the night of October 7,
Chelsea Elizabeth Deardon
did commit the crime of murder
against the person of one Victor Taft.
That, with intent to cause
the death of Victor Taft,
she shot him in the chest three times.
We'll call witnesses
who'll testify under oath that they saw
Chelsea Deardon flee the scene of the crime.
Ballistics will prove
that the gun used to kill Victor Taft was
registered in the name of Chelsea Deardon.
And most important,
her fingerprints were all over that gun.
So, we'll prove Chelsea Deardon
was at the scene of the crime,
possessed the means to commit that crime,
and had every opportunity to do so.
Opportunity and means.
Crucial evidence which, by themselves,
would be enough to establish guilt
beyond a reasonable doubt in a murder case.
But we will also provide
a compelling motive as well.
This was a crime committed by a woman
who was secretly Victor Taft's
lover for two years,
during which time he was
her only means of financial support.
It's been one lie after another.
We looked like incompetent idiots out there.
Why didn't you tell us
about your relationship?
Did you really think you could
keep a lid on that?
It wasn't common knowledge.
Victor ad I never went out
in public together.
I thought if you knew,
it would only make me look more guilty.
You went to his apartment,
you had a fight with him and you killed him!
No! No! I didn't!
We had a fight, but I didn't kill him.
You shot Taft,
then you went to Logan's apartment
and got him emotionally involved
so he could clear everything.
I went to Logan's apartment
because I was scared.
Why don't you believe me?
I didn't kill anyone.
That's the most preposterous explanation
I've ever heard.
Yeah, it is.
- I believe her.
- What?
What, based on her track record so far?
No, hunch. Instinct.
Let's hope it's coming from above the waist.
I believe her, too.
Okay, she's telling the truth.
You ready to do some tap dancing?
Oh, hey.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Chelsea Deardon did not kill Victor Taft.
The prosecution has suggested
a possible motive,
but one based entirely on hearsay,
conjecture and circumstantial evidence.
Evidence that on the surface would appear
to have some substance,
but upon closer examination
will prove to have no relevance
whatsoever to this case.
You're not buying this, are you?
You're not listening to a word I'm saying.
Really, are you?
Guess what? I don't blame you.
After listening to Mr. Blanchard lay out
the prosecution's evidence,
even I'm convinced
my client murdered Victor Taft.
After all, if I had walked in the room
and found Victor Taft dead on the floor
and Chelsea Deardon's fingerprints
all over the weapon that killed him,
there isn't much in the world that would
convince me that she wasn't guilty.
Look. Let's just save ourselves
a lot of time here.
Let's be honest. I'm sure there are a lot
better things for us to be doing.
Who thinks Chelsea Deardon is guilty?
Objection, Your Honor.
Mr. Logan.
Come on. Here, don't hold back.
I got my hand raised. Look here.
I believe that my client murdered
Victor Taft in cold blood.
Isn't everybody convinced?
- Mr. Logan.
- Who agrees with me? Come on.
- I object!
- Mr. Logan.
- You're convinced, aren't you?
- Your Honor.
- Your Honor!
- Look! Prosecution says she's guilty.
Everybody in the jury says she's guilty.
Let's save the State of New York
a lot of time and money
and move directly to sentencing.
- What?
- Isn't she entitled to a fair trial?
Oh. Let's give her
a fair trial and then convict her.
Mr. Logan!
You are totally out of order
and you know it!
This jury is disqualified.
Court will stand in recess
while I consider holding you in contempt.
Your Honor, I recognize that my opening
remarks are highly irregular,
but, please, let me continue
even though the jury
may consider my client guilty
at this time,
I'd like to state for the record that
I still believe in this jury,
and I'm willing to accept their final verdict,
whatever it might be.
I concur, Your Honor.
Prosecution has... Has equal faith
in this jury, Your Honor.
May I proceed?
Very well. You may proceed, Mr. Logan.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Okay.
So we all think she's guilty.
Now what do we do?
That's a dilemma, isn't it?
It's an especially difficult problem
because we've developed
a legal concept in this country
to protect ourselves,
to protect our rights,
and it's called "presumption of innocence."
In simpler words that means
that one is presumed innocent
until proven guilty.
That means that whatever assumptions you
might have already made in this case,
Chelsea Deardon must be seen in your eyes,
must be believed in your minds,
must be understood in your hearts
to be innocent.
So what is the truth?
Maybe the truth begins 18 years ago
when dozens of paintings,
works of art by the defendant's father,
Sebastian Deardon,
supposedly perished in a fire,
which also tragically took his life.
Now, the insurance paid on those paintings
totaled $2.5 million.
Now, that's a staggering sum
but only a fraction
of what they'd be worth today.
We believe
that those paintings still exist,
and are today worth more than $20 million.
Victor Taft was not murdered
as an act of revenge by the defendant.
Victor Taft was murdered to protect someone.
Someone who himself, 18 years ago
was a co-conspirator
to arson, fraud, and murder.
Someone who took advantage
of Chelsea Deardon
and who tried to frame her for a crime
for which he himself was responsible.
Listen, ladies and gentlemen,
this is a complex case,
but I'm confident that
once you've heard all the evidence,
that you will come to a decision
that is the truth.
And the truth is,
Chelsea Deardon is innocent.
Thank you.
Without objection, this court is adjourned
until 9:00 Monday morning.
Eloquent, Tom.
Better have the goods by Monday.
- Yeah, just show up, Blanchard.
- Great opening.
Congratulations, counselor.
If you meant to baffle them with bullshit,
my hat's off to you.
Would you excuse us?
If that's an indication
of where you're heading with this case...
Count on it, Forrester.
Daddy!
- Murderer.
- What?
- How dare you?
- I was there.
A small child was there, hardly qualified
to come to a rational conclusion.
You're a liar.
I won't be made the scapegoat
for the desperate act
of an emotionally disturbed young woman.
Is that clear?
Yes, could you get Mr. Crane
in records, please?
Mr. Crane,
I have Mr. Morrison from claims.
One moment, please.
Crane?
Crane. Crane, where are they?
I'm talking about the shipping files,
the Taft Gallery warehouse shipping files.
Where are they?
I've got customers all over me.
Claim they never arrived.
Huh?
Immediately!
No, not tomorrow, now.
Taft! Do I have to spell it for you, too?
Listen, Crane, get those files
up to me right away.
Morrison. Claims. Now!
Otherwise you can talk
to the legal department.
May I help you?
Is this claims?
- No. That's on 26.
- Oh!
Well?
How do I look?
Joe Morrison. It's my first day on the job.
Trying to make a good impression.
- Where's my office?
- Morrison.
Nobody told me. Are you sure?
- Laura, do you have that...
- Yes, of course, Mr. Morrison.
It's right here.
"Effective immediately,
Joseph J. Morrison." That's me.
"Position of claims adjuster."
Blah, blah, blah.
It's all here.
This is the claims department, isn't it?
Yeah. Was somebody let go?
What a jungle.
They fire someone and don't even tell them?
- Welcome to corporate America.
- This memo isn't signed. I'll have...
- Mr. Morrison's office?
- That's me, son.
- Mr. Morrison?
- Yeah.
I need to do this work from an office.
Could you tell me which one it is?
I'll have to speak to Mr. Phillips
about this. Please, just wait right here.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Hong Kong. Two crates.
Please excuse me. What?
- You put the London form in the Asian pile.
- No, that's not...
- That's not the Asian pile.
- What's that, South America?
No. Medium-sized crate pile. Medium-size.
We're doing it geographically.
We're trying to find out what the pattern is,
then what breaks the pattern.
No, I know that, Logan,
but I'm doing it by size. See?
"Taft Gallery to Victor Taft,
40 x 80 x 15."
- I see, but...
- Very large crate, very large crate.
Guess where it goes? Large crate pile.
Here's another one. "Taft Gallery to
Victor Taft." Very large crate. So big.
- Goes right there.
- Where did they ship to?
Manhattan. Sutton Place.
Sutton Place?
Victor Taft at a Sutton Place address?
I thought he lived on Central Park West.
What are the dates?
Mid-September, all of them.
- About the time we were at the gallery.
- Yes.
So Taft sends himself a large shipment
to a strange address?
About the same time
that we went to see him at the gallery.
The Deardons!
It's me.
I think they found
what you're looking for.
You'll get there first.
I'll take care of it.
Want to drive?
You all right?
- You all right?
- I'm all right.
Logan, what are you doing?
Logan!
- Logan!
- Hey!
What's your rush, man?
What are you...
What's the matter with you?
Oh!
I can do this. I can do this!
Holy shit!
God! Are you okay?
- Oh, my God.
- He ran right in front of me!
- You see it?
- No, but I heard a crash.
Okay. Okay.
Logan!
What are you doing?
- He took his wallet!
- Hey! Hey!
- Logan!
- Hey!
- Get in!
- Kelly! Brake! Brake!
Help! Police!
Are you okay?
- Good driving.
- Thanks.
Credit cards.
$45 cash. Cleaners.
Look at this.
Robert Forrester's business card.
- Forrester?
- Forrester.
What we got here is Fort Knox.
Here's Taft. 2-B.
Okay, you can come up,
but none of that funny stuff.
Yeah? Then what's the point of coming up?
What's this? It's open.
Be careful.
Chuck Close.
The Transcontinental Express.
That's the same size as the shipment.
Somebody's already
been through this stuff. Look.
Campbell's soup.
Look at this Lichtenstein!
God, it must be worth $200,000.
Why would somebody leave paintings
worth $200,000 lying around?
Mondrian...
Steinberg...
There's millions of dollars' worth
of paintings here,
but there's no Deardons.
Look at this.
A wall-to-wall bed.
You could have a tag-team match
on that thing.
Tom.
If Taft has. Jeez!
Oh!
Forrester.
I'm going to call the police.
No, on... On second thought,
maybe we shouldn't call the police.
Maybe we should.
What?
- What?
- God.
- You scared me to death.
- Oh!
What are you doing here?
There was a message on my machine
to meet you here.
- There was no message.
- You left a message.
How did you get in here?
This was Victor's and my place.
I have a key.
Oh no, not again.
Okay, let's hear it.
That famous Logan instinct.
You first.
All right.
I don't see how she could've lifted
a 200-pound man on the bed.
Therefore, she's innocent.
What in the hell is that?
Where have I seen that before?
That's the Bertolini.
Remember we saw the model
for it in Taft's office?
The one he couldn't sell
for sentimental reasons.
Victor hated that sculpture.
He thought Bertolini was a joke.
We got to get to the Taft Gallery.
I'll find Cavanaugh,
get a search warrant and meet you
at the gallery in a few minutes.
The private Victor Taft was also
an incredibly warm human being...
A leader,
a benefactor.
Victor Taft championed my work
at a time when no one else was interested.
But Victor had vision.
...the contribution that Victor made
to young artists,
and through them...
What do you think?
- It sounds hollow.
- Yeah.
Uh...
Cavanaugh, Detective Cavanaugh,
you guys. Where...
Uh... Detective Cavanaugh?
Yo.
- I'm looking for Detective Cavanaugh.
- That's me. What can I do for you?
- You're Cavanaugh?
- Yeah.
You're...
You're the only Detective Cavanaugh
in Manhattan South?
There must be a way into this.
Cavanaugh.
The name's Joe Brock.
And whatever's inside
that piece of crap belongs to me.
Oh, God!
Shit!
Hey! What the hell are you doing over there?
Breaking into my car.
Oh.
Is that the gun you used
to kill Taft and Forrester?
It just might be the gun I use to kill you.
Take that.
All right, Kelly, go on, take a whack at it.
Pretend it's my head.
Who was the guy that shot at us?
The one that followed Chelsea?
Nobody. A hired hand, paid to do a job.
It's in there!
Come on, hit it again!
When did you decide to kill Taft, Cavanaugh?
After Taft and Forrester set me up
for that prison stretch.
Just waited for my chance. Come on.
Come on!
Come on.
It's mine!
Fire! Fire!
Logan!
Laura!
Oh, God.
Please hurry.
Ah!
Whoa!
Kelly!
Come on, Chelsea!
Go on!
Kelly!
Logan!
- Can we go down the stairs?
- No, you can't get out there.
- Over here!
- Chelsea, come on!
Down here.
Let's go!
What about me?
Over here.
Oh, my God!
Oh, God.
And so in conclusion,
Your Honor, in light of the new
and seemingly incontrovertible
evidence presented before this court
on the admirable initiative
of the estimable co-counsels for defense,
we, the people, now recommend
that all charges against
Chelsea Elizabeth Deardon
be dismissed.
So be it.
This case is dismissed.
The court is adjourned.
Ha-ha!
Congratulations, Tom.
Wonderful job.
Comeback of the year!
Oh, I had a little help.
Yeah, sure. Good work, Miss...
- Kelly.
- Kelly. Right.
- Tom, you got a great opportunity here.
- What?
All these reporters. It's the perfect time
to launch your campaign.
- Campaign!
- For district attorney, remember?
I remember being fired
as an assistant district attorney.
You were fired, not officially.
- I Never put the paperwork through.
- This is amazing.
In his own way,
he was backing you 100 percent.
You got to start thinking like a politician.
Tom, you're the hottest legal property
in the city.
We could win this election
by just announcing your candidacy.
What do you say?
Forget it.
- Forget it?
- Forget it.
Too proud to come back?
Too happy where I am.
Should have put the paperwork through.
Ms. Deardon, what will happen
to your father's paintings?
I'm not sure.
I'm just happy they still exist.
Were you ever
actually in love with Taft?
Once.
Maybe.
I can't remember.
Yet you lived with him
for some time.
For some time for one purpose.
How do you feel now that you've...
Vintage Chelsea.
First she seduces Taft
because she needed information.
Then she seduces you
because she needed help.
With the risk of seeming immodest,
I'd like to think she did with me
what she did with me
because she found me simply attractive.
Oh, it's...
It's perfectly understandable.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Because Chelsea's very good
at luring men onto her bed.
Extremely good.
No, no. I pick the adjectives.
"Big eyes."
"Hypnotic eyes."
"Unforgettable eyes." She has great eyes!
Yes, she does,
but they're not as great as yours.