That exhilarating morning,
I could hear the birds in the city...
...from my privileged,
impregnable position.
I thought of the luck, the courage and...
...the stroke of genius
that had brought me here...
...where my active imagination alone
could never have brought me.
Six weeks earlier, I was an ordinary man
only focused on my family...
...with no interest in other women.
- Sixth floor.
- Me too.
- Well... it's that way.
- Do you think?
Excuse me.
Come pick me up.
I'll leave the car here.
Yes... me too.
You love me, right?
Undeniably... yes.
I really don't have time, Marthe.
Are you going to give that to
the minister every morning?
Is something wrong with you?
The minister asked for it again.
He lost it.
Excuse me.
It's alright, dear.
- Are you afraid of me?
- No.
Shit.
Hello.
Let's have dinner.
What?
Tonight at the Récamier.
I recognize your voice.
Nine o'clock?
Why?
Just because.
I can't at nine.
Ten past nine?
Why do you speak English?
I was told you... were
a British citizen.
No.
Let me check.
I'd be surprised, because...
Wait... what time is it?
Where am I going?
Why do you look at other cars
like this?
To see them.
I see.
Why are you looking at me?
How do I look?
Seductive.
No, I'll just be working hard.
These hurt.
Here, I don't have a handbag.
At 41 years old, she'll be working hard
at uni. When are your exams?
You're terrible... in 23 days.
- Is it all under control?
- Yes.
Do you have a newspaper here?
I wouldn't mind seeing a movie.
- It's all been arranged.
- What?
You'll be going at 8 o'clock,
with the girls. I promised them.
- That's alright, isn't it?
- Great.
Don't lose my earrings!
Good service. 30 - 30.
Out.
- Yes, just.
Shut up,
you're distracting me.
- Ready?
- Ready!
An Elephant Can Be Extremely
Deceptive
I was wrong - footed. He doesn't
shut up. It's getting on my...
What, I'm not saying anything.
- How are you?
- And you?
I'll tell you later.
Guys.
My ball, please, madam.
She missed.
Damn!
Did you see those legs?
Do you like buns, guys?
Stop it. It's embarrassing
when you act like that.
Do you live in the area?
I think I've seen you both before.
If he comes to the net, play in his
feet. Don't try a lob.
Why?
Not today.
Your lobs are too short.
- Are those Peugeot rackets?
- No, Montanas.
They're terrible.
I think I pulled a muscle.
Go, Simon!
And no foot fault!
Are you messing with me?
Yes, an ace!
15-0. Bravo, Mr Bouly.
Great passing!
Well done, Mr Bouly.
I don't need to do anything.
Do you have a smoke, Simon?
Ok, 30-30.
Here we go.
Hurry, hurry!
Don't mind him, Miss.
They have no manners.
You play very well.
Are you ranked?
- What were you trying to do?
- A lob with topspin.
Funny, you can't do topspin.
I asked you not to play any lobs.
What do you want from me?
And my shoulder hurts.
Let's play mixed doubles.
We're losing.
- What's the score?
- 40-0 and match point.
Yes!
- Sorry, guys.
- You're just not in good shape.
We'll see on Sunday.
I didn't know she had a sister,
but yesterday she introduced Carmen.
Are they Spanish?
I don't know.
I didn't ask for her papers.
No, because the tall one's called
Esther.
Well then... Esther's not...
It's not really Iberian.
Hey... pretty?
I'd give the tall one 12. I'll tell you
tomorrow about the other one.
I'm going out with her tonight.
Simon!
I bet he forgot his towel.
Your turn.
You can have my shower!
Simon!
I can't.
I don't have a towel.
Phone call for Boulifet!
Bouly!
A phone call for you.
Can't you go for me.
Because I... you know.
If it's the Seita, I'll call them back.
We have problems with maize paper.
- Bad?
- A director died.
- Did he smoke maize cigarettes?
- No, but the family's suing us.
- And Marie-Ange?
- What about Marie- Ange?
Does she never notice...
all that stuff... Carmen for instance?
- Or that pharmacist...
- Snow- white!
- No!
- Jocelyne!
Marie- Ange has the kids,
the TV, the house. She's 38...
I don't like clichés, but she's
a happy woman.
- And how about her?
- What?
Is she perfect?
Wait a moment...
He's stupid!
Marie- Ange...
- Are you having lunch here, doctor?
- No!
Bouly...
It can't be.
This can't be.
Didn't she say anything on
the phone?
Mrs Philippot? She came to do
the ironing.
She saw them all on the staircase,
Marie- Ange, the children and...
...the furniture.
- Why did you carry your bag upstairs?
- So they won't steal it.
I don't believe it.
This is crazy, guys.
She took everything.
Yes, even the wallpaper.
The two shepherdesses with
the flutes.
Did you have a prenuptial
agreement?
That determines if she has the right
to take everything.
Can I make a phone call?
There's a letter there.
What... where?
- Isn't that a letter?
- It's a letter.
Mouchy, I wanted to call you from
the tennis club, but I couldn't.
No, no.
How did he say that?
That's quite something.
I wouldn't have expected that
from Charles.
No, I can't talk to him now.
Why do you say I'll be rid of you
when you're in hospital?
Doesn't she say where they've gone?
No, you're fine.
It's psychosomatic.
Doesn't she say why?
Yes... she...
...she found a photo.
Of me and a woman.
Naked?
No, in a booth.
My kids.
What did he say?
My kids...
But you said you hated them.
He was tired.
He loves his children.
This can't be happening, guys.
This isn't happening! Shit!
And I also cut myself,
like an idiot.
The kids might be at school.
No, it's Whitsun holiday.
- Marie- Ange...
- She'll come back.
No, I don't think so.
They never come back.
They leave in the morning and by noon
they don't recognize you anymore.
You have to admit Bouly has been
going too far for years.
If a guy has a very nice dinner
with another woman...
Does anything happen afterwards?
I don't know.
But his wife won't leave the next day
with the kids and the furniture.
Yes, she will. They're capable
of anything!
- What about Mrs Lubéron...
- Same thing.
Who's Mrs Lubéron?
You were in Iran.
The professor's wife.
Your boss, right?
I can only go there at night.
And only during emergencies.
It depends on the severity.
I won't go for an appendicitis.
But she will call me for a peritonitis.
Because to drive there and back
is 25 minutes by car.
The time it takes him to wash his
hands and put on his gloves...
"Darling, he's taking off two legs."
"I'm on my way!"
Tell me...
Are you home this afternoon?
- Yes, I'm seeing patients until 6.
- Can I drop by?
- What's wrong?
- Nothing, I need a favour.
But it's personal.
Hurry. I have to return the car
by 3 o'clock.
- Is the owner of the Rolls here?
- No, not yet.
I'll wait here and...
That afternoon I submerged myself
in my work like a man taken...
by surprise by a twist of fate.
For the first time ever, I was prepared
to cheat on Marthe.
And I hated that thought.
The looks of my colleagues, unaware of
the drama that was about to unfold...
hurt me as if they were already
blaming me for what was about to happen.
I respected the morals of our
society...
but I have to admit that the young
woman in red occupied my thoughts.
Hello... hello?
That's enough, Lucien.
I'm fed up, do you understand?
- Why don't you reply to my letters?
- Which letters? I didn't get any.
I've sent 14 letters and they all
didn't arrive, unheard- of.
I love your breasts.
I can't live without them.
My breasts?
When I came to see Delphine,
I saw them through the open door.
- Which door?
- Of your room.
I love your breasts.
Especially the left one.
I'm going to talk to your parents.
I told them.
That I'm going to marry a married woman.
Totally sick!
What did they say?
The old fools won't face reality.
We can do without their permission,
my love.
Listen, Simon, you're the only one
I can ask this of.
Yes, but what will you reply?
I'll reply: "Can't you cope, Deschanels?
Should I come over?"
"You're really a pain, Deschanels."
- Who is Deschanels?
- Someone from work.
Ok, goodbye, doctor, thank you.
At 9 o'clock.
Don't get it wrong.
- Are you going home?
- No, we're going out with Bouly.
Mr Daoud!
Come in Mr Jouglen.
I'll see you in a moment.
Is this about a woman?
Are you crazy?
Politics?
Bye, buddy.
Did you receive your results,
Mr Jouglen?
Didn't the lab call you about
the results?
No.
That's strange.
No, it's not.
Well?
The last time, you got me all
worried, doctor.
- What is it?
- No, no... nothing.
Then why did you go...
Call Lavallée and ask if they've made a
mistake with the results of Mr Jouglen.
I don't know what I have,
but it hurts.
Must be a pulled muscle.
Barney Bigard on clarinet.
Cozy Cole on drums.
Not Cozy Cole, Gene Krupa!
Want to bet?
Typically Cozy Cole.
Recorded on April 20, 1950.
He left Benny Goodman in '39...
I'm fed up with your clarinets.
Get off my bed, I'm studying.
Do you study in your bed?
That explains a lot.
- Get out.
- Ladies.
Do you have a cigarette?
Stop smoking.
You don't even know how.
I don't smoke anymore.
Makes it harder to get a tan.
Why do you care about that?
I've decided to look after my body.
- Don't you have your keys?
- Yes, but...
Didn't they come for the elevator?
I don't know.
I always take the stairs.
- Did it break down?
- It doesn't stop at our floor anymore.
Lucien! Delphine told me you passed.
How old are you?
17, but this year, I'm motivated.
What time are we leaving?
Where?
To the cinema.
We're not going.
They gave me this at the last moment.
Of course!
Don't act like that.
I have enough on my plate.
Today I'd like to talk about...
- Hello.
I'd like to talk about a case...
Hi, can you get us a beer?
Mind if I put down my things?
Are you going through my pockets?
No, I need 1000 francs.
I have to repay Catulle.
- Is he the one with the hair?
- Yes, that's him.
He wants to have their glasses
filled up.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing.
I was leaving after talking to
Deschanels, when I walked into Hawkeye.
"Hello, Minister."
"Hello, Dorsay."
You're going home. Good, have a look
at this before tomorrow.
So now I've got my work cut out
for me.
The one time you were doing something
with the girls.
That hurts me the most.
Is it that much work?
It's 600 pages, but I gave half
to Deschanels.
But will Deschanels be able
to cope?
- Do you want a drink?
- Yes, I do.
Oh, I'm so...
...tired.
Why are you shaving?
Yes, why am I shaving?
What's that?
What that is? Bouly's kid.
I know, but what is he doing here?
You... don't know?
Yes I am but is Marie- Ange here?
Just for one night.
Where is Marie- Ange?
- I asked where she is.
- I understood, but I don't know.
- Come on.
- I swear.
- What do you want, André?
- A pastis.
Two pastis.
- René!
- Yes.
I feel good!
I'll be back.
Do you want one?
What's that?
Nothing, I gave you your pastis.
- René!
- He said he'll be back.
René!
- You find that funny?
- Yes.
Not this way.
Follow me, please.
- What an idiot.
- Yes, he's an idiot, but it's funny.
Hey, André.
Why did you leave me?
Never leave me again.
Sorry, he can't...
You're sick.
That time in the Coupole
was better.
No, no.
I like telephone pranks because they
can't see you.
I called her family.
They don't know where she is.
Don't think about it.
Stop thinking about it.
You made me laugh.
Want me to do the cop?
Give me the kepi.
Thanks, you're great.
If you want, we'll go to a brothel.
Let's not go anywhere.
Go to sleep. When you wake up,
your mother will come.
Goodnight, little fellow.
I heard you're really bad
at tennis!
What did he say?
Now you have to go to sleep.
It's late.
You always want to play a smash,
but you're no good at it.
- Who says that?
- My father.
He always beats you.
That's crazy.
Give him a kiss.
Asshole.
She takes off with the other 2 and
we get the ugliest one.
She said it was only for one night.
And what do we say to Bouly?
Nothing!
She doesn't want it and neither do I.
Does she need your opinion now?
She doesn't need anyone and
especially not him.
What an asshole!
Really, if it had been me...
What if it had been you?
I'm warning you, Etienne. If it happened
to us, I'd show no class at all.
Anyway, let's not...
We can talk about it calmly.
Protect me, Etienne.
I may seem strong, but in reality...
not with everything...
Why do you say that?
Because you asked.
But Marthe...
Where did I put it?
But you're completely insane!
Who gave you this?
- Mummy... back when...
- Back when?
When they moved, they gave
everything away to their children.
You could have shot me.
I wouldn't shoot you,
because you haven't hurt me.
You're not Bouly.
Do you know what he did to Marie- Ange?
Last Thursday, I was there.
He called her at 10pm to say he had
to stay and work.
Did he do that?
Does that trick still work?
No, it doesn't work anymore.
- What was that noise
- Nothing.
- You could have knocked.
- The door was open.
I'll go back to work.
Go to sleep!
Walking around at this hour...
Hello? Yes.
Deschanels!
Hello... yes... what?
What?
Why on earth do you call me
at home?
I told you to?
I didn't tell you anything!
No, I'm not coming over.
No, Deschanels, I'm not coming over!
No, Deschanels, goodbye!
What's wrong with him?
Oh no!
What's wrong?
This is crazy. Shake hands.
Hello?
A haemorrhage, are you sure?
Ok, I'm coming, sweetheart.
- Where are you going?
- Don't worry, I'll be back.
It's 1:20am.
- Who was that on the phone, Marie- Ange?
- No.
Esperanza!
- Hello, Mrs Esperanza.
- Hello, Mr Deschanels.
- Hello, Dorsay.
Wasn't I supposed to get the list for
Mauretania last night?
The copier was broken, but I've
got it here.
No, I don't have time.
Thank you, Mr Deschanels.
Tell me, Esperanza, what did
the doctor say last time you saw him?
Hurry,
it's starting 15 minutes earlier.
Why is that?
Nobody ever tells me anything.
What's this?
The test prints for the advertising
campaign.
Who is she?
Who?
Her.
You should ask the minister.
He found her.
Where?
On a horse in Saint- Germain.
He goes every Thursday.
And what does Hawkeye see galloping
through the fog?
She's not...
No...
The next day it was Thursday.
I ignored Marthe's questions...
...and pulled out my riding boots, from
the bag they had been in since 1958.
The year when General De Gaulle
came back to power.
Not that those events had anything
to do with each other.
That summer I had practiced a bit
of horse riding.
A sad event that led to a rift between
this kind of animal and me.
Marthe didn't fail to comment on
that fact.
I replied that she had picked up her
studies after 20 years.
Then I kissed her and regretted
my behaviour.
I left the house, all dressed up,
accompanied by my godmother.
I always had lunch with her
on Thursdays.
I didn't look back, but knew
that Marthe was watching me leave.
She kept wondering...
...just like the first horse that had
to deal with me.
I took it easy on the horse.
But soon its lively character took over.
I realised that women are beautiful,
horses are high and forests are deep.
It's personal.
- Hello?
- Shall we smoke a peace pipe?
Who's on the phone? Someone who
dined alone at the Récamier restaurant.
Is it you?
It's you.
My mother had an attack.
I spent that night in hospital.
You couldn't know that of course.
Better... thank you... yes.
She trots.
Do you know the Ascot?
An American bar at the Champs- Elysées.
Six o'clock.
Alright?
Hello.
Le Pavillon du Régent?
Would you have a table for 2
tonight?
Nine o'clock, yes.
Blaumet... Mr Blaumet.
I was also told that you have
little bungalows.
The girls aren't here, Lucien.
What do you want?
You can't come in.
What's with the skis?
I'm selling them to a friend,
so we'll have some money.
I said you can't come in.
Have you been vaccinated against
smallpox?
Why?
Leave me alone.
In order to go to Mexico, like I wrote,
you need to be vaccinated.
I won't go to Mexico with you, Lucien.
Lucien!
There are other options...
No... no!
I'm married, I have children.
That may sound stupid and
conventional.
You're 17 and I'm 41.
Poor idiot!
Go away!
But have you been vaccinated against
smallpox?
You need a vaccination in
your brain!
Hello? Yes, I had to run.
The phone rang as I came home.
No, no.
At the ministry or at his place?
Don't worry about me.
We're working here, with 15 people.
I need a vaccination in the brain,
that wasn't funny.
You must be so unhappy
to say that.
Why do you tell me all these details?
I trust you.
- Lucien, I'll scream.
- Me too. You'll be more embarrassed.
Just call Simon.
He's expecting you for dinner.
I told him I couldn't make it.
Mum!
Must be about Bouly's kid.
Yes, she came.
What are you doing here?
For your mother. Her dryer wasn't
working. It was the fuse.
- Good evening.
- Good evening, sir.
- Bye.
I don't get it.
Last summer, with Mouchy, it worked.
I'm not going to make soufflés.
Dinner's served, boy scouts.
Don't you have something to remove
the stones from the olives?
Everything's in that bag.
Plates, bowls, camping table...
What time is it?
Dinner's served.
Serve yourself.
- What kind of totem were you?
- Cut it out, I was never a boy scout.
Look at my stone removal
technique.
- Artistic, ain't I?
- You're disgusting.
You finally showed up.
Yes, that idiot didn't...
We waited and waited...
My sister recommends getting
a legal statement drawn up.
What does your sister know?
Hey, she studied law.
I don't think you need to do that.
Unless you want her to pay you
alimony.
Sorry, but I have to laugh.
Simon, talk to him!
Please, Mouchy, can't you see...
Talk to him! Or would you rather
I kill myself?
Hello, Etienne. Don't get up.
Don't get up.
Hello Bouly. Simon told me.
So you're all alone?
You had a haircut.
- Still as beautiful.
- He's such a flatterer.
Listen, I received a letter,
very innocent. You'll read it.
I met this guy.
What's wrong with a letter?
Mummy.
He creates such a drama.
What right does he have?
Know what he said?
But why do you tell us this?
Can't I find some warmth with my son?
Would you rather be rid of me?
You come barging in here.
We were relaxing...
Do I have to inform you before I visit?
Do I have to make an appointment?
But look at them...
They're looking at you...
Don't you have any pride?
Don't think I don't know what
you're doing!
Women liked Simon,
but they had to like him in secret.
Simon had had this relationship with
his mother for 35 years.
She was the centre of his universe
and his tormentor.
The man who lived with her was
Charles Du Tillet.
We respected his light- hearted
stoicism.
Mouchy said he was the international
king of sports shoes.
He looked much older than he was.
Not without reason.
My friends had too many things
on their mind to realise...
...that I, in spite of a missed
appointment...
...was getting ready to enter an unknown
world, inhabited by just one woman.
In the meantime, I made precarious
progress in equestrian matters.
The animal seemed to empathise with
my problem and helped me spy...
...on the dressing rooms, but there
was no sign of the woman in red.
At the ministry, no one paid attention
to my transformation into a sportsman.
Only the behaviour of Mrs Esperanza
remained extremely strange.
I had many questions for her
but didn't dare ask them.
Could her female intuition have noticed
the intrigue I was involved in...
...since the day I called the woman in red
at her office?
It seemed that Mrs Esperanza, herself
a loyal wife and mother...
...was defending Marthe against me,
without ever having met her.
I decided to ignore her deliberate
provocations.
I did, however, suffer a short
period of depression.
Hey, forward!
Hey!
The fact that all my searching was in
vain didn't make me less patient.
But my physical condition
suffered seriously.
I had to continue playing tennis,
because Marthe knew how much I loved it.
Yet I couldn't call myself unhappy
compared to the suffering of a friend...
...whose smile couldn't hide
that he was worrying.
Marie- Ange gave no sign of life. Bouly
lived alone with Simon's camping gear.
Then, just when I was about to give up
hope, my life became a fairy tale.
Stop, Belle- de- Jour...
Hello.
He's beautiful.
I know about horses.
He's fantastic!
He's super!
Yes, she's beautiful.
Haven't we met before?
At the ministry, when I signed
my contract, right?
You think?
- Do you go riding often?
- Every day, for years. You?
Since 4 or 5 years only.
You must have started as
a child then.
About the other night...
Cruel, but well played.
- Which night?
- Alright.
My riding crop.
Careful, Belle- de- Jour.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Don't move, alright?
Hey, where are you going?
You're forgetting something.
What?
Excuse me.
- Hello.
Take your time.
Sorry, I had a flat tire.
Again?
- Use another excuse or get another tire.
- Did a woman bite your knees?
- No.
- Don't you believe me?
- How do we play?
- Like last time, the decider.
Give him a few minutes to warm up.
He'll warm up while he's playing.
Did you know I found the kids?
You tell me this like that?
Sorry, I should have sung it.
- Where are they?
- With an uncle in Dunkirk.
We don't even get time to warm up.
What about Marie- Ange?
She's still missing in action.
What should I do when she
comes back?
I guess that's up to...
Simon!
Don't pay any attention to me, boys.
I have to say something to Simon.
Simon, come here!
What are you doing here?
Why are you wearing your fur coat?
I'm leaving.
Do you know what he said last night?
He actually woke me up to tell me...
Guess.
You have to guess.
I don't know. You're not going to
tell me now, are you?
When can I tell you then?
I was at your place this morning.
That crazy woman wouldn't let me in.
Mrs Paquet? Of course!
I was talking to Mr Simoni!
Why do you talk to Mr Simoni
when your mother's close to suicide?
Mummy!
Besides, he's fine.
He's a play- actor.
He's fine?
Do you want to see his X- rays?
He's fine.
Ask Mrs Paquet.
But he pays you.
So you receive him with a smile.
If I have to pay, tell me how much
I owe you..
Stop, stop!
Don't talk like that to your mother.
I'll slap you in public!
What did I do?
Listen, mummy!
Goodbye or farewell.
Bye, Bouly. Don't look for me.
Where are you going?
Where is she going?
I won't leave you my address,
so you won't have to buy a stamp.
Stop it!
- Goodnight, sir.
- See you tomorrow, Pintard.
- Goodnight, Delpech.
Dorsay, I wanted to talk to you.
The telex...
Hello.
I came to bring you your earring.
My what?
I picked it up after your
horse freaked out.
Yes, but it's not mine.
I don't understand...
vHow are you?
- Fine.
- Shall we have dinner?
- No, thanks.
Tomorrow? I know a really nice
Chinese restaurant. Lunch?
Tomorrow, I'm not available for lunch.
Or for dinner.
Or a drink?
You're all wet.
Whereas you seem a bit dry.
Why?
You confuse me.
I'm sorry.
I do that well, don't I?
But I'm late.
No, no!
That's impossible!
What's impossible?
I have to tell you something,
I've never told anyone.
Your name, perhaps?
Etienne Dorsay.
- How old are you? 40?
- Just about.
Tomorrow, 4:40pm at the Rhumerie.
Will you be there?
Affirmative.
Have they still not fixed
the elevator?
Hello, young folk!
Hello, old man!
Did you fall in a puddle?
No, the water fell on me.
What about your raincoat?
My raincoat...
My raincoat?
I had left it at Bouly's.
What a day...
I lost an earring.
What?
I don't think horses get more attached
to people than dogs.
Dogs are more... horses are colder.
But I don't mean to say that...
No.
You may think it's a cliché,
but when you get on a horse...
...do we ask its opinion?
No.
You see, Charlotte, maybe it's because
I never married...
...or because I want to have
children...
...but without the friendship of animals...
some nights... when life's...
Oh, I hate sentimentality!
Where did you get your suit?
Yes, that's it.
Because that photo at the ministry,
where you're all on the steps...
- How many pairs of pants?
- How many? One.
No, get two.
You're sitting all the time.
So one with lapels and one without.
And no pockets.
Would you like a half belt?
Yes, do you want a half belt?
To be honest... I don't know.
Did she just say it like that?
That you're badly dressed?
No, she's not like that.
You know Marthe.
She looks at you without talking.
So you say...
"What is it?
What are you looking at?"
And then she'll say:
"How old are your suits?"
Hyenas!
They're all hyenas!
With all these young people in the
house... if I want to stay up to date...
- Hairspray or loose?
- Completely loose.
You can look now.
Well...
What? Hey... Errol Flynn!
Hello, godmother.
Hello, girls.
- Good evening, Marthe.
- Good evening.
Hello.
Sorry I'm late. I was...
What was I going to say?
How do you do?
Hello, the Pavillon du Régent?
Hello.
Mr Chabert speaking.
Chabert.
Stay on the line.
I'll have a look.
Mr Dorsay.
Hello? Yes, if you want.
Miss Charlotte who?
It's for me!
Hello Charlotte, Etienne speaking.
Aren't you coming?
- I'm in London.
- Why are you in London?
For work. I called you but it was
busy all the time.
Yes, the Minister of Justice kept
me busy for an hour.
- Come here, Etienne.
- Where?
There's a plane at 10pm.
I'll wait for you at the airport.
In London?
Yes.
We'll spend the evening together
and we'll come back at 10am.
Tomorrow morning?
Yes... hello?
Have they still not been?
- What's that?
- A little party.
- But why?
- For fun.
I thought we'll have a little party
at home. It'll be fun.
See what daddy gave me: an orchid.
What would you like?
A whiskey?
Yes, for instance.
And take the phone of the hook.
You don't want to make love now,
do you?
I said: Take the phone off the hook.
What's that?
- I don't know.
- Are you answering the door?
Yes.
- A telegram.
- Telegram?
- For whom?
- For you.
Open it.
- It's the ministry.
- You're kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Who's Martin Guillot?
He's the head of... what's the word...
of the entire floor.
Is he your superior?
Not for much longer,
but at the moment... yes.
Are you going to read it?
Presence required- Tonight.
Brussels- Back tomorrow 12pm.
No.
No!
This time it's no! No!
I won't go!
Etienne!
I'm not a puppet!
This is the limit.
I'm not their hostage!
- What do you want to do?
- I don't know.
Call him at the ministry.
I have his private number: Balzac 14- 39.
Tell him to go to Brussels
with his servants.
But that I stay home!
With my wife!
And my children!
Listen, Etienne, you have to go.
Don't be a child.
No!
Wait for me!
Bloody hell, Marie- Ange!
Marie- Ange!
Mrs Philippot! Did she go upstairs?
- Non.
- What did she want?
- Her mail.
- Did she have any?
- No.
Driving school...
There's this guy.
- What? What guy.
- Well, a guy.
When I rang, a guy opened.
Blue T- shirt with stripes.
I don't care about a T- shirt.
Did you see Marie- Ange or not?
No.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
When I saw the guy, I said
I rang the wrong doorbell.
I'll drag Marie- Ange out by her dress.
You'll see.
Be careful, because that guy's
not very nice.
Hey.
Bouly can come get her himself.
She's not our wife.
We're about to land in London.
Fasten your seatbelt.
The weather doesn't allow us to land
in London.
We'll be landing in Brussels instead.
We'll soon give you more information.
I closed the roof. It started to rain.
What's wrong?
He'd be a guest of honour at
the Assholes Ball.
I can't control myself with guys
like that.
Give me a Kleenex.
- Want me to fix you up?
- He scratched me.
Asshole!
Did you see Marie- Ange?
What?
Sort of... yes.
She sure won the lottery!
To take 3 kids away from their dad to...
Hyenas!
But what did you say to her?
What? Nothing.
I was working on that dwarf.
What dwarf?
That guy.
- What will we say to Bouly?
- I don't know. We'll have to be tactful.
- What if we write to him?
- No, no.
We'll say that there was a driving
school, because we can't...
That Marie- Ange wasn't there...
and then we'll think of...
We won't mention the dwarf.
No, exactly.
Welcome to Brussels. Passengers from the
Paris- London flight are invited...
...to go to the airport restaurant, where
refreshments will be served.
They will receive more information
later.
Hello... yes...
Why are you calling?
Yes, I like it, but I know
you're in Brussels.
That's not it. I mean...
I wasn't worried.
You're so sensitive.
I was asleep.
I took something because...
Yes, yes.
No, you hang up.
Last time I hung up.
Yes, I love you.
1, 2, 3.
I know he's not home.
Mum?
Now what? Turn off the light!
Understood?
You're not going to ring all night,
are you?
Yes, I am.
What do you want?
It's now or never, my love.
Now or never what?
Go away.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone!
I lack the perseverance of Frédéric
Moreau in Sentimental Education.
I see.
I'll be hard, very hard. It's no fun
to be abandoned at 40 years of age.
But you have to forget about me.
It's better that way, Lucien.
Are you for or against the ban on heavy
vehicles on the banks of the Seine?
Why do you ask me that?
I'm conducting a survey for an agency.
Are you for or against?
I don't know... against.
Right, bye Madam.
Anyway, you made me lose my head.
When I think of my past,
I remember more beautiful nights.
Yet, in this foreign land,
where I'd ended up by coincidence...
I could feel the wind of adventure
in my neck.
One woman was waiting for me in London,
the other in Paris, and I'm in Brussels.
The next day, Charlotte braved the fog
and flew back to Paris.
We spent a series of intense moments,
every day between 4:55pm and 5:52pm.
That was the time when Marthe would come
home with or without her friends.
During these short hours, Charlotte
and I burnt the candle both ways.
We made exciting little trips
and had lovely meetings.
Charlotte and I
cherished the mystery of Charlotte.
She spoke little about herself
and I respected her silence.
To hide my real intentions,
I didn't suggest meeting at night.
We'd separate without exchanging
addresses.
She would be speechless with joy
and my face would be marked by desire.
During that time, Marthe passed
her dreaded exams.
She only failed one oral exam.
I admired her.
I got promoted, without any
further exams or intrigue.
I got the job of Martin Guillot,
who was entitled to retirement.
So I was in charge of the entire floor.
My promotion didn't lead to jealousy.
On the contrary, even the most
aggressive characters relaxed.
I was too busy to wonder what
had brought about this change.
I wasn't the only one to see
their life take a positive turn.
Simon gave his mother away.
He was over the moon and so were we for
him. Charles Du Tillet was on his guard.
But as Mouchy put it:
"It's the end result that counts."
The wedding was chaotic,
noisy and a big success.
Who's is this?
Mine.
Don't lose your stuff.
But the best surprise was the return
of Bouly's wife and furniture.
Why she came back was unclear. Simon and
Daniel said it had to do with a dwarf.
But their reports were confusing
and contradictory.
Bouly thought he was so charming
his wife couldn't stay away any longer.
Unfortunately, the next day he
returned to his old ways.
Don't do that. You don't even
know her first name.
What's her first name?
- Tell us!
- Come on!
Hyacinthe.
We're laughing because we're stupid.
It's not a bad name: Hyacinthe.
Hey guys, who wants to play
checkers?
You're terrible, Bouly.
Do that at home.
I can't do that at home.
Hello, do you also have
the pieces to play with?
And then you're surprised...
- Surprised about what?
- Nothing.
- Tell me.
- No, nothing.
Hey, that's my glass.
Did you see the legs on the
one on the right?
Can we get our coffees, please?
She wasn't wearing a bra.
I don't care, stop it.
Bitch.
Goal.
Say, Daniel.
What about my car?
I should get it today, but the
guy's not there.
Because I'm fed up with this one.
The key's in the door.
Oh, it's you.
How have you been
since we last saw each other?
Are you painting everything?
- Yes, I started on it.
You can stain that floor.
- Shall we have a drink?
- Yes.
Let me see what I still have.
Do you like Chartreuse?
I wanted to tell you that my life
isn't all that simple.
I also have as secret.
Feel that dashboard, Etienne.
Excuse me, Charlotte.
Do it.
Tell me what you think.
Why are you showing it off?
I'm buying it anyway.
Where do I drop you two off?
At the Puy de l'Ermite.
Since we're close.
Are you seeing your godmother?
Yes, like every Thursday.
Does she know you?
No.
What will you tell your poor
godmother?
Nothing, it's a surprise.
Well, I'll be...
That's saying something. Us guys have
never been to see your godmother.
- Come up for a drink. She'll like that.
- Quickly then.
You can't park here.
It's only for 5 minutes.
Give me a break.
This is a crossing.
You have to move.
Etienne, go upstairs.
I'll park at the corner.
Press the 7th floor.
She's a piano teacher. She lives alone.
She has a son, Claude, in Italy.
You're beautiful.
You smell very nice.
What is it?
Sandalwood.
- Hello, Etienne!
- You're in the dark, godmother.
Happy birthday to you!
Claude!
- I thought you were in San Remo.
- That's the surprise.
- And Yaya.
- Not Yaya anymore, but Christian.
Marthe, my darling.
Wait, let me introduce...
I'm so emotional that...
Let me introduce a friend...
Hello, godmother. You didn't tell me.
What's happening?
We organised a surprise
for Etienne.
Hello, children.
I'm not staying. I just wanted to thank
godmother for the beautiful jumper.
- Did Etienne give it to you?
- Yes, it was a bit big for me.
He means to say you need to be
broad shouldered for it.
Say hello, Mimi.
Hello.
Get glasses, Claude.
No, we won't have a drink.
We're leaving.
I spent a bit of money, didn't I,
baby?
I've got two concert tickets.
But you must have two minutes.
No, out of the question...
Say goodbye, Mimi.
Well... bye.
Bye.
Happy birthday, Etienne.
Why do you want me to change them?
It's a great gift.
Marthe, is Etienne with you?
I need to see him right away.
Etienne, Etienne...
I don't know what to do anymore.
He's going bonkers. He wants to
kill her, he wants to kill himself.
He hit me in the face, look.
But... who... what... how?
Bouly.
Marie- Ange left again.
Marie- Ange?
He's in the car. Have a look.
You know... Etienne's the eldest
and Bouly looks up to him.
I'll kill her!
- Stop it, Bouly!
- Shut up, Daniel!
Don't be a pain.
- It's getting out of hand, Bouly.
- I'll kill you!
Etienne, I'm going home... or what?
Yes, go home.
Have you got the key?
Yes!
Come.
My kids!
- I'm bleeding.
- No, get in.
Find me a bridge to jump off.
That's enough.
He's crazy.
I'm deaf in my right ear.
You're alright, Simon. Get in.
- Bouly, listen.
- No, shut up.
Apologies.
You're quite something!
We didn't know what to give you.
I don't know where she lives.
Number 72, she told me, 8th floor.
What did she tell you?
She told me she'd tell you.
- You really hurt me.
- I was pretending.
- I'm sorry.
- It sucks, I can't hear anything.
Here it is.
Happy birthday, Etienne.
Yes?
Etienne Dorsay.
Listen, Etienne Dorsay.
A month ago, I met a man with no wife,
no children, who liked horse riding.
In a month's time, you got married
and had two 14 year old girls.
You don't ride horses,
they ride you.
The way you dress, children in the
countryside would throw rocks at you.
Your plane lands in Belgium
when I'm waiting in London.
Stop looking at your shoes and
look at me.
I want you...
the way I've never wanted anyone
before.
How do you explain that?
I don't know.
I want your hands...
I want to see your undressed
body.
You mean... naked?
Why?
I think you shouldn't explain.
I suggest you take off your
bow tie.
Hello, Titou? Marthe speaking.
Are your parents home?
No, they're both gone.
I'm home alone.
Simon's not home either.
Nobody's home.
Do you know when they'll be back?
No and dad broke a chair.
If fate had wanted me to be a person
of national importance...
...this night would have gone into
the history books.
Charlotte said to me in 1 second, what
I had been unable to say for a month.
Come.
A beautiful imperative that
set my life on fire.
However, the male soul is so ugly, that
I never considered leaving Marthe.
Not even after giving her an allowance
consisting of 35.8% of my salary...
...after subtraction of benefits.
Hello?
Simone?
Yes.
What's going on?
Nothing, it's my husband.
He's downstairs.
- Your husband?
- Yes, hurry! Hurry!
- Hurry, why? Which husband?
- Come on, get out of the bed.
He was supposed to be gone
all week.
But it's only Friday.
We'll have to ask him for an
explanation, won't we?
Your watch.
But... what are you doing?
Leave it to us, Charlotte.
I'll talk to him from man to man.
You're crazy.
You have to go.
- No, that's the window.
- You can't go through the door.
Don't worry.
Get on the ledge.
He won't stay long.
Wait for me there.
Where are your things?
In the bathroom.
I put them there last night and...
I'm coming!
The doorbell rings,
I have to hang up!
I was on the phone with Jeanette.
Hello, darling.
- Did you see that?
- Damn!
There's a man up there.
No, he's not here.
Do you think he'll jump?
- I'll land in Marrakech at 3:10pm.
- Yes, but I have to work on Monday.
Take the plane on Sunday evening.
- You're beautiful.
- What?
You're beautiful.
You heard what I said.
Can we call the fire brigade?
There's a guy about to jump.
There he is!
Come on.
I'm not playing along.
What's wrong now?
After all our fooling around,
she left for real.
Marie- Ange?
It got so late, she thought I was
spending the night with someone.
With the furniture?
What's wrong with you?
When the prof arrived at the hospital,
the guy had died, so he went back home.
And he finds Simon...
He was nice about it. He drove me
to the hospital to get the bullet out.
What a guy...
Is Etienne not at your place?
Why would he be at my place?
No ladder! That scares them!
It always makes them jump.
Or think about it.
Didn't she say if she'd be back?
If only to see the children.
Alright...
... at the corner of the Rue de Tilsitt
and the Avenue de la Grande Armée...
Hey, guys!
Commander Gaudion of the 5th
Brigade and his men are at the scene.
They're trying to intervene
from the roof.
- Who moved the antenna?
- Not me.
...a desperate man whose identity
is not known...
He looks like dad.
But, Etienne...
Be reasonable, sir!
Jump in the canvas!
With Charlotte gone, I realised that if
Marthe would leave me too...
...it would be for good reason.
I decided to fall carefully...
I counted the number of women in
the crowd who could catch me.
I noticed a platinum blonde
who took my picture.
To be honest, I was only at the
beginning of my ascent.