Hey, I like your knee socks
They're not knee socks
They're fashion tights
It's all one... whatever
You wouldn't get it
Yeah, I do
You mean, they're all pure black up
to the thigh, sheer black up top
Yeah, that's...
that's exactly right
Yeah, I like it
I think it's hot
Yeah, I like it too
I've just been really into, like
wearing my thighs out lately
Like, I feel like it's sexual-ish
and super powery
You like the superpower sex, huh?
Yeah
Yes, I see why you think that's funny
Like, in your world that's probably
really clever word play
Could you guys buzz off?
I'm trying to focus
Focus on what?
The wall?
"Focus on what?
The wall?"
That's what you sound like
No, I'm shooting a special here
for HBO, maybe you've heard of it
It's kind of a big deal
At Largo?
That's like barely 300 seats
Well, I'm actually doing it
in the littler room
The little room?
That's like 50 seats
Thirty-nine with the fire marshal
Oh, whatever
Hey, you need to call your agent
You can't be doing no
HBO special for 39 people
That's like super tiny
It's called intimate, fuck face
What's that? Pot?
It's a bunch of stuff
Hey, tell us a joke
What do you call a car full
of Mexicans?
What?
Pains in my ass...
Hole
"Please put your hands together
for Miss Sarah Silverman"
- Tell me I'm great
- What?
Tell me I'm great
Tell me I'm great!
You're crazy, eh
Crazy great
I very rarely, occasionally
obsessively watch porn on my phone
And when I do, I integrate it
into my nighttime rituals
I wash my face, I floss
I take a puff, then I brush
then I do my stretches
then I type in my search words
Let me just say, my search words
are not anything
I would want to happen in real life
I don't know why they're my search
words, but they are
A great man once said
"The heart wants what it wants"
So, my search words are:
gangbang, I do not want
that to happen in real life
amateur, because I don't like seeing
like piercings and tattoos
It takes me out of it
Cum, which I would not have thought
you had to put cum
I thought that was given in pornography
You have to put cum
If you don't, you might not get cum
If anything, I would think you'd
put non-cum if you don't want cum
And then there's one more
Oh, high-fives So...
I put my iPhone and lean it against
my water on my nightstand
and I think I'm maybe the only person
that watch this video
all the way until the end, end, end
like when the video freezes
It's of course a gangbang
and, you know
it basically ends with all the guys
cumming on the lady's face
And I don't know why face
was the quiet word of the day
All the men cum on the lady's face
And then right before the video freezes
I heard a guy say to her
"Hey, great job
I know you were sick"
You find humanity
in the oddest of places
So my mom was in the hospital
and I visited her
I don't need segues
The brain doesn't work that way
A train of thought bounces
around from thing to thing
But anyway, speaking of a whole
bunch of men cumming on a lady's face
my mother has been sick
And I visited her in the hospital
and she said, it's weird
You know, there was this Jewish
volunteer service that came by
and they were visiting
the Jewish patients, which is nice
but isn't that so, like, elitist?
Like, what are they like banana
around the non-Jewish patients?
Like, "None for you"
But my mother's last name is O'Hara
She married a John O'Hara
And she said, "They visited me
Like, how they do know I was Jewish?"
And we looked into it
and it turns out they count how
many times you press the call button
I had a...
have you ever had a memory
and you... that you haven't had
since the event happened?
You know what I mean?
It's so crazy
I had this memory of being like three
and I would shower with my mother
and, like, my mom's... okay
My mom got her water
from the shower head
like that's where she would get her
water with which to cleanse herself
That water would then
cascade down her ample bosom
and, like, pike off of her '70s
Jew bush...
That was my water
And that's the thing
it was a happy memory
I associate it with happy
I don't know why
Like, it was my very own curly
shower or something
Maybe because we didn't
need words, you know
It wasn't like she was, like
"You get my water from my pubes"
you know, it was...
We didn't need any of those
Like, I was...
I was like a native that knew you could
get water from this leaf or some things
Very animalistic
I was a bedwetter
well into my teens
And when you're a bedwetter
there's only one group of people
you can feel better than, bedshitters
And unfortunately,
they're hard to come by and...
I love this
The HBO 39
When I grew up in New Hampshire, and
there are not many Jews in New Hampshire
and we... we weren't really
raised with any religion
We were just Jewish and that
it oozed out of our pores, you know
Um, but I didn't feel so different
until maybe like around third grade
Kids started blaming me
for my people killing Jesus
I remember, like,
even then thinking like
"It's not like we killed Baby Jesus"
I mean, the man, like...
He had quite a run
He was 33
Thirty-three is young
If someone dies now at 33, it's terrible
But I mean, back then
in the olden oldie timey times
33 was like elderly
Thirty-three... dying at thirty-three
was like he had a full life, you know
And by the way, you're welcome
If we had not killed him
he wouldn't even be famous
You know, and nothing seems crazy
when you're used to it
There's so much crazy shit everywhere
We're used to it
And everything seems crazy
when you're not used to it
That's why so many comics
make fun of scientology, right?
Because like...
Well because it's
a bat shit crazy religion but...
It's no more bat shit crazy
than like every single religion
It's just new, you know
Christianity is super old
but it's fucking crazy
I mean, it's...
You're born a sinner
By being born, you are a sinner
and you're going to hell
but you can just apologize
and then you can go to heaven
No big deal
If you're a murderer, same thing
you just apologize and go to heaven
You can be Hitler
and go to confession and say
"Forgive me, Father
I killed six million Jews"
and the priest would just be like
"No problems, say ten Heil Marys"
And Hitler goes to heaven
Hitler Goes to Heaven
is the name of my band
Scientology is weird
because it's new, it's...
It feels weird in our ear holes to hear
people worshipping a guy named Ron
We know Rons in our life
He had to change his name
to L. Ron
because there was another
Ron Hubbard in the Writer's Guild
That's how recent a religion it is
And people who follow their religion
to the letter of the law are just silly
I mean, I want to tell Hasidic Jews
"I promise you, God will not mind if you
wear a nice cotton blend in the summer"
You're being fucking ridiculous
But we live in the greatest country
in the world
A country where we have
freedom of religion
and separation of church and state
only we daunt it all and nobody says
anything 'cause we're used to it
It says, "In God we trust"
on our money
above the judges bench
in a courtroom, in a court of law
where you have to put your hand
on a Bible... the Christian Bible
It's not my Bible
I mean, if I... if I told the truth
it's because I tell the truth
not because I put my hand
on a book and made a wish
It's fucking crazy
That's craziness
And stop telling girls they can be
anything they want when they grow up
I think...
I think it's a mistake
Not because they can't
but because it would've never
occurred to them they couldn't
You're planting that seed
in their heads
It's like saying,
"Hey, when you get in the shower"
"I'm not gonna read your diary"
"Hold on...
Are you gonna read my diary?"
"What? Are you crazy? I just said
I'm not gonna read your diary"
"Get in the shower"
Girls grow up so fast
It's like they don't have
childhoods anymore
They're sexualized so early,
you know
I... a girlfriend of mine has a little
baby girl and I babysat to her
I changed her diaper,
totally shaved
Six months old
What a country!
That's my new catch phrase
I know that Yakov Smirnoff
said in the '80s
but I'm repurposing it
with a malaise
I just wanna shake girls, all the girls
here, I wanna just tell you
"You don't need
a vaginal deodorant, okay?"
I know it seems like a real thing
because there's real commercials
and for some reason, we trust that
That commercials mean it's real
you know
And there's real products on shelves
No, it's a made-up need
made by greedy money-addicted
faceless corporations preying
on a woman's greatest insecurity
smelly vagina
If you use regular soap
and water in the...
Use whatever you wash your asshole with
How about that?
Surely that's strong enough
for your disgusting vagina
Rinse, and if... when you get out of
the shower, there's still like something
like a rancidishness coming
go to the doctor
Don't spray perfume on it
That's fucking crazy
That's what a crazy person would do
Do you see now?
Are your eyes open?
Are you living a conscious life?
I'm lucky I don't have to worry
about that because...
I've been with the few men
who have told me
that my vagina smells like a um,
a peach...
A peach tree...
Peach tree dish
Is that a thing?
That joke took real acting
real life acting
You had the craziest reaction
He just... his arms were folded
and he just went like...
Like,
"Oh Sarah, you're incorrigible"
Oh, I'm corrigible
It's not all demand
It isn't
It's not all corporate America
It's us too
We have to take responsibility too
We shit on ourselves
We scrutinize ourselves
We think that self-deprecation
is modesty, It's not
It's self-obsession
and there's no room for anything else
You think... you think Mother Theresa
walked around complaining
that the tops of her thighs touched?
I mean, they didn't
She was stick thin, fucking, bitch
But she wasn't like...
"Okay, this is fine, okay. But it's like
then, I clench and it's all oatmeal"
No, she was busy
She had things to do
You know one thing I've noticed
people who say the phrase
"Threw me under the bus," um, say it lot
You know...
and I don't think it's because
they get thrown under the bus a lot
I think it's because they...
they deflect blame a lot
I think it's because they look
inward not a lot
And I... you know,
Jesus had a great quote
and I know all his quotes are great
There's no Jesus B sides
But...
and I'm paraphrasing
but it's basically like...
"If you don't deal with your shit
your shit deals with you"
you know
but it had like doth in it
And it's so true
And I... I made a short list
that I think can help people
who don't look inward ever
One, if you quit being cunty
the whole world
will stop being against you
If you have terrible luck with roommates
you're the terrible roommate
It's you, doll
If you feel like the whole world
is judging you all the time
you're an alcoholic
I don't know why,
but specifically alcohol
Dear sirs, your middle-aged
pierced ear
tells a different story
than you think it does
To women of a certain age
your heartbreaking and drastic
attempts to look younger
are the reason your daughter
doesn't dream about her future
Insecurity burbles up
in all corners of us, you know
Either you have a chip
on your shoulder
You feel like people are disrespecting
you all the time
or you get really braggy
You want people to know who you know
but you like hide it by shitting on them
Like...
how many fucking videos
of a monkey smelling his assy fingers
and falling out of a tree can
Helen Mirren send me, it's like ridic
Look at my space work there
It's impressive, isn't it?
What does that tell you?
Blackberry
Guess what?
I don't even own a Blackberry
I shadowed someone
who does for months to do that bit
There are people that,,,
it's there survival
It's the way they deal with life
to see themselves differently
than the way the rest of the world
sees them, you know
You get the idea if these people were
one or two degrees more onto themselves
they fucking kill themselves
I consider myself one of them
I get out of the shower and I'm like
"Nice try, mirror...
Those are obviously my mom's boobs"
Sometimes insecurity proves you right
I mean I... when I moved to L.A.
I had an eyebrow
And my roommate at the time was like
"Hey, let's go make this into two"
"Like each eye can have one"
And so I went to her waxing lady
I had never been to like a waxing lady
and the lady called me in and
I'm like following her into a room
and she turns around and she goes
"What are we doing today?
Just the mustache?"
"I don't have a mustache
What?"
"I bleach my mustache.
That means it's invisible"
Bright yellow means you can't see it
But she did and she waxed it
and I remember walking out
of the door and being like...
I could feel the wind on it
You know?
What about this one?
Yeah, whatever
Like jerk off thing, right?
I believe that's from insecurity
"Yeah, whatever"
What is a guy saying
when he does what he's saying?
Whatever it is we're talking about here
I don't give a shit
Really?
I think you do give a shit
If you didn't give a shit
wouldn't you be just be like...
I think you do give a shit, sir
What is he saying?
He's saying, "Whatever it is
we're talking about here"
"please don't think I care"
"Oh my God, I would die
if you thought I cared"
"In exchange, feel free
to know my personal jerking off style"
"It is so important to me
that you think"
"I don't care about whatever
it is we're talking about here"
"I'm willing to exchange that
for you knowing"
"that my masturbation style is that
like I don't... I don't move my hand"
"Like my hand is still and I, like
fuck my hand"
"My hand is locked"
"And then, like
I fuck... I pretend it's a vagina"
"I'm not a faggot"
"And I fuck my hand"
"I make it like she's shorter than me"
"Like it's lower and I have
to like scoop it in"
Fuck you
Sometimes you can say and go
"Scoop, Scoop, Scoop"
"But please don't think I care
oh my God, I would die"
Traumatic things
happened to that guy
Traumatic things happened
to all of you by the way
Traumatic things
happened to all of us
We just don't realize it because
there's no music informing us
how to feel
or what's gonna come up
There's no slow motion
It just happens in real time and then
the next moment and the next moment
My sister used to be babysit me
when I was three
And she would...
She would... okay
I used to think this was
a heartbreaking story about me
It's a heartbreaking story about
my sister Susie, because she was so...
she was so starved for love
She was so needy for love and
she would come out and she'd say
"Sarah, if I drink this orange juice
I'm gonna turn into a monster"
And I was so scared
I wish I had the foresight to say
"Hey, how about don't even pour
the orange juice?"
But I didn't, I didn't think that
far ahead, I was three
And I'd go "Susie, no, no"
Whip open the laundry nook
and put on this brown leather ski mask
which... why the Silverman family
needed a brown leather ski mask
I still do not know
She puts it on and she like...
I mean I thought I was going to die
I felt the feeling of I'm going
to die when I was three
And then this is what's
so heartbreaking
She'd go "I will only turn back
into Susie if you hug me"
"Like, I wish I had the wherewithal
to be like, Sus, you want a hug?"
"I'd love to hug you"
"Let's cut out the middleman
where I shit my pants"
But instead I'm inching towards
this monster I'm terrified of to hug it
Oh, God
I'm sorry
That's every relationship
I've ever been in, There you go
Breakthrough on stage, HBO Special
She would take the...
that threw me for a loop
She'd take the biggest knife out
of the kitchen drawer and be like
"It's so funny
Like, I could kill you right now"
"Isn't that funny?"
She gets so upset
when I bring those up
No, She's so sweet now
And she... it literally makes her cry
when I bring those up
but thank God, I...
She is in at HBO
But she's like this liberal, hippy
feminist rabbi that lives in Israel now
and she's got five kids and her oldest
daughter is going to Brandeis next year
which is only from Israel can going to
Brandeis be a step down in Jewy-ness
I don't know if your familiar
with Brandeis
It's not technically a Jewish school
but I think the team mascot is a nose
Yes
It helps you at all
Okay. This would be terrible
if I had just made it up
I didn't
This is really upsetting
But the University of North Carolina
did a study and what they found was...
that 9/11 widows give great handjobs
And I...
Don't shoot the messenger
I wish it wasn't true, but I am happy
for them and their new boyfriends
I made that up, I'm sorry
I made that up
I thought of it and it made me giggle
and then I got really sad
and then I still needed
to say it to you
I don't know what part of me
needs to say to you
that 9/11 widows give great handjobs
it's dark
That's something I'm gonna talk
about in therapy
But I wanted to say it
I needed to say it to you
and so I built a frame around it
that forced you to not be able
to blame me for saying that
And...
But you know what?
I feel like you should take some
of the blame
Honestly because
you decided to believe
that the University of North Carolina
spend money on a study of what?
Trauma-based handjobs
That's crazy
You're crazy
You're being crazy right now
Hmm, I need more rape jokes
I do
I... rape jokes are a hidden gem
in comedy
Let me explain
Rape, obviously the most
heinous crime imaginable
Rape jokes are great
No, because they make a comic
seem so edgy and so dangerous
And the truth is it's like the
safest area to talk about in comedy
because who is gonna
complain about a rape joke?
I mean, I would say rape victims but
they're traditionally not complainers
I know
That's a tasteless joke about the fact
that rape victims often
don't report rape
I mean the worst thing that could happen
really is someone comes up to you
after a show and it's like
"Look, I'm a victim of rape"
"and I just wanna say I thought that
joke was insensitive and inappropriate"
"and totally my fault
and I am so sorry"
Yeah, right?
Let's take that to the night back
My God!
I hope I don't have to say that
You know no woman is asking
to be raped
I actually do think there are some
women who are asking to be motorboated
I have a dog who is 19 years old
and that's true
And he... you know
sometimes the audience claps
because they're really happy for me
that I took care of a 19...
No, forget it now
Don't, stop
He has got this beautiful big blue eyes
floating over his big brown eyes
His breath, I've really
really thought about this
His breath smells like
if all the farts
from all the different like cultures and
nations in the world combine together
and then past through
my grandpa's teeth
And he was constipated
and it's so heartbreaking
You know, when a dog gets constipated
and they... you can tell
because their little knees
like quiver, quiver
And his pushing so hard
and then like something broke through
and his mouth made a shape
I've never seen on a dog
I didn't know it was possible
It was like perfect circle
Ohh!
And his little tiny rectum
was bleeding
and I went to take
a picture for the vet
The vet
is what I call Twitter
You know, when you take a picture
but it's video, and you don't realize it
It was basically a picture
but it was like a second and a half
and it had breath
ended with me going like, "Urg"
He's great now
He shits like crazy
Only thing that keeps him from shitting
in his pants is he doesn't wear pants
that's a horrible joke
If you do have a dog,
here's a great game
You're gonna love this
When you're having sex
lock eyes with your dog
And then you see
who looks away first
It's a fun game
Pussy
Pussy is a word... it used
to have so much power over me
like when I was in high school,
the word pussy...
it was so...
it grossed me out
and yet it was titillating
and I just had... it...
I felt like I had Christmas
lights inside me
like it just affected me so much
I don't even understand how
but when I was young it was like
if somebody said it or
if I read it somewhere or sometimes
I would write it down
and look at it
Now, I'm just dead inside
Pussy, pussy
Who cares?
I found a way to make pussy gross again
It's so simple
All you have to do is like puff out your
cheeks when you say it like, "Puhssy"
"Puhssy"
"Puhssy!"
Now, say that becomes old hat
You can add some elements
A deadness in the eyes, a lisp
"Puthy"
"Hey, man you wanna go out
and look for some puthy?"
"Puthy"
You look so confused
You don't know how to feel just
like me when I first heard "puthy"
If you're drunk and throw up
on a man's penis mid-blowjob
you can save the moment
if you can muster a "ta-da"
Oh, you guys
this is embarrassing
This is a... this is a confession, okay?
Sometimes I get an orgasm
from giving a blowjob
is that normal?
Like to get an orgasm
from giving a...
oh, not giving a blowjob,
taking a shit
I... you don't understand
I'm at a show too
You're my show
and that joke is so fun to tell
because, like,
at the first juncture
the guys are like this
and the girls are like this
And then it just goes whoo!
It's like the wave
Don't forget God
can see you masturbating
But don't stop
He's almost there
I'm just kidding
There's no God
I believe in miracles, though
I really do
I mean, that... They're obviously
science-based But...
They're beyond my comprehension
so to me they're miracles
That's what miracles are
And we are miracles
Think about this
Every single person
in this room tonight, all 39
including me, 40 of us
there was a time in history
a bleep ago in the scope of history
where we were all microscopic specs
That was far out, right?
Everybody got deep
There was a time where you could fit
a million of me on the head of a pin
There was a time where
I lived in my dad's balls
That's the only life I knew
There was a time where I literally
was choking on my dad's cum
I was five
No, I'm just kidding
That's disgusting
Erase
That's not part of that joke I...
It's just it went in my head
and then I couldn't be alone with it
There was a time my dad
Donny "Schleppy" Silverman
who does my taxes
who I Skype with every Saturday
there was a time
where I literally exploded
out of the guy
who taught me to skeez penis hole
I can't believe
I was ever that thin
I'm an Obama person
Yeah
I like him
I liked Obama since before
he ran for president the first time
when he was a senator in Chicago
Not like I'm so smart or hoity-toity
I just... he was on Letterman
and I thought he was cool
And I remember
when he decided to run for president
I was like, "I'm gonna work
on that campaign" And I did
And because I live in Los Angeles
I could go to this fundraiser
out here that was just star-studded
Like a who's who
And you could walk, you know
he was just a senator at that time
so you could walk right up to him
and pet him and...
I did
I wanted to think of something
smart to say or a question to ask
and I was like "Senator Obama
when you were a student in Boston"
"did you ever encounter any racism?"
And I'll never forget what he said
He said...
he said, "I'm Kanye West"
I was like, "Totally
I'm Kanye West too. We all are"
I get it
We're so divided
We live in a very divided country
like it's crazy, you know?
It's not even about ideas anymore
It's not even about ideals anymore
It's just teams
It's just the Red Sox and the Yankees
It's just hatred, you know?
And I think whether you're liberal
or you're conservative
it's so important to remember that we...
All of us love our families
love our country
believe what we're doing is right
You know, maybe liberals
are a little more open-minded
a little more progressive
You know, maybe conservatives
are a little less progressive
a little more faggotish
But I pray for them
I do
I was just literally praying for the
billions of teeny tiny Republicans
that die every single year
in hookers' assholes
I know that some of you are thinking...
and you're right, you're right
Really? That's what you're gonna pick on
the Republican Party?
That's what you're pick...
Choosing to pick on?
You know, I mean, surely
there are Democrats
that have butt sex with prostitutes
You're right
You're a hundred percent right
There are, but Democrats
aren't trying to take my rights away
So, when a Democrat
gives a hooker anal warts...
She can then go to a clinic
and get that shit zapped
It's just bewildering to me
that a party
that is so about having big government
out of their backyard is so intent
on legislating my "puhssy,"
my pussy
Puh, pussy
People don't make the simplest
connections, you know?
I feel like I have shit here
I don't.
That'll be my biggest fear
Okay
Do I have anything in my teeth?
I had blueberries
Yeah. People don't make
the simplest connections
I've... I think because we're
so close to our own lives, you know
but even in deep ways
but even in not deep...
like I used to work at a club
like a music club, kinda like this
And tables and I was, you know
I lit the candles of the tables
and put the fliers out and stuff
And the band that was playing
had sound check
and they did their sound check
and left
but the drummer stayed
and she was just sitting at her drums
watching me set up
And I was talking to her and I made some
stupid joke and she goes, "Pa, rum, pum"
I was like, "You know
that comes from drums" Right?
"You're sitting at drums"
It's like people who go
"Don't get your dog from a breeder"
"Get your dog from a shelter"
"You're a fucking asshole
if you get your dog from a breeder"
Okay, I agree
I got my dog from a shelter
but it's always coming from a woman
who's like nursing a baby
with four other kids
and I just wanna say like
"Get your people from a shelter"
You know there are human puppies
in shelters, right?
But people don't like people
as much as they like dogs
'cause they don't...
They don't see what they hate
in themselves
looking back
in a dog's eyes, you know?
If Africa was just all Labradoodles
dying of AIDS...
We would take care of it in one day
But I wanna have kids
I'm great with kids
I am
I have a lot of bits
Like little girls between like,
two and sixish
I like to go like this, I go
"I'm gonna tell you a secret,
you cannot tell anybody"
"I'm a princess"
"But I dress regular
so people treat me normal"
And their brains fucking explode
It's so funny
And then, the rest of the day
they're spying me like I'm a celebrity
which I know I am
but a lot of toddlers
don't know that
and it does at levels of playing film
Or boys or girls like toddler age
like two year olds
if their parents like introduce me
I like to go, "I'm your new mommy"
They're so into like
their mommies at that age
They're always like,
"No, you're not"
And then I go, "I'm just kidding"
And then just as I start to relax
I go, "I'm your real mommy"
That's more just fun for me
But I do
I want a baby
The thing with me is like the caveat is
I don't want like a 10 year old
in 10 years
You know what I mean?
I want a baby
I figured out a solution
like I think works for me
I'm not preaching it to anybody
but like, I think I'm gonna
adopt like terminally ill babies
Every six months
to two years-ish
I feel like there is like a blanket
of judgment in this area
Why?
Are you thinking like what kind of
person would look to adopt a dying baby?
I mean, I think an amazing person
I'm amazing
I have a hu...
my heart is too big
Like, I can't take it
My heart can't take
I don't like being made to feel
Like Pixar movies, no fucking way
Wall-E, like the idea to me
of a lonely robot and space breaks me
Good, bad, I don't wanna feel
I don't like it
Like, my mother sent me an email that
said "Elephants reunite after 20 years"
Delete
I am not even gonna read that
That will kill me
I'm afraid it will kill me
Those commercials with like a
starving kid in Africa
with flies buzzing around him
I have to remind myself like
"It's just an actor, it's just an actor"
I love being able to see all 39 of you
It's so cool.
But you know, what's amazing
is the Make a Wish Foundation
just to... you know, they...
if you're not familiar with what they do
they work with terminally ill children
and young adults
And what they will do is
they will grant these kids
any wish they dream up
except for not dying
Which I feel like I'm being nitpicky
'cause what they do is amazing
but like, I feel like that's gonna be
maybe even like 60%
of their number one wishes
I just feel like if there's
a suggestion box or something
I'd say, "Maybe call it like
Make another Wish"
You guys did a great job
I'm gonna reward you
with an incredible song
Is this in tune?
Are you a musician?
Oh, you should get a haircut
Let's make this real hot and sexy
Nothing but the best for the Largo 39
"If you call yourself a diva"
"You better be a singer"
"and not somebody
cutting me in line"
"If you call yourself a diva"
"you better sing a solo"
"and not be someone
treating me unkind"
"If you call yourself a diva"
"you better be for reels"
"and not some sad pathetic
kind of front"
"If you're selfish
and you're thoughtless"
"and you're broken
and you're heartless"
"you're probably not a diva,
you are a cunt"
"Cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt"
"cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt"
"Cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt"
"Cunt"
"Cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt"
"Cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt"
"Cunt, cunt"
"cunt"
Thank you so much
Good night
Hey, how did it go?
Oh, it was, oh...
You know
it's hard to say
'cause it's me and it's...
Comedy is so subjective, you know
But I guess if I had to say in one word
I'd describe it as like, "Game Changer"
Oh, that's two words,
what am I saying?
Mind Blowing
That's two words again, God!
Okay, I'm gonna have
to describe it in two words...
Great job, Sarah
Hey!
Subtitled by: Image Production House