Climb!
Yes, sir!
Hibito.
We need to conduct an in-depth investigation.
I hear and obey, Mu-chan.
An older brother...
must always walk in front of his little brother.
July 9, 10:01 PM.
Discovered a Japanese tree frog in the grass behind the bamboo shoots near the Metro.
Mu-chan...
Mu-chan!
What are you doing?!
Mu-chan, over there!
What?
Hurry up!
What is it?
That, that!
What is that?!
I don't know.
It's flying to the Moon!
Hey, Mu-chan...
Yes?
I...
I've made up my mind.
I’m going to become an astronaut and fly to the Moon.
Huh?
Mu-chan, how about you?
Me?
I...
I think...
UCHUU KYOUDAI
SPACE BROTHERS
This fall, mission CES-51...
will leave for the Moon.
Our mission is to establish a habitable environment.
It'll make longer stays on the Moon possible.
As you know, the necessary modules and equipment have already been transported.
We are now ready,
to take the first real steps towards terraforming the Moon.
With the ability to stay there for an extended period of time,
the chances of an alien encounter is sure to increase too, wouldn't you say, Captain?
That kind of question really should go to him. He's the expert.
Who? Me?
Well...
You are right, I saw an UFO when I was a boy...
Please. Don't hold the microphone.
Sorry.
That was just like the sound the UFO used to communicate.
No worries.
Anyway, of course the UFO I saw when I was a boy is one of the reasons I am here today.
But, on the Moon, I will be focused on our mission.
That's certain.
Here.
Mr. Hibito Namba.
On Japan's National Day, what would you say about becoming the first Japanese to land on the Moon?
Yes.
The Japanese are particularly reverent about the Moon.
On behalf of my province, I am very proud.
However, when I land on the Moon, then
I'll find the words to tell you. Now is not the time. Apologies.
This model is completely overturned. I’m baffled.
What's really the reason for this?
The performance and specifications of the design are optimal.
This is rotten, we have our hands tied compared to Namba's predecessors.
Namba,
your predecessors spent a whole five years on this design.
Well gentleman, do not pity me.
I was born on the cursed day known as the Agony of Doha.
The curse even extends to having a boss of limited flexibility and imagination!
The United States gives you head space to innovate...
The astronauts are so young these days.
You don't know?
About Hibito Namba?
Although it's a secret.
The fact is that...
No way!
They're nothing alike!
What's the gossip?
What the hell is going on?
What is this?
The aerospace industry is simply a waste of the national budget.
Reads like a hippie propaganda piece.
Look at their idiotic smiles.
While they're playing Rocket-man, Japan's international competitiveness has stagnated.
Is it really necessary to go to the Moon?
This is the result of ill thought out plans from such a degenerate era.
These astronauts serve us better by being fireworks.
Director!
You're fired!
What's your problem? Get the hell out!
It hurts!
Dammit, it hurts!
Ah crap... I’m really screwed...
31 years old, Mutta Namba.
I used to work in a concept car design company as a project team leader.
I'll be there in 5 minutes.
The design philosophy is contained in the TK-11.
The crappy boss slandered my name to the entire industry,
making it difficult to find employment.
31 years olds aren't really spring chickens.
I understand.
What's with the funny afro?
It also doesn't help when I’ve inherited mom's quirks.
Thanks. Hear from you soon.
Happy birthday to me.
Where's Mutta?
Upstairs.
In the end...
What am I doing with my life?
Mutta.
What?
What are you doing?
I brought you cake.
Hey...
The acute angle is a little too narrow.
The eldest son should work harder than the father.
I'll find a job soon.
You've got to try harder!
Mutta, the unemployed.
You've got mail.
JAXA?
Why would JAXA send me a letter?
Hello.
He-llo?
Ah, Mu-chan, long time no talk.
So, how's it going?
I've got nothing.
Ah, could it be that they've screened your material?
Congratulations.
Just in time. Perfect.
Man, after five years, they just fired you. That sucks.
You're better than them, Mu-chan.
So it really was you, out of the blue.
You're destined for better things, Mu-chan.
Why did you do it?
What? I can't hear you.
I said, why this extra thing?
I know I’m a vagrant at the moment.
But being accepted to undergo astronaut exams is not funny.
Who's being funny?
Hey...
So...
I’m into vehicle development.
I've been doing it for almost ten years.
You know what I mean?
Cut the bullshit.
All in all.
Floating in the sky for work is your specialty.
My feet are firmly grounded.
You don't have to worry about me.
You've totally forgotten.
Our promise.
Promise?
Well, all right.
Do me a favor and listen to the tape of July 9, 2006.
Huh?
- Bye-bye.
Hey, wait...
Let's go!
Really, telling me to do stuff out of the blue.
July 9, 10:01 PM.
Discovered a Japanese tree frog in the grass behind the bamboo shoots near the Metro.
Mu-chan, over there!
What's the matter with the recording?
Could it be?
Coincidence?
Hey, Mu-chan.
I...
I've made up my mind. I’m going to become an astronaut and fly to the Moon.
Huh?
Mu-chan, how about you?
Me?
I...
I think...
If you’re going to the Moon,
then I would definitely have to go further!
I'm going to Mars!
Amazingly ambitious, Mu-chan!
There has to be a day
when the two of us become astronauts
and explore the universe together!
An excellent idea, Mu-chan!
Then, that will be our promise.
I used to want to become an astronaut.
We used to go to lectures every day and fill our heads with the universe.
But, one day, I realized...
Only a small number of exceptionally talented people could be accepted.
Being completely ordinary, it was practically impossible for me.
This realization made me run straight back.
I made peace with myself
and decided to strive for something a little more realistic.
Hurry, Hibito!
We have to photograph the UFO!
Yeah! UFO! UFO!
But...
UFO! UFO! UFO!
I actually...
I actually regret... not pursuing my dream.
Welcome.
Thank you everyone for participating in JAXA's Junior Tour.
Thank you "everyone".
Ha, that's including the lady up there.
Firstly, how about we start off with a little history about JAXA's Space Center.
The Tsukuba Space Center covers an area of 530,000 square meters.
That's equivalent to an area covering 12 Tokyo Domes.
In addition...
JAXA also has pilot training facilities in the International Space Station (ISS).
Japan plays a significant role in commanding and maintaining many cabins and facilities in the ISS.
Hey, who are the afro kid and the spiky kid?
They come all the time.
Next, please watch the history of space travel developed by VTR.
Okay.
Hey, you are not allowed to record in here!
But Miss, we want to be good knowledgeable adults.
Perhaps, one day, we could even help JAXA.
Please, let us record it.
OK, just this one time. But don't tell anyone.
Great!
Oh, Yuri Gagarin.
Assist JAXA? What a joke.
With their attitudes, I’m certain they can become astronauts.
Yes.
I think that one must be physically and mentally resilient to become an astronaut.
I’m fit and learn quickly. If selected, I will give my all, for JAXA.
I stand corrected; for the world and the National Space Development Agency.
Good. Time's almost up.
If there are no other questions...
Forgive me, I have one more question.
I don't mean to be the bad guy but...
Hibito Namba is your brother.
He's considered extremely talented and charismatic.
It seems that you're trying to catch up. How do you see this playing out in the media?
Yes, in that regard.
I was certain people would ask me so I spent three days and nights thinking about an answer.
I wrote my answer down.
If it pleases you, may I read it?
Sadly, time escapes us.
Allow me to recommend a more efficient way of doing this.
That's a tad harsh, no?
The answers are a bit...
It goes against Japanese values.
He's filled with a sense of inferiority compared to his brother? Hmm...
Seems to be that he's running out of patience.
Wait.
The facts.
The bolt on the chair is tight again.
What's going on, Hoshika?
In the morning I loosened the screw.
I pulled a little NASA prank.
I assumed this would go unnoticed by the participants.
During the interview, he was fiddling with the screw.
Hmm, short attention span.
Or you could interpret it as...
An excellent instinct for machinery.
Wouldn't you agree?
I tip my hat to you, Mr. Suit.
Aerospace research and development institutions.
Commonly known as JAXA.
After a lapse of five years, they placed an ad for recruitment.
They managed to attract a total of 789 people; me included.
Through interviewing the applicants, they culled the numbers down to 45 people.
Now, we're into the second round of exams.
Good. Stop calculating.
Next, please wear the oxygen mask.
Excuse me.
That's...
I’m sorry, I’m a little nervous.
No problem.
Twenty-seven thousand feet above sea level.
Twenty-eight thousand feet above sea level.
That's him.
My name is Mutta Namba.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you Mutta Namba?
Yes.
Your brother is Hibito Namba, the astronaut, right?
He's the brother of Hibito Namba?!
You didn't know?
He's a very well-known candidate.
I see.
I see, indeed.
Being the brother of the first Japanese going to the Moon is a big deal.
It's no big deal.
Must be nice to have an advantage.
You must have had some really handy tips on the exam content.
Your brother could probably influence the examiners.
He would do no such thing.
How naive do you think we are?
This conversation is a bit rude.
In addition, I don't think these exams are easy.
You should play your games elsewhere.
Right? Mutta Namba.
My name is Makabe Kenji. I'm 31 years old. Nice to meet you.
We're the same age. Nice to meet you too.
Hey, Mu-kun.
Do you think that at this stage the best scores...
Belong to the two impertinent youngsters?
No, I think it's the lady.
Good call.
Serika Itou is her name.
Her physical fitness and English speech was ranked highly.
I think the examiners hold her in high regards.
Impressive!
Anyway,
after the little breathing exercise, I suspect only 6-7 participants are left.
Talk about brutal.
Hey, Kenji.
Yeah?
How did you answer "that" question?
Which one?
The second interview.
"Tell us something new you've discovered about yourself"?
Oh, a tricky one.
It's like coming across a book I’ve never read.
A simple fictional storybook.
However, when you read it with your two year old daughter,
you feel an opportunity to create something wonderful,
regardless of the story, you really start to get into it.
In short, as long as you're reading without prejudice.
The story and the task will bring new stimulation, perspective and experience.
I found the selection process to be very similar to this.
Mu-kun, how did you answer it?
Well...
It was quite tricky.
Something new you've discovered about yourself?
That using shampoo significantly reduces the itch on the scalp.
See you later.
It's like being rejected by a girl.
Farewell, JAXA.
Speak of the devil.
Hello.
Hello Mu-chan, how goes the second round?
I think it's making my scalp itch.
How do you mean?
I’m sure you did well.
Well... ah...
If I fall, I shall rise again to fight twice as hard!
Admirable words, Mu-chan.
Hey, do you want to come to NASA?
Huh, NASA?
Yeah, NASA.
So, this must be the famous Apo.
Yes.
A spiritual place.
Welcome to the sacred grounds.
You're living quite well.
Well...
I'm only renting, so it may not feel the same as our home in Japan.
What's up?
Nothing.
Was Apo's name taken from the Apollo missions?
Hey, Pup.
Yes.
It must be nice,
to grow up with such little stress.
A life untouched by the hands of a tragedian.
Let's hope so.
Apo, the adorable.
Hey... hey, come on.
The curtains are unhooked.
Twilight drops her curtain down, and pins it with a star.
What's this?
On the plus side, your saving on the water bill.
Hey, the price tag is still on this.
All fixed.
Very observant of you to instantly detect the defects, Mu-chan.
You're too sloppy.
Unbelievable,
this guy is going to the Moon in week and yet neglects his chores.
Mu-chan.
Heads up.
Impressive.
It's beautiful out here.
All you need now is a blond bombshell of a girlfriend.
Love to but I’ve got no time to spare.
Such is life.
How many years has it been since when we last observed the skies.
Who knows.
What are you doing?
Imitating Tom Hanks.
He did it in Apollo 13.
Oh yeah, right!
Three hundred eighty-four thousand kilometers from the Earth.
It's not a walk to the corner shop.
I can't believe my little brother is actually going.
It must be an incredible feeling.
What are you talking about? You sound as if you didn't do too well in the exams, Mu-chan.
Well...
To tell you the truth,
I’m predicting the demise of my space career.
In hindsight, there were things I could have done better.
As of late, I predict the probability of my going to the Moon
to be less than 1/384,000.
You may not realize.
But my space travel ambitions diverted years ago.
I’m beginning to suspect my fate has further distance itself from the Moon.
Enough of that, Mu-chan.
Let me find the words.
Hmm...
You're strong.
But you don't seem to realize how strong you really are.
As a child.
What are you talking about?
The topics we had as kids are not the same as now.
Just listen.
You know, I’m here now...
because of you, Mu-chan.
You've been pushing me for 19 years.
The two of us observing the night sky.
I know.
You're asking for a beating.
Our classmates have been saying that you've seen a UFO.
They said you were bragging out loud with your afro swinging back and forth.
It's a lie, right?
Hurry up and answer!
I was...
Say it already.
Was it not my friend who was talking about the UFO? I think there was a miscommunication...
I...
Mu-chan, you coming out?
Not today.
Why not? We've got to take a photo of the UFO to prove it to our classmates.
There's a chance our classmates will still not believe.
But... a photo doesn't lie.
Listen, Hibito.
On Japan’s national day, we undoubtedly saw a UFO.
Yes, I concur.
Hold this belief, tightly, in your heart.
Okay?
Okay.
15 minutes before depressurization.
The depressurized environment is stable. Get ready to work.
We have a vacuum.
A vacuum is formed.
Okay, Hibito, Buddy.
Let's start the oxygen supply simulation.
Copy.
Checking Buddy's EMU operational conditions.
Main tank: Empty.
Back up tank: 2 minutes worth of oxygen remaining.
Attempting connections between the two EMU's.
Okay, connect it from blue to red.
Dammit!
What's this?
This is...
Although I am reluctant,
NASA has advised us to complete our will as part of protocol.
I want to tell to Mu-chan one thing.
It took me 19 years to reach my goal.
I am certain that you'll fly, too, Mu-chan.
Unfortunately,
it's seems I've died before you got this message.
But, Mu-chan...
even in death...
I'll be waiting in space for your arrival,
so that we can see the stars together again.
Hibito.
Today, we're about to witness a true leap for mankind.
As everybody knows on the surface of the Moon, there is no air or water and certainly no chance of survival.
The challenge of building any kind of Moon base is probably the most ambitious project in the history of science.
In this mission, all our eyes are on Hibito Namba.
The samurai boy will be the youngest person ever to walk on the Moon and Japan's first.
On this beautiful day in Florida, we are now together, the people here, in Japan and all over the world...
Excuse me, excuse me.
Mutta!
Mutta! Mutta! Mutta!
Hey hey, he told me to tell you that this spot is the best for the interview.
Isn't that great, honey?!
Hibito!
You are famous now.
Thank you.
Sorry, apologies.
Hibito!
Dad, mom, I'll be back soon!
You're going to be 11 stones on the Moon! Eat well!
Don't forget it!
Please, look after Apo!
Apo's a good dog!
You're embarrassing us, dad.
Mu-chan, don't forget.
Forget?
Of course I won't forget!
So...
I’m just giving you a head start. I'll see you in space. Believe it!
Don't chip your tooth whilst on the ride!
100% for style.
My brother.
Right, Apo?
Dad, where's Apo?
Apo, Apo!
Apo!
My dog!
Hibito!
Hibito, we'll take care of everything!
Apo!
Wait for me!
What are you doing?
Apo.
Wait, Apo!
Give me a break.
What's with the sudden walk! Let's go!
Hey, you!
Come up here broccoli!
Don't just stand there.
You want to see the lift off, right?
Climb up the ladder, there.
What the hell?
Mister!
Old man,
I'm very sorry.
I don't have time to hang out with you.
Just a minute
You know we live one life.
You can't play around with two.
You follow me, broccoli?
Now look at what you can see.
Amazing!
This used to be the control tower way back, before the Apollo missions.
In the beginning, it was just small unmanned rockets.
You just made a choice you'll never regret.
My little brother is in there.
But I... I have so many different feelings.
I just don't know how I should look up at that rocket.
I've been feeling everything, looking at that guy.
So kid, tell me, that big rocket over there.
You know what powers it? What lifts it up?
The heart of the people. That's real power.
It's the courage of the astronauts. Every rocket and every single mission,
so full of passion and determination. And then, all the tireless people on the ground.
Every single one of them, an expert.
So proud. So full of knowledge
Then think of all of those people out there watching.
Full of hope and prayer. Respect.
That's what ignites. That's what catches fire inside and then explodes
and lifts that 2000 tonnes of metal into space.
So that thing that's bothering you, it's stirring inside. That confusion.
Well it's just helping lift that rocket a little higher.
Do you feel better?
I don't know.
Thanks, I guess.
So... who are you?
I’m just an old man who took a stroll on the Moon a long long time ago.
Enough of that, it's about to lift off.
T minus 20 seconds and counting.
18... 17... 16...
15... 14... 13...
12... 11... 10...
9... 8... 7... 6...
Main engine start.
4...
3...
2...
1...
And we have lift off!
Go...
Go!
Congratulations...
Hibito.
Deneb, this is Houston.
2 minutes and all is going swift and smoothly.
Roger. Ready for SRB seperation, over.
Roger.
Clear.
EDS to manual.
LES set.
Third phase has been set. Brace yourselves, guys.
Second engine cleared.
Okay guys, are you ready?
This is it.
Alright, let's do it!
Welcome to space, Hibito.
Into...
outer space.
Out of this world.
Okay everybody, let's go to the Moon!
Hoshika, it's over.
I don't think so.
Sawaki seems to have 2 more votes than Namba.
The discussion is over.
It's just two votes. The candidates should be discussed further.
Two additional votes is still a majority.
Our data also highlights the strengths and weaknesses of each candidate.
Values processed by the computer doesn't guarantee the better candidate.
After all, a program is limited by what it cannot measure, right?
Are you suggesting the programs we have used are all for naught?
Why are you so obsessed with Namba?
It's something I can't clearly articulate...
But it's almost destiny that it should happen.
Imagine, two brothers in space.
Pardon the intrusion,
but I vote for him.
From my experience, Hibito's passion for space is insurmountable.
As a child, he and Mutta would attend all of JAXA's presentations.
Also, imagine the world's first space brothers,
exploring the Moon together; I vote for Mutta!
All the way!
Hey hey...
Sadly, she's not apart of this committee.
Indeed. Ms. Yuan does not have the right to vote.
Okay Hibito, it's rolling.
You ready?
This is going out all over Japan.
You'd better look cool coming down that ladder.
That's one small step for man. One giant leap for mankind.
Neil Armstrong proclaimed those famous words when he was on the Moon 56 years ago.
Since ancient times, the Moon has held great reverence to the Japanese...
I can't believe it...
I've got to tell him the good news.
It's starting.
Why is this camera so slow?!
Apo seems optimistic about the news.
You can use it as it is. Image reception is still good.
Copy.
Awesome!
Okay!
Yay!
Look at him go!
Wait wait wait...
Hell of an entrance. Yeah!
Hibito's first step is well received.
On the day of the first Japanese to land on the Moon, his entrance could be described as energetic and youthful.
A bold entrance!
What was that?
Our very own lunar rabbit is hopping around.
Excellent. Excellent!
Excellent!
Kenji Makabe (31)
Serika Itou (26)
Yamato Mizoguchi (28)
Naoto Fukuda (54)
Yasushi Furuya (30)
Mutta Namba (31)
Please, enter.
Incredible.
Hey, check it out.
It's obviously a sealed environment but there are windows.
A nice touch.
We're now floating in space.
Yes, where there's a lack of oxygen and gravity.
You sound like a talkative fellow. And you wear your heart on your sleeve, too.
Furuya's the name.
We should be cautious of what we say.
This is an exam.
Our actions will be monitored by the command center.
That includes what we say.
The test has begun.
Please.
Let's give them the first challenge.
I concur.
Your attention, please.
Please observe the screen.
This cabin is self sufficient and it is designed for long term space travel.
You will spend ten days in here and undergo numerous tasks.
A careful note, the air pressure in this cabin is set at 0.8 atm.
Please pay attention to any abnormal physical conditions.
The wrist bracelet you are wearing must never be removed.
Consider it a lucky charm imbued with the power to guarantee your safety.
What the hell is this?
It's recording our physiology
and allows them insight into our psychology.
Lastly,
you will vote for the top three candidates at the end of this exercise.
Only three will be able to pass.
During your stay you will be given free time.
Feel free to spend it any way you like.
Hey, what the hell is this? We're being observed like chimps!
Guess that's the instructions.
Let's formally introduce ourselves.
Okay!
An exceptional idea.
By understanding each other, we can function better as a team.
Let's start with Mizoguchi...
It doesn't matter.
Makabe-san...
Yes?
I'm not here to play games and make friends.
I thought we all had an opportunity to win.
He has a point.
Do I look a little pale?
Delicious.
What's up?
Thanks for the meal.
That was fast.
A friendly reminder.
You have 15 minutes to complete breakfast.
At 0730 please be prepared to receive instructions on today's task. End of announcement.
A day in the confined capsule of M8,
directives are being issued every 15 minutes.
Talk about micro management.
Dude, it's all white!
This puzzle is sadistic.
Logical thinking, spatial cognition, reasoning analysis, they're all being tested.
Eat. Sleep. Work.
It seems we're all keeping to ourselves.
What a dreary state of affair.
It seems the rules and tasks are intended to foster competition.
Our results for each task were also recorded.
It's taxing my eyes.
I know what you mean.
Oh crap, I lost my position.
Dammit...
The most unbearable task is the log at the end of the day.
Good night.
I'll turn off the lights.
Okay.
Let's see. Log column.
I suspect the most intense moment will be when we have to collate the scores.
A group battle?
Group A, please to work with you.
Likewise.
Pleased to be working with you.
Let's work hard together.
Likewise.
Try your best!
I will.
What surprises are installed for us this time?
What's inside?
Let's open it and see.
Yes, let's open it!
What the...
Hey, what's this?
Model kits?
There are heaps.
Looks like fun.
Today's task is as follows.
As a group, design a 2035 lunar surface facility.
Please draw on technical experience and imagination.
The facility is designed to last over ten years.
In addition, write an instruction manual for your design.
Be prepared to dedicate 1 to 4 hours a day on this task.
On the last day, you will be asked to give a speech on the designs.
Firstly,
let's have a look at our inventory.
Let's do it.
We'll leave the box on the side of this table.
Good.
A lunar surface facility, they say...
I’m a little excited by this assignment.
Agreed!
Let's work together and make the best lunar surface facility!
Okay!
Houston. Houston. This is Hibito.
KU activated, power unit exchanged.
Now complete.
Roger that. Hibito, always at full throttle.
It's just that I really enjoy this.
I've spent five years training for this moment.
I hear you.
The whole time we did emergency simulations, man!
You know, I hope we get lost in space or something,
that way, I can really test my skills.
Come on, Buddy. Bad joke!
Yeah, of course it's a bad joke.
The gravity up here makes it a real possibility.
Yeah!
Yes.
You've got to hurry up and see the scenery.
Fukuda's meditating.
It's been a week.
The physiological readings are showing differences bit by bit.
Must be tough to live with strangers for 24/7.
Let's not forget living through a heavily regimented routine.
Stress was likely to build up.
Communication is the key component.
It was no mistake I was unsuccessful in my attempt.
20 years ago, I was a touch too sensitive. Strange how we change.
True that. Age and experience brings control.
Regardless of the circumstances, I’m going to sleep well tonight with a clear conscious.
The basic requirements for an astronaut cannot be measured with absolute certainty using test papers.
Good to see an elevated level of stress in the capsule. Who's going to crack first?
From studying the six candidates.
I'm getting a sense on who would work well in teams.
We're almost out of time.
Time to play the green cards.
Yes.
For today, the diagnostic ends.
Good night.
Thank you.
Just a moment, Namba-kun.
This is Hoshika.
Yes?
There's a question I want you to answer.
Okay.
Rest assured, everyone will eventually be asked to do this.
Feel free to cut loose and state what is on your mind.
Who do you think is suitable to become an astronaut?
Answer with your gut instinct.
The most suitable person is...
Kenji Makabe and...
Serika Itou.
A combination of both would be perfect.
Makabe-kun conducts himself with impeccable excellence.
His weakness resides in respecting the views of others too much.
He has a natural ability to lead. Extremely trust worthy
As for the next...
Itou-san, her beauty aside,
she has a ravenous appetite but knows how to get people to act.
Despite being the only female, she doesn't feel out of place nor is she easily irritated, if at all.
The group works well together because of her cheerful disposition.
Now, let's work.
Scary.
But...
One moment...
How to put this...
It would appear,
in my opinion,
each person has their own charm.
Mr. Fukuda,
may look a little frail,
but he is, in fact, in good health.
After all, he did not come last in the squat exercises.
As for Mizoguchi-kun...
The first impression he gave was rather frosty.
If you look at his t-shirts, you'd realize he's a Gundam fan.
Perhaps he's putting up a front like a character from the show.
Furuya-kun is...
He's interesting.
He may appear to be very opinionated,
probably because he comes from Kansai.
However, he is extremely meticulous,
very clean by nature.
Thanks to him, the cabin is spotless.
Guess there's a lot of positive traits to consider.
In the end,
everyone has something that'll make them a suitable astronaut.
I see.
This may be slightly embarrassing...
But what everyone here has in common is a strong desire to go to space.
Especially me.
Got it, most appreciated.
Okay.
Allow me to give you a personal message.
Mutta Namba-kun,
you will receive a green card.
Everyone come here now!
Who would do this?
I’m wondering that myself.
Could it be one of the crew members?
Undoubtedly, it was from someone standing here.
There are six members,
most likely, it was someone from group B.
Are you suspecting me?
I can assure you, I’m innocent.
It's certainly not me.
and it's extremely unlikely it's Mr. Fukuda.
What are your thoughts?
How quick group B are to defend each other.
Don't joke around.
If you're going to accuse us you should, at least, show some evidence.
Evidence?
Only our group's work was irrevocably damaged but group B's project remained miraculously safe.
A rather interesting point to consider, don't you think?
Hell, even a child could figure this one out.
Despite that, you're still mistaken.
There's only so much bullshit I can take!
Relax relax relax!
Let's cease this futile argument!
Guys, you've got to cool down!
I'm calm!
Furuya-san, let's just cool off first.
Itou-san is good to speak.
A week's worth of work, completely trampled.
Hey, why don't you pipe up!
Well...
I guess...
There's no point crying over spilled milk.
Our only option is to rebuild it.
Funny how exam conditions makes everyone so wholesome.
Hey...
I'll never forgive the scumbag who would stoop so low!
That's the only consolation I have.
Why put me in such a compromised position?
Good morning, Mu-kun.
Oh, good morning, Kenji.
Thanks.
Today's the end.
True.
Hey, Mu-kun.
Do you think it's someone who undermined their own project?
No idea.
Absolutely no idea.
Oh, I see.
Perhaps if the underminers should meet,
they should shake hands.
Group B's project has been vandalized.
Merciless. Utterly merciless.
How is this so?
Based on yesterday's logic, it must be retaliation from group A.
No doubt, Furuya.
What did you say?
Don't deny it!
Venting your anger. Vengeance is yours, right!
I see.
One has to explore all the possibilities.
Are you that bitter and self-centered that you had to do this?
You're calling me self-centered, hypocrite.
Let's stop this, guys!
It's even be possible that the true culprit may not be from A or B.
There are six of us in this team.
Stepping in to play hero again, Makabe-san?
Whether playing team leader or judge, you just want power.
I never agreed that you were the head of our group.
I...
I never realized.
You keep to yourself and become a lone rebel.
You're too immature to become an astronaut.
Right back at you, shorty.
Doesn't matter how many times I see this,
it's amazing.
Could we see similar things on the Earth if there were no air?
Like this? Sure.
But my eyes are getting pretty tired.
Those mountains over there, they are so clear.
Well, if your eyes are tired,
I'll wake you up with my U-F-O story.
Maybe I’m tired of hearing Hibito's UFO story, too.
I know. But people say, my UFO story sounds better on the Moon.
Alright, alright. I'll listen to it.
But once we found the lost lunar probe, okay?
Okay.
I'll look for the probe using the manual. Where is it?
It's in the box under your seat.
Oh, thank you.
Damian, stop!
What!
Mutta Namba-san, please report to the video phone room.
Namba-kun.
Yes?
Please remain calm and listen.
While on a lunar rover assignment, Hibito-kun may have had an accident.
We've lost contact with him and his partner.
NASA and JAXA are pulling their resources together to find them.
The intelligence is scant.
We are currently reviewing our satellites to get more detail about the situation.
That's the emergency.
My apologies for interrupting your exam.
If you pull out of the exam, your results will not be affected.
The choice to stay in the capsule or not
is yours.
Do not think of the worst.
If it's any comfort,
JAXA is well prepared for dealing with this type of scenario.
Namba-kun...
I don't know what to say.
I can imagine.
The suits they're wearing should keep them alive for 3 nights, at least.
We'll be working closely with Houston on this.
I'll stay on.
Are you sure?
I...
I'll complete this exam.
Besides,
even If I leave,
there is nothing I can do.
I'm powerless to do anything.
As it stands,
I can't even get into space, yet.
I understand and respect your choice.
This matter must not be revealed to the other candidates.
We will continue with the capsule test.
Understood?
Yes.
Are you okay, Mr. Fukuda?
I’m just a little dizzy.
I need to rest a little bit.
Hang in there, the exam is almost finished.
Don't let Mr. Fukuda rest.
After all, you cannot present work that's accidentally broken.
Now's not the time, Mizoguchi-kun.
Oh look, the team leader has now become the teacher.
Knock it off guys.
I’m fine.
You should rest.
It's okay.
Time's up.
Group A will give the first presentation.
Game over!
Namba-san, it's finished.
Hey, can't you hear me?
Enough...
It's concluded.
It's over.
I have something to say.
Mu-kun wait...
What is it?
Nothing, Kenji.
But, don't you think it's kind of bleak...
to let it end this way?
Don't say it, Mu-kun.
Don't mention anything about the green card or you're screwed.
Everyone...
in fact, I...
Shut up!
Mu-chan, over there!
What were you going to say?
I...
I once saw a UFO.
You saw a UFO?
It was on Japan’s national day that I saw it with my little brother.
How can I describe it...
It was round like this and flew ultra-fast in zig-zag.
Kind of like a fire fly on steroids. It then flew to the Moon and disappeared.
What are you ranting about this time?
After that, I fell in love with space.
I would often go to JAXA with my brother to watch the ISS.
As long as we looked up, we could probably see it again.
But...
a short time after,
when I started talking about the UFO with my classmates, they branded me a liar.
My point is...
I guess I really enjoyed this exam.
It was hard,
but it was nice to share this experience
with people who have a similar passion.
People who are enthusiastic about astronomy.
We...
We gel well through our love for space.
I’m sorry.
You know.
I also grew up being heralded as Frankenstein by my classmates.
As a kid, I use to observe the ISS with my dad.
I always hoped to come across aliens, too. Good memories.
That's a nice story, Serika-san.
Yeah.
In fact, I came here with the intention of becoming an astronaut.
As I wish to conduct medical research on the ISS.
Some drugs are easier to produce in space due to weightlessness.
Who knows, the drugs produced may even save many people.
Unfortunately, it was too late for my dad.
I see.
I want to go to Mars.
Oh, why?
A whole lot of reasons.
The challenge, the discoveries, the adventure. But overall,
its bigness.
But Mars is smaller than Earth.
Yet when we get there,
we would see how Mount Olympus is 3 times taller than Everest.
In addition, Valles Marineris would make the Grand Canyon comparable to a crack on the road.
A landscape of red hues. I've got to see it in this life time.
I understand this simple mood.
Of course, we can't just ignore our desires and give up.
Unlike everyone else, I’ve attempted becoming an astronaut twice.
It was probably 20 years and 5 years ago
that I also participated in the astronaut selection test.
I've never made it this far before.
But,
really,
I've always wanted to go to space.
A dream I’ve harbored since I was a child.
I used to work so hard, I’d neglect my family.
Eventually, my family just got up and left.
Now, I’m 54 years old.
Even facing death, I will not renounce my desire.
You still have a chance. John Glenn was 77 years old when he went to space.
So 54 years is young in comparison.
Mizoguchi-kun.
Thank you.
We understand, Namba.
You're here because you saw some stupid UFO as a kid,
you fluffy hair bastard. Hendrix called, he wants his hair back.
Despite going through his own personal adversity, he can do this?
Perhaps it's the adversity that's motivating him.
Think what you want.
This guy is incredible.
Please,
be safe right there, Hibito-kun.
Damian...
Houston. Houston. This is Hibito.
Houston. Houston!
Dammit!
News from Houston.
They've detected flair lights from within a canyon.
Get the maps up and send it to the main display.
Understood.
Here?
The deepest part of the crater?
Not good.
Hopefully, the thermoregulation on their suits is okay.
But being at the bottom of the crater is not good.
In about an hour’s time, it's going to be -60 degrees Celsius.
Estimated time to destination: approximately 50 minutes.
They're at the bottom of that crater and no sun...
We've got to keep going!
Buddy, stay cool.
Focus, okay? We're doing everything we can.
Damian!
Damian...
I can do it.
We're going back, Damian.
Wow, it's dazzling.
Congratulations.
Okay, next is the final interview.
But, before that, please enjoy the sun.
Applause for the candidates.
You soldiered on well.
Congratulations.
Must be hell being so far.
You did well.
Very good.
It was hard.
Please, take a seat.
Sure.
Namba-kun.
10 days. It must have been tough.
Must have been.
Thanks.
In this final interview, we are only prepared to through with it, if you're okay.
Yes.
We don't want to place any unnecessary stress on you.
I am ready.
All astronauts have to confront this challenge.
Namba-kun...
Are you prepared to die?
Mu-chan...
I'm sorry...
And that's...
That's my answer.
I understand.
That's all.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry but...
I lied.
In fact,
I don't want to die.
I don't.
Regarding...
Regarding your question on life and death,
I would try to live every last second.
Until the very end,
I would try my hardest to live.
I shall replace your answer
at the conclusion of this test.
I...
Thank you.
Let me conclude this test
by showing my gratitude
for my brother and I.
Hibito.
You've watched over us since we were kids.
But,
I've been a hopeless big brother.
I have kept a promise to my brother.
I've seen the test through to the end.
Really,
thank you very much.
Looks like I'm having a déjà vu.
Five years ago,
I assessed your brother, too.
You guys really are brothers.
Yes.
Please, follow me to the control room.
Sure.
Hey, wait...
Bastard...
Bastard!
Passing this...
Passing this can't save your life!
Hibito.
You're not going to be a tragic story.
You're not allowed to die!
Hibito...
Hibito, hey...
Hibito, there's an UFO.
Where?
Just kidding.
What the heck, Mu-chan. I thought it finally appeared.
How'd you sleep, Hibito?
I was just resting my eyes.
Well then, let's play a game, yes?
Yeah!
Space quiz!
Yay!
Gorgeous!
Mu-chan...
If I don't try...
I'll die.
The next space question is as follows.
Yay!
What was the biggest space news in 1961?
Hmm...
Gagarin makes it to space.
Correct!
What about 1969?
Hmm...
Apollo 11 landing on the Moon.
Hey Mu-chan, give me an easier one.
Then, what happened in 1993?
No idea, how about a clue?
The Doha tragedy.
That's when you were born, Mu-chan.
That's correct!
That's the year when the future astronaut Mutta Namba was born.
Next one, what happened in 1996?
Easy, that's the year when the future astronaut Hibito Namba was born!
We choose to go to the Moon.
We choose to go to the Moon!
That's one small step for man.
One giant leap for mankind.
America's first space shuttle.
The shuttle has cleared the tower.
What's it like to work out there,
maneuvering freely in space?
Well, we've had a great deal of training,
sir, so it feels quite comfortable.
Station, from Endeavour...
Yuri Gagarin.
John F. Kennedy.
Neil Armstrong.
Names forever synonymous
with man's greatest
achievements in
space exploration.
Could they have imagined this day?
The day in which two little boys from
Japan, inspired by those legendary men,
became the first brothers in
history to set foot on the Moon.
Hibito Namba, who miraculously returned to Earth from the Moon five years ago,
and his brother, Mutta Namba, who
finally earned his ticket into space today.
Have encouraged and inspired each
other to make their dreams come true.
We are now about to
witness these two brothers
pick up the banner from their
heroes and begin a new chapter
in the history of the space program.
Hibito.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
No problem.
It's time for space!
They're going to launch in 2 minutes!
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
This is Houston.
How's it going, Space Brothers?
One, two, in!
Mu-chan, quick, look at that!
★ COLDPLAY
♪ Every teardrop is a waterfall
♪ I turn the music up, I got my records on
♪ I shut the world outside until the lights come on
♪ Maybe the streets alight, maybe the trees are gone
♪ I feel my heart start beating to my favorite song
♪ And all the kids they dance, all the kids all night
♪ Until Monday morning feels another life
♪ I turn the music up, I'm on a roll this time
♪ And heaven is in sight~
♪ I turn the music up, I got my records on
♪ From underneath the rubble sing a rebel song
♪ Don't want to see another generation drop
♪ I'd rather be a comma than a full stop
♪ Maybe I'm in the black, maybe I'm on my knees
♪ Maybe I'm in the gap between the two trapezes
♪ But my heart is beating and my pulses start
♪ Cathedrals in my heart~
♪ As we saw~
★ oh, this light~
♪ I swear you,
★ emerge blinking into
★ to tell me it's alright~
♪ I swear you,
♪ As we soar~
★ walls~,
♪ Every siren is a symphony
♪And every tear's a waterfall
♪ Is a waterfall...
♪ Oh...
♪ Oh oh oh...
♪ Is a waterfall...
♪ Is a Is a waterfall...
♪ Every tear...
♪ Oh oh oh...
♪ Is a Is a waterfall...
♪ So you can hurt~,
★ hurt me bad~
♪ But still I'll raise~
★ the flag~
♪ It was a wa wa wa wa wa-aterfall
♪ A wa wa wa wa wa-aterfall
♪ Oh yeah...
♪ Every tear...
★ Every tear...
♪ Oh yeah...
★ Oh yeah...
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
♪ Oh yeah...
★ Every teardrop is waterfall
★ Oh yeah...
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
♪ Oh yeah...
★ Every tear...
★ Every teardrop is waterfall
♪ Oh oh...
♪ Every tear...
★ Every tear...
★ Every teardrop is waterfall
♪ Oh oh...
♪ Every tear...
★ Every tear...
♪ Oh oh...
★ Oh yeah...
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
♪ Oh oh...
★ Every teardrop is a waterfall
★ Oh yeah...
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
♪ Oh oh...
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
★ Every teardrop is a waterfall
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
★ Every teardrop is a waterfall
★ Every tear...
♪ Every tear...
SPACE BROTHERS
UCHUU KYOUDAI
★ Translation: Anonymous & Ryuka
★ Editing: Ryuka
★ Timing: Anonymous & Ryuka
★ Karaoke: Ryuka
★ Additional work: M74