"I mean, you must understand that
he is in every sense of the word"
"a gilt-edged investment."
"I mean, he is
the most important personality"
"of the entire history
of show business,"
"and therefore, he has to be
watched very carefully indeed."
Give it up for the star
of Yogi bear 3-D, Mr. TJ Miller.
Denver!
Oh, Denver
I'm so happy to be here. I'm...
I'm from Denver and I'm...
Yeah, why not?
Why not?
Well, we made it.
Okay.
This is the only city,
that's how great
the city of Denver is,
is the only place that
you would cheer for the city
and Denver, not only does
the cheer not die down,
it builds, and it builds
and it builds, until...
Wasn't so
friendly here, I love it.
I really love Denver, I love uh...
Yeah, I just made a decision,
not going to say
Denver again in the show.
You're such friendly people.
Yeah, we're friendly people here.
That's not the case
in Los Angeles or New York,
you know what I mean?
You'll, you'll look someone
in the eyes in Denver
and not only will you not
look away, you'll smile.
That happened to me yesterday.
This guy was walking his dog,
he just walked by me
looked me directly in the eyes
and he's like...
Like some sort of fucking Colgate
commercial or something like that,
something like that.
But I wanted to throw him a smile
back, you know what I mean?
Why not, what's that cost ya, huh?
Not a pretty penny,
not a God damn dime,
not a fucking five dollar bill,
hmm. Hmm.
So he gave me the little... yeah,
and I threw him one back,
I gave him a "Yeah!"
What's under there?
And he was like, "Under where?"
And I was like, "That's what I thought."
I bet you didn't think
you were going to see that today.
Not here,
not for this show,
not for this discerning crowd.
I mean...
I mean, this fucking city,
you know?
Have you guys been saying that?
I say it all the time.
Not, it's not about Denver,
it's just, I think it's very funny.
You ever do that? Just drink,
drink your water
from the bottle like a little
gerbil, like a hamster?
What's that, Diane? No, no,
no, I, I, I don't need an appetizer.
This fucking city is a funny thing to
say because you can say it anywhere.
I was at a yogurt store
and I, uh I was like,
"Do you guys have
chocolate sprinkles?"
And the girl was like, "No,
we only have multicolored."
And I was like, "This fucking city."
"God damn it, no, it doesn't
have anything to do with you."
"But this, this fucking city
is tearing me apart."
You gotta start saying it. Do it
to your boss on Monday.
If he gives you a new task
just be like,
"Can you
get this done by Wednesday?"
"This fucking city."
"Are you, are you upset with me?"
"No, it's not you."
"It's this God damn municipality."
Do you guys ever have nightmares?
- Yeah!
- Oh, thank you.
The last crowd,
this is real, I asked,
I said, "Do you guys
ever have nightmares?"
and they said... Nothing.
They said nothing.
You ask 2,000 people,
"Do you have nightmares?"
And they, "Mm-mm."
"Mm-mm, we don't have them,
we're just in yours."
You always want to tell people
about your nightmares.
Why do we all want to tell, because it's
a prison of your own minds' devising.
It's really a horrible thing but
it, no one wants to hear it
because it's not a linear narrative.
Right? And we're used to stories,
okay, okay,
so I had this nightmare last night,
I woke up in m-,
it was like my principal's office but
it was also my parents bedroom,
but it was neither, does that
make sense? And then suddenly
I turn around and I'm on the beach
and I'm like, "Oh my God,"
"there must be jellyfish." Because,
you know, I'm scared of jellyfish.
Do you remember? Did I tell you,
when I got stung in New Jersey?
Haven't told you that story?
You're going to love that story.
Halfway through it they're,
you know your friends are like,
"Just stop, stop, stop. Don't
tell me, I don't want to hear this."
"Just stop wasting my time. Time is
an incredibly important commodity,"
"just stop."
And I was in the middle
of telling my nightmare
to this group of people,
and this guy,
you know he was kind of like a,
kind of a douchey,
kind of a guy, I'm trying to look around
and find somebody that...
You know, look like see there's no
douche bags in Colorado that didn't...
Well, look, he looked
a little like you.
Ki-, look he had a backwards
Pro back hat on.
No, not you, sir.
The person behind you.
You look like a cool teacher.
This fucking guy had his glasses like,
like reading glasses,
bifocals perhaps.
He's got reading glasses
but he's got sunglasses
hanging from his
white button down shirt,
like just that cool teacher that's like,
"Hey, school's out."
"Let's talk, let's rap.
How are you kids doing?"
"You guys all right? yeah?"
"A lot of people wanting
to do drugs. Huh?"
"Putting on the pressure.
You take it from me, all right?"
I did cocaine in the 1990s,
alright? A lot of it. Alright?
A lot.
I ended up in a hotel,
a motor hotel room in Omaha,
coked out of my mind
after being up for eight days.
You know what
I told myself?
"God darn it,
I'm going to be a teacher,"
"and I'm going to be the coolest God
damn teacher on the face of the planet."
And I decided never to
button more than,
always will have two
or three buttons unbuttoned,
so that while I talk to you
my chest hair is distracting.
Mr. Gerlich I hate you.
Ha ha ha ha.
So, this kind of douchey
guy was just like,
"Oh, you have nightmares?
Ha ha. Hmm."
"Cause I actually ah,
I have night terrors."
I was like, "Fuck you, don't one up
me with your night, terrors."
You're like, "Oh, sorry to
hear about your bad dreams"
"about female horses. Sorry
to hear about your night-mares."
"But actually my nights,
my nights are filled with terror."
So, what I did is I went to
his house in the dead of the night
and I built a bed that was
a mirror image of his bed,
and I put the feet of the bed
together and I dressed exactly
as he was dressed in
identical sleeping garments,
and I went to sleep and I waited him
awaking from his night terror,
and then I also awoke
and mirrored
all of the things that he did.
So he was like... "ah!"
And I'm like, "Maah!"
And he's like, "Ah!"
And then I hit a button and then
all these lights from Home Depot
that I had set up just
tuf tuf tuf tuf tuf,
just flooded the room
tuf tuf tuf tuf tuf tuf,
then I went, "Which is more terrifying,
your night or my day?"
It's super expensive.
And buddy I'll tell you what,
if they wake up while
you're setting up the lights
you can kiss
that friendship goodbye.
But so I'm from here, I live
in Los Angeles, I smoke marijuana
in Los Angeles,
I have a prescription...
I have a prescription
for marijuana,
that guy stood up,
hey, okay.
That's how high he was, he was like,
"Everybody's going to stand up"
"for marijuana, yeah! Oh."
"We're not, we're not standing? Okay."
"I thought everybody
was going to stand."
But I have a prescription
for marijuana in Los Angeles,
it's medicinal, okay?
It's for anxiety.
Primarily anxiety about
getting arrested for marijuana.
America was founded on two things.
One of them we don't like to
talk about and the other is tobacco.
So, marijuana
is the new cash crop
that's going to take us, you know,
through the next millennium.
It's excit-,
excit-, excit-, exciting.
And Denver's
at the forefront. I love it.
Now...
I like your laugh.
Ha ha ha ha.
You laugh like he looks.
You laugh, you laugh like
a cool teacher, like he just,
one of the kids made
a reference to snap chat
and he thought it was funny
and he was like,
"Ha ha ha ha ha ha."
I'm not making fun of your laugh,
I would never do that.
Have you ever had a friend make
fun of the way you laugh?
Ever had a friend,
but you have?
You know what
your friend is saying
when they make fun of
the way that you laugh?
"Hey, you know that sound that you
make when you're happy and joyful?"
"And the tragedy
that permeates our everyday life"
"is momentarily abated
for an ephemeral escapism?"
"Yeah, you sound stupid."
"You should feel self-conscious
when you're happy."
You should be like, "Uh everything's
okay for a moment, ar ar ar ar."
"Wait, do I sound like a seal?
Ar ar ar ar."
"Don't throw me the ball.
Ar ar ar ar ar ar ar ar."
You know alcohol's a better
friend to you than marijuana is.
And I like marijuana, no,
it is. It is, it's a better friend
because you blackout.
That's important. Everybody in
here thinks they drink too much.
Everybody in here said to
themselves, "You know, I, I, I"
"I should drink less."
Every single person.
But no one in here has ever been like,
"You know what..."
"I should drink more.
I mean..."
"I'm, I'm, I'm having
a half a glass of wine"
"every night that I go out to party."
"I should try this four, five, six,"
"forget to pick up your kids
at school of glasses of wine."
"What have I been doing?"
What a great friend, alcohol.
When you black out,
basically alcohol's going
"Hey,"
"it's about to get pretty
messy here in a second,"
"you can go ahead and take off."
"We'll take it from here, we've
got it from here on out."
But when you smoke too much,
marijuana is not a good friend.
Instead of turning your mind off,
like when you blackout,
it turns your mind all
the way up completely.
You're using your mind way
too much and become paranoid,
you know what I mean? You're
in a room with your good friends
and you're like every time I look away
they keep glancing at each other like...
"This fucking guy."
And they create a sort of,
some sort of and language
where they are like, "The party would
be more fun if he wasn't here."
"If we could
get him out of here,"
"the party would be more fun."
"Uh, nothing, ha ha ha ha ha."
But, when you smoke just
the right amount of marijuana
it can be the greatest
thing in the world.
I had smoked a lot of marijuana,
a lot, okay?
And I was having trouble getting
the movie to work, uh,
in the motor hotel that I was
staying in, which is a motel.
And uh, when I am very very high
I speak very formally
so as if to appear not to be high.
But I speak so formally that no
one would ever talk like that
unless they were very, very high.
So, I called the front desk
and I go, "Excuse me,"
"I would like to speak with
the proprietor of this establishment.
"The inhabitant of room 113
is having difficulties"
"with the entertainment center."
"He would like this remedied
immediately, and when I say he,"
"I speak of myself in the third
person, for it is I"
"the man who is having difficulties
with the entertainment center."
And then I was on
hold for a very long time
and I kind of drifted off, but
then I realized suddenly
that I had forgotten
if I had told him to hold on...
Or if he had told me to hold on.
I go, you know, I figure
make it ambiguous.
So I go, "Hello?"
A little bit of angry,
a little bit of a quandary,
but he was good, because he
came right back and he goes,
"Hello?"
I mean now, now I'm like,
"What's the move?"
Do you know what I mean?
It's my move, okay?
It's my move. But I don't know,
I'm pretty good so I go,
"Are you there?"
But he was good and he just goes,
"Yeah. Are you?"
Checkmate.
That did it for me, I was like,
"I don't know if I'm here."
"I'm high, I'm in room 113,
call the police."
"I don't know if I was supposed to
work today, you call the police!"
I was like "Only if we can
ride together." He said yes,
friends ever since. Yes.
That's how remarkable marijuana is.
There are approximately
5 reasons I don't give a fuck.
One, Parsley's not
a garnish for me.
When the plate hits the table that's
the first fucking thing I eat.
Two, there is no stem to a strawberry,
that's just the green part,
and when I
eat a strawberry Sir,
I eat the whole fucking thing.
And when shrimp is fried I eat the tail.
Oh dear,
what did I just say?
Three, I always choose
the Spanish option at the ATM.
What's the worst that can happen?
I can always cancellar.
Four, I don't put toilet paper
down on public toilet seats.
I don't do that. Sorry you had
to hear it from me but
that's what butts are for. Yeah.
That's what butts are for,
and no one's ever
gotten sick through their butt.
I mean except for AIDS and syphilis.
A lot of sexually transmitted diseases
that, a lot of them,
most of them are f-,
uh fatal, so...
The number five reason
I don't give a fuck,
sorry I'm taken,
but I fuck 'til I truck.
Do you know that means,
you know what that means?
That means I fuck and I fuck
and I fuck and I fuck
and I fuck and I fuck and I fuck
until I get a CDL, that's
a commercial drivers license.
I started
with short hauls in state,
then I started doing the tristate
hauls, then I do the longer hauls.
Pac Northwest down to San Diego,
then I do the transcontinental hauls
between San Diego to
Pennsylvania down to Florida.
Then I truck and I truck
and I truck and I truck...
until I fuck.
And I gotta be honest,
I try not to fuck too much.
It's completely disproportionate
to the amount of
trucking that you have to do
to get back to the fucking,
and so it's a lot of trucking and it's,
I don't know if you know any truckers
or you've ever trucked before,
but it's a lonely road.
It's just an open road
and all you have is your,
your CB and your,
your handle. It's the type of life, huh,
type of life where you get
a French manicure
just so it looks like you're
getting a hand job
when you jack off.
Who's your favorite American
historical figure, hmm?
Who is it?
Who is your favorite...
Who's your favorite American
historical figure? Hmm? What?
Roosevelt, that's a good one.
Get her the fuck out of here.
Get her out of here.
My favorite, my favorite
American historical figure
is George Washington Carver.
Geor- yes. Yes. Yes.
A much,
the greatest American inventor.
A much better
inventor than Eli Whitney
who invented the cotton gin.
Something that
we all know exists,
but none of us could imagine
what it looks like at all.
Watch, right now
everybody, everybody
think of a cotton gin. Go, imagine it.
I propose you're merely
thinking of some kind of a loom.
And that's the only
loom joke you'll ever hear.
George Washington Carver, right?
I mean peanut, yes, peanut butter,
exactly. Peanut butter.
He invented over 100 things with
peanuts, but peanut butter.
Can you imagine
if you invented peanut butter?
Would you keep it a secret just for
a little while, for like a week or two?
You wouldn't tell your wife
or any of your friends?
You just show up, your friend's like,
"Why are you so happy?" You're like,
"No reason."
"But if you have some celery
and some raisins,"
"shit's about to go down."
"Oh thank you. I'll be in the
bathroom, don't come in."
"I'll call it ants on a log, yeah."
Right, but George Washington
Carver, great man, right.
I like to think he had
a great relationship.
But any great relationship requires
transparency, okay?
So that transparency is essential,
right, in a great relationship.
So I figure like, she would
kind of start to know
that something was up, you know
she's like, "George,"
"you want me to bring
the jelly sandwiches"
"down to your invent workshop?"
And he's like, "No, no Martha'"
And I don't know if her name
was Martha, but neither do you.
"No no Martha, that's okay, uh"
"just leave the
jelly sandwiches outside"
"and I'll eat them without adding
anything to them at all."
"Certainly nothing that
would antiquate the idea"
"of jelly sandwiches altogether."
So eventually she's got to come
to him and go, "George,"
"you got a secret, I can see it, there's
a secret behind those eyes"
"George. I try to create
an environment for transparency,"
"George, what is
the secret, George?"
And he doesn't have to say anything
because fellas, isn't, is not
the best get out of jail
free card, she's angry,
but he just invented peanut butter.
All he has to do
as she's yelling,
you know he's just slowly,
pushes a peanut butter and
jelly sandwich into her mouth.
That fluffy white bread,
he's cut the crust off
and she bites down. Ladies
it's the first time a woman
has ever had a peanut
butter and jelly s-,
you gotta know she just came.
I mean she is,
she just had the most
violent orgasm of her life.
And he gets, he gets on her,
guys you gotta know,
he gets on her and he fucks her.
I mean he does.
He fucks, he f-, he,
there's no other way to say it,
he fucks her like the guy who
just invented peanut butter. Alright?
And I'll tell you what,
if you go home tonight
and you have excellent
intercourse, you know,
which I can see cool teachers gonna...
You're going to do a little role-
playing. Somebody's going to get
their diploma tonight.
She's in a graduation cap, look,
I can do the whole thing alright, I-.
But if you go home and you have
excellent intercourse tonight,
this is really important, okay,
I want you to take a beat after
you've both climaxed, just...
take a breath and then turn
to the person that you're with,
you know, turn to the person
next to you and just say,
"That was like you just
invented peanut butter."
Because it's either the greatest
compliment they've ever had or
a lot of people are going to blackout
and not remember the show,
and then it's the strangest
ending to sex ever.
So look, I was in Yogi Bear
so I made a lot of money
and uh... I want to talk, listen,
I want to talk to you guys
about something, and that is
when you make a lot of money
don't spend it, okay? Save it.
All right, don't spend it like
more is coming. All right?
I mean you saw my wife Kate
and she puts up-,
I don't know if you can tell
from my performance tonight
but I'm a handful,
I'm a bit of a handful.
And she puts up with a l- I,
I lost $73,000 last year
on Carnival games alone.
Oh, ha ha ha laugh it up,
it's a disease. All right?
It's a disease.
But she's with me. I mean,
yeah, 'cause you know...
bitches be crazy. Am I right?
Am I right?
Bitches be crazy.
I mean, bitches be crazy.
That's real though, bitches be crazy,
I mean they do live in
a society that expects them
to have both family and a career,
because if they only have a career
and they don't have a family,
and then just a lonely careerist woman
and they only have a family
they're considered a housewife
which is some sort of failure
because they
don't have a career.
Shit, if that was my situation
I'd be crazy too, alright?
Yeah. Bitches be crazy.
Ever sneard of it? Hmm?
Ever sneard of it?
Do you know what that is?
That's when you smell
something a nerd heard.
Ever sneard of it.
Like if you're in your
living room, you know,
and uh you're with your friend and
he does computer programming
but it's kind of as a hobby,
so that's pretty nerdy
and he's just like, "Wait a second,
I heard a crash in the kitchen."
And you're like...
smells like chrysanthemums.
Must have been the flower vase.
"I sneard of it."
I wish I hadn't done that joke.
Not pleased.
Well, that's the real litmus test
for how the more
absurd stuff is going to go
and I'll tell you,
I am not confident.
I'll stop wasting your time
with that sneard of it stuff.
Time again being a very
important commodity,
incredibly important.
I mentioned that earlier.
Time in a post religious,
post meaning society,
it's the closest thing
we have to a deity.
That's true because it's
the only thing that's omniscient,
omnipresent and omnipotent.
It's omniscient because everything
that happens, happens within time,
so it must know about it. Also
that expression "Only time will tell",
that means that time
knows something and it's
not telling you until later.
It's omnipresent because sooner
or later you realize that
the very infrastructure of our language
is infected with temporal terms,
even right now I'm talking
in terms of time
so we can't even communicate
without, you won't,
you may not realize it now,
but years from now
you're going to look back and be like,
"I didn't realize it at the time but"
"he was right
about the time thing."
And then it's omnipotent because
eventually it will vanquish us all,
but that brings us back to death.
We don't talk about,
we don't talk about death
in our society
because it's morbid, right?
That's the only adjective we have for
talking about death. Morbid.
That's never
a positive adjective, right?
It's a negative connotation we have
talking about death.
You know, you never compliment
somebody with the word morbid.
You'll never be like,
"Hey, Steve, sorry,"
"I know you're going home for the
weekend, I just want to tell you,"
"you were
super morbid all week."
"Thank you so much.
Always talking about death,"
"the ephemeral nature of your existence,
we have to reevaluate our values,"
"look, I, just do
me a favor, next week"
"keep it morbid. Alright?"
"Have fun with your family, I hope
they don't die. Just kidding,"
"but think about it, you piece of shit."
Talk about death with
our friends or our family.
Uh, we should. We don't talk
it about with strangers.
We'll talk about weather
with strangers.
That's always interesting to me. We
have nothing to do with the weather,
and people always talking about it.
"Summer's coming up. Yeah?"
"It's going to be pretty hot
next month I heard. You know?"
"Win- winter's coming up.
Ooh, fall's right around the corner."
"Summer vacation's coming up.
Hey, guess what else?"
"Death is, death's coming up."
Yeah, death.
But you could never.
Can't talk to somebody
you don't know about it.
You never get, you couldn't
get on an elevator. I've tried,
you know what I mean? Just...
"Hot one, huh? Yeah."
"Not as hot as last week
though, huh? No."
"Tell you if I had to go, I'd
rather go this week, you know."
"No, not go anywhere,
not go somewhere,"
"go like,
go no go nowhere."
"You see, on that one
I took the sleeping pills"
"and then I decomposed?
I died and then decomposed."
"Oh, no, you don't have
to press a button for me, I'm"
"just along for the ride."
Talk briefly about, suicide.
Suicide, also, we don't talk
about it. Negative connotations.
People who are suicidal
feel ashamed.
They feel like
they shouldn't talk about,
it's, they feel vulnerable,
they're at the end of their line.
And I had a great friend
who died a year ago today.
And I like to talk about him
on stage, his name was
Gleep Glarp the Gobblesnarf.
And... You know what? Hey,
it's suicide, it's an uncomfortable
subject, we can laugh, alright?
Gleep and I went to college and,
you know, obviously Gleep
Glarp the Gobblesnarf,
he came from a wealthy family,
the Gobblesnarfs.
Who made
a fortune gobbling snarf.
We all know what snarfing is,
it's when you sneeze and barf
at the same time.
So they made
a living gobbling that.
I mean, that is disgusting.
It's like the Koch brothers,
it's just deplorable.
It's disgusting.
It's despicable.
Right? It's despicable.
It is despicable!
But, you know, Gleep didn't want to
follow in the footsteps of his family.
So, after college, and he
was always a bit depressive.
After college he
started his own business,
and he tried to switch it up
he started snarfing gobbles.
You know, which is
much less disgusting,
you just have to go in the little turkey
fields and wait near their beaks
and when they... you
just snarf it up, you know.
Much less disgusting.
It's basically inhaling audio.
It's not gross at all.
But, you know, that didn't work out.
This economy. This fucking city.
And he got depressed,
and he started
getting sick on purpose,
drinking all the time.
And I said to him,
"Gleep, reach out to me, you
know, you're depressed,"
"talk to me, call me. You're
getting sick all the time."
"Use me as a resource."
During flu season he touched
his tongue to a toilet seat.
Yeah, that's what butts are for,
you know what I mean?
I don't think that's...
But sure enough, he got
really really sick one night
and he got so drunk, he passed out,
on his back, on purpose,
face up. And,
he, sure enough he,
he snarfed in his sleep.
And because no one was there
and he was face up, he,
well, he gobbled his own snarf.
So he choked on his own sneeze barf.
And I want to tell you something,
some of you laughed
at his, at his last name,
at what his family did.
That was the thing about Gleep,
he would never
ever make fun of you because of
your family, where you're from,
who you are. Because
I come from a family
of burp farmers. You know that?
I come from a family of burp farmers,
and I think that farming is the backbone
of this United States of America.
Alright?
And I'm proud to be from
a family of burp farmers.
I even keep a little burp farm
in our backyard.
Kate and I, and how do I put this?
This year's harvest
came in pretty good.
And here's a little burp
I like to call beeps.
Beeps.
We got to talk about
yet another reason
that I do not give a fuck.
And that is,
that morality is relative,
is what I'm going to tell you
right now. Your values,
what you think is good
and bad depends wholly on
where you were born,
where you're from,
what time period you were born in.
Two thousand years ago,
you know, people would come
up to each other and be like,
"Hey, I just wanted to tell you,
when the eclipse happened yesterday"
"during the day
and dark eye covered the sun,"
"thank you for sacrificing"
"and, you know, killing your
entire family and eating them."
"That was really good of you.
You're a good person,"
"and we baked this,
we made this,"
"this just a rock that we found,
we want to give it to you."
"We thought it looked cool.
We want to give it to you."
Thousands of years from
now people will look back,
they won't even be able
to believe our values.
Barely a hundred years ago,
you know,
or two hundred years ago,
slavery was A okay.
Somebody would be like, "I'm doing
pretty good. Business is good,"
"I think I'm going to buy
a couple more people."
Doesn't that sound crazy now?
Thousands of years from now,
people will look back they'll be like,
"I can't believe they ate animals
when they didn't need to."
They just sent them to
concentration camps
and, I mean, don't get me wrong,
I had a bacon cheeseburger
earlier today
and then, later on,
another bacon cheeseburger.
Because the piggy taste good
on the cow cow, alright?
You can quote me on that.
Also, something
that you take for granted,
but if you think of it this way.
Pets are actually friend slaves.
That's a hard one to hear,
isn't it? You know, there's...
It's a tough one. Because
there's a lot of people in here
that don't want to hear that.
I mean, they're going
to go home after the show
and, you know, they're going
to greet their dog, he's like...
And you're going to be like,
"See TJ was wrong. Look at you,"
you love me." But you
can't communicate with that dog,
they might be like...
"Is this the day that I'm free?"
"Sometimes I shit and you
pick it up with your hands,"
"other times you yell at me!"
Friend slaves. Man, I was walking,
I was on the phone with Kate,
and I was walking
alongside a graveyard ironically.
And, there was this little doggy,
this little Chihuahua,
that was running away from
me, but it had a tag on.
So, it looked like a lost dog,
wasn't an owner.
Sorry, a master.
There wasn't a master around.
And, I told Kate and Kate's
like, "You got to go get it,"
"go get the dog."
So I go after it, it's like...
So I don't know what's going
with that dog. It might be like,
"Get away from me, I finally
escaped from the prison."
He was talking to its dog
friends earlier and was like,
"I found a weak, I found
a weak spot in the fence."
"I dug a bunch of dirt over there,
I'm going to jump the fence."
"Tomorrow during the day
once they go away"
"to wherever it is
they're gone for eight hours"
"and then we're just
in the prison being like,"
"are they coming back or is this
the day that I starve to death here?"
"If I reach freedom, I'll
come back for each of you."
"Triffany, wait for me."
Triffany's a poodle.
"Triffany, will you wait for me?"
And then Kate goes, "Alright,
you got to bend down, okay?"
"And pretend
like you have food."
How fucked up is that?
This poor dog is like,
"I'm so hungry."
I'm like, "Hey I have food. Hey,"
"here you go, food. Food."
And the dog's like, "Are you one of
the good ones? I'm so hungry."
And then it comes back,
and I'm like, "Yeah!"
Back to prison we go.
And I return it to its master,
and the master is like,
"You know, I'd love to offer you
a reward." And I'm like, "No, no."
"I just ask if
one of my slaves escaped,"
"that you'd do the same."
The number six reason
I don't give a fuck,
I won't even inherit it
to my American list.
The number seven reason...
I don't give a fuck is I will buy
a battle axe in Philadelphia,
at an establishment called
Asian Treasures.
Hello! You think I'm fucking?
You see that?
That's a... You want to hold this?
Come on, get up here.
You got to take it, thought, and then
you got to turn to the audience
and just scream your
biggest battle cry, okay?
And... What do you think?
That's a real balance.
Yeah!
Wow!
It's got some weight
to it, right? Yeah.
Wow, that was... You went
above and beyond.
That was, that was fantastic.
I mean, he really made an effort
to cover the entire room.
That was important.
That was an important and wonderful
thing that he did, he was like...
"Yeah! Yeah!"
"Yeah!"
I bought this in a place
called Asian Treasures.
When Kate and I went in there,
we thought it was going to be
a very different type of establishment.
So, you go in there, it sells kimonos
and like travel chess
and swords, it sells swords,
I don't know if you've
ever been to a place, and
she immediately thought
I wanted a sword, I guess I
looked at the swords for too long,
and she started trying to sell me,
she's like, "Oh, no, this for
a good price. Very good price."
"Blue steel, carbon fiber, handle,
very good price."
"Good price. You like scabbard?
Good price."
"You like a battle axe?
Good price, this good price."
"Battle axe, good price."
And I was like,
"Compared to what?"
I wasn't price checking
on Amazon before I came.
And I'm like, "A hundred dollars for
a battle axe? I don't know,
"that's a little steep." So
I talked her down to ninety five.
Because it does, it has a skull
in the middle and its hand painted.
But, you know, I had to ask Kate
if I could buy the battle axe.
So I said, "Kate, can I please have
this battle axe for the bus?"
"I mean, it'll be so awesome
if I have a battle axe."
The bus battle axe. We'll get off
at each city and I'll be like,
"Ah!" Now
I'm going to be like, "Ah, ah,"
"ah, ah, ah..."
Then I go, and she goes, "You want
to buy a battle axe for the bus?"
"That's what you want to do?
You want to have a double headed"
- "axe on a moving vehicle."
- Hell, yeah!
That's what I said, "Hell, yeah."
And she said, "No. You can't
have a battle axe on the bus,"
"you're going to cut yourself."
And I was like, "Please."
But then I saw it, see it has these sort
of plastic sheaths on either side.
Can you guys see that?
And so I said, "Well, what if I
keep the sheaths on?"
"Then it won't
hurt anybody, right?"
She was like, "Are you going
to super glue them on?"
And I was like, "Uh. hmm."
Well, fellas,
guess what I didn't do.
So, I took them off
and I was practicing
in my room, on the bus.
And I cut myself.
And who walks in immediately?
She walks in,
she sees me holding a battle axe,
blood coming down my other hand.
This is not a knife,
this is a,
this is a battle axe.
This is an axe specifically designed,
to cut and to kill.
So, I'm bleeding, it's dripping
down my hand. She goes,
"What's happening?
What just happened? Did you,"
"did you cut yourself with
the battle axe?"
I was like, "Mm mm."
And she was like, "Give me the
battle axe." And I was like,
"Mm mm."
She's like, "TJ, give me
the battle axe now,"
"you did not superglue
those things on."
"Give it to me and I'm
going to super glue them on,"
"and then you can have
your battle axe back."
And I went...
And so she
super glued them on.
I took it to a Subway,
"Can I have banana peppers?"
"Banana peppers.
Provolone, provolone. Prop,"
"the provolone."
"Yeah, I'll have jalapenos,
can I also have jalapenos?"
"No, no, not olives, not olives. Jala,"
"no, in the front.
The front most bin,"
"no, jalapeno, not, not olives!"
So I'm going to tell this
story really quickly.
Kate and I were working
at the Mall of America,
which is a gigantic mall in Minnesota.
We were both walking,
because we couldn't get through
the Mall of America,
it was too late, we
were partying on the bus,
it was like
three thirty in the morning.
And we couldn't through the mall
to the hotel, so I was like,
"Let's just walk around it."
And, Kate was really cold
because she was
wearing spaghetti straps.
Mama mia, these spaghetti
straps make you so cold.
They make you so cold.
So I said, "Look, you're
cold, you should,"
"why don't you take my shirt?"
Because I wasn't wearing this,
I just had a shirt. And she's like,
"No, then you're going to be cold."
I was like, "Hey hey hey,
chivalry isn't dead, alright?"
"Will you take my shirt?"
And she goes, "Okay."
So she puts on my shirt and
we keep walking. And now,
I'm shirtless with a battle axe.
So we got this
little girl kind of walking
with a shirt over her
and a shirtless man
with a toddler body,
just walking with a battle axe.
And I swear to God
I turned to her, I'm like,
"I mean,
how funny must we look?"
"Woop! woop!"
We turn around,
there's a cop,
there's a police officer
standing outside his car,
he's like,
"Sir, drop the battle axe
and approach the vehicle."
He called it a battle axe.
So I drop the battle axe.
Because I'm not afraid of
anything. And I walk over to him.
He goes, "You want to explain
what's happening here?" I was like,
"I'm a comedian, the battle axe
is a prop in my act"
"and I took off my shirt to give to my
wife because she was cold."
And he says, "Kate,
can you come over here?"
And she goes, "Alright." He goes,
"You want to explain"
"what's going on here?" I love that.
That he thought I might be lying,
like this is the strangest
hostage situation that's ever been.
I just found her
at a club and I was like,
"You're coming with me!"
"To the funeral pyre!"
And so she said, "You know,
this is my husband, he,"
"you know, he gave me,
he's a comedian,"
"he's kind of a prop comic, it's
really embarrassing actually."
"But he's a real gentleman, he gave me
his shirt so that I wouldn't be cold."
"So, he's a great husband."
And, the guys goes,
"Okay, I need to see ID."
And then he went and he ran
our ID's, I don't know what for,
perhaps to see
if I had any previous
medieval armor offenses.
"So I understand you got caught with a,"
"a jousting lance in Michigan,
is that true?"
"In Lansing, no less?
That's ironic."
And I, he gives us our ID's
back and he goes,
"So, this gentleman
is in fact your husband?"
And I laughed out loud.
Guys, I laughed right
in his face and he's like,
"What's so funny?" I was like,
"Do realize what you just asked?"
"Okay, you literally were
just like, so,"
"you did in fact, this was, this
was the decision right here."
Shirtless with a battle axe, this is
till death do you part? Death?
So the police officer says, "Alright,
well, where you guys headed?"
I was like, "We're going back
to the hotel." And he said,
"Listen, I'll give you
a ride back to the Radisson."
Which is the definition
of white privilege.
So he gives us a ride
back to the Radisson,
and the battle axe is the, the trunk,
because I guess he thought if he gave it
to me in the back seat I would be like,
And, so we get
to the hotel and I'm like,
"Oh, no, he's going to
confiscate the battle axe."
"Right? He's going to take it."
So, I run back to the trunk,
I go, "So, can I have the battle
axe back?" And he goes,
"You know, you're walking around
with a battle axe that was"
"you know, that was the
first problem, and then"
"you were shirtless, I just.
You know,"
"it's a double headed battle axe. I
just, I think we got to confiscate it."
I was like, "No no, but here's
the thing. It's just a prop"
"and you can tell because, see
the sides are these plastic sheaths,"
"on either side. So you can't
hurt anybody with it. See?"
And he goes, "Okay."
How cool are the Minnesota police?
So I was so excited.
So I run back in to the lobby
to tell Kate, you know,
and Kate goes,
"Did they let you keep the
battle axe?" I was like, "Mm hmm."
And she goes, "Why?"
And I just go...
The number eight reason
I don't give a fuck.
I'll tell a Derek's parents
to go fuck themselves.
We got any Dereks here tonight?
We got any Dereks here? Hmm?
- Derek!
- You're Derek?
Well, howdy do.
Looky what we got here.
It's just like a Derek's friend
to out him for being a Derek.
This guy
immediately was like...
Come on stage.
Come on up here. Come on, Derek.
Yeah!
Yes!
These fucking Dereks.
That's a tough thing to try
and get you up here. Whoa!
You're awful
quick for a Derek.
Alright, show me your papers.
- Show me your ID.
- ID?
Show me your,
yeah, show me some ID.
What is that?
A Qdoba card?
I mean,
that is so Derek of you.
- How much is on it?
- Zero.
Look at Derek
getting those deals.
Oh, we do.
We got a Derek.
D-E-R-E-K.
You're not fucking around
with that I-C-K stuff, huh?
No double R's for this Derek.
Alright, let me see your phone.
Call your...
look at this Derek at night
in open toe footwear, I mean.
What the fuck is going on balcony?
You see what I'm talking about exactly.
I mean, these fucking Dereks.
I swear to God,
some of these fucking Dereks.
They're ruining the country,
these Derek's are.
Not you, you've
been great sport so far.
Go ahead and call your parents
and put it on speaker phone.
"Hello."
- Hello.
- "Hello?"
Hi, is... are are you
the mother of a Derek?
- "Yes."
- Yes.
So that that's the
name you went with, Derek?
My name is TJ Miller,
I'm the star of Yogi Bear 3D.
Thank you.
And, as you can tell,
we are here at a live show
at The Paramount Theater.
- Your Derek...
- "Okay."
- What's that?
- "What did you say?"
I said, I said, we're at a live show
here at The Paramount Theater.
- And,
- "Yes."
And, and, your Derek was
brave enough to come on stage
and people really appreciate that.
I think, let's give him
another round of applause.
So as you can see
your Derek is one of the
most well liked Derek's
I've ever come across.
But, Miss, unfortunately now
I'm going to have to tell you,
to go fuck yourself.
Thank you.
Give it up for Derek!
So I had an AVM in 2010,
that's an arteriovenous malformation.
It's a congenital disorder,
that is a malformed area in your
brain which you don't use,
but it's subject to hemorrhaging.
And, that indeed occurred,
during Yogi Bear 3D in fact.
My brain hemorrhaged and
I started literally going crazy,
because there was more blood
in that area of my brain.
I started narrating my own
behavior, I was obsessed
with entanglement puzzles,
it was a bad scene.
I'm going to talk
to these fake bears
in the forest in New Zealand.
They're not even there,
it's just Booboo's two
ping pong balls on a stick.
And there's this weird guy like,
"Alright, talk to the fake bear."
And I am going insane.
Literally. And,
so I have a neurologist. His,
yeah, hey, neurology.
Yeah. So I have
a neurologist, Dr. Stokel.
He's a very famous
neurologist internationally.
He works at
Cedars-Sinai in California.
And he's, he's the greatest.
He's pretty cut and dry,
but he's a great neurologist.
And he called me and said,
"Would you..." Yeah,
hey. You know what,
he calls me, didn't
call me that often, so.
You're right. Ow! That's what I said
when I saw his name on the
the phone. I was like, "Whoo whoo!"
So Dr. Stokel says, "You
should come down to the office"
"so we can talk."
Now, I don't know
if you have a neurologist,
that's never a good thing.
You never get down
to the office and he's like,
"Hey, I just wanted to tell you in
person, you have thirty percent"
"more brain capacity
than all other human beings."
"Let's go take shots of tequila. Yeah!"
That doesn't happen.
But I went down there, and he,
he just looked at me
and said, "Hey, TJ,"
"in my experience there's
no easy way to say this"
"so I'm just going to, you know,
cut to the chase and say it."
- "You're going to die."
- No!
And, yeah, that's what
I felt inside, right there.
No!
But I looked in to the eyes
of this man
who's had to say this a lot. He's
probably had to tell a lot of people,
you know, that they're going to die.
And I just felt so bad for him
strangely in that moment,
maybe that's why I'm a comedian.
So I looked back
in to his eyes and I said,
"In my experience
there's no easy way to say this,
"so I'll just cut to the chase."
"You're going to die."
And he goes, "No, I'm not."
And I was like,
"Denial. That's the first stage."
He's like, "No, but I'm saying
you're going to die before me."
"I know I'm, but you're going
to die before me." I was like,
"Bargaining. Second stage.
He was like,
"Stop talking about my death.
We're here to talk about"
"your impending death." And
I was like, "Okay,"
"Anger, third stage."
And I got him through all the stages
until we got to the last stage,
Acceptance. And then after,
you know, I got him to, really,
that stage of acceptance,
I stole his plant.
Now let me explain. I saw,
he had a fern and
I always wanted a fern.
And so, I stole it.
And as I was leaving the room,
and it was too tall
to get through the doorway,
so I had to
kind of bend it down.
Which is an awful thing
to show a man
is to take his plant
and bend it in half,
so that you can get
out the door. And he said,
"What are you doing?" I was like,
"I'm stealing this plant."
And he's like, "Why?" And I was like,
"In lieu of our recent conversation,"
"you tell me."
But I used to love the idea
that one day he'll be like
at a dinner party or something
and someone will say,
"So, you're a neurologist,
you probably have to deliver"
"bad news, you know, sometimes."
He's like, "Yeah,"
"sometimes I have to tell people
they're going to die, yeah."
"Hey, I don't want
to be morbid, but what's the,"
"you know, what's the worst
reaction you've ever had"
"when you had to deliver that
news?" And he's just like,
"One guy took my plant."
Oh, oh. This?
This is Evian facial spray.
You know that? You
ever heard of this? Huh?
Cool teacher,
you ever heard of this?
- You ever seen this?
- Yes.
Yeah, you have? Here,
you sir, come here.
Come on. It's okay.
You know what, actually
now that I see you.
Can you come?
Come on.
Come on up. It's okay.
What I want to do is, listen.
This moisturizes,
refreshes and tones.
It moisturizes because
it's water.
And it refreshes because
And, so what I want to do
is I want to spray this on you
and just tell me the first thing
that comes to mind.
Because it feels really great.
And don't try and be funny, just
say the first feeling that you have.
Okay, ready?
Here you go. Come a little closer.
- For real?
- For real. Come closer.
- Refreshing?
- Yeah!
Give it up for her.
She said one of the words
that I said. Give it up for her.
So this is ironically the most
American product on the market.
I know that seems strange,
it's imported water from France
in an aerosol bottle.
Is there anything more
American than that? I mean,
people are dying
in other parts of the world
because they can't get
a cleanly source of drinking water,
and in the
United States we're like,
"Sometimes I like it
on the outside."
"Oh, sure, when I'm thirsty
or parched I'll put it inside."
"But other times it's
like safari jungle day. Yeah!"
But I bought this for that joke,
but then like many things in my life
the comedy began
to bleed in to the reality,
and the reality began
to bleed in to the comedy,
and vice versa,
and also the inverse.
And I started using it in real life.
But I found
one incredible use for it.
Have you ever talked to
someone who's on their phone
the entire conversation?
Do you ever do that?
They just have chosen not to be
connected to the individual
with which they
are physically present.
They're just making you feel
so absolutely unimportant.
She's pointing to this guy.
But here's what you do.
Because you can do this.
These are thirteen dollars
at Sephora.
As soon as he goes into his phone,
as soon as that person goes in
their phone, you just pull this out
and you go...
And then when they look
up from their phone just go...
"We got to get out of here."
"We got to get out of here!"
And we do.
Thank you. Good evening.
Subtitled by: Captivate Arabia
Amman - Jordan