- Pam?
- Yeah?
Did you see Oprah yesterday?
- No, I didn't.
- I, uh...
I am going to be a father.
What was Oprah about?
Angelina Jolie was on.
And she adopted a baby from Asia,
and she said that it changed her life.
And that really inspired me.
So, I want you to look into seeing
how much a little Chinese baby would cost.
- That's a really big decision.
- I know.
Maybe you should wait before
you adopt. Or not adopt.
Just do it, okay?
Roy's sister looked into it, and the
application alone costs a thousand dollars.
Um... find out if there's a cheaper,
less expensive baby out there, okay?
You know, she also said the waiting
list is like eight months.
- Eight months?
- Yeah.
I don't even know if I'll want
a baby in eight months.
You probably won't.
You know what, Pam?
If in ten years...
I haven't had a baby,
and you haven't had a baby...
No, Michael.
- Twenty years.
- No, Michael.
Thirty.
Sure.
It's a deal.
All right. Three pairs of pants.
Three pairs of socks.
- Three packs of condoms.
- Yesh.
Uh, fun jeans.
- Sign.
- Per diem.
Guess where I am going!
I will give you a hint.
It is a booze-fueled sex romp,
where anything goes.
You are correct, sir!
I am headed to Philadelphia
for the Annual Northeastern
Mid-Market Office Supply Convention.
And Jim Halpert is going to be
coming, which will be fun.
Poor little guy. He's been
stuck working under Josh,
the poor man's Michael Scott,
as he is known around my condo.
Don't be mad, it is a business trip.
But I don't understand.
It's for managers.
Monkey, I am an A. R. M.,
Assistant Regional Manager.
I know!
It... I was just really hoping
we could spend some time together.
- Are you still there?
- Yes, Monkey.
Don't "Monkey" me! You can't wait
to get out of here, A. R. M.
In the Martin family, we like to say,
"Looks like someone took
the slow train from Philly."
That's code for "check out the slut."
What is...
why are there flies in here?
Oh my God! Are you so
excited for tonight?
I am so excited. You guys are
going to click, I can feel it.
So what are you wearing?
This.
You look so pretty.
Thank you.
Yes, I have a date.
He's a cartoonist for the local paper,
which is really neat,
because I like to draw too.
I'm kind of nervous.
I haven't been on a first
date in nine years...
probably shouldn't broadcast that.
Well, remember, no matter
how much you may want to,
do not sleep with him on the first
date. It gives him all the power.
Sleep with who?
Whom, whom... whom?
My neighbor Alan. They're
going on a date tonight.
Oh, wow! Oh my God,
I have a great idea.
You know what you should do
to be hilarious?
Wear your wedding dress.
It would be a great icebreaker.
- And your veil.
- Yeah, do it!
- I'll probably just wear this.
- Really? Okay.
Well, word of advice:
unbutton that top button.
Let those things breathe.
Any message you want me
to relate to Jim?
- Um...
- Um. Okay, um.
- Um. - You got that?
- I got it.
- Write it down.
- Um. Um....
There's my girl.
I noticed you handing out some shekels.
How would one get on that train?
That was for per diem for Philadelphia.
Ugh, that town smells
like cheese steaks.
That town is full of history.
Andrea's the office bitch.
You'll get used to her.
Creed.
Can I have my neck pillow back?
Michael!
- Hey, Michael.
- Hey, Josh, how you doing?
- Pretty good. How you doing?
- Good to see you. There he is.
There's the traitor.
Traitor! Traitor!
Come here, you. Come here!
The product...the progital...
my son returns.
I was shocked when he told me
he was transferring to Stamford.
It's like the firemen.
You don't leave your brothers behind.
Even if you find out that there is
a better fire in Connecticut.
Really good to see you, man.
Yeah. Wow.
I didn't expect that.
It's good to see you too.
Oh, hey. How's it going up there?
Have you made any sales yet?
Yeah, sold about 40,000.
Shut up. That's impossible.
No, it's not. And I did.
Yeah.
Well, I did it too.
You know, when I saw Dwight,
I realized
how stupid and petty
all those pranks I pulled on him were.
And then he spoke.
I wonder how hard it would be
to get a copy of his room key.
- So did you hear?
- What?
- Pam's back on the market again.
- Really? She's dating?
Oh, if I weren't engaged,
I would so hit that.
So what kind of commissions
you get up there?
Oh, Dwight, I missed you so much.
You're so immature.
Listen, Michael, I heard you
were a great salesman.
And I just want to let you know that
if our branch absorbs your branch,
I'm going to look for
a place for you at Stamford.
- Oh, hey!
- Hey, Jan.
- We all checked in?
- Yes.
Great. Let's dump our stuff and meet
back down here in a half an hour.
- Okay.
Jan? Look, I think
we need to set some ground rules.
- What are you talking about?
- The 800-pound gorilla in the room.
Carol. I'm still dating her.
So nothing can happen
between us at the convention.
- Step away from me, Michael.
- Thank you
for being so brave with all of this.
Thank you.
Alan's cartoon is so funny, right?
And they're, like, so smart. I don't
even know what they mean half the time.
- This party is gonna be awesome.
- I know.
That is specifically why I chose a room
close to the elevator. More foot traffic.
Check it out.
That is crooked on that side.
Hey hey!
- That is a lot of liquor.
- Yeah.
- And a dart board.
- Well, that's how we do it in Scranton.
Or did you forget?
Ain't no party like a Scranton party,
'cause a Scranton party don't stop.
We should probably head on down,
you know, hook up with Jan.
Well, we have time.
One for the road, gentlemen?
A shot of Midori, perhaps.
Oh, no, sorry, it's an inside joke. There
was this bartender at Stamford who...
You know what?
You'd just have to be there.
Wish I was.
I love inside jokes.
I'd love to be a part of one someday.
- We should...
- Yeah, all right.
- All right, see you guys down there.
- See you guys.
Change your mind, come back up.
- I'll do a shot with you, Michael.
- Ugh, that would be gross.
It's not even lunch yet.
SWAG!
Stuff We All Get.
I basically decorated my condo for free
with all of my SWAG!
Check it out.
Hi, I'm Michael Scott. Dunder Mifflin.
Dwight Schrute. Assistant Regional
Manager, Dunder Mifflin.
I am a huge fan.
- Thanks. I appreciate it, guys.
- You know what?
I am having a big blowout tonight,
room 308. Hope you can come.
- I...maybe. If I can.
- Well, cool!
Okay, so can I tell people
you're gonna be there?
No, you cannot.
So maybe. See ya.
Why do they call him The Bus?
Because he's afraid to fly.
Smile.
Do you remember me from last year?
There's a party in my room, 308.
Can't miss it. Right off the elevator.
Tonight. Be there.
All right, Jan just emailed me.
She wants us to meet her up front.
Yep. Yeah, she's up front.
You don't have email on your phone.
I don't have to, I just know.
Yes, hello?
- No one just called you.
- All right, nice meeting
you, Ted. Take care.
- I'll see you soon.
- Yeah, stop by later.
- See you in a bit. Bye-bye.
May I have a moment
of your time, please?
- I need you to do something for me.
- Yes, anything.
I want you to dig up some dirt on Josh.
Find out if there are
any skeletons in his attic.
I'll talk to my buddy down
at the station, stat.
Hey, Pam.
- Hey, what's up?
- It's, uh...
- I was...might ask if you wanted...
- Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
He's not in the office.
Can I take a message?
I will.
You too.
- Sorry. What's up?
- Um, if, uh...
I just completely forgot
what I was going to say.
It's so weird.
Okay. Well, if you think
of it, I'll be here.
Okay.
So I called my buddy down
at the station today.
Had them run a background check
on Josh Porter.
See if there's any known
aliases, et cetera.
And?
He wasn't volunteering today.
Yeah.
Things have been pretty
crazy around the office.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
We moved Ryan over to your desk.
Oh. Tell him I say hi.
I will call him later with that message.
Hey, how's... Toby?
Toby Flenderson is everything
that is wrong with the paper industry.
- Is he why you left?
- Oh, no. It was just...
you know, a good opportunity for me,
a promotion. I got a chance to...
Opportunity, promotion. Blah blah.
You know, Jim, those are just words.
Have you taken into account
other factors?
Vis-a-vis bosses?
Is Josh funnier than I am?
Does he even have a girlfriend?
Because I have two, basically.
Michael, it's really not a competition.
Jim got us a great lead with a new rep
from National Envelope.
We can grab lunch with them tomorrow.
Hey, Jan. Jan?
Don't worry. I have got the tip.
Whoa, Michael.
- Wow. Oh, my God, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Was that your per diem?
No, that was a different
hundred dollar bill.
What have you generated, Michael?
I have generated a lot of interest
in my party this evening.
- What party?
- Party I'm having tonight in 308.
Obviously, you are invited.
Michael, um...
Jim and Josh are in meetings
all day and I am
in and out of meetings.
I can't stay on top of you 24/7.
You should order
the most expensive thing on the menu.
So he knows you're worth it.
If you do that, you're gonna
have to put out.
Oh, yeah. You'll have to put out.
Is there a key for Jane Doe?
Thank you.
Any messages for 308?
All right.
Hey hey, fellers.
- Michael. Hey, what's up?
- Hey, Michael.
Uh, well, Jim and I have a meeting
with Uni-ball in about 45 minutes,
- so we should probably go.
- Hey, check this out.
How about that?
A little friendly competition.
Stamford versus Scranton.
- I don't think so.
- Oh. Jim?
Looks like you picked a bad time
to defect, my friend.
Fine. All right.
Okay. Excellent.
Oh, just shut it.
Hey, Pam, what's up?
Yeah--uh, no. Tell him I will give him
general specifics tomorrow, okay?
Yes. Say hi to Pam!
Hi, Pam.
Yes, that is Josh and Dwight and Jim.
Pam says hi.
Have fun on your date.
Very good. Talk to you later.
Bye.
You first.
- Oh, nice try, Josh!
- Not. It hit the rim.
Okay, and...
Okay, double or nothing.
What? We didn't bet anything, Michael.
- Well, let's...
- You know, we should go.
- Come on, come on. Come on!
- We'll do it later.
Say, while I have you here,
can I talk to you about some new and
exciting advances to our product line?
Fine.
Jim and I have different
definitions of friendship.
I think it's talking and being friends
and Jim thinks it's moving to Connecticut
and being best friends with Josh.
Well...
phooey on that.
I, uh... I'm done. I am not going
to be speaking with him anymore.
Whatevs.
Long distance relationships never work.
That is so true.
Ready?
Okay, let me tell you
what we're looking for.
Sorry, my meeting ran late.
- Really?
- Yes, Jan. Really.
With a rep from Hammermill.
They're exclusive with Staples.
Used to be.
Evan'll call you in the morning
to work out the details.
We can now sell Hammermill products.
Yes!
Well, Michael...
I underestimated you.
Yeah, well, maybe next time
you will estimate me.
Dwight's room key.
And Dwight's room.
What can I say? Old habits die hard.
D?
Oh, my God. Dwight got a hooker.
Oh, my God, I gotta call...
I gotta call somebody.
I don't even know who to call.
Dwight got a hooker!
So, Alan, Pam is obsessed with
your cartoons. She reads them every day.
Oh, great.
I don't want ketchup.
You love ketchup. He loves ketchup.
So how do you come up
with your cartoons?
I just...I kinda think
about stuff that I see.
Or dream them.
You dream in cartoons? How fun.
Hey! First guest!
You are going to have
some tequila, my friend.
I thought there was a party in here.
This is the party.
- This is room 308?
- Party central.
So what can I do you for?
All right.
See this one is great.
Because it could work
on a couple of different levels.
Freedom fries for the table.
Freedom fries. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
people always say, like,
don't be edgy. But,
I don't know any other way.
Yeah, you get it.
Well, it was really nice
meeting you, Alan.
Yeah, next time bring some of your
illustrations. I'll let you pick my brain.
- More freedom fries.
- Yeah.
- That's great.
- Okay.
I went on a date.
It wasn't a love connection.
I think when I like someone again,
I'll just kinda know.
Michael.
Am I the first to arrive?
People have been filtering in and out.
- Can I get a drink?
- What?
- Sure.
- You like cosmos?
- Yeah, sure. Sounds good.
So why are you here?
Is Josh busy?
- Michael...
- I get it, you know?
- Did I do something?
- No, I totally get it.
He made a better paper airplane.
Stamford is better in sales.
I get it. We had some fun.
We had some laughs.
Wait wait wait,
I didn't transfer because of you.
You're a good boss.
You're a great boss.
Not better than Josh.
Michael, it's not about...
I transferred because of Pam.
Oh, my God.
You don't even know. She's single now.
No, I heard something about that.
It's just, I kind of
put it all on the line.
Twice, actually.
And she said no. Twice.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you know what? I will talk to her.
- No, that's okay.
- Yeah.
- That's all right.
- I will.
I'll talk to her.
You should at least talk to...Roy.
I mean, he knows exactly
how you're feeling.
Yeah.
Okay, maybe.
- Are we early?
- Hey, no.
You know, people have been
filtering in and out.
- Hey. Evan, this is Jim.
- How are ya?
- Hey, Arnie Risman. Michael, Jim.
- Hey, Arnie, how you doing?
- You guys work together?
- No, we used to.
- Yeah.
- Now, we're friends.
Best friends.
Some people need dozens of friends
to say, hey, look at me, I'm popular.
But not me. I'm very picky.
I need three. Maybe two?
When you meet that someone special,
you'll just know.
Because a real relationship...
can't be forced.
It should just come
about effortledlessly.
Would you do the pleasure of
hitting the lights, sir?
Whoa. What are all those stains?
- Blood, urine, or semen.
- Oh, God, I hope it's urine.
www.tvsubtitles.net