Oh!!!
she's absolutely ????
He!
Oh, sorry
He's dressing color pink
that's paper colour
well, look at that
- cute
- thank you
oh, may I ....
I am sure
Hey, look at me
I am a baby
Hey Mama
I'm thirsty
I'm thirsty, Mama.
I want some milk.
And you know where
milk comes from.
The catch 22 team vous présente...
Episode 9 Saison 3
"The Convict "
http://www.theofficeus.fr/
http://www.forom.com/
Hey
You almost done?
Just about, yeah.
Now.
Yes, I've started to see Karen.
It's very new,
and I'm not really ready to talk
about it openly yet just because
I think once the word
gets out there,
it might affect the way
people behave around us.
Or...I don't know.
Just not yet.
ah, Jan, it, um,
looks like a check.
A piece of paper
of some sort.
A receipt.
Jan, this is Angela Martin
from accounting.
Mm-hmm.
Look, we have a rebate
from the Federal Work
Opportunity Program.
And no one knows
what that means.
We get that money
for hiring an ex-convict.
I didn'tire an ex-convict.
Unless they mean Toby.
Convicted rapist.
I'm just kidding.
When did the check come?
Last week.
Okay, that's when
the branches merged,
so Josh must've been taking
advantage of this program.
Smart move.
One of the Stamford
people is a criminal?
Hey, Jan,
speaking of Stamford,
Hannah brought in a baby.
Jan, which one of new
employees is a criminal?
A reformed convict.
And I'm not sure.
Don't hang on.
Let me email our H. R.
Stay on the line.
Who is it?
Hannah?
Hmm.
Andy?
Andy.
Martin?
Oh, you are such a racist.
- Wait, why am I a racist?
- Because you think he's black.
He is black, right?
Stop it.
Stop it right now!
Okay, 's someone
named Martin Nash.
Yeah!
Michael?
Why did the convict
have to be a black guy?
It is such a stereotype.
I just wish that Josh had made
a more progressive choice,
like a white guy...
who went to prison
for polluting
a black guy's lake.
I wonder what he did.
In our society,
a black man can be arrested
for almost anything.
He was probably
at a sporting event
and saw some people
pushing each other.
And he intervened.
Why would anyone
go to jail for that?
So...
what we need to do
is to forget
about this whole
"Martin in prison" thing.
People will draw
unfair conclusions about Martin
and/or black people.
- Cool.
- Okay.
Angela?
Sure.
Let's protect the convicts
at the expense
of the general feeling
of safety in the workplace.
As a 90-pound female
that sits in an ill-lit,
rarely-visited corner of the office,
naturally I agree with that.
Good.
All right.
-  Jim Halpert.
- I am so horny.
Okay, I can't help you
with that.
Oh,  I think you can,
Big Tuna.
Tell me about that
Indian chick Kelly.
She seems pretty slutty.
Good for a romp in the sack.
She is dating Ryan, I think.
Oh, and I care why?
She's high maintenance.
Next, How about...
Blondes are more fun, come on.
trust me on that.
Yeah, trust me.
That would be fun
for no one.
- Okay, fine.
- Okay.
Pam, the receptionist.
Pam. Should I go for it?
Absolutely you should.
Jackpot.
Just try to be cool.
I am cool.
Are you cool really?
I'm so cool.
Tell me what is
going on
Um, Martin from Stamford
was at one time in prison.
No, Dwight.
Be cool, be cool.
I am greatly concerned
about having a convict
in the office.
And I do not care
if that convict is white,
black, Asian, German,
or some kind of halfsie.
I do not like criminals.
Oh, God.
All righty.
Let's get started.
What is she into?
I know Pam pretty well.
I know the things
that she likes.
And just as important,
I know the things
that she hates.
So one of the things
that she likes is pranks.
And the things
that she hates...
Frisbee-based competitions.
Are you kidding?
I started the main
Frisbee golf club at Cornell
where I went to college.
I live to frolf.
Lead off with that.
Okay.
She loves hunting.
She also loves those ads
for Six Flags
with the old guy.
Got it.
Also...do you speak
pig Latin?
Hey, Martin.
How's it going?
Good.
Getting settled, you know.
Ah, good, good.
Good.
Just a second.
Everybody, may I have
your attention please?
I realize that a lot of you
have already heard
that Martin here
has had some trouble
with the law.
But I just want
to declare publicly
that I trust him completely.
And that anybody who doesn't
is an ignorant,
dumb person, okay?
As a matter of fact,
you show me a white man
you trust,
and I will show you
a black man
that I trust even more.
Pam, tell me
a white person you trust.
My dad.
Danny Glover.
- Yeah?
- Jonas Salk.
- Who?
- Justin Timberlake.
Oh, please.
Colin Powell.
Hey, I got one.
Yeah?
Jesus.
Apollo Creed.
Close your eyes.
Picture a convict.
What's he wearing?
Nothing special.
Baseball  cap on backward,
baggy pants.
He says something
ordinary like,
"Yo, that's shizzle."
Okay, now slowly
open your eyes again.
Who were you picturing?
A black man?
Wrong.
That was a white woman.
Surprised?
Well, shame on you.
So, you all want to know
what I was in for?
No, that's not cool.
You don't
have to tell them.
I really don't mind.
It was a stupid mistake.
I was working in finance,
and I got involved
in some insider trading.
So I spent a little time in the clink.
Oh!
That is awesome.
I had Martin explain to me
three times
what he got arrested for,
because...
it sounds an awful lot
like  I what I do here
every day.
What was prison like?
Not terrible.
Boring.
We do the same thing
every day.
But at least
we'd get outdoors time.
You got outdoors time?
Two hours every day.
Sometimes we'd play
pickup football games.
Michael, why don't we get
outdoors time?
Yeah, some days
I never go outside.
Well, we are
running a business.
What was your like?
Not good.
It was a little bit bigger
than Michael's office.
But you know,
I really only slept there.
You know, during the day
our time was our own.
They had classes.
I took some
watercolor classes.
- They have art classes?
- Yeah.
They have business
classes there?
They did, taught by some
Harvard Business School guys.
A lot of the guys also that
were in the class
he inmates a lot of them
have gone on to do
extraordinary things in
business. Terrible things.
Kind of sounds like prison's
better than Dunder-Mifflin.
Okay, well,
that's not true.
I would so
rather be in prison.
Prison sounds great.
No, you would not.
This place is not prison.
It's way better than prison.
Baby!
Hello, baby!
Here, you want to play
with this?
You can't give
paperclips to a baby.
He could swallow.
Oh, it's okay.
I've got tons of 'em.
You like that?
Goo goo goo goo?
Pam-a-lama-ding-dong.
Listen, you're cute.
There's no getting
around it.
So I don't know
if I like country music,
but I was thinking
maybe one of these days
we could drive out
to the fields,
crank up some tunes.
Smoke a few Macanudos.
Maybe even toss
a disc around.
Utway ooday ooyay
inkthay, Ampay?
Wow. I--
Shh!
Think about it.
I'll hit you back.
Wow.
That was...
W ow.
Okay, listen up,
everybody.
Um, you guys said that prison
was better than this place.
And I heard you
loud and clear.
So I am instituting
some changes
to make this
more like prison.
We are going to start
with an hour of outdoor time.
So let's go!
Michael,
it's freezing out.
I can't feel my toes.
Why don't we
pump some iron?
Anybody want to pump up?
What is that,
like, five pounds?
It's two and half.
I'm not going for bulk.
I'm going for tone.
I'm going back inside.
It's freezing.
Yeah, it is freaking
cold out here.
Anybody wants to stay out,
you got about 27 minutes
of rec time.
Oh, hey, Martin!
You have TV in the joint?
Yeah, in the rec room.
Ah, got a ten-inch
black and white?
Actually, our TV was
bigger than that one.
These people do realize
how lucky they are.
This office is
the American Dream.
And they would rather
be in the hole.
Oh, Andy.
I thought of one last tack
you can take with Pam.
- Yeah, what?
- Quick question.
Do you play the guitar?
I play the banjo.
Hold on.
Let me think about that.
Yes, that'll work.
But can you sing in a sexy
high falsetto voice?
* You know I can, my man *
Yep, that's perfect.
Hey.
I'm gonna go get
my banjo out of my car.
Perfect.
What is going on?
I'm messing with Andy.
I'm sending him to all
the women in the office
with just
terrible information
on how to get them
to go out with him.
I love it.
I want in.
Who's the target?
Oh, you know what?
- It was gonna be Pam, but--
- Perfect.
What do I do?
Just give me an assignment.
Oh, you know what though?
I feel like I already
sicced him on Pam.
We'll give her a break.
Let's think
of someone else.
All right, everybody.
There has been
a lot of name-calling
against our office today.
Corporate maligning, slurring.
Much of it coming
from one of you
who claims that
prison is better
than here.
And none of us
can say "boo"
because none of us
have ever been to prison.
Well, here's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Somebody else who has
been to prison
who can tell you what
it is really like.
I'm  Prison Mike.
You know why they call me
Prison Mike?
Do you really expect us to
believe you're somebody else?
Do you really expect me
to not push you up against
the wall, beeyotch?
Hey!
Whoa, whoa!
Hey, that's just the way
we talk in the clink.
Been a lot of fun talk
about prison today.
But I am here
to scare you straight.
I am here
to scare you straight!
In prison, you are
somebody's bitch.
Oh, and you.
You, my friend, would be
da belle of da ball.
Don't drop the soap.
Michael, please.
Where did you learn
all of this?
Internet.
So not prison.
And prison.
It's 50/50.
Both.
Look, prison stinks
is what I'm saying.
It's not like
you can go home
and recharge your batteries
and come back in the morning
and be with your friends
having fun in the office.
What did you do,
Prison Mike?
I stole.
And I robbed.
And I kidnapped
the President's son
and held him for ransom.
That is quite
the rap sheet, Prison Mike.
An I never got caught neither.
Well, you're in prison,
but, mm-hmm.
Prison Mike, what was
the food like in prison?
Gruel sandwiches.
Gruel omelets.
Nothing but gruel.
Plus, you can eat
your own hair.
Wow.
Prison sounds horrible.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, thank you, Andy.
Thanks.
Prison Mike,
what's the very, very
worst thing about prison?
Don't encourage him,
Dwight.
The worst thing about prison
was-- was the Dementors.
They were flying
all over the place,
and they were scary.
And then they'd come down
and they'd suck the soul
out of your body,
and it hurt.
Dementors like
in Harry Potter?
No, not Harry Potter.
There were no movies
in prison.
This is my point.
You guys got it soft
and cushy.
This place is
freaking awesome.
The people are awesome.
Your boss is nice.
Everybody seems
to get along.
People are tolerant.
People who would jump
to conclusions
can redeem themselves.
Nobody's nobody's bitch.
I hope that this scared you.
And from me, Prison Mike,
to you,
I just want to thank you
for listening to me.
And letting me be a part
of your life today.
'Cause you got
a good life!
You got a good life.
A good life.
So, what do you think?
It doesn't sound so great,
does it?
Wow.
Thank you.
Um, that must have been hard
for you to relive that.
Both of you.
Yeah, that wasn't really
at all my experience.
There were
certain elements
of what you performed
I've seen on television,
but it didn't remind me
of my time in prison.
Okay, okay.
Fine.
You guys think prison
is so great?
All right.
Well, here you go.
Okay, Michael.
Come on, let us out.
No, if you think prison
is so wonderful,
then enjoy prison.
- Are we locked in here?
- They are such babies.
I am going to
leave them in there
until they can
appreciate what it's like
to have freedom.
And if this doesn't
bother them,
then I am out of ideas.
Hey!
Let us out of here!
Hey, I have--
Shh!
This is Toby.
Hey, Pam.
Where are you
calling from?
Michael, why is everyone
locked in the conference room?
They were very disreectful
to me and to the office.
And Martin has had
a bad influence.
To think that I gave him
the benefit of a doubt.
It's--
Well, you're gonna have to
let them out or I will.
Okay, you know what, Toby?
I am teaching them
a lesson, so...
You know
they're teasing you.
I mean, obviously this is
a much nicer place
than an actual prison.
We get paid to be here.
We go home afterward
and have social lives.
And we have parties here.
They're teasing you.
To be funny.
Okay, nutcases,
get out of there.
Good work.
Long day.
Really long.
Why don't you guys
head home early?
Time off
for good behavior!
Good job.
Enjoy your freedoms.
Martin went from being
a new guy from Stamford
to a convict,
to my friend,
back to a convict,
then to kind of
a nuisance, actually,
if we can be
completely honest.
And finally to a quitter.
And I will not miss him.
And that is not
because he is black.
www.tvsubtitles.net