Woo! Wow, it is raining
cats and dogs out there.
Holy moly.
Phyllis says the same
12 cliches every time it rains.
So... I promised everyone that if
she says them all by noon today,
I will send out
for hot chocolates.
So how's the drive in?
Oh, nobody knows
how to drive in the rain.
You don't say?
Yeah, you know the roads
are actually the slickest
in the first half hour?
Oh, the plants
are gonna love this.
I actually sleep better
when it's raining.
Tell me about it.
Time's almost up.
How many are left?
Just one.
"This weather makes me
to stay at home,
curled up
with a good book."
Phyllis.
This rain... Does it make you
wanna be doing something?
What do you mean?
You know,
like aren't some things
just so nice and cozy
in the rain?
Hey, come on.
Lots of things
are cozy in the rain.
And that's noon.
Exactly.
I mean, normally the rain
would make me
want to stay at home,
curled up with a good book.
But everybody's being
so nice to me today.
I'm really happy being here.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ My girlfriend's back
and there's gonna be trouble ♪
♪ hey la, hey la ♪
- ♪ my girlfriend's back ♪
- ♪ his girlfriend's back ♪
Anyway, I know
it's the end of the day.
We just wanted to stop by
and say hi.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Kev!
- Yeah.
- Nice... sweater.
- Thank you.
Nellie was nice enough
to give it to me.
She's sweet.
I just wish there was pockets.
What happened to Old Salty?
Nellie let me bobblize him.
His name is now Captain Mutato.
I've written quite a bit
of X-Men fan fiction.
Captain Mutato is half man,
half mermaid.
So he can fight crime as a man,
and make love as a mermaid.
Most of my writing involves
the latter.
Okie doke.
Yes?
Whoa.
Well, you must be the famous
Nellie Bertram
I've been hearing all about.
I am the famous Andy Bernard
you've been hearing all about.
Oh, yes.
I just want to thank you
for jumping in
and minding the store
during my temporary absence.
You are most welcome.
Anyway, now that I'm back,
I would love
to have my office back
whenever you get a chance.
No.
Obviously, we'll figure out
the, uh, logistics
of moving all of this stuff
out of here.
But... You know,
the sooner the better.
- Mm-hmm.
- Get back to normalcy.
Hmm, no.
And then just lay him
in his crib,
and then bicycle his legs.
And then after Jim quiets down,
you do the same thing
with your baby.
But if he keeps having problems,
just give me a call.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you so much.
But seriously,
we don't wanna bother you
- any more than we already have.
- That's it.
It's no bother.
You guys are our friends.
Ravi, our amazing pediatrician,
was asking us
if we knew any girls.
And I said
I know the perfect girl.
Yep.
Because Kelly is Indian, and...
Oh, that's it.
Race had nothing to do with it.
I just knew
they'd be good together.
Why!
Kelly has been a handful
in the past.
But she's had a bad influence.
She's like an addict.
And I just had
to get her clean.
Get lower.
Um, also, little tip,
never shake the baby.
Sorry, just to be clear,
you're saying do not shake
the baby.
Don't shake the baby.
Um, a lot times,
parents get frustrated
'cause the baby's crying
and they shake the baby.
And you gotta--
You can't do that.
- Don't shake our baby?
- Yeah.
Okay. I'd never heard
that before.
- So, thank you.
- Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm glad
you said something.
Me too.
Kelly and I broke up and
she can do whatever she wants.
And her new boyfriend
seems awesome...
If you're into Indian people.
I'm not.
Hey, um...
What's the deal with this guy?
He's really into Kelly, huh?
Yeah, they're really great
together.
Maybe we weren't
right together,
but... it's weird.
I'd rather she be alone
than with somebody.
Is that love?
That's about it, yeah.
Nellie!
You've been terrific
in your interim capacity.
But,
Andrew is the rightful manager,
so if you would just
give him his office--
- No.
I'm sorry.
This is what
I was trying to tell you.
I'm not accustomed
to people saying no to me.
Oh, Bobby,
get accustomed to it,
because then it feels good
when they finally say yes.
You're both adults.
I'm sure you can...
figure this out
between yourselves.
I never allow sexual desire to
influence a business decision.
So I find it best to...
recuse myself temporarily
until I've had a chance
to make love,
and then go back and...
analyze the situation
rationally.
Buffett operates the same way.
I'm gonna count down from five,
and if are not
out of my office,
I'm going to dock
your pay $100.
Okay.
Five... four...
You can't dock my pay.
Angela!
Dock Andy's pay $100!
On it!
Great!
Um, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Angela... Please dock
Nellie's pay $100.
Angela?
- Do you want to go again?
- Angela?
Let's go again.
5...4...
Ooh, she's counting again.
- 3... 2... 1.
- Oh, oh!
Angela, $200!
You got it.
Seriously, Angela?
I got a little bit
of an anger problem.
Got me in some trouble
a couple years ago.
When I see him start
to get mad, I just...
Put my hand on his arm
like this.
I know what, let's go...
$10,000.
5...4...
You're just saying numbers.
It's meaningless.
- 3...
- It's literally like...
2...
One.
There you go.
Hey, we're gonna have
a nice, hot date.
Hey. So last night was so not
a big deal.
Oh, yeah, I was just tired.
- We both were.
- Yeah.
Plus, I was definitely
not my normal sexy self.
Whoa. No.
Are you kidding?
You were so sexy.
Just the thought of you
last night, like,
crazy turns me on.
It just didn't last night.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah.
I know it's not... a big deal.
I found this the other day
while I was journaling,
and... they reminded me
of you.
Oh, those are from
our weekend at the Timeshare.
Yeah, the fractional
ownership property.
Oh, we took this one
right before we got
in that huge fight.
I don't even remember
what that fight was about.
You were being really bratty
about where we would
go out to dinner.
But--
All I remember...
is how pretty you looked
taking those pictures of me.
Anyway, if you wanna order
prints of your own,
I can send you the link.
I'm in love with Kelly Kapoor.
And I don't know
how I'm gonna feel tomorrow
or the next day
or the day after that,
but I do know that right here,
right now,
all I can think about
is spending
the rest of my life with her.
Again, that could change.
When you lost
the manager job...
Yes?
Did it affect you
outside of the office?
How?
I don't know
what the technical term is.
Hmm.
Penial...
softiosis.
Erin, I am so glad
that you trusted me.
You came to the exact
right person for this.
No, I have never once
experienced
anything remotely like that.
Never.
- Oh... okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
- Washington Monument.
- Okay.
- Eiffel Tower.
- Okay, okay.
Hmm.
I saw you were getting along
with Ryan again.
He's so sweet.
He pointed to my latte
and he said,
"Kelly, that will be
the color of our children."
Yeah, he's so great.
Remember how it felt
when he cheated on you though?
Which time?
I am not going to let Kelly
throw her life away on Ryan.
And it has nothing to do
with access to my pediatrician.
Why you would even ask
or were going to ask,
because I-- I feel like
that question was coming.
One of Toby's eyes
is getting smaller.
So there's that.
Gabe bragged about having
an extra ticket
to the air show this weekend.
And Meredith said
she was interested,
and then Gabe said immediately
that his friend might be
taking the ticket.
So I'll keep you posted
on that.
Every day, I brief Nellie on
what's going on in the office.
Most of it's irrelevant.
But a good informer doesn't
judge what's worth passing on.
Oh, and Andy lost
his masculinity,
so congratulations on that.
What do you mean?
Erin made it clear to me
that he was unable to perform
sexually last night.
By contrast, I went to sleep
with an erection so large
it was like I was wearing
no blanket at all.
Wow, I knew you'd win,
but you just demolished him!
I'm a little bit jealous, actually.
Reduced him to a mere ant.
I just wanted to take
the man's job, not his manhood.
Okay, I would like
to invite everyone
into the conference room.
You can't call a meeting.
But I would like
to have a meeting
in the conference room
right now!
So let's get
in the conference room.
Thank you.
Good.
Thank you for coming
to my meeting.
Okay, if you would like
to take a seat,
- we can get started.
- Oh!
Can't do it
'cause I gotta run a meeting.
- So.
- No.
Wanted to talk
to all of you guys
about importance...
and know that each
and every one of you
is vitally important.
Andrew, not everyone here
is important.
And the word is impotence.
Which is important
in its own way.
So if you'd just like
to take a seat, Andy.
"Take a man's job,
but leave him his balls."
Margaret Thatcher
said that... probably.
Don't know.
Don't read.
Didn't see the movie.
This meeting is not about
any one person in particular.
It is a human problem.
It's not just a human problem.
Flounders frequently
experience impotence,
especially when converting
from male to female
and then back again to male.
Nellie, does the person
affected by this
want us to help her
in any way in particular?
Oh, oh, it's not me.
No, no.
I've never had any problem
in that arena.
And I have been with several
older men.
- How old?
Jinx. Buy me some coke.
Dwight told me
about it earlier.
Dwight!
You promised.
Dwight couldn't get it up
for Nellie?
No, no, no, no.
It's not me.
I'm gonna prove it
right here and now.
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
- Stop that!
- Dwight!
Dwight, stop that.
Stop it.
Fine, it was me.
I couldn't-- I had a problem
with Erin last night.
Happy?
I had a lot on my mind
last night...
and I didn't perform.
Okay? It happens
to plenty of guys.
It's usually not followed
by a giant workplace discussion
and an interview.
Every guy in this room
has been touched
by this affliction.
Tuna.
T-dog!
Um...
I have other issues.
I'm terrible at math.
Overweight.
You--
You're in great shape.
A lot better shape than I am,
tell you what.
It seems Andy is the only one
with this problem.
- Fascinating.
I don't really see
what the problem is.
Erin doesn't even like sex,
remember?
You said it feels like
getting tackled by a skeleton.
Chumbo, come on, help me out.
Any problems
with little Chumbo?
Tip-top shape.
Oh... Stanley.
No.
Mm-mm.
Creed, you are 1,000 years old.
Haven't heard any complaints.
Wouldn't care if I did.
Okay, so I-I-I--
Actually, Andy,
I think maybe we experienced it.
What happened?
- That a couple of times--
- Couple of times.
Jim, maybe you could tell us
about one of those times.
- Yeah, Jim.
- Get it out there.
Um... I don't--
Uh, yes, that time
that it was very late.
Uh, we'd had sex
so many times already,
I was exhausted.
I could barely see.
- Okay, stop.
- I was very drunk.
If it makes you
feel any better,
I never had an orgasm
until I was 42.
And then when I did,
it lasted till I was 44.
43 was ju--
I got nothing done.
I've read-- And I don't know
anything about this personally--
But they say prostate
stimulation can help.
Ugh.
This is just--
This American Life
I think I heard it on.
No, that's absolutely the case.
I know, right?
You know, my rectal
electro-ejaculator
is rated for bovine use only,
but I could let you rent it.
Andy, why don't you tell us
about the best erection
of your life?
Or does anyone else have
any remarkable erections
they'd like to share?
Wow, what are we talking about?
Toby, doesn't HR have
some rules against talking
about this kind of stuff?
Erin, HR is a joke.
I can't do anything
about anything.
The most important thing
to remember
is do not stress about this.
Stress just makes it worse,
and then you stress more.
And that's a vicious spiral.
I almost didn't come in today.
Dad, don't think of it
as a demotion.
Just think of it as a promotion
to a lower level.
I don't think you have
to tell your friends anything.
It hasn't been decided yet.
Erin, on phone memos,
you're righting the date
American style.
Month, day, year.
I prefer it day, month, year.
Small, bigger, biggest.
Oh, sexual innuendo.
Not intentional.
Shut up!
I am sick of your dumb
opinions.
And if you don't like the way
that I take phone messages,
here.
Take 'em yourself!
Oh, and another thing.
Our sex life is none
of your businesses!
And Andy is the manager,
not Nellie!
Stop protecting me.
I'm a man-- I can protect myself.
This is misdirected anger
and I'm sorry.
I don't mean to lash out
at you.
There's a lot coming up
right now, all at once!
Dad, go to hell!
I'm taller than you!
Okay, just calm down.
You are not the manager.
I earned that job.
I was personally chosen after
Robert was chosen and quit.
Andy, why don't you just
take a seat?
Why don't you
take a seat, you idiot?
And why don't you
take all your stupid memos
and your stupid pens...
and your dumb caramels?
- And your stupid face!
- Oh.
And your stupid office!
- Ah!
- Ow.
He does not like that wall.
Maybe we'll get sent to
anger management together.
That would actually be cool.
I'd love for you to meet
some of the guys.
Andy, Erin,
you can join us now.
Hey, I hear you been
bad-mouthing me to Kelly.
All I did was remind her that
you used to treat her badly.
Well, that's your opinion
and it's her opinion,
but it's not my opinion.
If you have something bad
to say to me, Pam,
say it to my face.
Fair enough.
Um...
I don't think
you're a very good person.
And forgive me, but I feel like
I've said this to you before.
I don't like you very much.
Well, a lot of people would say
that I'm a better match
for Kelly than Ravi is.
Oh, come on, Ryan.
Really?
- Ravi's way better.
- For Kelly?
Yeah.
Man, you're insane right now.
Ravi's the whole package.
I've never met Ravi personally,
but I'm gonna go ahead and say
just having knowing
you short while, Brian,
that I prefer Ravi.
And again, I've never even
met the guy.
Kelly, I wrote you
the most amazing love poem.
But I can't even read it.
My heart couldn't handle it.
- Oh, come.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Read it, please.
I love amazing poetry.
No, it would cause me
too much pain.
Read through the pain.
Be strong.
This poem would crush you!
Ryan, go away!
She found herself
a beautiful boyfriend!
Yeah, man,
he's absolutely gorgeous.
- Please leave her alone.
- You see, Kelly?
Our love scares them.
It screws up
their cookie-cutter world.
Ravi makes me incredibly happy.
And Ryan puts me
through so much drama.
So I guess
I just have to decide
which of those
is more important to me.
Andy, we're going
to go with Nellie as manager
and put you back
on the sales team.
I promise you, in time,
we'll all laugh
about this incident.
I already think
it's kinda funny.
No.
Excuse me?
I'm saying no.
- Well, you can't say no.
- No.
Oh, boo!
Boo!
Pam.
- Boo to you! Boo!
- You are toxic.
You are toxic!
Kelly, I have a few things
to say to you,
- and please don't interrupt.
- I wasn't going to interrupt.
Well, you do a lot,
so just don't-- Thank you.
I know that I haven't always
treated you the way that you,
for whatever reason,
feel you deserve to be treated.
But I wanna marry you,
Kelly Kapoor.
Maybe not today,
maybe not tomorrow.
But someday.
And probably.
Barf!
Ugh, you suck!
What is your problem?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can we turn this back around
quickly, please?
Can we turn this around
quickly?
- This is very important to me.
- Betsy, turn around.
Turn around.
Turn around!
Help me turn this fucking
thing around, please.
- Thank you.
- She don't wanna turn around.
Thank you.
Kelly, I can't promise you
that we'll always stay together.
I can't promise you
that I'll never cheat on you.
Nor should I.
Modern marriages
aren't built that way.
Men aren't built that way.
There's a very interesting
article I can email to you.
But I can tell you this.
Even if the odds are 50/50 that
we'll break up within the week,
I wanna roll those dice.
I love you, Kelly.
Ryan.
Will you roll those dice
with me?
You mean so much to me.
But... I love Ravi
and I choose him.
- No, you don't.
- I do.
No, you don't.
I hope we can still be friends.
Can I have a hug?
What?
This was really cool.
Well, it's good to see
Kelly's maturing.
Oh, God.
Look, Andrew, we can discuss
the specifics of the job.
No.
It's the apology.
I really have to insist.
- No.
- Stop saying no.
No.
Andrew, if you say no
one more time, you're fired.
So... is there anything else
you wanna say?
No.
I can't describe it.
I just, for the first time
in a long time,
I actually feel in control.
- I feel... alive.
- Here.
A-da, da, da, da.
I got it.
- But you hurt your hand.
- I... got it.
- Right now?
- Yes.
You're not a least a bit
curious to hear a poem
straight from Ryan's soul?
Not at all.
Can we go?
Kapoor and Kadesperate.
He watches...
- Second line.
- He is a drifter out to see...
It went the Indian Ocean in calms,
one speck of white remains
and waters called and Kelly grinned.
It's just so dumb...
but when he describes
himself as a child,
lost and...
Ryan can never know.
www.tvsubtitles.net