Hey. Ready?
Come on!
Show me excited.
- Yes!
- Yeah. I'm pretty excited too.
Today I'm headed over to the Job Fair
at Valley View High School
to find some new interns.
Wanna get some fresh blood...
youthanize this place.
- We doin' this thing?
- Yeah.
Oh, my god, Darryl.
You look like Barack Obama.
Everybody, I'm dating Barack Obama.
- Why you dressed like that?
- Like what?
Like you're applying for a loan.
Maybe he's going to church.
Or court.
Figured I'd look presentable.
You... went a different way.
- You look nice.
- Thank you.
Here's what we're going to do.
I'm going to instruct the kids
about management and sales.
Oscar will be
in charge of accounting.
Pam will be eye candy.
No, and also because
that is your alma mater.
Darryl will hire some kids
for the warehouse.
No need to worry with them because
they definitely ain't goin' to college.
What college did you go to, Mike?
Let's go!
Transcript: SwSub
Sync: DarKsh
Today I am meeting a potential client
on the golf course because...
Ryan put me on probation.
You remember Ryan.
He was the temp here.
Yeah. And...
It is not a good time for me
to lose my job since I have some...
pretty big long-term plans
in my personal life with Pam
that I'd like her parents
to be psyched about.
So I am about to do
something very bold at this job
that I've never done before...
Try.
Mr. Maguire.
It's been a couple of years.
Hey, Jim, how are ya?
Nice to see you, man.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no.
My grandfather
would be spinning in his urn
if he knew that I was out here
with a Dartmouth boy.
You take that shirt off right now,
or I will take it off for you, sir.
I am totally
and completely kidding!
Andy Bernard.
Cornell, '95.
Phil Maguire, Dartmouth, '74.
- Got some blisties.
- Yeah, you do.
Hit about 1,200 balls last night
in preparation for today,
so hands are a little tender.
It's actually not funny at all.
It's incredibly painful.
Let's make it interesting.
Say... 10 bucks a hole?
- Great.
- What are we talkin'?
Skins? Acey deucy?
Bingo bango bongo?
Sandies, barkies, arnies?
Wolf?
What?
I'm gonna take
this petty cash
that I got from Oscar
and turn it into next month's rent.
So many memories in this old gym.
Pretending I have PMS
so I didn't have to play volleyball.
so I didn't have to play basketball.
Those were the days.
Little over the top,
don't you think?
Show 'em what you brought, Mike.
- That's all we brought.
- This is all we need.
- We'll see.
- Yes, we will see, Oscar.
We will see,
because a blank sheet of paper
equals endless possibilities.
Conceptual.
All right.
We are...
open for business.
Hello.
- Andy, you're up. Let's go.
- Giddy-up. Let's do this.
People assume I'm great at golf,
but like everybody,
I hated golf lessons
when I was a kid, so...
I used to just hang out
with the sailing club instead.
Got my knot on.
Damn it!
Guys, do we have to stay all day?
I mean, Michael's gone.
Can't we just go?
Yeah. And I finished
my work months ago.
Excuse me, people.
It has come to my attention
that some of you have forgotten
who is in charge here.
When Michael is gone,
Jim is in charge.
When Jim is gone,
Andy and I are in charge.
When Andy is gone,
you answer to me.
Okay?
Excuse me, where do you
think you're going?
Oh, no, no.
You're not leaving.
No! Stanley.
Do not walk out that door!
If you walk out that door,
so help me, I will...
He left.
Last time I checked,
the american workday
ends at 5:00 P.M.
You will all stay at your desks
until that time
or you will suffer
the consequences.
What consequences?
I will tell on you.
There's some filing,
restocking the supply shelves,
replacing the water jug,
which nobody likes to do.
We...
- eat a lot of cake.
- Cool.
Yeah, and... you know, you basically,
you learn how an office runs.
- Hello.
- So...
Hi. Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Excuse me.
- This is Michael, my boss. Justin.
Hey...
remember what we talked about
in the car on the way out?
"Only the best and the brightest"?
He's nice, and he seems interested.
He's totally wrong, Pam.
- Hi.
- How you doin'?
Listen, I don't think
that a handsome, funny, smart,
funny-looking kid like you
should limit himself.
You could do whatever you wanna do.
You could be a classy janitor
or a cashier with dignity or a...
migraine worker.
Maybe for you,
paper should be more of a hobby.
- Sorry for wasting your time.
- Oh, no problem.
And he signed!
He put his name on the piece of...
Okay, that...
was supposed to be a blank canvas
on which to put their hopes and dreams,
and he just...
made it
into a stupid piece of paper.
We need another one immediately.
Yeah. The booth is lame without it.
- I only brought the one.
- Are you mental?
Michael, do you remember
you specifically told me
to only bring one sheet of paper?
You said it only takes
one sheet to make a difference.
And I said, "Are you sure, Michael?"
And you said, "Pam, Pam, Pam."
And then you sneezed in my tea.
And then you said, "Don't worry.
It's allergies." Do you remember that?
I... don't.
Okay. I'll go look for another one.
And that...
is why I need a smart intern.
So... how's the direct mail
business going?
I can't complain.
People love their junk mail.
Now, are you gettin'
all your paper from PPC, or...
You know what, Jim? I'm not really
looking to change things up right now.
I just came out here
to get out of the office,
so why don't we just play, okay?
Absolutely. Will do.
So I guess I'll just...
work on my short game.
Hello, there.
What is this company?
Well, it's funny that you should ask,
because it's really...
- more than a company.
- Dunder Mifflin. Paper.
- Thanks.
- It...
Okay...
Damn it, Oscar!
Yeah, I'm trying to lure
these kids into my booth.
But...
kids are very wary
of being lured these days.
Thank you, dateline.
Thank you.
- Extension 128.
- Hiya, pumpkin. It's Creed.
Say we're gonna ditch this bitch...
You in?
- No.
- You out?
Pumpkin's out!
Let's go, gang.
My old art room.
Oh! Maybe it's still here.
No.
No, they must have taken it down.
Never mind.
- What do you want?
- Michael, I know you're swamped.
I just thought you should know
that everyone in the office has left
except for Angela and I.
Do not worry, though.
I have taken down their names,
and I have docked them a personal day.
Who cares? I'm not there, neither's Jim.
Why should they have to be there?
So... what else is up?
Mich...
Thank you!
Wha... What is this?
- Piece of paper.
- This isn't Dunder Mifflin paper.
It's some sort of Pendleton crap.
I think they'll get
the spirit of it.
Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam!
We're dying here.
I want you to go back to the office,
and I want you to get the real stuff.
I want you to get
ultra white card stock.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
And don't call me Shirley.
Okay.
Ah, damn it!
You could just pick it up,
take the triple bogey.
Yeah, I...
I'll get it out.
Thank you.
Yep.
Come on, Tuna!
Hey. Can't really talk now.
What's up?
Just checkin' in.
How's it going?
You know.
We'll see. We'll see.
I just drove 20 miles round trip
back to the office to get Michael
a single sheet of white paper.
So... I could have just had them
fax it to me, I guess.
Oh, I like you.
Talk to you later?
Yeah, all right.
Bye.
All right.
I'm sorry, I got to annoy you
one more time.
What if I bring down
shipping costs?
You can try.
But I looked at your prices.
Even with free shipping...
doesn't work.
It's just...
it's not in the stars, Jim.
Six.
- Yeah...
- All right, race to the next hole!
Winner gets ten bucks.
Wait... wait for me!
- Andy!
- Shortcut! Shortcut!
I fell in the sand trap.
All of these jobs suck.
I would rather live jobless
on a beach somewhere
off the money
from a large inheritance
than to have to work
in any one of these crapholes.
They suck.
Hey.
Game over.
Justintime.
- Hi.
- Justincase.
- What's your last name?
- Polznik.
"This... just in:
"Justin Polznik."
Justin is the ugly girl
in the movie
who takes off her glasses,
and she's hot.
And you realize that she was always hot,
she was just wearing glasses,
and that you were the blind one.
He's the most...
important thing in my life
right now.
I want you...
to meet my family. Come on.
Oscar Martinez,
accountant extraordinaire.
- This is Justin.
- Hey.
This is Darryl Philbin.
Isn't he big?
And you already met her,
Pam Beesly, office hottie.
She will do you.
No. No.
But she has already dated two guys
in the office that we know of, so...
this could be number three,
you never...
Come here.
I would never say this to her face,
but she's a wonderful person
- and a gifted artist.
- Why wouldn't you say that to her face?
So...
What do you think?
Think these guys are nice?
Guys I didn't bring are even better.
Justin...
I'm willing to commit right now.
Would you do me the honor...
of spending the summer with us
at Dunder Mifflin?
I think...
I think you are very special.
You didn't want me before.
- That's what you said.
- No, I didn't.
You were... you were
kind of a jerk to me.
I...
And I'm gonna go now.
Why don't...
Bless you.
Thank you.
Okay, Jim, you owe me 120.
And Phil, you owe me 230.
Let's open a tab, 'cause you and me
are gonna be playin' more often.
- Count me in.
- No.
All right.
Okay.
You had some fun and...
and got paid for it.
So let me just get
my last shot in there.
- Is there anything you can do for me?
- I'll tell you what.
My fiscal year ends in two months.
Let's talk then.
- Sound good?
- Absolutely.
Good playing with you guys.
You know, it's a tough thing
seeing a grown man take six shots
to get out of a sand trap, but...
I had to give Phil credit
for not quitting.
Which is what I told him.
I also told him
that I don't quit either...
and I'd call him every single day
until he gave me his business.
Which he then did,
after...
15 minutes of me blocking his car.
So I am now his paper supplier.
And I shot a 102 today,
so I'm feelin' pretty good.
The Job Fair will be closing
in five minutes.
Eighth period will commence
as scheduled.
Hold down the fort.
I have to do something.
Excuse me.
If you can hear me,
I would like you to look around
at all these companies
and know
that none of them
are good enough for you.
H&R block?
Come on!
I mean,
I don't even know what they do.
"Frank Regan Funeral Home"?
Too much formaldehyde.
The Air Force?
Air Force is cool.
The refreshments?
Bush league, you know?
That's not what you want.
Dunder...
That... Okay.
I see security is coming,
so I just wanted to say
come to Dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin,
a great place to work.
Anybody? Show of hands?
Anybody wanna intern at Dunder Mifflin?
We do not offer college credit,
we cannot give you any sort of pay,
but it is a really fun
work environment.
Anybody?
Show of hands?
Damn it. Okay.
I'm gonna wrap it up here.
Thank you...
for your time,
and drive safe.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Beers?
- You closed it?
- I closed it.
Yes!
- Congratulations to you, sir.
- Thank you very much. Appreciate it.
- Well done. Nice job.
- Thank you.
You know what?
Screw this.
Today I did something stupid.
I questioned myself,
and I'll never do that again.
'Cause I look at somebody
like Jim Halpert,
and I think that guy
can do anything he wants to do.
He could...
do anything,
and he chooses to work here
selling paper.
Just like me.
Yeah. Kiss her.
Kiss her good.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I was just wondering
what kind of jobs do you guys have?
- Are you interested in graphic design?
- Yeah.
- Can I fill out an application?
- Absolutely. Here.
Take a seat.
I should let you know right away
this is just an entry level job.
It's really basic.
We're looking for like a self-starter,
someone who can meet deadlines and
just pretty much just go the extra mile.
- I can do that.
- Great, and...
Obviously, we're looking
for someone who knows Photoshop
and Dreamweaver, Corel Painter,
Illustrator, After Effects...
All the basics.
I don't know any of those.
It's actually not super-complicated.
I'm sure there's some sort of, like,
adult education classes
in the area.
But if you're really serious, one thing
about New York or Philadelphia...
They got amazing programs
out there for design.
- New York or Philadelphia.
- Yeah.
All right.
Cool. Well, thanks.
- And I'll look into those.
- You should.
- New York or Philadelphia.
- Absolutely.
- That's where the action is.
- Thanks.
www.tvsubtitles.net