...But the Lord of the Rings trilogy,
if you see it back to back...
Dunder Mifflin this is Pam.
Pam, it's Michael. Help me,
I need help right now !
- Michael, what's wrong ?
- I'm hurt, I have hurt myself.
- Oh my God !
- Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait !
This is not looking good Pam !
Michael, do you need me
to call you an ambulance ?
No, I want you to pick me up.
- Okay.
- What's going on ?
I thought you said
that you were hurt.
- I am hurt. I hurt my foot.
- I'm sorry ? Pam, what's going on ?
I want to come to work...
...but I need you to come pick me up.
- Ohh, God !
- Hey, whoa ! Michael !
- Oh, God !
- It's okay. It's Jim.
Just say again, really loudly,
uh, what happened.
Okay, Buhh !
I burned my foot.
Very badly on my Foreman grill
and I now need someone to come
and bring me into work.
You burned YOUR foot
on a Foreman grill ?
I enjoy having breakfast in bed.
I like waking up with
the smell of bacon. Sue me.
And since I don't have a butler,
I have to do it myself.
So, most nights before I go to bed,
I will lay six strips of bacon out
on my George Foreman grill.
Then I go to sleep.
When I wake up, I plug in the grill.
I go back to sleep again.
Then I wake up to the smell
of crackling bacon.
It is delicious, it's good for me.
It's a perfect way to start the day.
Today I got up,
I stepped onto the grill
and it clamped down
on my foot, that's it.
I don't see what's so hard
to believe about that.
Pam, could you come get me ?
Uh, I have to stay here
and answer the phone.
Okay, could someone come
and get me, please ? Ryan ?
Michael, you should stay home and rest.
There's no toilet paper here.
Could Ryan...
Tell Ryan to bring toilet paper !
Could you tell him that ?
Can you hop ?
I tried hopping Kevin,
and I bumped my elbow
against the wall,
and now my elbow
has a "protruberence".
No one wants to pick me up ?!
What is going on ?
Michael is, um, sick.
And he wants one of us
to rescue him.
- I'm not sick, I'm...
- I'm coming, Michael !
- I'm going to save you !
- Don't ! Is that Dwight ?
- I do not want Dwight.
- Hold on Michael, I am coming !
- Wait there !
- I do not want Dwight !
Michael, why don't you call
your girlfriend ?
I don't have a girlfriend.
But you said you went out
with her this weekend.
It was all made up.
Just, someone come, okay ?
Anyone. Anyone but Dwight.
- What was that ?
- What WAS that ?
He hit the pole.
- It's broken, right ? He can't...
- Oh my gosh.
- Oh my God.
- Oh my Gosh.
Is he okay ?
He's still driving.
Dwight... you forgot your bumper !
Hello ?
Please don't send Dwight.
Saison 2 - Episode 12
The Injury
Transcripts : Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation : El Uploador
pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus
http://www.forom.com
Morning everyone.
Don't freak out.
I forbid anybody to freak out.
Clearly I have had a very
serious accident.
But  I will recover.
God willing.
I just wanna be treated
normally today.
Normal would actually be good.
Considering the trauma
that I've been through.
You missed two big conference
calls today. One with corporate.
Did you explain why ?
No, I didn't mention that
you cooked your foot.
Burned my foot, Pam.
Please stop popping my cast.
Thank you.
So where are you
shipping your foot ?
So where are you shipping...
Your foot.
Thank you.
Pam, messages please.
- You didn't have any.
- Really ?
Well, seemed, uh, very important
to you earlier,
that you needed to stay and..
- Do my job ?
- No.
Your job is being my friend, Pam...
and...
- God !
- It slipped.
- What did...
- Sorry.
It's just that before,
you said you didn't want
any special treatment.
I don't want any special
treatment, Pam.
just want you to treat me
like you would
a family member who's undergone
some sort of serious physical trauma.
I don't think that's too much to ask.
Do you want some aspirin ?
Because you seem a little fussy.
No, I don't want some aspirin.
Yeah, I am fussy.
Asiprin's not gonna do
a damn thing.
I'm sitting here with a bloody
stump of a foot.
Pam, I am Assistant Regional Manager.
And I can take care of him.
Part of my duties are to...
What ?
- Part of your duties are to what ?
- What ?
You just said part of your duties
are to something.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
- What is wrong with you ?
- Where is my cornbread ?
- Here you go.
Thank you. Did you get all
dark meat like I like ?
Yes, I ordered three full rotisserie
chickens worth of all dark meat.
Where are the yams ?
They were out of yams.
I got you creamed spinach.
Did you go to the one
in Stroudsburg ?
- And they had no yams ?
- They had no yams.
How strange.
Because they always have yams.
Oh, man, is that
a Prism Duro Sport ?
You've seen one of these ?
Yeah, they're like an iPod,
only they're better.
'Cause they're chunkier
and more solid.
Roy gave it to me for Christmas.
I'm trying to figure out
how to put songs on it.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't go there.
I know this Russian website,
where  you can download songs
for two cents a piece.
- Really ?
- Yeah,
I'll write down the address for you.
Only, the only thing is...
is that all the songs,
are in Russian.
Kidding !
Why would they all be...
Okay, see you later, Pan.
Pam ?
Pam ? Pam !
Oh, God.
What ?
Come here, please.
Tell me before I come there.
I want you to rub butter
on my foot.
- No.
- Pam, please.
- I have Country Crock.
- No.
Ryan !
These covers...
are totally indestructable.
- Really ?
- Yeah.
Throw it. I promise it won't break.
Chuck it.
- Oh, no, it's broken.
- What ?
No, it's fine.
I told you it wouldn't break.
You could throw it all day long.
That is so cool.
- Thanks Dwight.
- You're welcome.
So, I guess Pam and Dwight
are friends now.
Oh, God, no.
Dwight isn't my friend.
Oh my God...
Dwight's kind of my friend.
No, no, no one is helping me out
at all, Mom.
No, I'm not gonna call Jan.
She'd just worry.
Drive down here and
make a big thing.
Who told you that ?
No, it was mutual.
What is Pam doing chatting
with you ?
Do you like candy ?
It's alright.
'Cause you're sweeter than candy.
What is wrong with you ?
Hey, cut...
Wow, you just dive right in.
You know, around age 12,
I just started going for it,
you know ?
Oh, help !
Help me !
What happened ?
I fell of the toilet.
I'm caught between the toilet
and the wall.
- What do you need ?
- Not you.
Someone  else. Get Pam.
I don't think Pam's gonna want to
come into the men's room.
Get Ryan.
He needs to lift me.
And he needs to
clean me up a little bit.
Bring a wet towel.
Ryan is, uh...
- dead.
- No he's not.
- Dead.
- I just saw him.
He's...
can you just get up yourself ?
I... you only grilled your foot.
Oh, forget it.
I'll just get up myself.
Ow, God !
Do you think Dwight's being
a little weird today ?
No...
He's actually been really
nice and helpful.
And that isn't weird ?
Well...
Can I have everyone's attention,
please ?
Phyllis...
Oscar...
Ryan, who is supposed to be dead.
Can  I ask you all a question ?
Do you know what it's like
to be disabled ?
Oscar  ?
I had scoliosis as a girl.
Never heard of it. No...
a real disability.
Not a woman's trouble.
When I was a teenager,
I was in an iron lung.
What... how old are you ?
No, it... Look,
the point is...
I am the only one here who has
a legitimate disability.
Although I'm sure Stanley has had
his fair share of obstacles.
I'm not disabled,
and neither are you.
Okay.
What does this look like
to you, Stanley ?
Mail Boxes, Etc.
Shut...it.
Okay. Well...
Well, you know what ?
Disabilities are not things
to be laughed at,
or laughed about.
You people are jerks.
Imagine if you had left
Stevie Wonder
on the floor of that bathroom
instead of me.
Oh, we wouldn't.
We love Stevie Wonder.
I burned my foot !
Okay, 20 minutes, conference room.
Everybody's in there !
Dad ?
While we are waiting for
our special guest to arrive,
I wanted you all to take a look
at a few of the many,
many disabled icons who have
contributed so much to our society.
- Quick question.
- Yeah ?
- Why is Tom Hanks on the wall ?
- Twice.
Good question.
Forrest Gump, mentally challenged.
Philadelphia... AIDS.
I think that's from Big.
I don't think so, no.
Yeah, he's dancing on a piano
with Robert Loggia.
He grew into a man overnight.
A rare disability. It still works.
A crossword puzzle Stanley ?
Seriously, are you learning
nothing here ?
What do you mean, "Mm-hmm" ?
- I mean I'm learning nothing.
- Okay.
Michael Scott.
I'm looking for Michael Scott.
Yes, right in here.
- Good.
- Come on in..
Great.
This ladies and gentlemen,
is our special guest.
Sorry I'm late. Somebody parked
in the handicapped parking space.
Hey, everyone.
I'm Billy Merchant.
You may have seen me
around here before.
I'm the properties manager
of this office park.
You are so brave.
Thank you.
Actually, I've been meaning
to come by here or a long time...
But it's hard for you, right ?
Because you're in a wheelchair.
No, I just have a lot of properties
to manage.
Let me ask you something.
How long does it take you to do
something simple ?
Everyday, like...
like brush your teeth in the morning.
I don't know, like, 30 seconds.
Oh, my God.
That's three times as long as
it takes me.
How did you,
get in your wheelchair ?
This morning ?
Just like every other morning.
Just climbed on in.
Hey, hey, hey, hey !
Not funny, not funny !
Hey, hey, relax just, uh..
joking around here.
Well, that's good.
He still has a sense of humor.
Listen, I've actually used a chair
since I was four years old.
- I don't really notice it anymore.
- Well, they do.
They notice it. Don't you ?
You notice it.
It's the first thing you saw when
he rolled in here, isn't it ?
I wanna clamp Michael's face
in a George Foreman grill.
So there are jsut a couple things
I wanted to remind everybody of.
- Okay.
- First is parking.
You can't block the freight
entrance with your car,
even if your blinkers are on.
Does anybody have any questions ?
Yes ?
Yeah ?
Dwight, you have your hand up.
Ignore him.
You know what ?
We're not that different,
you and I.
When I clamped my foot
into a non-stick...
- You know what, Michael ?
- Yeah ?
- Let me stop you right there...
- Okay.
and leave.
Did you see
"Born on the 4th of July" ?
I was under the impression that
Billy would be more like that guy.
What's wrong with that guy ?
You mean today ?
He stepped on a George Forman grill
and he burned his foot.
No, not Michael.
The moon-faced kid who crashed
into the pole.
He looks like he has a concussion.
Hey !
I found the pudding cups
you wanted at a gas station
in Carbondale !
You did it.
Look at you !
And with the plate and the napkin.
Very nice. Thank you, Ryan.
- You're very welcome.
- Did you get the yams ?
No, the gas station in Carbondale
did not have fresh yams.
Okay.
I'll just have the pudding.
- You sure ?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You know what ?
I feel better.
Ryan brought me some
chocolate pudding
and his kindness healed my foot.
Yeah, baby !
I am feelin' better.
My body's literally healing itself.
It is amazing what the human body
is capable of when you have
a powerful brain.
I ground up four
extra strength aspirins
and put them in Michael's pudding.
I do the same thing for my dog
to get him to take his
heartworm medicine.
Ohh, finally feel the blood coursing
through my foot veins.
Okay, I think we need to take him
to the hospital, because...
I'm pretty sure he has
a concussion.
Oh, now you feel some
compassion for him.
He needs to go right now.
And you're his emergency contact.
- I think you should go with him.
- Why don't you go with him ?
- I barely know him.
- I want Michael to take me.
I can't take you.
I don't have my car.
- Please ?
- And yours is all vomity.
- You can take my van !
- Oh, okay.
That's great. No, I can't drive.
Jim, why don't you drive ?
- Fine.
- We'll go.
I'm still recovering.
So let's just...
Ryan, can you get my coat please ?
Slowly. 'Kay ?
Let's just get to the elevator.
- What are you doing ?
- Vietnam sounds.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
- Tired. Can't lay down.
- Just take a rake...
Wake up !
Wait, here, let me help you Dwight.
- Come on. Get up.
- Thanks.
- Get up.
- You're the best.
- Just keep him awake.
- It smells like chicken soup.
- I know.
- I have to go to the hospital.
- Where are we going ?
- I just wanna say good-bye, okay ?
- I'll be back, I mean...
Yes, I know.
But it's gonna be different.
Why ?
It's just hard to explain.
Oh, Pam, you're adorable.
Oh, my goodness.
- Come here.
- Ohh. Huggy hugs.
Shotgun !
You don't think you should sit
in the back with Dwight ?
The rules of shotgun are
very simple and very clear.
The first person to shout shotgun
when you're within the sight
of the car gets the front seat.
That's how the game's played.
There are no exceptions for someone
with a concussion.
Oh, God, a minivan.
What is Meredith's problem ?
Well, I think she has a kid.
Yeah, she has one kid
and no husband.
She's not going to find one
driving this thing around.
- Where are we going ?
- Come on.
- Get inside.
- Where are we going ?
- We're going to Chuck E. Cheese.
- Chuck E. Cheese ?
Oh, God. I'm so sick of
Chuck E. Cheese.
We're going to the hospital,
Michael.
I know. I'm just sayin'...
- Dwight, what are you drinking ?
- I found it under the seat.
Oh, my God. Dwight.
-  I'm thirsty.
- Put that down.
Give the bottle to Michael.
- I'm thirsty.
- Just give it to me...
Just keep your eyes on the road.
Give me the bottle or you're fired.
You can't fire me,
I don't work in this van !
- Give it to me, Dwight !
- No, stop.
- Give me the bottle !
- Will you stop ?
- Give me the bottle, Dwight !
- Michael, stop !
- Just give it !
- Just stop it !
- Stop spraying ! Gimmme the bottle.
- Stop !
- Stop spraying me !
Gimme the bottle !
Dwight, what is your middle name ?
Danger.
Something with a "K."
It's Kurt.
Wow, I'm so sad that I know that.
What do I write under
reason for visit ?
Concussion.
What did you write ?
Nothing.
I wrote
"bringing someone to the hospital."
So you thought they meant your
reason for coming to the hospital.
You know what, Jim ?
This isn't about me anymore.
I made a miraculous recovery,
which is more than
I can say for him.
Come on, Dwight.
- Hi, Michael.
- Hi, Dwight.
Doctor, what is more serious,
a head injury or a foot injury ?
A head injury.
Well, you don't have
all the information.
The foot had been severly burned,
and, uh, healed quickly.
Very quickly.
Actually,
like suspiciously quickly.
So I'm ordering a CAT scan.
What is that ?
Look, since you have the machine
up and running,
can I just stick my foot in ?
We can take a look....
Well...for a burn,
you really just need to look
at the outside of the foot.
Okay, what kind of
machine is that ?
Does the skin look red
and swollen ?
That's what she said.
That's my joke. Damn it, Dwight.
Okay, no electronics past this point.
- Camera, sound equipment.
- It's okay, they're with me.
No metal of any kind.
All right, well, I guess this is
where we leave you off.
I don't wanna do this.
Well, you should have
thought of that
before you crashed your head
on your way to pick me up, so...
we'll see you when you get out.
Fine, fine.
- Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
- Dunder Mifflin, this is Jim.
Oh, my God, what's going on ?
Is Dwight okay ?
He should be fine.
But they brought him in
for a CAT scan.
I can't believe he's getting
a CAT scan.
Michael went in there with him too.
- It's pretty sweet.
- Really ?
Michael went in with him ?
But they shouldn't be
much longer now.
So we'll be back soon.
Okay, that's...
...good news.
- Uh, yeah, no. I'll let you go.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Hey, Oscar ?
- What's up Pam ?
I just wanted to let you know
that Dwight's gonna be okay.
The doctor said there's a really
simple treatment for a concussion,
so he'll probably even be back
at work tomorrow.
Okay.
I just, uh, thought you'd
wanna know that.
Okay, Mr. Schrute, inhale
with me on three.
One,
two...
Sir,
Sir, stop that. Stop...
Stop that.
www.tvsubtitles.net