Hello, hello.
Top of the morning to you.
(EXCLAIMS)
Green M&M's.
Nature's Viagra.
Two of my favorite joke areas
combined. It's gonna be a good day.
I don't want to
bring my friends.
Why can't it
just be the two of us?
Because it's St. Patrick's
Day. People go out in groups.
Well, why don't you
invite your friends?
Why are you being
so weird about this?
Stop fighting! Just on
St. Patrick's Day, okay?
Just one
perfect day a year.
No hassles,
no problems, no kids.
Why no kids?
Yeah, where are your kids?
Nope. Uh-uh. Not today.
MICHAEL: It is
St. Patrick's Day,
and here in Scranton,
that is a huge deal.
It is the closest that the
Irish will ever get to Christmas.
(DOOR OPENS)
(EXCLAIMS)
ERIN: Welcome back, Dad.
Oh, thank you.
Hey.
KEVIN: Hey.
Hey!
ANDY: Welcome back, Tuna.
Hey.
DWIGHT: Very good. Okay, we'll get
back to you on that right away. Thanks.
What do we got here?
Mega-desk.
Of course.
Command central.
Mmm-hmm.
Surveillance, gaming
and business.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
What? Come on. Jim!
Tweedledee and
Tweedle Dumbass
have been away
on maternity leave,
but now Tweedle Dumbass is
back and we have a problem.
Yes, getting hooked on
mega-desk was my own damn fault.
(SIGHS) I don't care
about assigning blame.
All I care about is mega-desk.
That is all I care about.
Getting more mega-desk.
Oh, I love this.
So much fun.
There's such team spirit
in this room.
Morning, darling.
Morning.
Well, this is my last day at
the Scranton branch for a while,
but I'm leaving it in
the very capable hands
of some of the loveliest people I've
ever had the pleasure of knowing.
You know,
I'm gonna miss this place,
and the snow.
(LAUGHS) Do my dogs
love peeing in that snow!
Makes me think
they're onto something.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Oh, good morning,
sweetheart.
Good morning, honey pile.
I'm sorry, but is that a
gift I see in your hands?
It is. This is a
little something for you
to remember your time here
in Scranton by.
Is that a lump of coal?
Yes, it is.
I haven't been that naughty.
No, no, no. That is
a good gift, actually.
Buildings here in Scranton
are literally powered by coal.
Uh... Thank you very much.
We don't get much coal
down in Tallahassee.
I mean,
just alligators
and some of the worst Chinese
food you've ever tasted.
Mmm, that sounds
great, actually.
Well, if you ever get down
in my neck of the woods,
you got a place to stay.
MICHAEL: When you work for
Sabre, only one thing matters,
and I don't care if you're a
loser or you practice bestiality,
if Jo likes you,
you are in.
And I am in.
Erin Go Bragh.
Andy "Go Bragh" to you.
Nice kilt.
Thanks.
It's actually my sister's
old field hockey skirt.
Erin and I have our first date
tonight and it has to be perfect.
Why? Because according
to How I Met Your Mother,
that's the date that your kids are
gonna wait patiently to hear about,
and you better have
a good story for them.
Nope.
Great.
JIM: No.
Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on. Come on.
Five more minutes.
Five more minutes
of mega-desk? Please?
Is this yours or mine?
They say that
no man is an island.
False. I am an island,
and this island is volcanic.
Mega-desk!
And it is about to erupt with
the molten hot lava of strategy.
Good Lord. I can't
believe I'm missing this.
PAM: It's kind of like that
lip thing she did last night,
like a half-snarl,
half-smile.
I get the sense
that she's very ironic.
Okay. Love you.
We'll talk soon.
Must be amazing
being a father, right?
The miracle of life.
It is. Big time.
Ah, that baby is just discovering
a whole wide world right now.
It's pretty amazing.
What up is, what down is,
who Mom is,
who Dad is.
Must be tough being here
with all that going on.
It's tough being here
for a lot of reasons.
I mean,
you're here at work
and the baby thinks that the
refrigerator is its father.
Is that what
happened to you?
I'll tell you
what happened to me.
I didn't see my father for
the first two years of my life.
I thought my mother was my father
and my wet nurse was my mother.
And that's
a common mistake.
Turned out fine
for me. But Mose?
Oh, same story,
different ending.
(SNEEZING)
Hey, are you sick?
Oh, no, I'm fine. I just
have a little indigestion.
In your nose?
Yes.
ERIN: I'm a little sick, but I
don't want to miss my date with Andy.
I'll get better.
Whenever I'm sick it goes
away within a few hours,
except once when I was in the
hospital from age three to six.
Now, after all the talking
I've been doing, it's your turn.
This is a town hall meeting. I
want to hear what y'all sound like.
That is a great idea, J.B.
Thank you.
JO: You know, I get way
too many ideas from the top.
Now, I want to
hear your ideas.
I mean, did you guys
know that Liquid Paper,
that wasn't invented
by some fancy engineer.
No, that was created
by a lowly typist.
Oh, Jo, I have an idea
for suntan lotion soap.
You know, it doesn't
have to be an invention.
I have a question.
Oscar, homosexual accountant.
In the training manual,
it says that
there's a minority executive
training program in Tallahassee.
I am so proud of Sabre's
Print In All Colors initiative.
Any Sabre employee of color
is welcome to apply, okay?
Darryl?
Darryl. Mellow, soulful,
smart for warehouse.
Okay, hush now.
Okay.
The Sabre shipping method
could be more efficient.
Combining inventory systems
makes sense on paper,
but printers and paper
ship differently.
It would be faster
to deliver them separately
instead of waiting
on everything to come in.
But you wouldn't need
more trucks? I mean...
Not at all. There's a
way it can be scheduled.
I sketched
this out downstairs.
Well, look at you.
Look at that picture
that you drew. Nice job.
We are very
proud of you.
You know what? We are
going to tape that up
on the refrigerator
in the kitchen.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
I like this, Darryl.
I like this a lot.
Maybe you should be
doing your sketching upstairs.
Would you like
an office up here?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Take Jim's old office.
Oh, I set my stuff
up in there.
So, just give me a few minutes
to clean it out for you.
Yeah. I want to
hear more from you.
Absolutely.
All right.
Yeah, thank you.
Okay. Any questions?
Anything on anybody's mind?
I'm leaving tonight.
This is your last
chance for a while.
No! Say it's not so,
Jo! We're gonna miss you.
We are gonna
miss you so much!
Don't go away!
Okay. Florida
ain't that far away.
Well, I'm heading
down there.
Well, anytime, now.
So, who...
How about
July 4th weekend?
Oh, honey,
you didn't buy a ticket.
I did.
Oh, honey,
I am not home very often,
and me and my relatives,
they take up the guest house.
I think you should
check with my office
before you book
any dates, okay?
You know what? In the
spirit of full disclosure,
I have actually reserved
a bunch of different seats
on a bunch
of different flights,
but there are a couple flights
that only have two tickets left,
so I think we should
pull the trigger...
Enough!
All right, everybody. Just
try to put a brave face on.
Let's follow
the chain of events.
Jo likes Michael,
Jo invites
Michael to house,
Jo doesn't like
Michael anymore.
Mmm.
(SIGHING)
Moving on up
To the east side
To a deluxe apartment
in the sky
Hello. I want you to stop
what you're doing right now.
You are stressed and I
am taking you to lunch.
No, that's very generous
of you, but I'm all set.
No is not an option.
Yes, it is.
All right, well, if you need me, I'll
be on the other side of that wall.
Knock once for yes,
twice for no.
How many knocks does it take
to get you to do some work?
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. I'll be over there.
And I'm actually pleased
to be able to offer you printer
cartridges and toner now.
Jim.
Yeah.
Jim, sorry to bother you.
What?
My headphones are broken.
Right.
Can I listen to
my music at a low volume?
That's great. Great.
Okay.
Yeah.
The cat's in the cradle and
the silver spoon Little boy...
When was the last time
you updated your printer?
"When you coming home, Dad?"
"I don't know when"
No. You need to stop now.
We'll be together then, now We're
going to have a good time then
Whether it's this time
or the next time.
(ANDY SINGING)
(ANDY AND DWIGHT SINGING) The cat's
in the cradle and the silver spoon
Little boy blue
and the man in the moon
No, we can definitely
talk about it...
You know what? Can I call you
back? That'd be great. Thank you.
We'll be together then We're
going to have a good time
No, I know I need
to work, I just...
I feel weird
not being home.
I am not surprised that Dwight's
using my baby to steal my desk.
I'm a little surprised
that it's working.
This fax came for you.
(COUGHS)
Oh, no, no, no.
Are you feeling ill?
Oh, no, honey, if you've got a
bug, I want you to go on home.
I can't have you getting
Callie and Jo Junior sick.
These dogs have gotta be in a
commercial with Dwight Howard next week.
Oh. No, I feel like
I could lift a car.
Yeah, but you sound
like death, girl.
Now, why don't
you go on home,
take care of yourself,
get in bed,
and shred that and have them
send me a clean fax, all right?
Well...
ANDY: She should go home.
It's not the end of the world.
We'll go on
a date next week.
She's still going to
like me in a week, right?
Yes?
I was just working at my desk and I
wanted to run some new leads by you.
Oh, you're sick.
(COUGHING)
Dang it.
That's exactly why I sent
that receptionist home.
No, no, I'm not.
Getting everybody
sick in the office.
I have some
good ideas that...
I don't need any
heroes here, honey.
It's time for you
to go on home now.
(SNEEZING) You sure?
Yeah.
You'll probably feel better once
you get some pants on. Come on.
(CAR LOCK BEEPS)
Very nice.
Not bad, huh?
Real Hoop Dreams story
you got there.
Oh, man, you seem
to have caught Jo's eye.
How'd you make that happen?
I impressed her
with my good ideas.
(CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
Seriously. How did you do it?
I made a suggestion at
the meeting that was good.
You were there.
How do I put
this delicately?
Does her family owe your family
something in terms of a past injustice?
Now, Mike, I have
to ask you to leave
so that I can learn
about this tiny television.
Mmm, okay. All right.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
JO: Hey, there.
Hey, there.
So, I think I'm done.
Gonna head out, unless you want to
chat, like we were doing earlier.
Well, there's chatting time
and there's working time,
and I'm still
on working time.
Mmm? Well, the clock
says chatting time, so...
Well, if you feel like you've
done a solid day's work.
Right.
What?
Well, I mean, if you can
put your name on this day
and be proud of the
amount of work you've done,
then by all means, you
should toodle on home.
Mmm...
Okay.
Is there something else
I can help you with?
No, no, no,
that's super clear-ish.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
KEVIN: Just because
Jo has no life
does not mean that the
rest of us don't have lives.
Oscar has a life. I
think Ryan has a life.
This is outrageous.
Hey, Pac-Man.
TODD: Hey, what's up,
Butt Plug?
How you doing, stud?
You're already there?
Dude, I've been
here since 3:00.
I've boot and
rallied twice.
How's the lady situation?
Fat and ugly.
You might actually
have a chance.
Oh, damn, that sounds great.
Unfortunately I am stuck here because
my boss is making us work late.
Oh, here's what you do. Hike up
your skirt and pull out your tampon,
borrow some balls
and come meet me.
Yeah, maybe next year.
Maybe next queer.
Hey, ladies, who wants
some bangers and mash?
(PHONE LINE DISCONNECTS)
(SIGHS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
Oh, Andy!
Hi.
I'm in my jammy-jams.
That's okay.
I'm in my worky-works.
You look amazing.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Thanks.
Come in.
Okay.
Hey, me and Creed are in.
Are you guys in?
Oh, I'm in.
I'm in.
All right.
(DOOR OPENS)
JO: Oh, you don't become the
most powerful woman in Tallahassee
by slacking off.
(CHUCKLES)
You do it by working hard.
Or marrying rich.
I did both.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Got a little client meeting
at Shanny O'Gannigans tonight.
It shouldn't
go all night long,
so if you'd like me to,
I can swing by your house
so the baby can experience
a strong male presence.
No? Nothing?
Okay, have fun working.
(WHISTLING)
Hi there, Jo.
Sorry to interrupt.
(PHONE RINGING)
This evening I have...
Hello?
Hey, Jo, it's Jim Halpert.
I actually scheduled a meeting at
7:30 with a very important client,
and it's so weird, 'cause we never
have meetings after 5:00 p.m.,
but I was hoping that maybe
just this once it would be okay.
Well, sure. You know, you go
ahead and push some printers.
You know I will.
And by the way, seriously,
we never, never do this.
Okay.
All right.
Sorry, sugar.
What did you want?
Well, you see, I actually do
have a meeting with a client.
I'm gonna just
reschedule for next week.
Thank you.
Thanks again,
by the way.
Hey, what are you
fellows doing up here?
We're here
to bust you out.
I wish, but I...
Dude, is your
shirt tucked in?
(COUGHS) Oh, yeah.
I must have did that
when I used the bathroom.
All right, then.
Let me get to it.
All right.
See you later.
(SIGHS)
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON TV)
Your hand's cold.
It is? I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Have some more blanket.
Oh, thanks.
(EXCLAIMS)
What's up?
You're awake?
Andy, this is
my brother, Reed.
I didn't know
you had a brother.
He's my foster brother.
Well, any brother of
Erin's is a friend of mine.
Nice to meet you.
Andy Bernard.
Cold hands.
Are we rotating seats or...
Yeah, you're the guest.
Go take the easy chair.
Best seat in the house.
Plus, you don't
have to sit next
to this big dork
and her smelly feet.
Hey. My feet aren't smelly. They
smell like roses. Smell them.
(GROANS) Whoa.
(CHUCKLING)
So how does the whole
foster sibling thing work?
Do you guys
share one parent or...
None. We were in the same
house from ages 10 to 12
and then from 15 to 18.
Right. Formative years.
Nice skirt.
It's a kilt.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yes, I am anxious
to get out of work,
but let me be clear,
it's not to celebrate
St. Patrick's Day.
It's so I can protest St. Patrick's Day.
Overnight all
my damn bags home.
I'm carrying nothing
but my sable gloves.
I've had it with
Homeland Security.
And I want you to put all those
tracking numbers in my BlackBerry.
How late are we
gonna work tonight?
You never know with Jo. Sometimes
we're here until midnight,
sometimes she doesn't
show up for three days.
Why does she do that?
Why doesn't she just tell
you what your schedule is?
Yeah. That'd be awesome.
I could get a girlfriend.
I wouldn't have to go to
Amsterdam seven times a year.
But I'm young, right?
I will date when I'm dead.
(LAUGHING)
Do I really want
to turn out like Gabe?
Twenty-six, single,
tied to my desk,
no life, no family.
I want to have been married by
the time I would have turned 30.
That's just...
That's just depressing.
Hello, Jo.
Anything I can do
for you, pudding?
There is, as a matter of fact.
It's getting sort of late.
It's 8:30 and
it's St. Patrick's Day,
which is
a world ethnic holiday,
so I have decided I'm going
to dismiss my employees.
Hmm.
I'm thrilled with the work
they've done today,
both the quality
and the quantity.
Great performance. Very,
very solid all the way around.
All right, then.
Okay. Happy St. Patrick's Day.
And also,
I would like to say that I will be
canceling my trip down to Tallahassee,
although I do look forward to
our professional relationship.
Michael?
Yes?
I look forward to that, too.
Oh.
It's coming down out there.
Yes.
Thank you
for coming all the way here.
No, no. My pleasure.
I'm sorry I was so sick.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Great. Now I'm gonna get sick.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Hey, guys, how are you?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Drinks are on me.
(ALL WHOOPING)
No, no, no, put your credit
cards away! It's on us.
(EXCLAIMS) All right!
MICHAEL: Did I mess up
my career today
or my future
prospects at Sabre?
I don't know.
There is a chance, yes.
I'll tell you,
I love my job,
but Jo wants me to put on a show
for her and pretend to work late?
Nah.
I spent all day trying
to make her like me,
but I forgot to
ask myself something.
Do I even like her?
As the Irish poet Bobby McFerrin
said, "Don't worry, be happy."
Whoops.
Okay. Okay. All right.
Best night ever.
What the hell is
going on back there?
JIM: Yeah. We should be able to
have that over to you by Monday.
Yeah, no problem.
(CHUCKLING) Thank you.
What the hell is this?
Oh!
This is not mega-desk.
No, it's not. They call it "quad-desk."
That's ridiculous. This
is made up of three desks.
Oh, my God.
We're gonna have to
rename it then, aren't we?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello. Dwight Schrute.
www.tvsubtitles.net