Attention, everyone!
Jim and I, on behalf
of the Party Planning
Committee have an...
Too loud.
Too, too loud. Too loud.
But effective. Look. On behalf
of Jim and I, Merry Christmas.
ALL: Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. Good.
My diabolical plot is
on hold for Christmas.
My heart just melts with the
sound of children singing.
(LAUGHING)
Not really. I'm just tired. The
days are short. I don't know.
Maybe I'm depressed.
It is time to
unveil the tree.
Hey, Rockefeller Center!
JIM: Yeah.
Uh, I've actually
been to Rock Center
and this is
nothing like that.
This is all we have.
Ugh!
Nope, it's not "ugh."
It is office camaraderie.
It is warm feelings.
Why don't we talk more
about it instead of doing it?
Thirty, 29, 28...
Why would you start so high? ...27...
Three, two, one.
...26...
PHYLLIS: Ooh!
You didn't decorate it.
No.
Exactly.
We didn't, because we think it
would be better to do it together.
Everyone. Why would
you wrap it in a sheet
if you're not
covering anything up?
Is... Is it fake?
Pam.
Yes! We are unveiling an
artificial tree that will never die.
Yes.
Like the spirit
of Christmas.
And we're supposed
to applaud you
for taking a giant
diaper off a fake tree?
This was a successful
unveiling! Go back to work!
Merry Christmas.
Hello. Sorry, guys.
Sorry, guys.
I'm not sure I've earned the
right to make announcements yet,
but whoever is giving me
the 12 Days of Christmas
as my Secret Santa,
please stop. I can't take it
anymore. My cat killed a turtledove.
The French hens have started
pulling out my hair to make a nest.
Please stop.
What psycho would
send that as a gift?
I begged Dwight and Jim to
give me Erin for Secret Santa,
and I decided to give Erin
the 12 Days of Christmas.
Bowtie time.
Is it my fault that the first eight
days there's basically 30 birds?
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Merry Christmas, boys and
girls. It's me, Santa Claus.
Hey, Santa.
They finally let you do it. Yeah.
Congrats, Phyl.
It's so edgy.
PHYLLIS: I have been wanting
to be Santa for years.
I believe I have
the right temperament
and the figure to
do the job well.
I slipped a note to Jim 11 weeks
ago, and he said I could do it.
(PHYLLIS LAUGHS)
It's been a long journey.
But I'm Santa Claus!
So, Santa, what can we
expect from this party?
It's going to be a very jolly
time if you've been good.
What if you've been bad?
Then nothing but
a lump of coal for you.
What if you've been
really, really bad?
More evil than
strictly wrong.
Hey, Creed? We covered it. Lump of coal.
Yeah.
For the past several weeks,
my Secret Santa has been
giving me pieces of a machine
that I've been
attempting to assemble.
I'm suspicious of this, because
I had the exact same idea
for catching Osama bin Laden.
I would simply send him
a different piece each day.
He would assemble
it to find himself
in jail!
You know, Oscar, every
time I make this lasagna
people ask me if
it's a family recipe,
but really, I just get
the recipe from the box.
That's funny.
Is it funny? I thought it was
more interesting than funny.
I think my water
just broke.
That's too funny.
Oscar and
the warehouse guy.
Go, Oscar!
Go, gay warehouse guy!
Here's Santa!
Hey, little girl, what
would you like for Christmas?
Ooh! You have been a very
naughty girl, I see.
Michael, we already
have a Santa. Phyllis.
What the hell is going on?
Phyllis, Jim?
Phyllis is Santa?
Yeah.
Phyllis.
Yeah. I told her a long
time ago she could do it.
Take it back.
That is absurd.
No. I'm not gonna do that.
No, Jim, come on!
I think she's
doing a good job.
It's insane! A woman
Santa? Where does it stop?
No! Jim, this may be the last
Christmas that we have here.
Doesn't it make you
a tiny bit anxious,
me not playing Santa?
Come on!
I'm not gonna go tell Phyllis
that she can't be Santa.
Fine. Then do it anonymously.
Ransom-note style. You can...
You know what?
I have a bunch of letters
cut out of magazines
in my desk.
You can use those.
If this were Russia,
yeah, sure,
everybody would
go to one Santa,
and there would be
a line around the block,
and once
you sat on her lap
and she asked you
what you wanted,
you would say,
probably, freedom,
at which point the KGB would
arrest you and send you to Siberia.
It's a good thing
Russia doesn't exist anymore.
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Why pay more to sit next to
old Trannie Claus over there
when you can sit on my lap?
Phyllis is only pretending to
be a man. I'm the real thing!
Sit down on my lap
and there will be no doubt!
Okay.
No, it's not,
like, penis-wise.
Hello, little boy!
What's your name?
Michael, it's me, Kevin.
Phyllis says
I'm too big for her lap.
Oh, I am so sorry that Phyllis
hates you and hates your body,
but Santa
remembers a reindeer
that was just a tiny
bit different as well.
When can I sit on your lap?
Right now!
Come on over here, big boy!
There we go! Oh, my God.
That's really comfortable.
What would you like for
Christmas, little boy?
I don't know. I didn't know
you were gonna ask me that.
Well, what did you think
was going to happen?
I didn't know. Nobody's ever
let me sit on their lap before.
(SOFTLY) All right,
just say some toys, please.
Can you give me some choices?
'Cause I really don't want
to mess up on this list.
Damn it, Kevin. Come on.
What about if I tell you
the things I don't want?
Okay, get off!
Get off! Off!
(GROANS)
Oh, God!
I didn't even get to
tell you what I wanted.
Okay, you know what you get?
You get a thousand helium
balloons attached to you
so Santa doesn't have
to go through this again.
Awesome.
Well?
I'm trying, Phyllis.
You're Santa.
The only Santa.
That's what I want.
You promised me this. Don't
make me get Bob involved.
What would Bob do?
Never mind.
I shouldn't have said that.
Does it hurt?
It stings a lot.
Hmm.
I keep trying to figure out
who's sending me these gifts.
I know, right?
So far no one
will admit to it.
(CHUCKLES)
Is it you?
Yeah!
Totally.
I admit it. It's me.
(LAUGHS) Seriously?
Seriously?
Are you serious?
Is... What... Is it you?
Yeah. Totally serious. I'm
your Secret Santa. Busted!
(LAUGHS)
There he is.
Hey, man.
Is Matt around?
I've got his check.
Matt is on a delivery. Just
leave it here. I'll take it.
I'll just wait for him.
Matt's a pretty good-looking
dude, don't you think?
I'll just leave
it here with you.
Come here!
Come here! Come here!
I'm doing something
over here. Come on! Ah!
Ho! Ho! Ho!
MICHAEL: Come on, I need
this. Come over here!
Just sit down!
No, no, no,
no, no, no!
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Ryan and I are
just having some fun.
Can I just talk to
you for a second? Yeah.
No, now.
Okay, what?
You can't yell out,
"I need this, I need this,"
as you pin down
an employee on your lap.
Okay. You know what, Jim?
With two Santas in the room,
things get ruthless.
Yeah. Do you understand?
You forced my hand.
Michael, it's Phyllis.
We want Phyllis as Santa.
Do we? Do we?
Is that what we want?
Why don't we
take a vote on it?
Great.
Hey! Okay, everybody.
The office is being pulled
apart. I realize that.
There are traditions at stake.
And there are women...
Who wants Phyllis as Santa?
No, no, no! Wait! No!
There are other choices.
There's information that we...
Are you kidding me, Kevin?
After you almost killed me?
Michael, I had you.
I just want to try Phyllis.
And if you want Michael
as Santa, raise your hand.
Can I get you
some punch?
I... No, I'll get some punch.
That looks delicious.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
KELLY: Michael!
Excuse me.
Whoever has been sending me
the parts to this gun,
I think you sent me a gear
instead of a trigger.
How do you know it's a gun?
What else does it look like?
Not a gun.
Well, I don't have
all the pieces yet.
Well, unless the missing piece
is a gun, you don't have a gun.
Not a gun.
In the North Pole, I spend many
nights alone tinkering with toys.
So today, let's put a twinkle
in old Kris Kringle's eye.
Let the party begin!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
I don't ask for much for
Christmas. I really don't.
It's not like I am begging
people to buy me diamonds
and broach pendants.
Oh!
"Buy me something expensive, or I'm
gonna kill myself." That's not...
I don't care about that!
All I want to be is Santa.
And you want to take that
away from me, fine.
Go ahead.
But when
you need my help
because I am
ruining everything,
don't look at me!
Behold,
Jesus Christ.
And I bring to you
glad Christmas tidings.
I want to remind everyone
the true meaning of Christmas.
Those of you who wish
to join me, that's great.
I am excited by that,
and those of you who don't,
I forgive you,
but I never forget.
Wow, Michael. This must be
obvious how wrong this is.
The Antichrist.
Okay, you can't...
(EXCLAIMS)
Look, you cannot
push religion.
But I can push drugs in here.
Is that what you're saying? No.
Well, you have to pick one
or the other. Your choice.
Pick your poison. Get back
to me. In the meantime,
I am going to spread my
goodness all over this company!
Hey, Phyllis?
Could you not reveal to Erin
that I'm her secret Santa?
All right, sweetie, I'll
just tell her it's Michael.
Okay.
BOTH: (SINGING) I saw
three ships come sailing in
PAM: Have you talked to him?
What?
Matt.
OSCAR: Is it that obvious?
No. Hey.
Hmm.
Good pâté, right? Oscar
made it. Have you met Oscar?
I don't think so.
Hey, Oscar, come here.
Oscar, this is Matt,
and Matt loves your pâté.
I had some.
Oscar's pâté's great.
I could eat it all day,
every day. Mmm.
How come the good ones
are never straight, right?
Okay, Pam.
Okay.
Yes. They're the only two gay guys
I know. But they should be together.
This just arrived from the
Dunder Mifflin North Pole branch.
We don't have a North
Pole branch. Idiot!
Uh-oh! What's Dwight
gonna get? What is it?
Yes!
Oh, yes! It's space garbage.
Dwight's gonna be able
to build himself a friend.
Deck the halls
with crappy gifts
And Stanley, you've
been very good this year.
I have.
Yeah, except for
cheating on your wife.
Adultery's a sin. Look it
up in the Bible, people.
What'd he get?
He got scented candles.
Well, that's appropriate. A
lot of fire where you're going.
Better get used to it.
You're going to H-E-L-L,
double hockey sticks.
Going to hell, Stanley.
ANGELA: Amen.
And this brings us
to you, little one.
I can't see from here, people.
Somebody shout it out.
Don't make me get up.
It's fabric.
I really wanted this.
That's fantastic! You can make
another dress that goes past your feet.
Andy, was this you?
It's a secret.
No, Andy had Erin.
PHYLLIS: It was a secret.
PAM: Michael!
PHYLLIS: You...
What? Was I not
supposed to say?
What? Turn it back on.
No.
(DOOR CLOSING)
DAVID: Yes, Michael.
What is so urgent?
David, guess who I am
sitting here dressed as.
I'm not going to guess. You
can tell me, or I will hang up.
I will give you a hint.
His last name is Christ.
He has the power of flight.
He can heal leopards.
Michael...
I am Jesus, David,
and you know why?
Because Phyllis, a woman,
has uslurped my role as Santa.
Michael...
What?
This is a very,
very bad time.
Really? What's going on?
Stephanie,
can you hop off, please?
STEPHANIE: Sure, David.
What the hell? How rude!
Does she do that all the time?
ERIN: Do you want me off
this call too, Michael?
Hey, what? Get off!
Get off the phone!
DAVID: Listen, I shouldn't tell you
this, but the company has a buyer.
The board will have no
choice but to approve,
and they are going
to clean house.
What does that mean?
I'll be fired.
Well, can't Alan protect you?
Alan will be out, too.
All of us.
All of us?
Goodbye, Michael.
Oh, my God.
MICHAEL: Earlier today,
this office needed a Santa.
And then it needed a second
Santa. And then it needed a Jesus.
And now,
it needs a Michael.
And that's one suit
Phyllis cannot fit into.
Hey, how's everybody doing?
Not great. You heckled
Santa for an hour and a half.
That was a different guy.
That was Jesus.
Jesus sort of
ruined the party.
Hurt, petulant Jesus.
Are you serious?
That is so offensive.
You know what's
even more offensive,
is bailing on this party because
some jerk ruined the first part of it.
Dwight, come here.
Here's my debit card. I want you
to go pick up a bunch of pizzas
and meet me in
the conference room.
What's your pin number?
I don't want to say.
But it's fun
to stay at the...
It's fun to stay at the...
Where?
Holiday Inn. I don't...
(HUMMING)
I thought that
you would like it.
It was a little much, Andy.
Well, it's the thought
that counts.
What were you thinking?
I suppose a gentleman might
throw in the towel at this point.
Guess what.
Not gonna happen.
You know what? Christmas
isn't about Santa or Jesus.
It's about the workplace. All
of you feel like my family.
Ryan, you are my son, and
Pam, you're my wife, and Jim...
And Angela and Phyllis,
you are my grandmas.
And Stanley,
you're our mailman.
And I can't help but look at all
of your wonderful, beautiful faces
and think, "How could
they do this to us?"
What?
(ALL MURMURING)
How could we do
what to you?
That's not...
Never... Nothing.
Why would we...
We deserve to know.
MICHAEL: I didn't
say anything!
We're going out of business!
What?
ANDY: You are kidding me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who said that?
David told me on the phone.
David told me.
ANDY: When?
When did he tell you, today?
Earlier today,
he said we have been sold.
JIM: What?
(YELLING)
JIM: Dwight! Jesus.
PAM: Come on!
Michael, wait.
So they said we are sold.
David is gone, Alan is
gone. We're all gone.
Okay, but we
haven't gone under.
We've been sold, and that can
mean many different things.
It's hard for me to
imagine a scenario
where Meredith Palmer keeps her
job and David Wallace does not.
No offense, Meredith.
No, I get it.
I'll call him.
I'll call David.
No you won't, because he's
not picking up his phone.
Yes, I will, because I always
know how to get through to him.
He told me where
his kids go to school.
I call the school. I tell
them I'm the pediatrician.
They patch me through to his
secretary. I use my little girl voice.
(EXCLAIMS)
DAVID: Hey, sweetie,
what is it?
It's not sweetie.
It's Michael Scott.
What the hell? Stephanie,
could you hop off, please?
Michael, I have never...
David...
... never, ever...
David, you are
on speakerphone
with the entire branch
and the warehouse.
Hi, David.
ALL: Hey, David.
Hi, everyone.
David, they do not believe me
when you told me
that everyone was canned.
You weren't supposed
to tell anyone, Michael.
Well, I think
we're past that now.
I am not supposed...
Okay, fine.
Guys, I was really
only talking
about Alan, myself,
and a few other
execs you don't know.
Oh, my God.
David, that's horrible.
How about us? It's Meredith. By the
way, your wife is a very lucky woman.
Look, they're buying the
company for the distribution.
You guys are the only thing
about this company that works.
So congratulations.
We're not fired?
No. Congratulations.
All right!
Yeah!
(ALL CHEERING)
Come on!
It's a Christmas miracle!
DWIGHT: Yeah!
(SINGING) Walk a lonely road
Only one that
I have ever known
Don't know where it goes
But it's all to me
and I walk alone
It's true.
Yes.
DWIGHT: We all walk alone.
Jim.
My shadow's the only one
That walks beside me
My shallow heart's...
Wow.
Yeah. That was the idea.
Thank you.
Awesome.
Thanks, man.
(SINGING) Christmas tree
Thou leaves are so unchanging
Of course!
You got it?
What is that?
I have no idea.
Well, maybe those will help.
Michael, please. Come on.
Sorry.
Sure.
Nice to meet you, Oscar.
Nice to meet you, Mark.
It's Matt.
Right, Matt.
I know what I'm doing, Pam.
Oh, man!
I can use this
for so many nuts.
Macadamias,
Brazil nuts, pecans,
almonds, clams, snails.
Hi, Santa.
Hi, Michael.
(GRUNTS)
Okay.
I'd like to make a wish.
What?
I would like an Xbox and a TV
that's compatible with an Xbox.
And I'm sorry.
An Xbox it is, because I've
decided you're a good boy.
Scott, what in the hell
is going on here?
No, no, no. We worked it
out. You called Bob? Phyllis!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
It was earlier today.
Okay.
Hi, sweetheart.
You okay, baby?
I'm good, baby.
Oh, God. Get a room, Santas.
DWIGHT: Thank you, Santa.
Okay, happy holidays.
It's real slippery out here.
Oh, my God.
Twelve drummers drumming.
Merry Christmas, Erin.
Take it away, boys!
(RHYTHMIC DRUMBEATS)
www.tvsubtitles.net