Today is the first day
of Sabre's new project:
Develop a chain of retail stores.
I am meeting my new boss,
Nellie Bertram.
Head of Special Projects.
Work starts at 9:00.
Sabre HQ is 30 minutes away,
driving the speed limit.
Giving everyone 20 minutes to shower,
plus 50 for Jim to style his hair,
20 for breakfast,
40 for Erin to get lost
between her room and the lobby,
90 for Ryan to do his morning ecstasy.
We're already 20 minutes late.
Wake up!
[Screams]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Wake up!
Ah!
Why are you sleeping that way?
Oh.
I was reading the mattress tag,
and I fell asleep.
Stanley!
Wake up! You've got to wake up,
the hotel's on fire!
Stanley, wake up, it's pretzel day!
[Sighs]
Mmm!
[Grunting]
Good morning.
Hey, wake up.
Let's have some fun.
We're in Florida now.
Hey, you.
I'm so glad this is happening.
I actually came to your door
twice last night.
Come on in, the water's fine.
I am on the two kid sleep schedule,
so I'm up and at 'em
at 4:15,
but no kids,
so I honestly didn't know
what to do with myself,
and then I thought of something.
Uh--
He-e-ere's Dwi--
What the--?
- Oh, man.
- What do you think happened?
[Gasps] Looks like Jim got
mixed up with some bad apples.
[Gasps]
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It wasn't me.
I gotta find Luwanda
at the Alcohol Club.
Oh.
[Both scream]
[Gasps]
[Cheerful music]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- Puppet.
- Cool, for your kids?
Yeah. It's weird
being away from them.
Never done this before.
[Laughs]
Attention, Dunder Mifflin Group.
Proceed outside.
The vehicle is waiting.
Seats have been assigned.
Shotgun goes to Ryan.
Congratulations, Ryan.
I need to make Nellie
see me as a leader today.
First impressions
get locked in forever.
When I first met Pam,
she said something
that slightly rubbed me the wrong way.
Since then I've loved
working with Pam,
and she's frankly wonderful,
but I hate her.
I'll have a bottle of the antacid.
Also, I want to get a souvenir
for my son,
but his mother doesn't
acknowledge my paternity.
Do you have anything for that?
Also, I want it to have
a Florida feel.
- What does he like?
- Power.
Okay, and this one is,
"Huh, don't see too many museums
around here."
Okay, Twiggy, that's enough.
Get in the car.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine, okay?
It's just stress.
You know, 'cause I care
about this project.
And frankly, the fact that none of you
are vomiting or diarrheal
right now I find very alarming.
Who says none of us are diarrheal?
Are you sure it's stress?
Because I did poison you.
[Laughs] Very funny, Jim.
Oh, no, I'm serious.
I was thinking,
"For this trip
I have to do something epic,
so what should that be?"
And then I thought of it.
I'll poison you.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna steal my newspaper,
or put a cricket in my cereal,
or something?
I'm gonna set your face on fire.
That's a good one.
Whoa, Stanley.
Did you just come back from
burning down a rival nightclub?
Laugh it up, Halpert.
I'm in Florida for a month
without my family.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Want to get in?
You can work the iPod.
Yes.
Ah.
You're a nice guy, Jim,
but have no idea how to vacation.
Find some Kenny Loggins.
Loggins and Messina.
Did I say "Messina?"
[Tires screech]
Ahh!
[Laughs] Sorry, I couldn't resist.
It's so quiet.
I like it.
It's so peaceful,
I've already written, like,
12 plays today.
It's so quiet, one might say,
you could hear a pin...
I thought that would be cooler.
I loved it.
Hey, can you pick up the pin?
Some of us like to work
in our bare feet.
Of course, I will pick up the pin.
It is right here.
Got it.
Can we see that?
Did you really find it?
Yes, right here.
Got it.
Dink, ow.
[Chuckles]
[Clicks tongue] In the trash.
Hey, why is it so quiet?
Shouldn't the phone be ringing?
Uh-oh. Erin set the phone
to voicemail.
Oh, great.
[Overlapping chatter]
We're screwed.
There.
[Phone ringing]
Oh! There we go.
Pam?
Yeah?
Can you get the phone?
Well, I'm not the receptionist.
Mm, well, you used to be.
I know, but I can't cover reception.
- [Grumbles]
- I have a lot of work to do.
Phone's ringing.
[Phone ringing]
Will one of you get the phone?
I am freaking out.
I know it's for me.
[Phone ringing]
Are you guys kidding me?
Stop flirting
and someone get the phone!
[General agreement]
Answer the phone.
- Andy, pick up the phone!
- Get the damn phone!
You're the closest one to it.
[Whining] Fine.
Hello, Dunder Mifflin.
[Phone continues ringing]
Hello, you've reached Dunder Mifflin.
How may I be of service?
[Boardroom chatter]
Man.
- How was the drive?
- Fantastic.
Stanley drives so fast.
Life is short. "Drive fast
and leave a sexy corpse."
That's one of my mottos.
I would love to hear the other mottos.
- Quick query, Halpert.
- No way.
- Still queer?
- Packer.
You can't put me down.
Too strong.
Yeah, Dwight and Jim
tried to get me fired,
but I landed on my feet
down here in Florida.
You see, this cat's got nine lives,
and a nine-inch--
Psst.
Say, "So who's leading
this thing, anyway?"
So who's leading this thing, anyway?
Psst. Say, "I can't wait
to meet him."
I can't wait to meet him.
Him, you say?
Don't think a woman can be a leader?
[Laughs]
- [Chuckles]
- I--
You poor, simple boy.
Expected a man, did you?
Strong, powerful,
huge, whopping penis?
Well, sorry to disappoint,
but my huge, whopping penis
is right here,
and I'm not afraid to use it.
So stop looking at my breasts,
and start looking at my penis.
[Slow clapping]
I'm Nellie Bertram,
president of Special Projects.
In the next few weeks
we're going to throw
everything you know about
business out of the window,
and do it our own way.
Are your minds blown?
So, how did this special
project come about anyway?
Well, I interviewed to be
the manager of your branch,
after you decided I wasn't
"a good fit."
- It was--
- Ah. Mm-mmm.
It was.
I went on a shopping spree.
Very destructive, I bought 13 pianos.
Then I realized,
what if Sabre had a store?
Hmm?
So I called Jo, old friend,
founder of Sabre,
and I told her, and
she grabbed me by the shoulders,
and she said, "Yes!"
So let's talk about
this Sabre store then.
Probably gonna look stupid, right?
Like a big turd
with a door on the front, right?
What do you think it should look like?
Um, it might be fun
if each store had a different theme,
like a beach one, a winter one,
a jungle one.
No, not a big fan
of the winter aesthetic.
Well, that was just one idea.
It doesn't have to be winter.
Oh, no, it does.
It does, it has to be winter,
and I reject it.
So I drew up a design concept.
Probably gonna be rubbish, right?
[Laughs]
Would you like to look at it?
- Just so you could laugh at it.
- Yeah.
Let me just get the projector working.
[Sighs]
You got to stop with the antacids.
It's not the antidote.
You didn't poison me,
it's just stress.
Okay.
What is the antidote?
True love's kiss.
Jim, help me lower this screen.
You're a big, tall man.
You'd be hilarious trying to do it,
like a little boy.
Just let go of his balloon.
I'll do it.
[Grunts]
I always say,
"You want something done right?
Ask Dwight."
Right? Dwight.
Right Dwight, right Dwight.
Sorry, now you'll never be able
to get that out of your head.
[Whimpers]
[Whimpering] Ah.
- I can do it.
- Mmm!
[Screams]
[Groans]
There we go.
Yes, a complete inability
to pass gas, pervert.
Ugh, yeah, it's tender.
It can't be appendicitis,
I eat more than enough bacon.
Okay, what poison mimics
the symptoms of appendicitis?
Oh, you don't know.
Hold on.
[Grunting and groaning]
What kind of poison did you use?
Dwight, I didn't poison you.
I was kidding.
Yeah, I'm gonna need an ambulance.
[Grunts]
Hold on, I have the address
in my phone. Hold on.
Hold on one second.
Uh, quick question.
Vice president, uh, who is that?
- There's no name listed.
- Is there not?
Maybe I'm just waiting
for someone to wow me.
[On phone] Sir? Sir, where
should we send the ambulance?
Send it to the frickin' moon, idiot.
I tell you what.
Since I moved down to Florida,
I've really gotten back
into hunting big time.
Hunting's so primal.
Almost sexual.
Totally.
I mean, I'd never bang an animal,
you can hardly tell the difference
between a boy or a girl, you know,
but hunting's intense.
You talking about hunting?
I love hunting.
I'm a master hunter.
Did you say,
"masturbator?"
I'm a decent baiter.
My cousin, Mose,
that's a master baiter.
Why are you sitting down like that?
Why is everyone else standing up?
Okay, team, let's get back to work!
Break's over!
Wow. Are that bored?
It's just rum.
I'm not bored, I'm a pirate.
Is that another motto?
It's whatever you want.
Mmm.
Or do you only drink with your kids?
Ah, let's do it.
[Laughs]
Oh, that's healthy.
I've spent so much of my life
telling myself,
"Please, don't end up like Stanley,"
and now I'm wondering
if I even have what it takes.
We have the Sabre pyramid, right?
Hmm? We've got
a bunch of humans, you guys,
humans... pyramid.
Human pyramid.
Do you follow?
It's a team-building
exercise.
You'll love it.
Who's in? Hmm?
- Yup.
- Yeah.
Tallahassee, let's go.
Jim, are you in?
Oh, I don't know.
Sounds like a hoot.
I'm in.
All right, what the heck?
Let's do it.
This is great.
This is gonna be great.
I feel like I'm in ancient Egypt.
I'll be on top.
It's the most important position.
Dude, I think you have appendicitis.
Ahh!
- Dwight?
- Dwight, why don't we just
hold off with
the human pyramids for a while?
Everyone stop moving!
Everyone stop wiggling!
Oh, I feel like I'm gonna vomit!
Dude, don't you yak on me.
This shirt is Van Heusen.
[Groans] Stop moving!
No one's moving.
[Struggles] Ohh!
[Laughs]
Oh, oh!
[General commotion]
Arrest Jim.
He poisoned me.
Wha--no.
No, it was not a poisoning.
The one thing Pam made sure I knew,
Florida's pretty loose
with the death penalty.
You need an operation.
You have appendicitis.
Oh! Who called it?
Nothing but net.
How long will he be gone?
Two or three days.
Don't remember me like this.
Remember me as the man
who pulled down the screen.
Drama queen, am I right?
Philip, if you're hearing this memo,
that can only mean one thing,
I'm dead.
You are the rightful heir
to Shrute Farms.
Please, you must do one thing.
Kill Mose before he kills you.
[Grunts]
Mose, hey, it's Dwight.
Listen, yeah, I just
want to give you a heads-up.
That was an interesting diversion.
Shall we get back to the meeting?
Whoa, are those mini pizzas?
Yeah, I figured
we'd keep things savory
while Oscar's mouth
is in canker country.
I also have some
bacon-wrapped dates on deck.
Look at these little mini pizzas.
Does this make me look huge?
[Giggles]
Hey, guys, look at me, I'm huge.
[Laughs]
Hey, Darryl,
good news, your fax went through.
Oh, [bleep] yeah.
- Up high.
- Yes, sir. Thanks.
[Phone ringing]
Dunder Mifflin, this is Andy.
[Whispering]
I put out some new magazines.
Check it out.
A dwell.
I'm acting like I like reception,
and I'm a really good actor,
so people are actually buying
that I actually like reception,
but I mean, seriously,
reception sucks.
[Phone ringing] Oh, there's the phone.
What's going on?
Fill me in.
Well, we broke into groups,
and the groups
are giving presentations later.
Who's doing the presentations?
- Packer's giving one.
- [Growls]
Jim will probably give ours, I guess.
Damn it!
[Groans]
Let's see, what else have you missed?
Ryan switched his name tag
to his pants,
so now it's like,
if you wear yours on your shirt,
you're a total dick, but
if you switch, you're a copycat.
But I think I figured out a solution.
What else?
My shoes are gonna--
[Sighs]
Features a tech support area.
Bring in your product,
a bunch of nerdy virgins
fix it on the spot.
Huge for building loyalty.
Yes, that is a very good point.
[Panting] Yeah, Todd, decent idea.
Obvious, but interesting.
Dwight, are you all right?
I'm great.
How are you?
Mmm.
Uh.
[Whispering]
What's our presentation about?
Dwight, will you go back
to the hospital?
You were there for like three hours.
I got the surgery,
what else is there to do?
Do 100 jumping Jacks.
No, I don't feel like it.
You do 100 jumping Jacks.
I don't feel like it, either.
97, 98, 99--
I want that vice presidency.
You haven't done any of the research.
"You're too slow, you're too small,
Seabiscuit
is a stupid name."
You guys sound just like
the enemies of Seabiscuit.
- I'm going to do it.
- Aw, let him do it.
Stanley, are you listening to music?
Yup.
All right, who's ready
for the next presentation?
Ah, what is your topic?
What is our topic?
Oh, what a topic it is.
Retail consumer habits.
Really? Okay.
Retail consumer habits is...
[Sighs]
The only thing you need to know
about retail consumer habits
is that consumers
are mindless lemmings.
They just want to be told what to do.
Fast-forward to today,
and the retail consumer
is independent,
well-informed,
super-smart.
Super-smart.
Okay.
Shopping habits
are both seasonal and cyclical.
What does this mean?
- I can field this one.
- No, sit down.
"Seasonal." Well,
the Christmas shopping season
is certainly a busy one,
back-to-school is, as well,
and in early summer,
it seems to slow down a bit,
but shopping is also cyclical.
The menstrual cycle determines
every choice a woman makes.
You see, during ovulation,
a woman's only goal
is to get pregnant,
and during menses,
she is sad that she has failed,
and how does the woman
console herself?
Shopping.
Just--
Jim, could you fetch me
some ice chips?
Thank you.
Just gonna...
Take a... brief pause
at this point.
Thank you.
Oh, God.
Next slide.
Mail call!
♪ His name is Oscar,
and he got some mail ♪
♪ and he better open it,
or go to jail ♪
♪ 'cause it's your taxes
♪ his name is Kevin
♪ and no mail for him
♪ but he got a coupon
for some frozen ♪
Yogurt.
Are those the lyrics?
"Anderson's
Three Pillars of Retail."
Crucial.
So important.
Next.
Are there any questions?
What are the three pillars of retail?
[Whispering] Convenience.
Ingredients.
Service.
Burgers.
Building loyalty.
Killing royalty.
The truth be told,
we should really disregard
Anderson's three pillars.
He was later diagnosed with dementia.
You know what is important?
Is Dwight's pillars,
and there is only one:
desire.
Do we have a desire
to dominate the retail space?
Not just succeed in it,
but to dominate,
and looking around this room,
I'm not so sure that we do,
but we can get there,
and I can lead us there,
and that is all that matters.
Very true.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
I once spent a passionate night
with Hugh Grant's brother,
John grant.
He's older than Hugh,
just a little bit uglier.
How did I pull that off?
Sheer force of will.
That is very good, Dwight.
Thank you very much.
Any other questions?
Jim.
You are bleeding through your shirt.
Oops.
That's embarrassing.
Egg on my face.
Ah.
Hey, having fun?
Yes, I am, as a matter of fact.
Well, I know how it is.
I know it's a lot of fun.
I don't know how it is.
Andy, this is a lame job.
What are you doing here?
I found my calling.
Andy, when I was 12 years old,
we did a field trip,
a lock-in at the zoo.
I met this girl,
I thought she was so perfect.
I was in love with her,
but when the sun came up,
I knew it wasn't real,
'cause she was ugly,
and I had grown tired of her.
I know you want reception today,
but tomorrow you won't want to do her.
She's a dog.
Guys, I don't like this analogy.
[Groaning] Ohh!
Fine.
Did you see this?
- It's nice.
- I mean...
[Giggles]
- How are you feeling?
- Amazing.
Just lost four ounces of appendix,
already replaced it with muscle.
Can I see the wound?
[Grunts]
- Oh, God.
- Oh! That's disgusting!
That's barely healed.
You're not paying me to heal,
you're paying me to kick ass.
A few hours ago, your body
was open like a cabinet.
- That's right.
- That is amazing.
- Todd, look at that.
- Oh, yikes.
- Incom--
- Ah! Not so fast.
Would you come in early tomorrow,
so we can talk about the store
over breakfast?
I feel you have a lot to offer.
It would be an honor, ma'am.
I'll go ahead and cancel
my post-op check-up right now.
I had two goals today.
The first was to make myself
the clear candidate
for vice president.
I achieved that,
no thanks to my appendix.
The second was to find
a memorable souvenir for Philip.
For that, I do have to
thank my appendix.
[Phone ringing]
Dunder Mifflin, how can I
help you save money on paper?
This is Andrew.
Hi, Andrew.
What happened to Erin?
Oh, she's on an assignment in Florida
- for a couple of weeks.
- Oh, good for her.
She's such a sweetheart.
You tell her Donna Muraski misses her.
Yeah, we all kind of miss her.
Everyone, we have a very special guest.
He turned an idea into a store,
into hundreds of stores.
I give you Wally Amos,
founder of famous Amos Cookies.
Yeah!
[Cheers and applause]
Ah.
Aloha, aloha, aloha.
So I hear you're all
looking to bake up some dough
in the sales game?
[Laughter] Well, back when I was
- a regular Amos...
- What's under the cloth?
We'll get to that.
***
It's cookies.
Let me... Let me finish my speech first.
***, isn't it?
*** make with the cookies.
Okay, yes.
Amos. Hi. I'm sure you get ideas
for your cookies all the time.
- But...
- Is it oatmeal with no rasins?
I'm sorry, I was wasting your time.
www.tvsubtitles.net