Hello, this is Dwight Schrute.
- Hello?
- Hello, this is Dwight.
Hello? Hello?
Yes, we do have that.
Hold on one second.
- Jim what are you doing?
- And how many would you like?
- Hang that up right now.
- I can get that out to you immediately.
It's an imposter. Don't do business
with him, this is not Dwight Schrute.
Dwight left his cell phone on his desk.
So, naturally,
I paired it to my headset.
Okay, fine,
I'll just let it go to voice mail.
- Hello, this is Dwight.
- Hey, is this Dwight?
- Yes, it is.
- Oh, my goodness, you sound sexy.
Thank you. I've been working out.
You're not talking to Dwight right now.
You're talking to Jim.
Pam, I'm over here.
I'm confused.
Disconnect that right now.
- You give me your earpiece.
- I can't do that. Unsanitary.
You know what, fine.
I will reprogram my phone
to go to my office phone.
Done.
This is Dwight.
And I forwarded
his desk phone to mine.
Oh, hello, mater.
Good news, I've married. Tell fater.
Such a nice woman.
Transcript: SwSub
Sync: DarKsh
Episode 4x14
"GOODBYE, TOBY" (1.00)
Today
is Toby Flenderson's last day.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I came in extra early.
So much energy.
There are certain days that you know
you'll remember the rest of your life.
And I just have a feeling
that today is one of those days.
- Morning.
- Mornin'.
So here we go.
Just a matter of hours now
until his horribleness
has left the building.
I'm going to set my watch alarm...
And...
Good morning, Kelly.
I can't believe this is your last day.
How do you feel?
Fine. Good.
I feel weird.
First thing on the agenda.
Actually, the only thing on the agenda
is that status
of Toby's going away party.
We have a buttercream cake
and a slide show of Toby.
But so far we only have
two pictures of him.
Okay, well, this will not do.
Toby is going away forever,
and we need to do something
very, very special.
In some cultures, when somebody leaves,
like New Orleans culture,
they have a parade,
and they have a band.
And people party in the streets.
Do you mean leaves as in dies?
You want us to throw Toby
a New Orleans funeral?
If the devil were to explode,
and evil were gone forever,
what sort of party would you have?
- Michael...
- Like a beach blowout?
- Or a toga...
- No, you know... No!
- Toga!
- You always do this.
We have a nice,
modest party planned,
and you come in
and demand the world.
Let me be clear.
There is simply no money
for anything other than a cake,
and to develop a few more slides.
Although Toby won't be in them.
I thought that you might say that.
Every year, my sweet,
sweet grandmother
sends me a check
on my birthday for $50.
And lately she has been...
sending me, like,
nine or ten checks a year.
As Nana starts to...
But I knew I should be
saving it for something.
I just didn't know what
I should be saving it for.
And then I had an awakening.
Michael, buy a motorcycle.
So I put the money in my shoe,
and then I forgot about it until now.
I want a party that makes me feel
like I'm flying through the air
without this...
ugly weight holding me down.
You know?
I want an antigravity machine.
I saw it in a movie.
You drink a potion, and then you just
start floating all around.
So how much antigravity potion
do you want?
No, you know what? This is not
a party-planning committee anymore.
And I don't want your foot money,
and I feel uncomfortable participating.
Phyllis.
Can you do this?
Yes.
- Hi, can I help you?
- Hi, yes.
I'm Holly Flax.
I was told to ask for Mr. Flenderson.
As part of my last day,
I'm training the new human resources rep
in the ways of the company.
Again, the company
has allotted for this training...
one day.
So this is H.R.
This is your desk.
I love the view.
Yeah, it's great, isn't it?
Hey.
What?
Guess who just got into
the Pratt school of design.
No way!
What'd I say?
I said that they'd love those sketches.
- Congrats.
- Oh, thank you.
I don't know why I doubted it.
Because I'm so clearly awesome.
Yes.
So when do you start?
I didn't read it carefully. I just saw
"congratulations," and skimmed the list.
I saw my name, I came in here
to tell you and get a snack.
Busy morning.
So...
you know, it means I have
to go to New York for three months.
It's not a big deal.
I'll come visit you.
And you'll visit me.
It's only two hours away. It'll be fine.
- It's gonna suck, but it'll be great.
- Yeah, it sucks, but it'll be great.
See how easy that is?
I wouldn't go if things
weren't so solid with Jim.
And down the road, if we have a family,
I couldn't go then either.
So the timing's perfect.
And that is the first time I've ever
used the word "perfect" in here.
Hey, Stanley.
I want to introduce you to...
Toby's replacement.
So what do we know about her?
Well, we know that Toby thinks
she'll be great.
Oh, strike one. I hate her already.
I hate her too.
Why do you hate her?
Because she...
stinks...
with her ways and her...
head.
You know, Dwight, sometimes...
I don't know, I think you say things
just to agree with me.
- Would that be such a bad thing?
- Yeah, it would.
Just have a thought.
Have an original thought!
Although I will agree
that her head is weird.
- You know what we need to do?
- What?
- We need to sell her an elevator pass.
- But our elevator doesn't require a...
Exactly.
A little old-fashioned hazing.
Hi, are there any local companies
that rent antigravity machines?
- Antigravity machines?
- That's right, yeah.
What do they do, exactly?
They make you feel lighter.
Antigravity...
Antidepressant? I could
put you through to someone on that.
Okay.
Yeah.
- Hey, Michael?
- Oh, hey, do you still work here?
I'd like to introduce you
to my replacement.
- Come on.
- No. I think I'll pass.
Michael Scott, this is Holly.
- Hi.
- Hi, yeah, right.
Okay, well,
they hired a female Toby.
Good for the world.
Thank you, god, for...
creating two of you.
Here's how things work here.
My job is to make the office fun,
your job is to make the office lame.
And we have an eternal struggle,
you and I.
And only one of us can be the winner.
Spoiler alert... I'm gonna win.
Man, someone doesn't like H.R.
Yeah.
- What did you do to him?
- Nothing.
T...
No, he tortured me...
with his awfulness.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I nearly fell asleep
when he gave me a tour of the files.
Well, look,
I'll let you get back to work,
but I really look forward
to working with you, Mr. Scott.
You can p...
Michael.
Thanks to Toby,
I have a very strong prejudice
against human resources.
I believe that the department is
a breeding ground for monsters.
What I failed to consider, though,
is that not all monsters are bad.
Like E.T.
Is Holly our extraterrestrial?
Maybe.
Or maybe she's just
an awesome woman from this planet.
- The pleasure is all mine.
- Oh, thanks.
I'm really looking forward to sitting
down with you and finding out more
- about what you do here.
- Any time.
What do you do here?
Excuse me.
What is wrong with this woman?
She's asking about stuff
that's nobody's business.
What do I do?
Really, what do I do here?
I should have written it down.
"Qua" something.
Qua... Quar...
Quibo... Qual...
Quir... Quabity.
Quabity assuance.
No. No, no, no, no.
But I'm getting close.
Have you been introduced to Kevin?
No. Which one's Kevin?
He's here on a special work program.
He's slow, you know, in his brain.
- Oh, good for you guys.
- Yeah...
Hazing is a fun way
to show a new employee
that she is not welcome or liked.
Accounting department, listen up.
Holly, human resources.
- Angela, Oscar, and Kevin.
- Hello. Hello.
Hi.
What do you do?
I do the numbers.
Oh, good for you.
Do you want an M&M?
Oh, no, that is so sweet.
But thank you, though.
Yeah, I keep them here at my desk
so that everybody
doesn't take them.
Well, that is a very
safe place for them.
- Yeah.
- Here she is. Holly.
You know, if we hung Holly
from the ceiling,
we'd have to kiss
underneath of her.
So... I know.
Sorry. Question.
Are you real,
or are you a Hollygram?
Nice. I've never heard
that one before, actually.
- That's good.
- I bet.
Are these guys
boring your ears off?
No, no, I...
What is your commute like?
How long does it take to get in?
You know, I should make you a mix.
Do you have a CD player?
Yeah.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Great.
Do you like it?
It's a photo of everyone in the office.
So you can take it to Costa Rica.
- You're... You're not in it.
- Well, I was taking the picture.
I love it.
I would love a picture
of the two of us...
to also take to Costa Rica.
- Sure, do you have a camera here?
- No...
Does anyone have a camera here?
No one has a camera here.
I'm gonna...
I'll go get one.
Stay.
So I just got the fax.
Closing the sale, and... it's big.
- It is really big.
- Congratulations.
Don't interrupt.
Congratulations on doing your job.
- You put the sale on the web site?
- No, I didn't. I just logged it in.
Try to be a team player here, Jim.
Log it in the web site.
- Well, it already went through, so...
- Don't worry about that.
Just re-log it.
Hello?
Hike up your skirt a little more
Jim?
- I am downloading some n3p music
- That's not it. Yeah.
- for a cd mix tape for Holly.
- Close.
And I'm looking for perfect songs
that work on two levels.
What are the two levels?
The two levels being
welcome to Scranton...
and I... love you.
Okay, let's start
with the "I love you" level.
Hey, what's the group
that was from Scranton
that made it big?
- Was that U2?
- Yes.
You don't love Holly.
- I think I do.
- But you just met her.
Well, it was love at first sight.
Actually, it was...
No. It was when I heard her voice.
It was love at first see
with my ears.
Oh okay, it doesn't work like that.
Well, you're not a romantic.
Actually, I think I am, and...
I've a little bit of experience
in office romance.
- Oh, really? Like, with who?
- Yeah.
- We've been through this.
- Pam?
Yes, we are still dating.
And guess what. I took it slow.
Yeah, you took it too slow.
- Well, we're really happy.
- This thing with Holly feels...
a lot like love to me.
And that's really sweet.
And you can think that,
but you don't say that out loud.
And you definitely don't say it to her.
I don't want her to get away.
I know.
Here, Michael, you can...
court her as you get
to know her, you know?
I mean, the office is
a great place for that.
Pam and I, we got
to know each other right out there.
I mean, first time we joked around
was at my desk.
And the first meal
we ever had was...
in the break room, actually.
We were at two separate tables and...
I remember that.
The first time we kissed even
was right outside, and...
Look.
All I'm saying is that you can get
to know someone really, really well,
like I did...
Right here at work.
I was thinking...
fireworks for the party.
What do you think?
Oh, boy, I appreciate
your help, but I can't...
Oh, no. I just meant I wanted to pay
to have fireworks at the party.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm gonna miss Toby.
Yep, he's...
a heck of a guy, and I think we should
send him off right. It doesn't matter.
Here you go.
Really?
Well, we all want
a good party, right?
I'm going to propose tonight.
Holy crap!
- Hey, Kevin.
- Hi.
Do you need some help?
I can't decide what to get.
Well, what do you like to eat?
Well, I like pretzels, but...
I really like chips.
Well, how much money do you have there?
Okay, let's see.
50...
This is a button.
55, 65...
Okay, you have 75 cents.
So that means you could get
anything up on the top row.
I am totally gonna bang Holly!
She is cute and helpful,
and she really seems into me.
Hey, Ryan, it's Jim.
I don't know what you got lately,
but you know what, I really don't care
because you're trying to get rid of me.
And I bet you think I don't care enough
about this job to actually fight back,
but you're wrong,
because I do, and I will.
So you can keep trying
to push me out of this place,
but guess what...
I'm not going anywhere.
Damn it!
Hello, Holly.
What are you doing?
You don't...
You don't have to do that. I mean,
we have already put-together chairs.
That's how we buy them, actually.
I'm trying to adjust
the lumbar support on Toby's chair,
and that made this up/down
lever thing not work.
And then I took
the whole chair apart, and...
that is the story
of me on the floor.
It's pretty good, right?
I'm gonna sell the movie rights.
And the sequel,
woman stands at desk and works.
So,
I have no idea how you...
How you sit like that.
Yoga.
Sit on floor and
put together chair we will.
Yo-da.
Pass curvy metal piece you will.
So are you in town this weekend?
'Cause I'm not...
I'm not...
I'm not gonna be in town.
I'm going out of town.
So you can't make my orgy?
Kidding.
Acting!
- Acting!
Lovitz.
Yeah.
I did it.
- What'd you do?
- I talked to her... Holly.
Just pleasantries. Nothing, you know,
not like, do you want kids?
Or religion or what side
of the bed do you want?
Hey, I can take either side
of the bed at this point.
- Okay, so how'd that feel?
- It was hard. I wanted to kiss her.
Oh, I'm so glad you didn't.
Oh, god.
Laying a base.
- Laying a base.
- There you go.
There's plenty
of base laying left, right?
Yeah.
Hello, Angela.
Phyllis, you look like
you're gonna have a heart attack.
Could I get a list of your vendors?
- I shredded it.
- Why would you do that?
Gosh, I just don't know.
Why do you think?
Sorry.
What'd you guys do?
Oh, there he is.
Thought you had gone home already.
Why don't you go home
and come back for the party?
Well, we still have to do
the exit interview.
Yes, we do.
I'll let you in on a little secret. I've
been looking forward to this moment.
Very, very much.
I... I have been steeped
in anticipation.
Toby has been
cruisin' for a bruisin'
for 12 years,
and I am now his cruise director.
And my name is captain Bruisin'.
- Thanks, Michael. I didn't expect...
- Can I just say that
of all the idiots
in all the idiot villages
in all the idiot worlds,
you stand alone, my friend.
- Hello.
- Hey!
- Hi, good to see you.
- You too.
I'm just having
a little exit interview.
Yeah, I know. That's why I'm here.
No, no. This is very boring stuff.
Why don't you take a tour?
Have you seen the bailer?
No, no, I'll look at it later.
It's part of my job.
Okay.
- Did you need me to take notes?
- Hi, Pam. Stay.
Okay.
All right.
Well then,
I will proceed.
I just have some...
questions that I was gonna ask.
Who do you think you are?
I'm Toby.
Yeah.
Correct.
What gives... What...
What gives you the right?
I brought the binder.
Do you wanna take a little look?
Sure, you know what, that sounds good.
I'll take a little looksie.
- Here we go.
- Thank you.
"What would you improve...
"about Dunder Mifflin?"
This place...
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- I've got some ideas.
I'm not asking it,
I'm just reading it out loud.
Oh, I'd like to hear the answer.
Well, let me see.
I would...
I'll kill you.
I guess everything's okay.
I made it this far, right?
What's the point?
Why don't you open your present?
This might not be what I think...
that I don't even know's in there 'cause
there are a lot of presents in my car,
and I don't know which is which.
"Suck on this."
- What the hell is that?
- Michael...
What do you mean "Michael"?!
That's not even my handwriting.
Hey!
What the hell is going on here?!
Who thought it would be hysterical
to give Toby a rock
for his going-away gift?!
- You did. You made me wrap it.
- No!
I thought it was over the line.
I just...
You know what that is?
You know what that is? That is...
a psyche.
Psyche.
So, that is not
my real gift to Toby.
- So what is your gift?
- My gift is forthcoming, Pam.
What is it?
I am going to give Toby...
Your watch?
Yes, I am.
That was it.
How did you know that?
- I just knew.
- How did you know?
Oh, that is so sweet.
Well...
That's my watch.
Thanks. I'm gonna set it
to Costa Rica time.
Hey, that's good.
Hey, it's the kid.
Look, look, look.
It's the temp. Look.
- Oh, my gosh.
- It's the temp.
- Is that the police?
- Yes.
This is what happened.
Ryan's big project
was the web site,
which wasn't doing so well.
So Ryan, to give
the impression of sales,
recorded them twice.
Once as office sales,
and once as web site sales.
Which's what we refer to in the business
as misleading the shareholders.
Another good term is fraud.
The real crime, I think,
was the beard.
Oh, my god. Ryan.
Oh, my god.
I cannot wait
to visit Ryan in prison.
I'm gonna wear my hottest track suit
and get my hair done.
And then be, like, "Hi, Ryan."
And then all the other prisoners
are gonna be like, "Damn!
"Ryan, you got a hot ex-girlfriend.
"I would never have treated her so bad
when I was outside of prison."
Would you do me a favor
and connect me to Ryan?
Absolutely.
Right to voice mail.
Hey, Ryan, it's Jim.
You know what?
Totally disregard that last voice mail
because you obviously
have your hands tied.
Good luck.
What's protocol on this?
Well, I normally do nothing,
I guess.
You shouldn't...
Michael, are you okay?
I'm just worried about my friend.
Of course you are.
Just... I'm fine.
I'm holding it together.
I have a business to run. I'm cool.
No, hey, stop.
You can let yourself be upset.
He's your friend.
You know what I usually find?
Holly is sweet and simple.
Like a lady baker.
I... would not be surprised
to find out that she had worked
in a bakery before coming here.
She has that kind of warmth.
I'm pretty sure she's baked
on a professional level.
Cool!
A bouncy house!
Kevin, take your shoes off first.
No anti-gravity machine, huh?
Sorry, Michael.
I don't think they're real.
The ferris wheel
is pretty cool, though.
Look at our parking lot.
Yeah, who'd have thought?
Is Jim gonna propose tonight?
He is, isn't he?
No, he's not.
Is he?
Oh, it was a pretty good company,
but I just couldn't see a future there.
They kept hiring from the outside.
It was easy to get in,
but impossible to rise up.
That's what she...
A lot of places are like that.
I think it's really cool
you hired Kevin.
Thanks.
- You have it?
- Almost.
Here we go, here we go.
Put it in.
That... that's my car.
What are you doing?
- What the hell's going on here?!
- Nothing you need to know.
- There is a raccoon in the car, Dwight!
- No, there's not.
- Why did you do that?
- It was playful hazing.
No, there's no such thing
as playful hazing.
Dwight, I want you
to look at Holly now.
Everybody, I want you
to look at Holly right now.
And maybe if you look at her deeply
enough, you'll see what I see in her.
And that is
that we are all very lucky
to have her here.
Holly is the best thing...
that has happened to this company
since World War II.
50 years...
She is the best.
- Take care of that, all right?
- It's not rabid.
- Thanks for bringing that up.
- Get it out, come on, get it out.
I'm really sorry.
Michael, thank you so much
for saying that.
I feel so welcome here.
I just...
Excuse me.
Did you see that? Did you see it?
Did you see what...
Well, Jan didn't believe
in showing affection, so...
sometimes I don't know how to react to
when a girl touches me.
I like it.
Mrs. Vance, we're all out.
Kev, I need you to do me a solid
and go buy some more barbecue sauce.
Okay.
Cool.
You drive your own car?
Yup, this is my car.
Do you drive your own car?
Yep, just like you.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'm really proud of you.
All right.
Let's hear it for Darryl and his band.
You know what?
Let's also give a shout out to Phyllis
for this awesome party, huh?
Probably the best one
that we have ever had, right?
But the real reason
that we are here
is to say good-bye to a guy
who we will probably
never ever see again.
Now, a lot of you know
that I am an accomplished songwriter.
Song parody writer.
I have done things like...
Beers in heaven.
- Classic.
- Or Total eclipse of the fart.
- Not my favorite, but...
- I love to sing them,
but I am not going to be
doing that today.
I am going to be doing
something I wrote specifically for Toby.
Do you know...
- Goodbye stranger, Supertramp?
- Yeah.
It was early morning yesterday
I was up before the dawn
and I really have enjoyed my stay
but Toby must be moving on
I'm gonna miss Toby.
He has a nice, calming presence
in the office.
Goodbye, Toby
it's been nice
hope you find your paradise
Don't tell him I said this,
but I always thought he was kinda cute.
Come tomorrow feel no pain
Feel no pain
Toby's goin' away!
See ya!
See ya, Toby, see ya!
He's outta here.
Goodbye, Toby
- Not bad.
- Oh, hey.
Thanks.
Someday I would love
to hear Beers in heaven.
Oh, okay. Yeah.
Well, actually, too soon.
It's...
It's very sexual.
Sorry.
Kevin.
Kevin, where are you?
You missed my song, buddy.
Yeah, Michael, I'm at Gerrity's.
You have to come down here.
Just pay for it and we'll
reimburse you when you get back.
No, I brought my money.
There's something
that you need to see.
- What is it?
- Just hurry.
- Is he okay?
- Yeah, he needs me at the supermarket.
The party, driving to the supermarket...
It was a big day for him.
Yeah, that's true.
Don't move a muscle.
I will be back momentarily,
all right?
No, you can...
Finish your drink and then I'll...
I'll be back.
- It was good to see you.
- It was great to see you, Jan.
Okay.
- Hello, Jan.
- Hello... Michael.
Kevin, really?
We're...
Sorry, we're in the middle of a party.
Is this why you called me?
Yeah, Michael, I just...
I think you kids have a lot
to catch up on.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Thanks, Kevin.
I can't believe it!
Look at you!
- Are you nauseous?
- No.
Do you...
Do you have cravings?
You never touched my Propecia
or my Accutane?
- No, I didn't... touch that.
- Good. Thank god. 'Cause that's...
Wow, I'm so happy.
I am so deliriously happy.
- Why?
- Because you're pregnant.
And because it obviously happened
when we were together, and...
- I am very proud...
- Yeah, it did happen
when we were together.
That's true.
But you...
are not...
You're not the dad.
You cheated on me?
- When I specifically asked you not to?
- No, I did not...
I did not cheat on you.
I did not.
Well... okay.
Okay. So it's not mine,
and it's not somebody else's, so...
I know...
the whole toilet seat thing
is a myth, so...
I went to...
a sperm bank.
You did?
- When we were going out?
- Yeah.
I don't understand.
You always used to be
very cautious.
- I'd wear two condoms.
- I know.
You'd rather have somebody else's sperm
than mine?
No, no, no.
It's not just any sperm bank.
I mean, it's really...
This is a really, really great place.
It's amazing, actually.
I'm gonna bring you the catalogue.
You should look through it. It's...
And it's a fact, it's right next to that
little breakfast place that you like
in the city where you can
draw on the tables.
Ihop.
If I was 22 and I had lots of time
to have lots of children, then sure,
let's let Michael have a shot at one.
But honestly, I need
to make this one count.
That's really good.
I feel so much better.
I just needed to get
all of that out onto the table.
I'm glad you told me.
I don't know what you're gonna
be doing tomorrow,
but I have my lamaze class
in Allentown.
And...
you could come.
I usually, you know, use
a foam noodle instead of a partner.
I've to think about it.
Okay.
My whole life, I...
have known two things.
I love sex,
and I want to have kids.
And I always thought that those
two things would go hand in hand.
But now, I think it might be
one or the other.
Oh, look they're starting.
Well, I hope you had fun today.
'Cause you're never ever
throwing a party again.
Can I have your attention, please?
I was waiting for
the right time to do this,
and I can't think
of a better time than right now,
with the music playing,
and all our friends around,
and the fireworks going off.
My parents are here...
Andrew and Ellen Bernard.
Thank you for sharing
in this joyous moment.
Miss Angela Martin,
will you please join me onstage?
Okay, then I will
come to you, my flower.
Damn it!
Angela...
Will you do me the honor...
Of giving me your tiny hand...
in marriage?
Okay.
Into the mike, sweetie.
I said okay.
She said yes!
And the crowd goes wild!
I've been carrying that ring around
in my wallet for six years.
Because you don't know
when you're gonna meet the right girl
and the moment's gonna be right.
And tonight,
with the fireworks and the music
and everything...
it was right.
Can I be your bridesmaid?
No.
Well...
It's my own fault.
Tuna!
I'm engaged!
I know. That's awesome, man.
That's great.
Mr. Andrew Bernard.
It's got a nice ring to it.
Hey.
Hey, you know, I just realized...
I don't have a picture of the two of us.
Oh, yeah...
- Yeah. Could we?
- Sure.
Meredith, do you mind?
- This one right here.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
Oh, let's do it again.
Pam, your smile is weird.
It's digital, so just
take as many as you want.
One, two, three.
I don't know, I just...
I really thought Jim
was gonna propose tonight.
- Hey there.
- Hey.
- So, you missed something really big.
- Yeah?
Andy proposed to
one of your accountants.
I'm not so specific as I can be
on my first day, but...
Well, I can see Andy
proposing to Angela.
I can also see him
proposing to Oscar.
So...
You know, somehow, after all those ribs,
I'm still really hungry.
I don't know, I was thinking of maybe
going off-campus somewhere
and getting some dessert.
Well, you know what?
You should go to the Glider Diner.
Ask Stanley about that.
He practically lives there.
Okay.
I'll go to the diner with you.
That would be great.
Yeah, we can go eat pie.
I love pie.
- Me too.
- Okay.
- Have a good night.
- Okay. Good night.
Yeah, it was a good day.
I mean, first day's are
always the hardest, right?
Well, I should go.
I gotta buckle him in.
Well, this is it.
- I am here to see you off.
- Thanks.
Really, Michael?
Sorry, corporate policy.
- It's not.
- You might take something.
- Don't think he's gonna take anything.
- Okay, security guard.
Oh, some kind of... alarm.
Okay.
Hi, Jan, it's Michael.
I just...
I just want to let you know
that I am going to go to your...
lamaze class tomorrow.
And if there is any details
you need to fill me in on, like...
what, exactly, lamaze is,
that would be great.
And I will see you
tomorrow morning.
I am going to be...
kind of a daddy.
Party planning's a real high.
Like a runner's high.
- Oh, my god!
- What?
www.tvsubtitles.net