Hey. Any luck with that big meeting yet ?
I've got Michael's lucky tie.
No, they're in the conference room.
- Okay.
- Wait, are those Michael's Levis ?
Yeah, who dry-cleans jeans ?
Michael and his jeans.
He gets in them and....
I'm not exactly sure what happens.
But...
I can tell you, he loves the
way he looks in those jeans.
I know that's why he
started casual Fridays.
I'll take those.
Thanks.
Episode 7 - season 2
" The client"
Synchro: Occeane
Transcript : Nikki (twiztv.com)
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus
This is a projection of
the county's needs.
Graphs and charts
Somebody's been really
doing their homework.
- Looks like USA Today.
- 13 schools,
2 hospitals...
So this possible client
they're talking about
Actually a big deal.
It's Lackawanna County.
Our whole county.
And if we get this, they might
not have to downsize our branch.
And I could work here for years.
And years...
Years.
So, when we get to
the Radisson, I'd like to
I changed it to Chili's.
Excuse me ?
Radisson just gives out this vibe.
It's like,
"Oh, I'm doing business at the Radisson."
It's kinda snooty, so...
You had no right to do that, Michael.
Here's the thing, Chili's
is the new golf course.
It's where business happens.
Small Businessman Magazine.
It said that.
It will. I sent it in.
Letter to the editor.
Alright.
But you will let me run this meeting.
- Powertrip.
- What ?
She had done a background check on me.
She had it printed out,
Yeah.
And she was asking me about stuff line
by line while we were having dinner.
- What's going on ?
- We are doing worst first dates.
Oh my God. I win.
Okay.
it was a minor league hockey game.
He brought his brother.
And when I went to the bathroom,
the game ended,
- And they forgot about me.
- Okay, that's a joke.
No, they had to come back for me.
Wait, when was this ?
It was, not that long ago.
Wait, not Roy.
Say it's not your fiancé
I always knew...
Pam has refused to go to
sports games with Roy.
But, I never knew why.
Interesting.
Okay, let's do this thing.
- Wish us luck.
- Good luck Michael,
- Good luck Jan.
- Thank you.
Kiss ass. Okay !
Probably going to go late tonight,
burning the midnight tequila.
So,
I think you all could, just take off now.
Michael, this shouldn't take
more than an hour.
Well...
Do you always shut down the entire
office when you leave for an hour ?
No, no, that would not be efficient.
Actually,  they just don't get very
much work done when I'm not here.
That's not true.
I know how to delegate.
And they do more work when I'm not here.
Not more...
The same amount of work...
Is done whether I am here or not.
HEY EVERYBODY LISTEN UP !
This is what we're gonna do.
You sit tight untill I
return, sound good ?
Doesn't matter.
It's an order.
Follow it blindly.
Okay ?
Alright, ciao.
Adios !
- So which way is Chili's ?
- I'll drive.
No, that's alright.
I want to leave straight from there.
It's just a couple blocks away. So..
Boy, you really don't
know Scranton, do you ?
- I know Scranton.
- At all.
- Alright.
- Have you ever been to Scranton, Jan ?
it's just a couple blocks away
we can go together.
Jan Levinson-Gould.
Jan is cold.
If she was sitting across
from you on a train,
and she wasn't moving,
you might think she was dead.
We should come up with
a signal of some sort.
Why would we need a signal ?
Well, in case one of us gets into trouble.
The other one can signal...
What kind of trouble are you
planning on getting in Michael ?
Well, I, it could be either of us.
You're going to let me do the talking,
we agreed on that.
Yes !
Hello ? Christian ?
- Yes.
- I thought that was you. Hi.
Michael Scott, this is
Jan Levinson-Gould.
-  Just Jan Levinson.
- No Gould ?
No.
Thank you very much for meeting with us.
- Have you been waiting long ?
- No, not long.
- Good.
- Jan, what happened ?
- Michael.
- Is Gould dead ? What...
Michael. We got divorced, okay ?
- I'm so sorry, excuse me.
- Wow, you're kidding me
- Do you wanna talk about it ?
- Michael.
- Could we have a table for three please ?
- When did this happen ?
- We're in a meeting.
- Okay.
This way please
- Christian...
- Alright, after you
Thank you
I thought we could start by going
over the needs of the county.
Right.
Well, Lackawanna County
has not been immune,
to the slow economic growth
over the past five years.
So for us, the name of the
game is budget reduction.
- Awesome Blossom ?
- What ?
I think we should share
and Awesome Blossom.
What do you say ? They are awsome.
You want to, Christian ? Awesome ?
- Sure.
- Okay, it's done.
Actually, Megan !
May we have an Awesome Blossom, please ?
Extra  Awsome ?
Not it's done.
-  So, if you have a...
- Hey, I heard a very, very, funny joke...
- You wanna hear it ?
- Christian...
You don't have to listen to this.
- It's okay, I like jokes.
- Okay.
- Just the one.
- Just one joke ? Okay.
Well, if it's just gonna be one...
I, will think of a different joke.
Let's see.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Pam, it's Michael. I need you to go into
my office and check some data for me.
Okay,
- You want me to read 'em ?
- Yes
Okay, um, a fisherman is walking down 5
th Avenue leading an animal behind him.
No! Nope. Told it. Not as good
as you think. Pick another one.
Okay.
There's a transcript
between a Naval ship.
Bingo! And a lighthouse.
Yes, that is hysterical. Could you
start that one from the beginning ?
Sure, there's a transcript between
a Naval ship and a lighthouse.
Is this real ?
It is a screenplay...
Starring himself.
Agent Michael Scarn.
Of the F.B.I.
How long is this ?
Pam, good work.
Wait, stop.
- Drawings.
- What is that?
Those are drawings in case,
the writing didn't really,
put a picture in your head.
And there he is, in the flesh,
Agent Michael Scarn
Now we know what he looks like.
First guy says, "Well, I'm
an astronaut, so I drive a Saturn."
And the second guy says,
"Well, I am a pimp, so I
drive a cheap Escort."
And the third guy says,
"I got you both beat, I'm a proctologist,
so I drive a brown Probe."
Oh, no! Oh my God, that's funny! I
almost had Awesome Blossom
coming out of my nose!
"S'il vous plaît," could I have
a vodka tonic, please?
Do we all have our copy of "Threat
Level Midnight" by Michael Scott ?
Yeah.
Alright.
Let's get this started. I'm gonna be
reading the action descriptions
And Phyllis, I would like you to
play Catherine Zeta-Jones.
- That's the character's name?
- You guys  should not doing this/
Why not Dwight? This is a movie.
I mean this is for all of
America to enjoy.
You took something that
doesn't belong to you.
- Dwight. do you want to...
- Brought it in here, made copies of it...
The lead role of Agent Michael Scarn ?
That's delicious! I love it.
We would probably be upset with ourselves
if we went this whole night
without talking business.
So, Dunder Mifflin can provide,
a level of personal
service to the county,
that the warehouse chains
just can't match.
- Well, we are out to save money.
- What's the bottom line?
Blah! Blah blah blah. Blu bad be bah.
That's why I wanted a signal.
Between us.
So,
I wouldn't have to just shout
nonsense words. That's her fault.
Did somebody say babyback ribs ?
I don't think Christian has time for that.
- Michael.
- I have time.
I want my babyback, babyback, babyback...
Chili's babyback ribs..
Inside the F.B.I., Agent Michael Scarn
sits with his feet up on his desk
Catherine Zeta-Jones enters.
- Sir, you have some messages.
- Not now !
They're important.
Okay, what are they ?
The first message is "I love you."
That's from me.
Not in a thousand years, Catherine.
We work together.
And get off my desk.
Yes, I have acted before.
I was in a production of Oklahoma !
in the seventh grade.
I played the part of Mutie the mailman.
They had too many kids, so they
made up roles like that.
And I was good.
If it isn't my old partner.
Samuel L. Chang.
Agent Michael Scarn, you
lost some weight.
Thank you for noticing.
Now, keep me company fo
r one more mission.
Hey, I have to work late.
You're joking, right?
Agent Michael Scarn takes
out a nine millimeter gun
And shoots the cake to bits.
Agent Michael Scarn, you so funny.
Word.
Michael's movie ?
Two thumbs down!
A man sitting several seats down who
has a gold face turns to Michael Scarn.
Oscar, you wanna play Goldenface?
Mr. Scarn !
perhaps you would be more
comfortable in my private jet.
Yes, perhaps I would Goldenface.
Sam, get my luggage.
I  forget it, brotha.
Samuel, you are such and idiot !
You are the worst assistant ever.
And you're disgusting Dwigt.
Wait, who's Dwigt ?
Here's what we think happened.
Michael's sidekick, who all through
the movie is this complete idiot,
who's causing the downfall of the United
States, was originally named Dwight.
But then Michael changed it to Samuel L.
Chang using a search and replace.
But that doesn't work on
misspelled words.
Leaving behind one, Dwigt.
And Dwight figured it out.
Oops.
D-W-I-G-H-T
Okay, you know what ?
I am done with this. That's it, the end.
Well, some of us wanna
keep reading, so...
You don't speak for everyone, Jim.
Okay, announcement.
My uncle bought me some fireworks.
And anyone who wants to see a real show,
come with me outside now.
That's actually a good idea,
we'll all take a brief intermission.
Hey, are you hungry?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
And so after watching my mom
go through so much pain,
I decided to keep that promise,
that I made to her and take care of her.
This brings us to Jan. Truth or dare ?
- Tell us about your divorce.
- Oh, no, Michael. Michael, Michael.
- Ooh, right ?
- Michael please, no.
Hey. So you're not gonna play.
She's not playing.
She's not playing the game.
- We've been fighting for a while,
- That's not fair.
he didn't want kids.
I knew that going into it.
But he also knew that I did. So I guess
I thought that he would change his mind.
He thought that I would change mine.
You didn't.
I was stupid.
No. No.
You were not stupid.
- Gould was stupid, right ?
- That's right.
You know, you were really brave.
I mean, you, you put your arms
out there, you slit your wrists.
It's true. Yous said :
"World, this is my blood, it's red."
"Just like yours, so love me."
I had plans to meet a friend tonight.
Which I had to cancel.
But this is cool too.
I'm not a complainer.
Wow.
For the bugs.
Nice.
That's excellent because bugs love..
My famous grilled cheese sandwich.
Yes !
Nice.
I can't remember the last time
someone made me dinner.
Right down the street ?
Kenneth  Road, born and raised.
Spent my whole life right
here in Lackawanna County
And I do not intend on moving.
I know this place. I know how
many hospitals we have.
how many schools we have.
It's home, you know?
I know the challenges that
this county's up against.
Here's the thing about those discount
suppliers, they don't care.
They come in, they undercut everything.
And they run us out of business.
And then, once we're all gone,
they jack up the prices.
- I know.
- It's bad.
- It's terrible.
- It is, you know what ? It really is.
I don't know.
I guess I could give you
guys our business but,
you have to meet me halfway, okay ?
Because they're expecting
me to make cuts.
Well, corporate's gonna go ballistic,
but, you think we could, Jan?
So, I guess I'll see you in..
10 hours.
What are you going
to do with your time off?
- Travel.
- Yeah.
I've been looking forward to it.
It's gonna be...
really nice. I'm gonna find myself.
You have new music ?
Yeah.
Definitely.
- See ya !
- Bye !
Thanks.
- Yes !
- We did it.
- We got it !
- We nailed it.
- I mean we got it!
- Come here.
I am really...
...thrilled.
- Let's go.
- What ?
- Go and, okay.
Where are we going ?
Doesn't matter.
Goin' to the go-go
Okay.
Michael ?
His car's not in the parking lot.
I should check the accident reports.
Who's this ?
Jan?
Morning, Pam.
No, nothing happened.
I swear ! Nothing happened.
What I'm...
totally being serious.
A gentleman does not kiss and tell.
And neither do I.
I'm...seriously, guys, I'm, I'm not,
I don't wanna go into it at all.
t's of limits. (
Fine, I took her back to her hotel,
and we made out for a little while.
It was great. I mean she told
me about her divorce.
We talked for about five hours,
she fell asleep on my arm. You know.
- Hello, Dwight.
- Did you do her?
- Who ?
- Jan Levinson-Gould.
No, no...
- No Gould.
- Did you do her ?
This is none of your affair.
- And she is your boss.
- And she is a woman.
She is a strong, soft...
...thoughtful, sexy woman.
And you know what ?
I don't think I can sit here,
And let you talk about her that way,
Without me defending her honor.
Jan, I defend your honor.
Is that all ?
Jan didn't come back for
her car last night.
What ?!
Could it be that Agent Michael Scarn
has finally found his Catherine Zeta ?
Oh, I don't know...
Oh, my God !
- This is Jan's cell.
- No way.
Dunder  Mifflin, this is Pam.
I know we have to register,
as a consensual sexual
relationship with HR.
My question, do I do it as the man,
does she do it as my superior ? I
I don't know. That leads to other issues
that we may have, in our relationship.
It's...Excuse me
Hello? Hi, just talking about you.
The camera.
No.How's traffic ?
I miss you, what ?
Okay.
Well.
if it was a mistake, it was
a wonderful mistake.
No, just...
No, I did not intentionally
get you drunk.
No, no. This is just a fight.
This is just a first fight of
many fights we're gonna have.
Right.
No.
You, I don't understand.
You wanna see other people.
Only other people.
I think you're still a little bit drunk.
Excuse me, Excuse me ?
I think you're stil- yes.
Why don't you just come back here?
We can go to the hotel.
Have a few drinks.
No, I didn't slip you something !
Some might even say we
had our first date last night.
- Oh really?
- Really.
- Why might some say that ?
- 'Cause there was dinner, by candelight
Dinner and a show, if you
include Michael's movie.
And there was dancing and fireworks.
- Pretty good date..
- We didn't dance
You're right, we didn't dance.
It was more like...
swaying.
- But, still romantic.
- Swaying isn't dancing.
At least I didn't leave you at a
high school hockey game.
I have some faxes to get out.
Oh, come on. Pam, I'm...
Okay, we didn't dance.
And I was totally joking, anyway.
it's not really a date if the
girl goes home to her fiancé.
Right ?
www.tvsubtitles.net