Hello, my name's Oscar,
I'm an accountant
at Scranton, Pennsylvania,
and I'm gay.
And I'm here to tell you
that yes, it does get better.
- When I was young...
- What's he doing?
Stretching at younger gays.
No, it's just a way
to tell young people
no matter how hard it gets for them,
there's a brave future ahead.
With you.
No matter how hard it gets for you...
Kelly! Seriously, I...
Keep chatting.
I'm checking my makeup in your webcam.
Do you not own a mirror?
Webcams make me look
the way I look in my fantasies.
I know, right?
What is it?
- You always look good in those things.
- I'm throwing out all my mirrors.
Okay, as you can see,
I now have a cool job
at a dynamic workplace.
Being gay is a celebration of life,
it's a simple...
No, I'm sorry,
I just can't sit idly by
and have the gay youth
of America mislead
- by some reductionist...
- I'm not misleading.
Pep talk.
Sexuality is a spectrum.
It's a paradox
to think of any sexual activity
as normal.
It gets better but it also
gets vastly more complicated.
Robert, that guy,
he looks just like you.
Damn it, Kevin!
God!
You okay, Robert?
- Fine.
- Put some ice on it.
In any case, it gets better.
Maybe not much better, but better.
- Feygnasse Team -
.: La Fabrique :.
8x24: Free Family
Portrait Studio
One, two, three!
I wanted to give a nice gift
to the tenants in the building.
At first I thought, "muffin basket".
Then I thought, "what's
even more precious to people?"
- Can you just smile, please?
- I don't want to!
Their own children.
Hey, everybody, just a few hours left
for the free family portrait studio.
We'd love to see little Jada.
- You can bring by your little angel.
- No, thank you.
Jim, you've got those two cute kids.
We sure would love to see them.
I know why you're doing this.
Last week, I may have gone too far.
I'll explain it.
I found out
where he gets his clothes cleaned,
ordered the same suit,
made with tear-away velcro.
And...
You can fill in the rest.
Wha...
Damn it, Jim!
Now he's trying to get me
to bring my children into work.
I think it's fair to be cautious.
Let me get this straight.
You lost all of it.
All your winnings.
$150,000.
You're telling me
no one wanted an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals?
They did not.
And you got half a million of these?
- Well, I gotta try it.
- I wouldn't.
Come on, what's the harm?
- What flavor was that?
- Coconut penis.
- The coconut's pretty subtle.
- Come on, man.
Can't you give us a yes or a no?
I don't know, man.
Y'all quit with a lot of confidence.
Y'all came up in here dancing
and everybody was...
Hold on a second.
If I were Val,
I would break up with Brandon.
Then I would date the hell out of me.
I wouldn't give in to me too fast,
let me buy myself
some nice dinners and such.
But when I finally did give in,
I would go crazy on myself.
Hi, guys.
How's it going?
I'm good, thank you.
And how are you?
Great, yeah, good.
How the mediocre have fallen.
Oh, God.
I'm not here to get my old job back.
I blew my opportunity.
I'm moving on.
I just wanted to come in here
and literally beg you
for something, anything.
I will sweep the floors,
water the plants, clean the toilets.
I don't need anyone.
- Pull the poop out of it.
- That's not a thing.
Please.
Give me something!
Why don't you clean the carpets
for today?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Up you get then.
Pick yourself up.
- There it is.
- Thank you.
You don't need to...
I have a delicious secret.
Good.
This carpet's overdue
for a good mopping.
Is a mop the most efficient tool
to use on a carpet?
Yeah, it is actually.
I can't hold it in any longer.
I am faking this, okay?
Because I convinced David Wallace
to buy Dunder Mifflin back
from Sabre.
And at 3:00 today,
he's gonna walk in here
and reinstate me
as manager.
Family picture!
What?
Honey, we talked about this.
No, we talked
about not bringing them in
to Dwight's photo studio-slash-trap.
Yes, and then we decided
that was crazy.
No, we decided it was crazy
not to worry about it.
No, we settled
in a much more rational place, remember?
We decided that there's no way
Dwight would harm a child.
But are you 100% sure?
I don't think any of us are.
But it's free.
And we'll keep our eye on them.
And we will make sure
that Dwight doesn't do anything
C-R-A-Z-Y.
Wait, C-R-A-Z...
Great, right up there.
You just sit right here one time.
Here you go.
All right, why don't you just...
give him to me and...
Perfect.
- Ready?
- This is great.
There you go.
- Let's do it.
- I'll just stand here then.
Keep your eye on Dwight.
- Sir, could you look into the camera?
- Let's do it, shoot it.
- Great.
- Up here.
Jim, right here, right here.
- Good.
- Oh, so that's it?
Yes.
- See? That wasn't so hard.
- Cute kids, thanks for coming.
- Hello, everybody.
- Uh, what? Why?
What... How are you doing?
My office got a call that they were
shooting family portraits right here.
And if there's one thing that every
politician instinctively understands,
it's a good photo op.
You're going
to go through the hallway.
Here's a map. And if you get lost,
just follow the blue line.
Senator Lipton, welcome.
Nice to see you.
May I hold him?
- Sure.
- No.
I am going to hold him because
I haven't seen him all day.
I think that Dwight
is doing this whole thing
to get a sample of my baby's DNA
to prove he's the father.
Which...
Is impossible...
Because the Senator is the only man
I've ever been with.
Okay, hold on a second, folks. A few
of the baby's hairs are out of place.
I like the baby's hair the way it is.
Really?
This is getting more and more
delicious by the minute.
It's go time.
Hey, Nellie, I made you...
I made you some soup.
Well, I don't want any soup.
But it's really good...
Oh, come on, Andy!
I know this is going
to be a great payoff.
A delicious moment.
But after you're manager,
some of these images
are going to be hard to shake.
- Well, but it...
- Just calibrate.
Okay? Calibrate.
Okay, here we go.
I don't want to throw
a wrench into the works,
but I want everything to be perfect, and
his fingernails are bothering me abit.
Leave us alone.
I guess we're okay
with the fingernails.
Okay, great.
Suit yourself.
Although, are those excess skin cells
on his cheek distracting to you as well?
Dwight, we're fine!
Oopsie,
did somebody make a boopsie?
I'm just gonna take him out
and change him just for a second.
He defecated.
You're stinky.
A lot has changed
since y'all left, okay?
You're gonna have to
jump through some hoops.
And the new foreman is here.
Now she's one of the best
we've ever known, okay?
So I need you
to show her your utmost respect.
Make sure that she feels welcome
and at home, okay?
Can you do that?
That's
some pretty blatant complimenting.
- I don't talk to her like that.
- Brandon?
I would.
- You would?
- Yeah.
- You're trying to hit on my girlfriend?
- He's not.
Yes, I am.
Just so everyone's on the same page.
So you really think
she's gonna leave a guy
who owns his own restaurant
for a dude who ate
his own restaurant?
- Good slam.
- Thank you, biggie.
- Good luck to you.
- Oh, and have a burger for me.
- Okay, shall we take a few more?
- I think we have all the shots we need.
- Thank you, Dwight.
- Okay, here we go...
Give me the diaper!
Dwight!
Is this what you were looking for?
Andy, we wanted to talk to you.
A lot of us are
very concerned about you.
You're dirty, you stink of booze,
you're limping inexplicably.
I just want you guys not to worry.
'Cause old Andy's gonna be just fine.
This is what we're talking about.
What was that accent?
And last time I checked, you were drunk
and now you're not drunk.
No, unfortunately it's true.
He's been a nightmare.
And the worst part is
he's been taking it out on me.
- You hit her?
- What?
That is not the deal.
Calibrate.
He's not hitting me.
But he's been verbally abusing me...
That's not true either!
That's also total...
Everyone, please relax.
I think you're gonna
like this surprise guest.
Happy birthday to Gabe.
Oh, get out, skeleton man!
I can refer you
to someone to talk to.
Hold on. {\*- Give you a name or--
}I'm just gonna...
Hey, what's the scoop?
Are you close?
What?
You have to come now.
Traffic clears.
No, next Friday...
That's not gonna work.
Okay.
Damn it!
Well, this is not gonna be quite
as delicious as I wanted,
but I do have a very tasty
announcement for you guys.
Not only am I not a lowly janitor,
I am the regional manager once again.
Guys, I got my old job back.
I'm not crazy.
I convinced David Wallace
to give me my job back.
David Wallace hasn't
worked here in years.
Okay, yes, I see the confusion.
I saw David at the fundraiser.
He is now a multi-millionaire
because he sold his toy vacuum
"Suck It," to the US Military.
- Andy, come on.
- Even I know that's weird.
I... Okay, I get
how that sounds crazy.
Hey, Andy, nobody's
calling you crazy, Andy.
We're your friends, Andy.
Stop saying my name.
- He's not making this up.
- Thank you.
Andy tells me about seeing
David Wallace all the time.
But have you ever
actually seen him yourself?
Oh, my God.
Wait.
Erin, come on.
You know
I've been talking to David Wallace.
Do you see David Wallace
in the room right now?
Operation Phoenix is a go.
Just get the car ready.
Look at me like you're adoring me
and I look at the camera
- like you're not there.
- I do adore you.
Andrew, it's time for you to go home.
You're better than this.
Yeah, I know.
Everyone's better than this,
because this is the worst thing
I have ever seen.
Why'd they add coconut?
I miss original.
Long time.
What are you doing here?
Is it true you're buying the company?
Okay.
I guess the word is out.
Please keep this a secret.
I've been talking with Andy...
What?
Thought I heard my name.
I'm the new manager?
I'll get to that in a second.
But... it's me, right?
- As we've discussed.
- What?
- It's very possible. Probable.
- My God.
From janitor to manager?
That's quite a cinderella story.
From M-O-P
to M-V-P.
There's an official announcement,
a few details to...
From total loss, to total boss.
Can we expect
any payroll interruptions?
Now that is a great question.
All your operations,
or most of your operations
are down in Florida,
so to shift back up...
I was so looking forward to that
and it did not...
go as I thought it would.
So we're not gonna be
a part of Sabre anymore?
Nothing is gonna be a part of it.
Joe Bennett's planning
on liquidating the rest of the company.
Wouldn't wanna be a Sabre employee
right about now.
I'm actually the CEO.
I didn't realize
you were standing there.
My friend, trust me,
this is for the best.
I never understood
that corporate mess.
- Great to meet you.
- Likewise, I'm Bob Kazamakis.
Pleasure.
I'd love to give you a little rundown
on what I've learned about this place.
That's very gracious of you, Bob.
I would love that.
Please.
Guess I'd better take off
these dirty rags.
Figure out how to be
a manager of this place.
Perhaps your year of experience
managing this branch will come in handy.
Gosh, I hope so.
- No! God, Mose!
- Hi, Angela.
Get out of the car!
Get out!
Where is he?
- I'm not supposed to say.
- Tell me!
Tell me where he is!
Mose, damn it!
Where did he go?
Mose, get back here!
Let's see that smile.
- Right here?
- Cool.
Looks like I might get
my delicious moment after all.
May I say one thing?
It would be rude of me
not to let you...
say whatever is on your mind.
The quality of mercy is not strained.
- No.
- It droppeth.
As the gentle rain from heaven,
upon the place beneath.
Do not bring Shakespeare into this.
How dare you play the bard card?
It blesseth he who gives
and he who takes.
'Tis mightiest in the mightiest.
I just want one
motherfucking delicious moment.
Is that too much to ask?
If I were to hire you back...
If...
What do you think you would do well?
Special projects manager,
that's my background.
I just go around
doing whatever I want.
All right, you sly bastard.
When can you start?
Okay, everyone.
Had a conversation with Bob,
and since I'm going to be CEO now,
there will be no need for him.
That's gotta hurt.
But he's going to make
so much money from the liquidation,
he's gonna be freed up
to do something much more important.
David has generously offered
to donate one million dollars
in matching funds
to a cause that's very...
dear to me.
So for the next three years,
I'll be traveling overseas,
concentrating on all of my efforts
on educating, mentoring,
some African, some Asian,
but mainly Eastern European women.
I had no idea how pervasive this was
until Bob explained it to me.
Oprah Winfrey's leadership academy
and other schools like it,
while wonderful,
end with high school.
I wanna see these girls
right through college.
Especially the gymnasts.
They've lost so many...
years of crucial education
to perfecting their bodies.
Muscle groups the rest of us
can't even fathom.
Gymnasts?
You're going to seek out
uneducated gymnasts?
Yeah, so I'm hoping to identify
some truly exceptional women
who show great promise.
It's been fun.
It's been a great year.
Hello.
Where is it?
They're testing it now.
How long does it take
to get the results?
72 hours.
You're gonna wait here?
Dwight, I can't do this.
- Hey, how are you?
- You didn't call.
Well, the issue that concerned me...
You know what this is about...
Cock.
www.tvsubtitles.net