Oh, damn. Lost another file.
Gonna have to reboot again.
Hey, Dwight, do you want an Altoid?
What do you think?
In school, we learned about this scientist
who trained dogs to salivate
at the sound of a bell
By feeding them whenever a bell rang
So, for the past couple weeks
I¡¯ve been conducting a similar experiment.
Dwight, do you want an Altoid?
Okay.
Altoid?
Sure.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I...
What?
I don¡¯t know, I...
Oh, my mouth tastes so bad
all of a sudden.
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
µð¾¾ÀÎ»çÀÌµå ¹Ìµå°¶
The Office 3x16 "Phyllis' Wedding"
Original Air Date: Feb 8, 2007 (NBC)
Always the bridesmaids. Right, ladies?
Okay, for the next one,
everybody hop out.
Just Phyllis and dad.
Actually, lets bring mom back in,
and the sisters.
And, you and you and you.
Great.
Phyllis is getting married.
And I am in the wedding party.
She has asked me to push
her father¡¯s wheelchair down to aisle.
So, basically, I am co-giving away the bride.
Since I pay her salary,
it is like I am paying for the wedding.
which I¡¯m happy to do.
It¡¯s a big day for Phyllis.
But, it¡¯s an even bigger day for me.
Employer of the bride.
Yes, I put Michael in my wedding.
It was the only way I could think
to get six weeks off for my honeymoon.
No one else has ever gotten six weeks before.
Phyllis ended up using
the exact same invitations
as Roy and me.
So, it was kind of like
being invited to my own wedding.
And I was like,
¡°Wait, I thought I called that off.¡±
So. What¡¯s in the box?
A toaster, you?
Uh, toaster.
Unbelievable.
- Hello, Angela.
- Hi, Dwight.
You look as beautiful
as the Queen of England.
Thank you.
Don¡¯t linger. Break left.
Left.
The Schrutes have their own traditions.
We usually marry standing in our own graves.
Make the funeral very romantic.
But, the weddings are a bleak affair.
Those flowers are nice.
Yeah. ¡°P and R?¡±
¡°Phyllis and Robert.¡±
Ah, of course.
Also, ¡°Pam and Roy.¡±
There she is!
I swear Phyllis, you are as beautiful
as the first day you started work at Dunder-Mifflin.
Thanks, Michael. That¡¯s sweet.
Same as when you said it outside.
How you doing? You excited?
- Yes, very.
- Me too.
If, um... if you need to vomit,
that is okay.
I did.
Do you want to talk about tonight?
No.
Because I know you¡¯re probably
worried about pleasing Bob.
A lot of pressure.
Phyllis, did you break wind?
It¡¯s okay if you did.
It¡¯s a very natural reaction.
It¡¯s your wedding and you¡¯re nervous.
Um, that wasn¡¯t me.
Okay. Um...
I¡¯m sure that Bob...
Wow, that is...
That is pungent.
Um, I lost my train of thought.
Are you set on the hairstyle?
- I thought it was...
- Here, let me...
Michael, no.
- Just cover up that bald patch.
- I don't need your help. Thank you.
No, Michael, please.
- Please, I just need some time alone.
- Okay, okay.
You might be surprised to learn
that I have only been to one other wedding.
It¡¯s actually a very cute story.
My mom was marrying Jeff,
and they asked me to be ring bearer.
And, I was understandably emotional
And, somehow my pants became wet.
I hate you!
Long story short.
Jeff¡¯s dog ended up as ring bearer.
And the irony is that after the ceremony,
that dog peed on everything
and nobody said boo.
Why are all these people here?
There¡¯s too many people on this earth.
We need a new plague.
Who are all these people?
You know what?
- I bet a lot of them are wedding crashers.
- No way.
- Did you ever see that movie?
- Of course I saw it.
I saw Wedding Crashers accidentally.
I bought a ticket for Grizzly Man,
and went into the wrong theater.
After one hour, I figured I was in the wrong theater.
But I kept waiting.
Because that¡¯s the thing about bear attacks.
They come when you least expect it.
You know, I just wish...
I wish I had the investigative powers
To actually smoke
some of these guys out, you know?
Once again, Jim...
I will take care of this.
I will locate the wedding crashers
And report them to Phyllis.
That way I won¡¯t have to get her a gift.
Hi, I¡¯m Kevin.
Where did you find her?
At the gym.
Right. The gym!
Could you scoot over?
You¡¯re on my dress.
I thought you¡¯re not supposed
to wear white to a wedding.
I know, but there was an emergency.
I look really good in white.
This strapping young lad sitting here is
Phyllis¡¯ father, Elbert.
And, he is quite the ladies¡¯ man.
Aren¡¯t you, Elbert, huh?
Ah, ring bearer.
I could¡¯ve done better.
I will do better.
I am going to be better.
Can¡¯t believe I¡¯m actually doing this.
Are you ready for this, Elbert?
I am.
Let¡¯s do it!
That¡¯s my dress.
No, no, it¡¯s okay.
It¡¯s a miracle.
This is bullshit.
Me walking Phyllis down the aisle
was supposed to be the highlight of the wedding.
And now... the wedding has no highlight.
I can¡¯t believe I pushed that¡¦
That guy¡¯s lazy ass around all day
Until he was ready to stand up
And steal the show.
That¡¯s¡¦
Well, I got news for you, Elbert...
If that¡¯s your real name...
The show¡¯s not over.
And, do you, Phyllis,
take Bob Vance of Vance refrigeration
To be your lawfully wedded husband.
I do.
Ladies and gentlemen!
May I present to you for the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
And do you, Bob, take Phyllis
To be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
- You may now kiss the bride.
- Ladies and gentlemen!
for the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
That's what I'm talking about!
Congratulations, Phyllis.
You look lovely.
Your dress is very white.
So white my eyes are burning.
Thank, Angela.
Congratulations, Bob.
You¡¯re a good man.
But, just know...
If you ever lay a finger on Phyllis, I will kill you.
If you ever lay a finger on Phyllis,
I will kill you.
Agreed.
No fingers will be laid on Phyllis!
Oh, decide to sit down again, huh?
Great.
But you can hear me, too.
Best of luck, Phyllis.
Also, I¡¯m gonna need to see a copy of the guest manifest,
as well as photographs of the caterers.
I don¡¯t have that, Dwight.
Damn it, Phyllis!
Are you alright?
This must be so awful for you.
What do you mean?
Well, this was supposed to be your wedding.
Oh, um... No, that¡¯s, um...
It¡¯s actually fine.
There¡¯s no way it¡¯s fine. I¡¯m sorry, but...
If I was you, I would just like, freak out.
and get really drunk,
and then tell someone I was pregnant.
Okay, that¡¯s a lot of good ideas. Thanks.
Excuse me, sir.
How do you know the happy couple?
Who?
The bride and groom.
What are their names?
Oh, I... I don¡¯t... uh...
- I¡¯m not sure.
- Oh, I get it, I get it.
Come on, freeloader, let¡¯s move it.
- Oh! Come on! Come on!
- Okay, okay. Where are we going?
You gotta find yourself
another wedding to crash, my friend.
Phyllis? Are you happy with everything?
What can I do to make it more perfecter?
Oh, it¡¯s beautiful.
Why don¡¯t you find your seat
and enjoy the buffet?
I¡¯m already on it.
Chicken, totally undercooked.
I sent it back.
It¡¯s fish.
I will take care of that.
I do. I know a fair amount about
fine food and drink.
This is a white.
No, this is not our first wedding.
This is the third wedding
that Scrantonicity has played.
We also played our bassist¡¯s wedding
And our guitarist¡¯s wedding.
Ah, attention, everyone. Attention, please.
Uh, I¡¯m supposed to ask
if anyone has seen Uncle Al.
He is old and has brown eyes
and dementia.
His family is very concerned.
It¡¯s a very serious situation.
The Police - Roxanne
¢Ý Roxanne ¢Ý
You don¡¯t have to put on your red light
- Hey
I know I don¡¯t normally notice
these kinds of things, but, uh...
This wedding is really nice.
I mean the flowers and stuff...
Phyllis has got some great taste.
You are kidding me, right?
I know you probably not gonna remember this.
But, um, those color roses...
I got you those color roses for our prom.
Roy, I picked those flowers.
Phyllis just stole all of my ideas for our wedding.
I guess I wasn¡¯t really too involved in the planning.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It¡¯s okay.
Well, I think it¡¯s suck for you.
I¡¯m the one who actually wanted to get married.
Phyllis, you¡¯re a wonderful woman.
And, you¡¯re a hell of bowler!
She is.
Cheers!
Thank you, Randy.
That was great. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hi, I¡¯m Michael Scott.
And, for the next 40 minutes,
I am going to be your tour guide
through the lives of Phyllis Lapin and Bob Vance.
One of the great,
seemingly impossible love stories of our time.
My name is Michael Scott.
Webster¡¯s Dictionary defines ¡°wedding¡±
As the fusing of two metals with a hot torch.
Well, you know something?
I think you guys are two metals...
Gold medals.
For those of you who don¡¯t know me,
I¡¯m Michael Scott, Phyllis¡¯ boss.
To quote from The Princess Bride,
"Marriage"
The most important part of a speech is the opening line.
When time is not a factor,
I like to try out three or four different ones.
Phyllis and Bob...
Their celebrity couple name would be
"Phlob.¡±
You look at her,
And she¡¯s kind of matronly today.
But, back in highschool,
I swear her nickname was ¡°Easy Rider¡±.
Now, as for Bob... Bob Vance...
- Okay, that¡¯s enough. Thanks.
- ¡¦ is a guy that
- Thanks, Michael. Give me, Michael.
- He works...
Okay, hold on. Hold on, hold on.
Look, um... I didn¡¯t say anything
when Phyllis¡¯s dad upstaged me at the ceremony.
And I think you owe me this, okay?
- Give me the microphone.
- Well, I¡¯m not going to.
- It¡¯s okay.
- Okay, good.
- You¡¯re outta here!
- Yeah, I¡¯m¡¦ you¡¯re outta here.
I hate you!
The Police - Message in a Bottle
¢Ý A year has passed since I wrote my note ¢Ý
When are we gonna get to see
some of those famous Beesly dance moves?
I¡¯m pacing myself.
Come on, get out there!
Give the people what they want.
- Oh, I¡¯m such a dorky dancer.
- I know
And it¡¯s very cute.
Hypothetically, if I thought Pam was interested, then...
No, it¡¯s totally hypothetical.
- Come... come on!
- I can¡¯t let you in, Michael.
Dwight, just...
No, it¡¯s Bob and Phyllis¡¯ orders.
Look, I just wanted to go in,
and quietly sit and have a piece of cake
I¡¯m not even gonna dance.
One song maybe.
You¡¯re a real-life wedding crasher
and I must bounce you.
I¡¯m sorry. It gives me no pleasure.
Okay.
Sting - Fields of Gold
¢Ý You will remember me ¢Ý
¢Ý When the west wind moves ¢Ý
¢Ý Upon the fields of barley ¢Ý
¢Ý You¡¯ll forget the sun ¢Ý
¢Ý In his jealous way ¢Ý
¢Ý As we walk in fields of gold ¢Ý
¢Ý So she took her love ¢Ý
¢Ý For the gaze ¢Ý
¢Ý Even after you¡¯re gone ¢Ý
¢Ý I know that you love me ¢Ý
They¡¯re playing our song, huh?
Yeah, that¡¯s weird.
I thought they only played The Police.
I know. I, uh...
I gave them 20 bucks.
You wanna dance?
Dreams last so long
¢Ý Even after you¡¯re gone ¢Ý
¢Ý I know that you love me ¢Ý
¢Ý And soon you will see ¢Ý
¢Ý You were meant for me ¢Ý
¢Ý And I was meant for you ¢Ý
Hey, you want to get out of here?
Here¡¯s a non-hypothetical.
I¡¯m really happy I¡¯m with Karen.
The Police - Every little thing she does is magic
¢Ý Every little thing she does is magic ¢Ý
¢Ý Everything she do just turn me on ¢Ý
¢Ý Even though my life before tragic ¢Ý
¢Ý Now I know my love for her goes on ¢Ý
One, two, three!
Toby! Yeah!
I just want Phyllis to have a great day.
Phyllis and you will be great together.
We are great together.
We are a great team.
The Celtics were a great team.
Yes, yes¡¦ they were.
Robert Parrish.
I should talk to her.
I don¡¯t want this to ruin her honeymoon.
Well, nobody ever helped me.
I had to do it myself.
Even the doctor didn¡¯t know.
Dude, keep it together.
I listened to you for a half an hour
Even though most of that stuffs were right over my head.
Phyllis...
Phyllis, wait, please?
I¡¯m sorry.
I just... I just wanted to
make this a day to remember.
You found Uncle Al!
Yeah, yeah. He¡¯s kind of a weirdo.
- Thank you, Michael.
- You are¡¦
You¡¯re welcome.
They say that your wedding day goes by in a such a flash
That you¡¯re lucky if you even get a piece of your own cake.
I say that¡¯s crazy.
I say, ¡°Let them eat cake.¡±
Margaret Thatcher said that a marriage is...
Smart broad.
Be careful with the Bob... Oh, no!
Phyllis, Phyllis! Come on!
You look like a clown. Here.
Oh, get me! Get me!
Script & Syncronization : EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
Date: Feb. 11, 2007
drama forum in South Korea : http://kr.dcinside13.imagesearch.yahoo.com/zb40/zboard.php?id=f_drama
www.tvsubtitles.net