I am actually looking forward to
take your daughter to work day.
I am not great with kids.
But I want to get better.
Because I'm getting married.
So I put out a bunch of
extra candy on my desk.
So the kids will come talk to me.
Like the witch in Hansel and Gretel.
Bribery. Nice.
I have more.
It's Pam.
Ms. Beesly if your nasty.
- Oh.
- Janet Jackson.
Hey, you having a wardrobe
malfunction.
You can't be you can't be
nasty today.
'Cause of the...
Oh, God. Is that today ?
I reminded you last night.
Listen, I like kids.
But this is not a kids environment.
This is like HBO.
No limits.
Who knows what I'm gonna say ?
Crazy stuff.
And it is R rated.
It is not rated G.
I am like Eddie Murphy in Raw.
And they are trying to make me into
Eddie Murphy in Daddy Daycare.
Both great movies.
But still.
Well, I'll be in my office.
Don't you think you should
say something ?
- They're cool.
- Michael, I think that as the boss,
- you should... you should really...
- Fine, fine, fine !
Hi children !
I'm Michael Scott.
And I am in charge of this place.
How do I make you understand ?
I am like Superman.
And the people who work here are
like citizens of Gotham City.
- That's Batman.
- Okay,
I'm Aquaman.
Where does he live, guys ?
The ocean.
I work with a bunch of nerds.
Episode 18 - Season 2
TAKE YOUR DAUGHTER TO WORK DAY
Synchronisation: Catch 22 team
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
Hello, tiny one.
Come on.
You are the future.
This is my file cabinet.
This is the partition between
my desk and Angela's.
Abby is my fiancee Stacy's daughter.
I think she'll have a good time.
I just hope she doesn't
look on my computer.
Actually, I'd better go check.
Michael, you remember
my daughter Melissa.
Oh, yes. Hello, how are you ?
Good to see you.
Wow, you've really grown up.
You know what ? Don't mind me saying so.
She is turning into a stone cold fox.
Better keep the frat boys away from her.
- I'm in 8th grade.
- She's in middle school.
Yeah, middle school's amazing.
It is extraordinary.
An extraordinary time.
It's not that children
make me uncomfortable.
It's just that, why be a dad
when you can be a fun uncle ?
I've never heard of anyone
rebelling against their fun uncle.
They want how many spiral pads?
Well, 50. I over ordered
because they had a back order.
I got permission to
bring Jakey in to work.
Which is great because,
he got suspended this week.
And now I don't have
to pay for a sitter.
Can you pull that down there ?
Okay,  tell 'em what you wanted to say.
- Do you need any help ?
- No,
Thanks.
We'd have to explain everything.
It's probably just easier
if we do it ourselves.
All right, I wasn't expecting that.
Let's, go draw.
Oh, my God. She is so cute,
I wanna die.
Don't you just love kids, Angela ?
I guess I wouldn't mind a
pair of small, well behaved boys.
God, I cannot wait to get
pregnant and have babies.
Kelly and I both agreed that
we would just have fun.
And I'm learning that fun for Kelly is,
getting married and having babies.
Immediately.
With me.
Just compare last year's
orders with this year's.
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
Yes.
We...
Yeah, they're very...
They're different.
Yeah, we can stick with last year's.
We're just gonna have to
supplement it somehow.
Hey, Abby !
Do you wanna help me
shred some old documents ?
It's actually pretty cool.
No thanks.
I only have one goal today
To make one kid like me.
Just one.
What are you reading ?
"From the Mixed up Files of
Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler."
Best book.
- Yeah, but I read it before.
- So have I.
Hey, question.
if you had to spend the night in the Met
Ior the aquarium which would it be ?
-  Definitely the aquarium.
- Definitely.
Yes. Glad you said that.
You don't want to help me
with some of my sales, do you ?
'Cause I'm kinda swamped.
- Sure.
- Really ?
Yes.
- And you're Abby, right ?
- Yes
I'm Jim.
And, let's sell some paper.
- All right.
- Let's start with your mom.
Yes. Well.
We can...
Hey, you know what ?
Can I call you back ?
I'll call you right back. Yes, I promise
Hello, can I help you ?
You can pick that up if you want.
That's all right.
Wanna bring it over..
Here, I'll make some room.
My name's Michael.
- What's your name ?
- Sasha.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you know what that is ?
That is a train whistle.
Like I'm the conductor.
But I'm sort of the conductor
of the office here, right ?
- You wanna try ?
- Sure.
All  aboard for sales !
Next stop, Cook...
Camonga !
- You broke my hand.
- There is no way that hurt.
Really ?
Cause she's pretty strong, Dwight.
Little girl, come over here.
Shake my hand.
Come on, I don't have all day.
I didn't feel anything. Nothing.
You're so weak.
Excuse me, these are expensive
collector's items. Okay ?
- Do you have any computer games ?
- No.
I don't have computer games
on my work computer.
That would be inappropriate.
Yeah, Meredith doesn't have
any either.
- It's so lame here.
- You call your mom Meredith ?
- That's very disrespectful.
- Whatever, okay ?
You can refer to me as Mr. Schrute.
That's your name ?
- Mr. Poop?
- Shrute.
- Mr. Shrute.
- Sure, Mr. Poop.
Schrute.
Are you Mother Goose ?
I drink like, 100 iced Macchiatos a
day and practically nothing else.
There's a really cool coffee place,
Jitters, at the Steamtown Mall.
You ever been there ?
- No.
- You've never been to Jitters ?
Ryan, you are so dorky.
Gimme your number
so I can text you.
Come on.
Can I have your e-mail address ?
I just thought you should know.
I think something a little
fishy is going on.
- A little fishy ?
- Yeah.
I've been noticing them all day.
And I was thinking...
That little girl is a child !
I don't wanna see you sniffing
around her anymore this afternoon !
Do you understand ?
Boy, have you lost your mind ?
- No, no.
- Cause I'll help you find it.
Watcha looking for ? Ain't nobody
gonna help you out there.
Jesus can come through that door,
and he's not gonna help you.
If you don't stop sniffing
around my child.
Stanley yelled at me today.
That was one of the most
frightening experiences of my life.
That was Greensleeves.
A traditional English ballad about
the beheaded Anne Boleyn.
And now, a very special treat.
A book my granmutter used
to read me when I was a kid.
This is a very special story
It's called Struwwelpeter by
Heinrich Hoffmann from 1864.
The great tall tailor always comes
to little girls that suck their thumbs.
Are you listening, Sasha ? Right ?
And ere they dream what he's about,
he takes his great sharp scissors out
and then cuts their thumbs clean off.
- Dwight, What the hell are you reading?
- There's a photo.
These are cautionary tales for kids.
- Yeah, you know what ? No...
- My granmutter used to read...
They kids don't wanna
hear some weirdo book,
that your Nazi war criminal
grandmother gave you.
- What's a Nazi ?
Nazi was a facist movement in the 1930s.
Don't, talk about Nazis in
front of... You know what ?
They're gonna have nightmares.
Why don't you just shut it ?
I was gonna teach the children
how to make corn husk dolls.
Why don't you just leave ? Okay ?
- Bye, Mr. Poop.
- All right
There goes Mr. Poop. Now,
- who likes Dane Cook?
- I do !
Children cannot lie. They are innocent,
and they speak the truth.
And out of the mouths of babes,
Michael Scott is freakin' cool.
You know, I never misbehaved
in front of my father.
Because he was a very
strict disciplinarian.
I can only hope my mate has
some of those same qualities.
This is where the magic happens.
Right over here, let me show you this.
See all these ?
You know what that is ?
That's paper. This is where paper
comes from. Any questions ?
So, you cut the paper
and dye it and stuff ?
No, we don't actually cut the paper.
That's a good question.
The paper is sent to us cut and
dyed from a paper manufacturer.
And then we sell it to a business
for more than we pay for it.
- That's not fair.
-  No.
- Yes it is.
- No, no.
You need someone in
the middle to facilitate...
- You're just the middle man.
- I'm not just the middle man.
Wait, why doesn't the sawmill just
sell the paper directly to people ?
You're describing Office Depot.
And they're kind of running us
out of business.
We have better service than they do.
There's Creed ! Let's take a look
at what he's doing, everybody.
This is Creed. And he is in charge of...
Something, right ?
- That is correct.
- Say hi to the kids.
- Hi kids.
You ever seen a foot
with four toes ?
- Cool !
- What are you doing ? Stop it, stop it.
Just no, no, no. No !
Would you cut it out ?
-  What is your problem ?
- Well, the hair covers it up mostly.
We're not gonna see the
four-toed Creed, okay ?
You know, there's something interesting
about me that you might wanna know.
I used to be the star of a kids show.
- No way.
- It's true, I did.
- You serious ? Really ?
- I am totally serious.
There was a show called
Fundle Bundle, and I was the star.
- That doesn't sound like a show.
-  It's true. I can prove it.
Watch this. Ryan,
can you come here a second ?
I would like you to go to
my mother's house in Dixon City.
And if she's at the pool, the back
kitchen window should be unlocked.
- I want you to boost yourself up.
- All right.
I want you to go down to
the basement.
There is a tape
labeled Fundle Bundle.
I want you to grab it.
I want you to get my guitar.
- Right, okay.
- I want you to get a tambourine.
Do you know how to
play the tambourine ?
I'm already getting the
pizzas from Bernetti's, so...
- You know, I can go with him.
- No ! I will go.
Okay ! Thank you, Ryan
Good attitude. Hottest in the office.
All right, now what kind
of pizza do you like ?
I don't get why parents are
always complaining about,
how tuff it is to raise kids.
You joke around with them.
You give 'em pizza
You give 'em candy.
You let them live their lives.
They're adults for God's sake.
I am going to give you a little blast
from the past of Michael Gary Scott,
when he was a child star.
And a show that you might
remember called Fundle Bundle.
Okay, without further ado, Ryan ?
Bundle, are you
ready to come on in ?
Let's have some fun !
That is Miss Trudy. Can't tell from her
costume, but she had an amazing body.
Okay, you can fast forward.
And I want you.
- Is that a real working windmill ?
- It's coming up. Stop ! Stop. Stop.
Yes. That is Edward R. Meow.
- That's pretty funny.
- Yeah.
Hey, what's your name ?
- My name's Chet.
- Well, hi Chet.
- Is that Chet Montgomery ?
-  I don't, I don't know.
Yeah, that is !
He's the meteorologist from channel 4.
Checking in with Chet. Doppler 7.
That guy's legit.
What do you wanna
be when you grow up ?
I wanna be on TV.
And he is on TV now !
Will everybody please shut up.
Please. So you don't miss it.
Okay, next.
- So, what's your name ?
- That's me, that's me.
Hi Michael, I'm Ed. What's your
favorite subject at school ?
- Recess.
So, tell me, what do you
wanna be when you grow up ?
I wanna be married
and have 100 kids.
So  I can have 100 friends.
And no one can say
no to being my friend.
Okay. Well, nice talking
with you, Michael.
Back to you Ms. Trudy.
Hi everyone, it's one
of my favorite...
- Could have sworn there was...
- Did you get married ?
- No.
- Why not ?
It just never happened.
So do you have any kids ?
Nope.
Do you have a girlfriend ?
- I do okay.
- Was Chet Montgomery cool back then ?
- Even I have a girlfriend.
- Okay. All right, okay.
So you didn't get to
be what you wanted to be.
I guess not.
You know, I have a load of work to do.
So I am going to grab a
slice of this delish pizza.
And I'm gonna go do my work.
Bye.
He's not coming out.
He won't pick up the phone.
I can't believe his mom dressed him
like that. That's the real tragedy.
Pam, Pam ! I love this guy !
So, Melissa, I met your
mom a couple times.
She's so nice.
Who, Terri ?
That woman is not my mother.
That is my step mother.
Mr. Poop, I have to tell you something.
Okay. But first, that's not my name.
You're ugly.
Well, at least I'm not
a horrible little latchkey kid
who got suspended from school,
so...
Meredith !
Yeah ?
I think these belong to you.
That's okay, she can keep those.
Believe me, she has enough toys.
She doesn't need your watch.
Thank you.
Is everything okay ?
You have to ask me that because
you work for human resources.
That's true.
You know, sure,
playing the field is great.
Don't get me wrong. But there's more
to life than notches on my bedpost.
Tell me something honestly.
Do you think, that it is too
late for me to have kids ?
Well, you need a wife
first or at least a girlfriend.
- What about...
-Not Jan.
- Okay.
- You really wanna have kids,
I guess you could somehow.
Foster parent or something.
Or biologically.
Somehow.
Thanks, that's...No, that really
means a lot to me.
Hey, does Sasha have a godfather ?
Because...
- Yes.
- O-kay.
Is it okay if I take one ?
- Sure.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is your job hard ?
It's not too bad.
I get to shred things sometimes.
Do you wanna see ?
- Yeah !
- Really ?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Here it is.
Don't put your fingers in there.
- Cool ?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I get to do this,
like, every week.
- That's so awesome.
- I know.
Yes, it is true
I, Michael Scott am signing up
with an online dating service.
Thousands of people have done it,
and I'm going to do it.
I need a user name.
And I have a great one.
Little Kid Lover.
That way, people will know exactly
where my priorities are at.
Go  ahead.
Do you wanna come over
for dinner tonight ?
Oh man, I would love to.
I can't tonight, but can
I come over some other time ?
What are you doing ?
You never have plans.
Thanks, Kev.
- I'm actually going on a date.
- Nice.
Hey, no, please. You can't leave yet.
There's still one more
thing we need to do.
You, you are on the road
Must have a code
That you can live by
And so become yourself
Because the past
Is just a good-bye
And teach your children well
Why does he own a guitar if he
doesn't know how to play it ?
I think he thought his
ukulele skills would transfer.
And feed them on your dreams
My theory is that...
The one they picked
The one you know by
Don't you ever ask them why
If I told you you would cry
You just look at them and sigh
And know they love you
And they do.
Your parents love you very much.
One more time.
You...
www.tvsubtitles.net