Hey
Oh, what's this?
That is a demerit.
"Jim Halpert, tardiness."
Oh, I love it already.
You've got to learn, Jim,
you're second in command,
but that does not put you above the law.
Oh I understand.
And, I also have lots of questions.
Like what does a demerit mean?
Let's put it this way.
You do not want to
receive three of those.
Lay it on me.
Three demerits,
and you'll receive a citation.
- Now that sounds serious.
- Oh it is serious.
Five citations, and you're
looking at a violation.
Four of those, and you'll
receive a verbal warning.
Keep it up, and you're
looking at a written warning.
Two of those, that'll
land you in a world of hurt.
In the form of
a disciplinary review,
written up by me and placed
on the desk of my immediate superior.
Which would be me.
That is correct.
Okay, I want a copy on my desk,
by the end of the day,
or you will receive
a full disadulation.
What's a dis-
what's that?
Oh, you don't want to know.
Script: EasyL
Sync: easyL, nemameya
theOffice.tistory.com present
3x22 "Women's Appreciation"
Original Air Date: May 3, 2007 (NBC)
Hey Phillis. You alright?
I think I just got flashed.
What?
Really?
- In the parking lot.
- Oh my God!
Move!
Okay, I'll call the real police.
What happened?
What can I do to help?
I'll check the web.
Thank you.
The police are on this. They said
they already have received 3 calls.
Can you tell us what happened?
I was walking to the building and
this man asked me for directions.
And he was holding a map.
And when I walked over, he had it out-
on the map.
Phyllis, you're a married woman.
The guy was just hanging brain.
I mean, what's all the fuss?
If that's flashing, then lock me up.
That's just like so creepy.
What's happening?
Some guy exposed himself
to Phyllis in the parking lot.
Really? Is she okay?
Yeah, Bob Vance took her
for a walk to calm down.
Okay.
Phyllis, you say?
What is so funny?
I mean, did he even see Pam?
Or, uh, Karen from behind?
I'm guessing not.
I'm sorry.
Pretty funny
when you think about it.
It really doesn't.
It's disgusting in the meaning.
Okay, masters of comedy.
A guy dropped his pants.
Have you ever been to the circus?
Okay.
He's back!
Hey, what's going on?
there's a police car is in the...
What?
What's going on?
Oh, Phyllis' got flashed.
It's um-
I don't think laughing about it
is an appropriate response.
Come on. We're laughing at Phyllis
and she's even not here.
So, no harm, no foul
I don't think
the woman in this office...
Incidentally, where're you
during all of this.
Maybe you're the flash.
I was at the parent-teacher conference.
Aha, Prove it.
Let's see your penis.
You know, as that was
coming out of my mouth,
I knew that it was wrong.
In all the excitement,
I forgot that my primary goal
is to keep people safe.
Women can't have fun
if they don't feel safe.
For example, Jan and I have a
safe word in case things go too far.
Foliage.
And if one of us says that word,
the other one has to stop.
Although last time,
she pretended she didn't hear me.
Michael, come over after work tonight, okay?
And, I miss your body.
I don't know.
I feel... I drive a lot.
Spending unfortune gas...
-
That- I don't know.
That makes me kind of uncomfortable.
$300?
I don't know...
you know, whatever, Just let
my assistant know if you're coming over
so he can get more vodka, okay?
- Hunter, are you on?
- You got it, Jan.
Employees of this office are
very small and delicate.
Deserve protection from local pervs.
Better a thousand
innocent men are locked up
than one guilty man roam free.
I'm sick over these things,
those people out there are clearly afraid.
And, that can't happen.
Not in my house.
Agreed. Let me show you
what I've been working on.
There are several penises there
I'd love Phyllis to run her eyes over.
You know, see if we can
catches the pervert.
This is the last thing
that Phyllis need to see right now, Dwight.
Think of that one
Dwight, are those your pants?
That's a Polaroid.
Attention everybody.
Dwight has something
he'd like to say.
Due to a recent incident
involving Phyllis,
a man, a map, and his penis,
I think you know
what I'm referring to,
Michael has authorized me to form
an emergency, anti-flashing, task force.
Question: Won't that interfere
with your other task forces?
Answer: No, because this is
being given primary one.
This is petition for the business
park to upgrade security cameras
As well as install two floodlights
in the parking lot.
And I know what you're thinking.
Won't that just shed
more light on the penises.
But that is a risk we have to take.
Pam, you can draw, kind of,
why don't you work with Phallus
on drawing a picture of the exposer
that I can post around the community.
Phallus?
Phyllis, sorry.
I've got penises on the brain.
Back to work everybody.
I don't often miss Roy.
But I can tell you one thing.
I wish someone had flashed me
when I was with Roy.
Because that would have been
the ass-kicking of the year.
Especially if it had been Jim.
He would not have wanted me
to have seen Jim's ...
I am, I am saying a lot of things.
I didn't really get a good look.
That's okay.
I don't feel like answering phones.
Hey, did you guys see this memo that Dwight sent out?
"Women will be sent home"
"if they wear makeup or heels
exceeding one-quarter inch."
"Females are not allowed
to speak to strangers"
"unless given written
authorization by Dwight Schrute."
This is ridiculous.
Attention, I am removing
all bananas from the kitchen.
Dwight, this memo
that you distributed, is insulting.
Desperate times call for
desperate measures.
"Sleeves down to the wrists,"
"button-up collars,
and muted colors."
Nobody dresses like that.
Okay, you know what
something, Dwight?
We are not the terrorist.
Why don't you just
take these women,
Put'em in the burlap sack,
hit'em with stick.
Because, that's what you're doing.
I celebrate these women.
They deserve the right
to dress as they please.
If Pam wants to show
more cleavage,
she should be able to.
I encourage that.
Look, it's really simple.
We just want you guys
treat us as those respect.
See? That's
what we're talking about.
Did you hear that, Dwight?
Yes. Did you hear that, Michael?
No, Dwight, Respect!
R-E-S-P-@-$-T!
Find out what it means to me!
Alright, you know what? That's it.
Conference room in 5 minutes,
women's appreciation.
Wait a sec, how are you
qualified for that?
Oh, I don't know, James.
Did I come from a woman?
Have I slept with a woman?
More than one?
Less than three.
That is not current.
You know what?
Why doesn't Oscar run the meeting?
He's a homosexual.
Why don't you run the meeting?
You play with dolls.
Those are collectible action figures.
And they're worth more than your car.
You know what?
I am the expert.
I will conduct it.
I know the crap out of women.
I- um- would like to
apologize for all the men
who thought that
this was a laughing matter.
Are we still discussing this?
I say again, what is the big deal?
Nobody likes to be flashed.
When Meredith flashed me
at that Christmas party,
I nearly vomited.
I don't remember doing that.
- What a surprise.
- Okay, no cat fights, please.
Let's- my point is-
My point is-
A penis.
when seen in the right context,
is the most wonderful
sight for a woman.
But in the wrong context,
it is like a monster movie.
Alien.
What are- Shut it. Shut up.
Okay, so what I want to
engage us in today,
is a hardcore discussion
about women's problems.
And it's use and situation.
Magazines and TV shows and movies
portray women as skinny tall goddesses.
Well, look around.
Are women like that?
No, no, they are not.
Even the hot ones aren't
really that skinny.
So what does that say?
That says that you women
are up against it.
And it is criminal.
Society doesn't care.
Society sucks.
I don't even consider
myself a part of society.
F.Y.I. because I'm so angry
over all of this.
If it were up to me,
you ladies would be
the fashion models.
Yes, Andy.
Then the fashion models
could come here and work with me.
What you're saying is
extremely misogynistic.
Yes. Thank you.
That was not necessary,
but I appreciated it.
And it proves my point.
Women can do anything.
I'm saying that you're being sexist.
No, I'm being misogynistic.
That is insane,
I am not being sexist.
- That- it's the same thing.
- Michael.
Yes.
When I got my hair cut short,
you asked me if I was a lesbian.
Because- uh- that was
one possible explanation.
That's the why
you got that hair cut.
And, when we get mad,
you always us
if we're in a period.
I have to know whether you're serious or not.
I wish I could menstruate.
If I could menstruate,
I wouldn't have to deal with
idiotic calendars anymore.
I'd just be able to count down
from my previous cycle.
Plus, I'd be more in tune
with the moon and the tides.
Can't we just get back to work?
Yeah- okay- yes- well-
- This is not work talk.
- You're right!
And you know why?
It's because of where we are.
This is a masculine environment.
We need to find a place where you feel comfortable.
You know where we're gonna go?
Steamtown mall.
Frankly, it's kind of insulting. But,
I have a bunch of stuff
I need to return in my car.
So, I can do that.
Malls are just awful and humiliating.
They're just store after store of these horrible salespeople
making a big fuss out of an adult shopping in a junior's section.
There are petite adults who are sort of ...
smaller, who need to wear...
maybe a kids' size 10.
Okay, let's go.
Ladies of Dunder-Mifflin.
Hey, we should have
a calendar printed up.
Pam, put that in
my good idea folder.
Let's go!
- Have you finished with the sketch?
- Yeah
Doesn't seem like the type.
Phyllis got a good look.
I plan on plastering
this pervert's face everywhere.
You can run,
but you cannot hide.
Meredith! Slow down!
We're not gonna get there
any faster for death.
Thanks. I know how to drive.
You really shouldn't litter.
My car, my rules.
Hey, Jim.
You wanna go in
the women's bathroom?
No. Thank you, though.
You aren't curious?
Not really, I've seen
a bathroom before.
Yeah, but-
it's every guy's fantasy.
I think you mean
a girl's locker room.
And in the fantasy,
there's usually girls in it.
I'm going in.
Go crazy.
Oh my God.
I really appreciate your
letting me work alongside you so closely today.
Of course you do, moonface.
That's because
you're a preppy freak,
you're the office pariah,
and nobody likes you.
So, start hanging these
all around the building.
This guy looks like a real deviant.
No duh! That's why
we gotta catch him.
Start hanging those!
Aye aye, Captain.
More like, "Aye aye, General."
I don't think she's gonna make it.
Don't think she's gonna make it!
It's a little too tight!
I'm gonna find another spot.
Many women are competent drivers.
Okay, come on.
This is what we know.
Well, I stand correctly.
This is pretty cool.
Yes
Hey- uh-
where did you
decide to take Karen tonight?
Anna Maria's
What's the occasion?
6 month anniversary
What?
Nothing. I think-
we all kinda thought
you guys were just like hookin' up
No, even dating for six months.
She might mention an email
that I wrote awhile back...
Oh, right. I remember that one.
She read it to me.
She said she's not really ready
to date somebody in the office, but,
she really likes you as a friend.
I figured. It's cool. I don't-
I wouldn't want to be
in an office relationship anyway.
- I hope nobody's on a diet.
- Thanks Michael.
- Thank you Michael.
- Welcome, welcome.
Okay. So- let's dish.
What do you wanna dish about?
Anything you guys want.
This is your time.
What is a Pap smear?
Or is it "schmear"?
Like...the cream cheese.
Okay, new topic.
Kelly, how are things with Ryan?
Awesome.
Um, awful, I mean.
But uh- sometimes awesome.
what do you think about role play?
- That can be fun.
- Yeah?
Jan has this school girl fantasy-
That's pretty common one.
I just-
I feel uncomfortable
wearing the dress.
Okay, I'm going to be
at the doll store.
Sometimes the clothes at
Gap Kids are just too flashy.
So I'm forced to go to
the American Girl store.
And order clothes for
large colonial dolls.
Michael, you shouldn't do anything
that you're uncomfortable with.
Jan says anything that doesn't
scare us is not worth doing.
I don't know, maybe
we're different people.
I like cuddling
and spooning, and
she likes videotaping us
during sex.
Oh my God.
And then watching it back
right afterward to improve my form.
That is not healthy behavior.
No, it's not that bad.
The worst part is,
that she shows it to
her therapist and they discuss it.
Michael, you need to get out of this.
Nah- she's-
she's- fooling around.
That's a woman thing.
No. none of woman do stuff like that.
This is bad.
Oh, that's alright.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
You guys-
what am I going to do about Jan?
Done.
Read the pros first.
Okay. Jan is smart.
Successful.
Good clothes.
Hot
Perfect skin. Nice butt.
She does have very nice clothes.
Okay, okay, cons.
Cons.
Wears too much makeup.
Breast.
not anything to write home about.
Insecure about body.
I'm unhappy when I'm with her.
- Flat-chested.
- What was the last one?
She's totally flat.
Shrunken chesticles.
No, the one before that.
I'm unhappy when I'm with her.
Michael, you shouldn't be with
someone who doesn't make you happy.
I'm happy sometimes.
When we scrapbook,
Or, right towards the end of having sex.
Look, most relationships
have their rough patches.
You just have to push
through it sometimes.
Yeah, that's smart.
Maybe.
But it sounds like you're
just wrong for each other.
That sounds good, too.
I don't know who's right.
I just don't- I don't know.
I bet you know.
Don't think just answers.
What do you wanna do about Jan?
I wanna break up with Jan.
Wow- I wanna break up with Jan.
My mom taught me that.
Wow, I cannot believe
this yogurt has no calorie.
No one said it has no calorie.
Oh, hey guys.
I wanna do something nice for you.
Because you did something
so nice for me earlier.
I want you to go in there.
I want you to find one item
on me as a thank you.
Come on, get in here!
Let's face it.
Most guys are from dark ages.
They're cave man.
And they like woman
to be showing her cleavage,
And to be wearing
8-inch hills,
And to be wearing-
um- see-through...
underpants,
But, for me,
A woman looks best when
she is just absolutely naked.
This is so great, huh?
We should do this much more often.
I think we hang out an appropriate amount of time.
What're you doing in here?
This is the women's room.
You're in here.
I pay for that privilege.
Okay.
I'm a pretty normal guy.
I do one weird thing.
I like to go in
the women's room for no. 2.
I've been caught several times,
and I have paid dearly.
You don't want anything?
My treat.
Some panties, or-
Got thong or G-string,
T-back,
Get a nice bra-
Padded bra.
See-through, push-up, lace?
Thigh-high? Bustier? Anything.
It just, you know what, I would
love to buy you a fresh set of underwear.
Phyllis,
what do you think? Too much?
Jim's gonna love it.
I'm kind of in between boyfriends right now.
So I don't need anything sexy.
But I do need some new hand towels,
I figure I could cut up this robe.
Slower!
Meredith!
Slow it up!
Oh- oh, no.
It's Jan.
what do I do?
Answer it.
Don't answer it.
Okay, it stopped.
Crap!
That is pretty cool.
Michael, you know how to
change a wheel, right?
Uh- yeah. Yeap.
Can somebody grab me
the rubber, and I will...
Here- uh- Meredith,
why don't you put your hazard on?
Yeah, get your
hazard on for safety.
Let me see.
Here you go!
Good, yes. We have the...
lever it
Alright- Here I got it.
Do you have a crescent?
A crescent Allan?
I don't think that
we really need that, Michael.
You know what? I'm going to-
You take care of that.
I'm gonna do traffic.
Detail.
You know?
I changed a tire today.
All by myself.
This bathrobe's already
coming in handy.
Coming!
Think we'll find him?
Yeah, I do.
'Cause justice never rest
Halfsies?
No. Wholesies.
Listen, man. I really appreciate
you let me shadow you today.
I feel like I learned a lot.
Natch
Yeap.
If you don't mind,
I think I'll hang up some of
these posters around my neighborhood.
Schools, post offices, etc.
You know, I may have
underestimated you.
You're not a total ass.
Okay, I am really going to do this.
- Good luck, Michael.
- You know what?
I need my girls with me.
Pam, Karen, even Phyllis.
Come on, let's do this.
Let's do it.
Okay, remember be strong.
I love you guys.
I can hear voice mail.
- Don't leave a message-
- Hey, Jan. it's me. Michael.
I'm just calling to say
that I think we need a little break.
Permanently.
And, uh, I know
everybody says this, but
I wanna remain friends.
Or at least, business
associates who get along.
Oh just so you know,
it's not me, it's you.
Okay, buddy. Somebody
just walked in, I have to go.
Um, so I'll talk to you later.
Michael,
I was um-
I was really unhappy with
our conversation earlier.
And, I-
I just- I couldn't
stop thinking about it.
So, I decided that
I would drive down here
and apologize to you in person.
So-
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
So, we're good?
Absofruitly.
Hold on, sorry.
- No, no-
- Just wait a second.
Oh, it's from you.
- Do you wanna grab some dinner?
- Hey, Jan. it's me. Michael.
I'm just calling to say that I think
we need a little break. Permanently.
And, uh, I know
everybody says this, but
- I wanna remain friends.
- Maybe some Italian, or ?
Or, at least, business associates
- who get along.
- Chinese.
Oh just so you know,
it's not me, it's you.
- Okay, buddy...
Any man who says he totally
understands women is a fool.
beause they are un-understandable.
There's a wishing fountain at the mall.
And I threw a coin in for
every woman in the world and made a wish.
I wished for Jan to get over me,
I wished for Phyllis a plasma TV,
I wished for Pam to gain courage,
I wished for Angela a heart,
and for Kelly a brain.
"Michael, how can you
appreciate women so much,"
"but also dump one of them?"
You mean, how can I be
so illogical and flighty
and unpredictable and emotional?
Well maybe I learned something
from women after all.
Dunder Mifflin Paper slash Sex
Predator Hotline. This is Dwight Schrute.
Hey, Dwight. It's Jim.
Jim, what are you doing? I'm busy.
No, you're not. I'm looking right at you.
- I'm hanging up.
- Don't.
I have information
about the sex predator.
You have information
about the sex predator?
I saw him two minutes ago.
Where?
In the women's bathroom,
above the sink.
Anti Flashing Task Force!
Above the sink-
Pam!
www.tvsubtitles.net