Today is the test launch day for
the inaugural Sabre store.
(Makes trumpets)
And I, Dwight Truth I'm in
charge of the entire operation.
If I can prove myself today
and the store
is a hit with the media
and Nellie sees this,
the vice presidency is mine.
- Are you holding this chair?
- Yes.
'Cause I feel like
I'm gonna fall off.
- Yes. Yes.
- I'm not wearing
- the right shoes for this.
- We went over this, okay?
Your tiny fingers
make the best knots.
Hey, strangers.
So stoked
for the Sabre store opening.
Hey, my name's Tabitha.
I'm camped out in front
of the Sabre store
so I can be first in line
for the new pyramid.
Psst. It's me, Erin.
Dwight had me pretend
to be a hipster to create hype,
and it's working.
There's already people
camped out behind me.
[Cheerful music]
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Test launch day, people.
Now, I would like
to fill you in
on a little secret about me
to inspire you today.
Now, I know you probably
all think
I'm this patrician goddess.
But here's the truth.
I was born in the little
working class town of Basildon,
and until the age of 32,
[cockney accent]
I talked like this,
which was bloody horrendous,
innit?
I came from dirt--
No, lower than...
What's lower than dirt?
Loam, magma, mantle,
outer core, inner core.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Loam.
Bloody loam, I came from.
I hit rock bottom.
When I auditioned
for the Spice Girls,
I didn't even get a callback.
Which Spice Girl?
The black one.
I never stood a chance.
Okay.
Now, think about
my journey here today,
and let it inspire
your journey.
Okay.
Nellie, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Yep.
Today is press day,
and press is gonna make
or break this store.
And for a tech company,
press can only mean one thing--
Bloggers.
Dossier on bloggers.
Bloggers are gross,
bloggers are obese.
Bloggers have halitosis.
You're gonna love 'em.
Ryan is going to be
the main event today.
He is the pitchman
who is going to give
the feisty, yet profound speech
worthy of a world's fair.
Ryan, you ready to do this?
When people
see this presentation,
they're gonna [Bleep]
in their pants.
- Okay.
- Come on, man.
Seriously disgusting.
Cathy, you will be the hot
girl who talks to bloggers.
Ugh.
Kill me.
That was my idea.
Packer, you will be
the sexual predator
who has come to prey
on the trendy teenage girls
who are obsessed
with the pyramid.
- Uh...
That is excellent.
I don't see what that gets us,
but I'm a team player.
Perfect casting, right?
Schrute's out to get me.
But I'm playing the long game.
As soon as he messes up,
I swoop in like
a sexual predator.
I want to create
a sense of wonder
and enthusiasm
as if, at the end of ET,
candy poured out of the screen.
Do you understand?
I wanna get goose pimples.
Speaking of pimples,
let's release the bloggers!
Morning, everyone.
Oh, Andy, guess what
happened to me this morning?
Don't care.
Tell me later.
Listen, it's important.
You've gotta hear this.
What do you got?
- Oh, my God.
- Do you have a black eye?
Yes, I do, Phyllis.
I woke up at 4:00 A.M.
by accident,
in time for the paper
to be delivered.
Guess what.
It's not a kid on a bike.
It's a man in a car.
Andy, who punched you?
Hey, I was on the can.
What's this about a black guy
in the office?
Black eye, Meredith.
Will someone please explain
what's going on here?
Since the interesting thing
happened till now,
so much time has passed,
it's like my life is buffering.
Here's what happened.
Pam and I were arriving
for the day,
and there was a gang
in the parking lot
on bikes,
on-- on motorcycles.
And they just were
hassling Pam...
- That's true.
- They had, uh...
- Weapons.
I just stepped in to talk
some sense into them.
But these were not the kind
of people who use their words.
Punches were going,
and I ducked a few,
landed a couple,
and I was fighting them off.
It was totally, like--
like, senseless crime.
- Thank goodness he was there.
- Good job, Andy.
Yeah!
[All murmuring]
I didn't do anything
any of you wouldn't have done.
Open the gates!
There's plenty for everyone.
No need to panic.
- There's plenty for everyone!
- Quit it!
There's plenty!
Don't stampede.
No need to stampede, sir.
- I was ahead of you!
- Okay, okay, hey, hey!
It's gonna be fine.
There's plenty of pyramids.
Come on.
I was in line before you.
So you're a blogger, right?
Yeah. Blogger.
God, stay away.
Oh, I always get in trouble
around bloggers.
I'm trying to be
a good girl for once.
Uh, yeah, I already
bought my pyramid,
but I don't want to leave yet.
I haven't had so much fun
since seeing...
Zoo-ey Desh-channel at
the Couch-arilla Music Festival.
So fun.
How can we feel safe knowing
that there are gangs here?
We should call the police
right now!
- No!
- Yes!
No, no, no, no, no, we don't
need to call the police.
They'll just ask everybody
questions,
get up in everyone's business,
right, Pam?
Police are a hassle.
We settled this on the street.
And my eye will heal.
But if the police come,
then we will forever
stain our neighborhood
as a troubled area.
Why would you care
what the police think
of our neighborhood?
Because I have
neighborhood pride.
1-8-5-0-5.
- 1-8-5-0-5.
- Guys, guys.
That's so vague.
You gotta do the zip plus 4.
1-8-5-0-5...
Dash 7-4-2-7!
Look, I don't feel safe.
I think we should
call the police.
Exactly.
We need to feel safe.
Which is why...
Toby is teaching us
self-defense.
Me?
Toby, will you teach us
self-defense?
Yeah. Um... I can't
believe you remembered
I do self-defense.
Um, I'll go put on my cup.
Great.
- Yes!
- Okay.
I wasn't sure which one
of you was Chuck!
Yeah, no, it seems
to be going great.
Andy got beat up
by a fifth grade girl?
Look at that guy.
He's got his Sabre phone on,
and he's not even using it.
This is a perfect photo
for my "Daily Fail" blog.
Uh, I-I gotta go.
Okay.
Dwight, what is a fail?
That sounds bad.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's good.
It's really-- on the Internet,
it's a really--
That's a really good,
good thing.
Are you trying to sabotage
this entire event?
I'm very sorry.
We gave you
an Arrowhead for free
for the day.
How hard would it have been
to do this, hmm?
"Hello. Hi, sweetie.
It's Jim.
"I'm calling you
from the new Arrowhead,
"which is why my voice
is crystal clear
"and my hand
won't ever get tired
because of the ergonomic
shape."
I'm really sorry.
Is there anything I can do,
maybe pretend to be Chuck?
You could have pretended
to be Chuck.
I begged you to pretend
to be Chuck,
but you chose to be yourself,
and you can no longer be Chuck!
Surrender the tripack.
You know what you have to do.
Point it towards
the store, idiot!
(Laughs)
You know what I mean...?
One of these buttons is--
Damn it.
Take over.
Oh, hey, hey, hey,
you guys, you must be lost.
Listen.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah, the fountain where
you can feed the pigeons
is out behind the bank.
Tell your great grandson
to bring his kid by.
Okay. So long.
Here we go.
Erin! Psst!
Come on!
The elderly suck the life
out of the young.
Get them out of here!
We are closed!
Come on.
Self-defense is not
some fun boxing match, okay?
This is about escaping
with your life.
So... Strike,
scream, and run.
All right?
Let's try it.
- [Screams]
- Ow.
That may have been my fault.
What the hell, Toby?
Okay, look,
in a real crisis situation,
you're not gonna
have time to think, okay?
So just remember,
I-a-a-t-g.
"It's all about the groin."
What if you're being
attacked by a...
Smallish man
who happens to not
have a groin?
I don't think
that's very common.
What if you're being attacked
by a 4'11" man
- who's penisless?
- Why are you fixated
on this hypothetical
transgendered attacker?
Why don't we start
with the basics?
Show us how to defend ourselves
against a baby,
and then like
a fifth-grade girl,
and then, you know,
if we have time,
on up to a scary man.
Well, the most common
scenario
is a larger man
attacking a smaller female.
So in that scenario,
what if the victim
sucker-punches the attacker
in the face?
What can the attacker then do
to better protect himself?
It's interesting
that you're drawn
to the point of view
of the attacker.
You would like
the turn of the table.
Okay, the latest
Chad Flenderman novel...
[Everyone groans]
Based from the point of view
of his nemesis,
Dr. Lucifer Wu.
Can I please leave?
I have a rape flute.
All right, well, let's try
one simple technique together.
Why doesn't everyone stand?
Okay, so...
You're being attacked.
You got your hands up.
Simple palm strike to the chin.
Up to the chin.
One, two.
All: One, two.
- One, two.
- [Softly] Take that, kid.
Cathy, I would like
to introduce you
to fatty gruesome.
He is a freelancer
for Wired Magazine.
Patty Grossman.
I'm a woman.
But you still work for
Wired, right?
Yes.
Good!
Okay. Flirt away.
Sabre.
It's time to come home.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I think...
It seemed like you were
a little nervous.
Yeah, no [Bleep], Sherlock!
Can somebody please tell me
something encouraging
about this presentation
before I go out there in front
of a million people and do it?
I know, I know, champ,
just calm down,
because listen...
When you're out in front
of all those people...
- Yeah, what?
- You just need to realize
so much rides on this.
- You have no idea.
- Dwight.
I'm trying to make him
feel important.
God. I wish Kelly
were here.
She always knew what to say.
Um...
[Imitating kelly] Oh, Ryan,
you're so smart.
You're smarter than
Mark Zuckerberg
and those Google guys
all combined.
- Hee hee hee.
- You're so ignorant,
you barely know
what you're talking about.
That's so ridiculous.
You really need
to read a couple of books.
What's a book?
[Giggles]
Oh, my God.
You're so embarrassing.
My mom would say
the best stuff, though.
[Ahem]
You can...
[Slightly effeminate]
You can do it, Ryan.
And you know
that I'm capable of this.
- You're the only one
who can do it, s-sweetie.
What did you think
of the presentation?
I thought it was great,
sweetie.
I would just fix
that one--
Oh, "fix" means you hate it!
I knew it!
- I need something to drink!
- Jim, get him a water.
No, not a water.
A sports drink.
I hate everything
in that fridge.
Not red-- Get me something
yellow or green
from a nearby store.
Not red!
Why are you just
standing there?
Go to a nearby store and get him
a yellow or green sports drink!
Now, if your attacker
is willing to defile a corpse,
you better stop playing dead
right away
and just make it known
that you're alive.
Forgive me for interrupting.
I believe my daughter
had an altercation
with somebody here,
some fancy gentleman
with a squeaky voice?
[Deep voice] I think you guys
might have the wrong office.
That's him...
The guy I hit.
- What?
- You've gotta be kidding me.
Poor Andy!
First you got beat up
by a gang,
- and now she kicks your ass?
- No, Kevin-- [Sighs]
What about the lady you hit
with a pine cone?
There.
That chubby one.
I just had a baby.
- Yesterday?
- Wow.
Apologize.
Sorry I kicked your ass
in front of your "thin"
girlfriend.
How 'bout we wait
till next year
after you have your kid?
You know what?
Tiffy's going to college.
[Deep voice]
Listen, I don't know
what you guys
are talking about,
but I guess I'll just
accept your apology
so we can get on with our day.
God bless.
Friend of mine uses your paper.
You do good work.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
So, Toby, I think we should
do a different
self-defense seminar--
"How to protect ourselves
against tiny little girls."
There's no shame in getting
beaten up by a girl.
My ex-wife
used to demolish me.
No, there is shame in it,
okay?
We have
to draw the line somewhere.
Oh, my God, I think I see
the imprint of a ring pop.
Oh...
[Kelly laughing]
Have you seen Erin?
I'm on break.
Oh, God!
No, hey, bloggers,
where do you think
you're going?
No, no, no, you gotta stay
for the big presentation.
We got
this young whiz kid-- Ryan.
He's like an even
more handsome Bill Gates.
When's the presentation?
It's moments away.
Just stay here!
Hey, Uncle Lucas,
it's your nephew, Ryan.
Honestly, I could use
a prescription
for ritalin right now.
Well, I know you did one
for Aunt Carol.
Oh, so it's different
because it's your wife?
Well, that doesn't make
any sense to me.
- How you doing?
- Don't talk to me right now.
I'm sorry,
I know you're my boss,
but seriously, you need to get
the hell out of my face.
What I don't understand
is why...[Voice fades]
Your little man
is unraveling.
Now, go and fix it.
Sorry about kicking you out.
It's just we don't want
our brand associated with death.
It's okay.
I'll go to the Costco
and search for handsome men.
You're not married yet?
[Laughs] Oh, I was.
My husband was my best friend.
He passed away.
My best friend
was my boss Andy.
We dated for a while,
but since then, he rejected me,
and we're not really friends.
Someone rejected you?
With that body
and those bazongas?
Forget him!
Yeah!
And you should
forget your husband.
Well...
How long has he
been in the bathroom?
- About ten minutes.
- Jeez!
What's he doing in there?
[Cell phone vibrates]
Oop, that's my phone.
Am I allowed to answer it,
- or are you gonna freak out?
- Are there bloggers around?
It's Ryan.
"I'm sorry. I lied.
"I'm not in the bathroom.
I can't do it.
I need to see my mom.
I'm going home."
What is the delay here?
Where's Ryan?
Why is he not here?
I had to send him home.
As brilliant and creative
as he is,
he is nothing...
- Compared to this guy!
- Uh...
- What?
- That's right.
Will you just give us a second?
You are gonna bloody ruin it.
You're gonna bloody ruin it
because you're a no-good
- half-ass cockeyed...
- Okay.
- That's--
- Jim--
- I'm not doing
the presentation.
Look at me.
Look at me!
Look... At... This... Face.
This is not the face
of a performer.
This is the face
of a scary apparition
you see before you die.
I'm telling you...
If you don't do this,
[whispers]
I don't stand a chance.
Please, Jim.
Okay. I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
O...kay!
Go get into Ryan's costume
and check out his notes.
- A costume?
- Of course there's a costume!
[Laughs]
Oh, this is gonna be great.
There's nothing like
some last-minute changes
to really energize
a presentation.
Huh?
Did you pass out in there?
What is taking so long?
I've been in here
for 20 seconds.
Hurry up.
Let me in.
I wanna watch you get dressed.
Did you find the eyeliner?
I'm not wearing eyeliner.
You are
wearing eyeliner, Jim.
[Coldplay's Clocks]
♪ ♪
Time. Space.
Gender.
[Dwight mouthing words]
There are no rules anymore.
All boundaries
are breaking down
in the wake
of the infinite future.
The only thing that--
The only thing that remain--
The only thing that remains
are the things
that have stood
the test of time--
Love, values,
and of course,
the pyramids--
The strongest shape
ever constructed,
a shape that fits
all other shapes inside of it.
[Softly]
No, that--
It's true.
This... is the future,
because...
this is the past.
I've been through a lot
of issues in my life.
I've seen drug addiction,
unemployment.
I've been in a relationship
that tore my heart apart
without ever being able
to accept
that love drove the pain.
[Scattered applause]
Yep.
When I was ten years old,
my parents took me
to Disney World.
I cried the whole time.
I was not able to comprehend
the beauty that was before me.
I just wanted...
To go home.
This is what the pyramid
will do for you.
It is the bridge to the world.
It has a USB port.
Wireless...
Will be available in 2013.
You can play anything
from Chuck to Cars 2.
With the pyramid,
you have the connection
to everything,
in time...
and space.
Crowd: Oh!
Psst!
Oh.
Ryan: Sabre.
It's time...
to come home.
All right.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Wow!
And good night.
[Applause continues]
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, this isn't over.
Let's stay focused, okay?
We made fun of Andy earlier
for getting beat up
by a little girl,
but... little things
can be dangerous.
Whether it's a Gremlin
or Chucky The Doll--
The key is to throw it
in something.
Like a fireplace
or a tub of electricity.
Okay, good point.
Um...
Good point?
What is a tub of electricity?
- I don't-- I don't--
- With all due respect,
we know
what we're defending against.
It's a 12-year-old
female bully.
- I was a 12-year-old bully.
- Great!
I think Kelly
should attack Toby.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not
a bad idea, actually,
because I have had a lot
of pent-up aggression.
- Thanks.
- Good. Go.
- I don't know if this
is gonna help--
Let's go, Kelly.
We should stay to maybe
some more traditional models--
You think you're so pretty!
Well, you're not gonna be
so pretty come prom time!
Okay, this is what's called
pre-violent posturing.
Take that!
Not so pre-violent anymore!
Okay, I'm at what's called
"the decision point."
- Hey, hey, hey,
Kelly, Kelly, Kelly--
[Smack] Ow!
God! My good eye!
Oh, boy!
Oh, no, I'm not
laughing at you.
I'm laughing at, um...
something that
Cece did on the playground
earlier-- Yesterday.
This morning.
You know why I got
hit by girls?
Because I stood up
for others...
Pam and Toby.
I stepped in, and I didn't care
that I was standing up
to girls.
You may wanna ask yourselves,
"where were you
when the girls came?"
Tough day. Yes.
But I feel good.
I put the office
in their place,
took a bunch of pain killers,
drank half a bottle of wine,
took my pants off.
I just feel good!
Okay, okay, I will be
the first to admit it.
We could have integrated more
Chuck into the presentation.
Dwight.
You're the Vice President.
Ha ha ha ha!
Yeah!
- [Squealing]
- Okay!
- Come on!
- Aah!
Right on!
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
Boom!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net