Where is my desk ?
That is weird.
This is not funny, this is totally
unprofessional.
Okay, well, you're the
one who lost the desk.
- I didn't lose my desk
- Okay, calm down.
Where was the last place
you saw it ?
Okay, who moved my desk ?
I think you should
retrace your steps.
Okay, I am going to tell Michael.
And this entire office
will be punished.
Colder.
Warmer.
Little warmer.
There you go, ooh, warmer.
Warmer.
Warmer, warmer !
Warmer, cold, cold ! Cold !
Back up !
Ooh, ooh, warmer.
Hot, red hot. Hot.
Very hot.
- Dwight Schrute.
- Hi Dwight !
What sort of discounts are we giving
on the 20 pound white bond ?
Jim, I've given you this
information like 20 times.
I know.
It's by the ream ?
- Uh, yeah.
- It is now 9.78.
- So it's a discount of 7%.
- Okay thank you,
I got to get back to work.
Wash your hands Kevin.
Saison 2 - Episode 6
The Fight
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation
Occeane & El Uploador
pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
Right. Oh, well,
let me just check the pricing list.
- Hold on one second.
- Sensei...
Hello, it's sempai.
Dwight.
You know what, let me give
you a call right back.
I'm going to find it and then
I'll call you back. Thanks.
Yes, I just had a ques...
Yes, sensei.
Arigato goazai mashta. Hai.
- Was that you mom ?
- No. That was my sensei.
- Thought it was your mom.
- I am now sempai,
which is assistant sensei.
Assistant to the sensei,
that's pretty cool.
- Assistant sensei.
- Okay.
I am a practitioner of Goju-Ryu
ka-ra-te, here in Scranton.
- Hai !
- 2 !
- Dwight, stamp and kick back. 3.
My sensei, Ira, recently
promoted me to purple belt.
And gave me duties of a sempai.
Not that a lot of people here in
America know what a sempai is.
But it's equally as
respected as a sensei.
I don't want to stay until
7:00 again this year.
I don't really have any
control over that, Stanley.
Michael tends to procrastinate...
a bit whenever he has to do work.
Time cards.
He has to sign these every Friday.
Purchase orders have to be approved
at the end of every month.
And expense reports.
All he has to do is initial these,
at the end of every quarter.
But once a year, it all falls on
the same Friday. And that's today.
I call it the perfect storm.
"I don't want to work,"
"I just want to bang
on this mug all day."
Did you ask me here
for any specific reason?
Ah, yes, I did.
Here's the bizzle.
I have a very top secret
mission for you.
I want you to update all the
emergency contact information.
- Why is that secret ?
- Hello. Oh, God
Busy work.
Ah, get away, get away. Cretin.
I put stickers so you know
where to sign.
Yes, thanks, I know where to sign.
It's  just that last year, you...
Last year, they were out of
order, weren't they, Pam.
Well, the last pickup for
overnight deliveries is at 7:00.
So you need to have them
signed by then. Or much earlier.
Shalax, Pam.
Stop Pam-MSing.
That's pretty good.
Actually, I'm sending Ryan
on a top secret mission.
Tell her what it is.
Updating emergency contacts ?
Well, is that really a priority ?
Is it a priority ?
Oh, I don't know.
What if there's a tornado, Pam ?
People's legs are crushed
under rubble.
Please, would you be so kind as to
call my wife ? No I can't.
Because we don't have any
emergency contact information.
Because Pam said
it wasn't a priority.
Think. Think with your head Pam.
Okay, well, she walks out.
That's the problem with being a
boss, is that when you are tough,
they resent you, and when you
are cool, they walk all over you.
- Catch-22.
- Catch-22,  yes.
Why don't you give me your contact
information to start with ?
Okay? What's your cell ?
- Larissa Halpert.
- What's her address ?
- 117 Vonburgen Street.
- Hello.
Hey Ryan.
This is Michael Jackson,
calling from Wonderland.
You mean Neverland ?
This is Tito.
What ?
Calling from...
Your major and minor
lines cross at a ridge.
That sucks.
You're making this up as
you go along, aren't you ?
- I am just following the web site.
- Well, at least I don't have cavities.
Yes, you have very nice teeth.
T hanks
Who's your emergency contact ?
Stacey.
Pick up.
Hello ?
This is Mike Tyson.
Hey, Dwight.
As sempai, do you ever think
there's gonna be a day,
where humans and robots can
peacefully coexist ?
Impossible.
The way they're programmed...
- You're mocking me.
- No, I'm not.
Well, let me offer you
a little piece of advice.
I am not afraid, to make
an example out of you.
That's not advice.
What advice sounds like is this.
Don't ever bring your
purple belt to work,
because someone might...
steal it.
- Okay, give that back to me.
- Okay, say please.
- No, that is not a toy.
- Please.
- Please ?
- Good.
And it absolutely is a toy.
Arigato.
Arigato. This is not a toy.
This is a message,
for the entire office.
So that everyone could see that I am
capable of physically dominating them.
And this is more of
a ying yang thing.
The Michael is all cursive,
Scott all caps.
Left  brain, right brain.
Or duality of man.
Could you practice on the forms ?
No women or children,
unless provoked.
Okay, Roy.
- Warehouse guy. Doesn't count.
- Okay
Michael. Could you beat up Michael ?
Yeah, I don't think
that would happen.
- Cause we're friends.
- Because I would kick his ass.
Well, Dwight's a purple belt. So...
So ? I've beat up black belts.
Yeah.
How'd you know they were
black belts ?
They told me, after.
See, I used to run with a very
tough crowd, street fighter types.
Real, real bad people.
I'm just lucky I got out.
Is your wife still your contact ?
Ex-wife, yeah.
Her last name is Becker now.
Okay.
You don't need to write ex.
And after that, nobody ever messed
with the damn rascals ever again.
Sounds tough.
When you're a jet, your're a jet
all the way, right ?
You're a jet ?
Have you signed
the expense reports yet?
Yes, in theory I have.
I just need to cross some
Ts and dot some Is.
Alright.
I am going to be in my office
if anybody needs me.
Oh Michael !
Sleeper hold. Bedtime for vato.
- Stop it.
- You are, the weakest link !
I'm friends with everybody
in this office.
We're all best friends
I love everybody here.
But sometimes your best friends,
start coming in to work late and,
start having dentist appointments
that aren't dentist appointments.
And that is when it's nice
to let them know
that you could beat them up.
- Just hit me. You'll see.
- I can't,
- cause I just got a manicure. So...
- Oh, queer !
Eye, Queer Eye. That's a good show.
Important show.
Go ahead, do it.
- Just have Dwight punch you.
- Oh, yeah
Well, that would be
kind of worthless,
because I know a ton of 14 years
old girls who could kick his ass.
- You know a ton of 14-year-old girls ?
- What belt are they ?
Look, Dwight is a wuss.
- When we rented Armageddon...
- No...
he cried at the end of it.
He did.
Michael, I told you...
That was because it was
New Year's Eve,
and it started to snow
at exactly midnight.
"Oh, Bruce Willis, they're going to
leave him on the asteroid."
- Okay I'll punch you.
- Okay, here we go.
Alright, come on.
Did I want to harm Michael, the one
man I've been hired to protect ?
- No, I did not.
- Are you okay ?
- Yes.
- Are you sure you're all right ?
Yeah. Yeah. Thank you.
I come from a long line of fighters.
My maternal grandfather, was
the toughest guy I ever knew.
World War II veteran.
Killed 20 men,
then spent the rest of the
war in an allied prison camp.
My father battled blood
pressure and obesity all his life.
Different kind of fight.
Okay, he has to be stopped.
Please, please, please,
please, just ask Michael.
- I don't know.
- Okay
Okay. I'll buy you a bag of chips.
Why are you twisting around?
- French onion ?
- Obviously.
Kevin, why are you
spinning around ?
- Okay.
- Yes.
Take this pen, okay.
And stab me with it.
- Go away.
- I just have a quick question.
I haven't signed them, okay ?
No, it's not that.
I was just wondering, since I'm
probably going to have to stay late
could you ask Dwight to stay late too,
so he can walk me to my car ?
Nice.
Come in.
Pam, I hate to break this to you,
but Dwight can't stop you
from being mugged.
He's just not tough enough.
He's a purple belt.
That's really high.
I could beat up Dwight.
That's ridiculous.
I can murder him.
- It's just that out there, you...
- Oh, is that what they're saying?
- Yeah, kind of.
- Okay.
Alright.
Where's Dwight ?
- Kitchen.
- Okay.
Try it again. Here we go.
Good.
- It way actually pretty good, right ?
- Excellent.
Now  watch.
Let me take you from behind.
Watch out Kelly,
might sucker punch you.
- I didn't sucker punch you Michael.
- No, really ?
In case you didn't remember,
I was defending my honor.
- Like samouraï.
- Really, oh, is that it ?
Well, the offer, Dwight,
was for one punch,
which I absorbed.
I had no idea that there'd be a
second punch. So, catch-22.
Okay, fine, tit for tit.
Give it your best shot,
two punches, go.
Look, if we were in a bar,
right now, there would be
two punches.
Me punching you and
you hitting the floor.
No, I'd block your first punch,
rending ineffective.
- Really
- Yeah
You know what, you're just lucky
that we're at work right now.
- What about, Dwight's dojo ?
- No, they just have classes.
It's free during the day,
it's fine.
- Look !
- I've got the key.
- Hey, Michael !
- Hey, Toby.
Any word on those...
You know what ? I have an idea,
why don't you just leave right now?
Why don't you walk away
from the room, okay ?
Fine.
We'll go at lunch.
Pam, make an announcement.
Figure out carpools.
Well, we're all getting
excited to see this fight
The Albany branch is working right
through lunch to prevent downsizing.
But Michael, he decided to
extend our lunch by an hour...
so that we could all go down to
the dojo and watch him fight Dwight.
Fight, Fight, fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, I'm coming, fight.
Sorry.
I recognize that. That is Japanese
for California roll.
No it's not.
I think it is, a guy told me
about that.
Actually, it's a symbol
for eternal discipline.
- Wow, that is really interesting.
- What ?
Your love line... I'm just kidding,
I can't see anything.
Look closer.
- Oh-kay.
- One point for me.
- Tied up.
- Oh you're dead
What ? What are you going to do?
Bring it Beesly. Bring it.
Ooh, yeah. Good move.
Ooh, not such an ultimate
fighter now, huh ?
Hey, put me down.
Put me down !
Oh my God. Hey, put me down.
Hey.
Okay, gentlemen, listen up.
After a clean strike to the chest,
stomach, or kidneys, I will
separate you and award a point.
First person to three wins, alright?
- Yes, sensei !
- Lot of rules. Lot of rules.
On the street, we didn't
have any rules. Maybe one,
no kicks to the groin,
home for dinner.
Hajime!
-  What the hell was that ?
- Dwight.
- Yes.
- No way.
- One point.
- Okay.
- Eat it !
- Alright
- That's the way you want to do it ?
- Two more.
You want to play dirty, huh?
Okay, game on, man.
- Sweep the leg.
- I'm coming at you, man.
Ha ! Okay, purple belt.
- Okay, I got it.
- No.
- I got his pants.
- That was my pants.
No points for pants.
Dwight, you have...
No, look. No, you have something...
You have something...
God, you look like such an idiot.
Clean technique gentlemen.
Come on. Do that again.
Do that again. I dare you.
Okay, break. Break. No holding.
Oh, you can't see ?
You can't see ?
One point. Two points. Three points.
- I said break.
- How many points now ?
I win, I win.
No, you didn't.
Eight points, nine points.
Stop it. No.
Come on, Michael!
- Open your mouth.
- No, Michael !
You talkin' to me ?
Raging Bull, Pacino.
Oh, I want that footage.
I want it. I need it.
Oh, I have to get back to work.
I have lots of work.
Check this out, come here.
There he is, Mr.Temp.
Having lunch by the car.
Let us play with him.
See what we can learn.
Oh, we're playing phone tag.
Seven new messages.
First new message.
Hi, Ryan. This is Saddam Hussein.
- Next message.
- Hey Ryan, this is your girlfriend.
And I'm mad.
My emergency contact
is Todd Packer.
Todd F. Packer
- You know what the F stands for ?
- Fudge ?
Yeah.
Oh, come in.
Oh, hey, Karate Kid.
The Hillary Swank version.
Hi, how are you ?
I need to change my emergency
contact information
from Michael Scott.
- Okay, to what ?
- Just put...
The hospital.
Contact number :
Just put 911.
He is such a sore loser.
You heard obviously,
that I mopped the floor
with him this afternoon.
You know what, do yourself a favor.
Just leave me as his contact.
And I will call the hospital.
Cut out the middleman.
- Later Jim.
- Later Kev.
- Have a good weekend.
- Yeah, you too.
Yeah.
I have the emergency contacts.
Just lay 'em on the chair.
I'll take it from here.
So what you up to this weekend ?
Hanging out with some
friends probably.
Well, if you do anything crazy,
give me a shout.
Yeah. Alright, I will,
see you Monday.
Alright. Bye.
- Dwight ?
- Michael, did you finish yet ?
This close. Dwight, may I speak
with you for a minute.
I'm busy.
Well, busier.
But I'm making the time.
Michael, can't your conversation
wait till Monday ?
- We want to go home.
- Well,
You  don't even have anybody
to go home to, Toby. So...
The shipping place closes
in a half hour.
I know.
But I've been carrying the
load on my back all day.
And if everyone would
just chip in a little bit,
might help me out.
What do you say ?
Let's gang bang this thing
and go home.
Good.
- This is illegal.
- I don't care.
I have been testing you
the entire day.
Did you know that ?
Of course.
And I'm happy to say that you passed.
So, effective immediately,
I am promoting you,
from assistant
to the regional manager
to assistant regional manager.
Michael...
I don't know.
I, I know. I know. I know.
I know. I wouldn't be offering it if
I didn't think you could handle it.
- I can handle it, I can.
- I know. Okay.
So I guess this'll just by my office.
No. No. Title change only.
- I'll have Pam send out a memo.
- No, nope.
Three month probationary period.
Let's just not tell anybody
about this right now.
- Just a formality ?
- Absolutely.
But not really.
Michael.
I have so much, to learn, from you.
Yes you do.
Thank you.
Sensei.
And, Ditto.
I told Dwight that there
is honor in losing.
Which as we all know is
completely ridiculous.
But, there is, however, honor in
making a loser feel better.
Which is what I just did
for Dwight.
Would I rather be feared or loved ?
Easy. Both. I want people to be
afraid of how much they love me.
And I think I proved
that today at the dojo.
- Typewriter torture.
- Sensei help !
- No.
- Typewriter !
www.tvsubtitles.net