Can you confirm that
the straps are tight?
Yes.
- But this one's a little...
- And now the chains!
A lot of people think that
magic camp is just for kids.
And that's why so many other people
in my class were kids.
Self-fulfilling prophecy
It's, um, really for anybody
With a dream,
and a belief in magic.
And a little extra time
after school.
Magic, magic, magic, magic...
And now,
Michael the Magic
will attempt to escape
from extreme bondage.
Can he do it?
I don't see how he can.
I know how
He'd dislocate his shoulder
and slip his arm out.
No, no.
Everyone now count down with me.
Three! Sorry
Sorry, quickly
So, is it true that
if you can't get out,
You don't want
anyone to help you?
I will get out.
Oh, yes, I will.
So we shoulnd't help you
no matter how much
you might beg and plead.
No, all right,
just- this is getting hot.
So let's just do this,
okay, ready?
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
Is everything okay, Michael?
Yes.
I cannot tell you
how I plan to escape.
Other than by using magic.
That's the magician's code
Help
Separately, on an unrelated note,
If you happen to find
a small brass key...
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL
theOffice.tistory.com
The Office 3x18 "Cocktails"
Original Air Date: Feb 22, 2007 (NBC)
All right, ready?
Come on, guys,
Early worm gets the worm.
Another worm?
Like, are they friends?
It's early bird gets the worm.
Pam, would you smell my breath?
Let me smell
Good, not great.
Michael, you go to parties all the time.
Why is tonight so special?
Well, tonight is so special
because my boss's boss's boss,
the CFO,
not his initials, common mistake,
is having a little shindig
for all the managers in the company,
and Jan and I are going as a couple.
For the first time.
So, it's kind of
our coming out party.
Really.
And, that is why
tonight is so special.
Jimbo, last chance carpool.
Oh, no thanks, I think
Karen and I'll take my car.
Sure? Might be a good idea.
If we all went together
we could save some gas.
- Have fun. Long trip!
- Thanks
Play some games?
Um- no, we're good.
I spy. Yeah
Why don't I wanna go?
Didn't expect to need a reason,
So, let me think here.
I don't know any of these people.
It's an obligation.
I don't like talking paper
in my free time.
Or in my work time.
And... did I use the word "pointless"?
Thanks for inviting me along.
Oh, sure.
Really didn't give it any thought.
Wait, should you be going?
Hey-wo, you!
- Michael?
- Hey, buttercup
I am on my way,
should be there in about 15-
Let's just blow this party off.
- That's what she said.
- Yeah
Am I on speaker phone?
Ah, yes you are.
- Is anybody else...
- Hello, Jan!
Hi, Dwight.
Okay, Michael,
take me off speakerphone.
No le problem.
Okay, let's just go to a motel...
Okay!
And, like, rip into each other
like we did on
that black sand beach in Jamaica
Hey, Jan?
Jan, this party is
actually a very big step for us.
So, I...
Still on speaker?
I don't know
Are cameras there?
Maybe
- All right, see you soon.
- Okay.
- Talk to you later, Jan!
- All right, bye.
Hey, Michael left early,
So, a bunch of us are gonna go to
Poor Richard's for happy hour.
You should come.
I can't.
My brother just unloaded the Jet Skis
And he kinda took a bath, so...
We're gonna go get hammered.
Okay, well, we're going to a bar.
Hey,
You have to come to stuff with me.
I'm serious.
If you're gonna be my boyfriend,
You have to do boyfriend things.
Okay
I have decided that
I'm going to be more honest.
I'm just start telling people
what I want directly.
So, look out world,
'cause old Pamie is
gtting what she wants.
And, don't call me Pamie.
Beauty.
Thank you, sir.
Ensalada. Thank you
You're dressed
exactly like the servants.
Shut up.
Okay, change shirts with me.
Wait!
I don't think your's will fit me.
I don't care.
Here.
Don't let my jacket...
Don't give me that.
That would have been
really embarrassing.
Yes.
Crisis averted.
Oh, that duck is so cute.
Hey, Pam
Hey guys
Oscar, Angela
Uh, hi!
Actually, it's polite to arrive early.
And, smart.
Only really good friends
show up early.
Ergo de facto,
go to a party early
become a really good friend.
Oh, uh- potato salad.
That's from both of us.
No, it's not.
- It's my bowl
- Wonderful
Let's- uh, see
where we can put this.
Okay.
Oh, you know what,
you probably wanna leave the cover on
Until the guests get here.
It's been sitting in my car all day.
Sun beating down on the mayonnaise...
Just...
you never know.
Kevin, you and Stacey set a date yet?
Yeah.
Oh my God, when is it?
It's complicated.
I would appreciate some space on this.
Hey
You made it.
Yeah, you said
it was important, so...
It is.
How's going?
- What's up Pam?
- Hey, Kenny
Sorry about the Jet Skis.
You guys all want around? On me?
Yeah!
Let's get you a drink.
Thanks, man. I'm thirsty.
No, thank you, Roy, I...
You should get around, Ryan.
Oh, you know that line
on the top of the shrimp?
That's feces.
Whatcha looking for?
Did you bring dip?
I'm sure that it's catered.
I need you to sign these, Michael.
That's a waiver of some of your rights.
You should read it carefully.
It releases the company in the event
that our relationship in your opinion,
or, in reality, interferes with work.
You get a copy, I get a copy,
And a third copy goes to HR.
Awesome.
I'm gonna frame mine.
I could frame yours too.
You realize this is-
this is a legal document
That says
you can't sue the company?
Over our love.
I've... never told you
that I love you.
You don't have to, Jan.
This contract says it all.
I am taking a calculated risk.
What's the upside?
I overcome my nausea,
fall deeply in love,
babies, normalcy,
no more self-loathing.
Downside,
I, uh- date Michael Scott publicly.
And collapse into myself
like a dying star.
What's this over the I?
It's a heart.
Why is this so hard?
That's what she said.
Oh, my God. What am I saying?
I love this woman!
Oh, no,
Michael, Please
Do you ever watch Battlestar Galactica?
No. No?
Then, you're an idiot.
Hello, Michael.
Rachel, boy, do you clean up good.
Place looks great with all the lights on.
And everything actually
looks bigger with people in it.
Weird. So...
Jan, glad you could make it.
Oh, of course, of course, David.
Do you remember, uh- Michael Scott
- Of course I do.
- From Scranton branch?
How are you Michael?
Jan and I are lovers.
That feels so good
to finally say that out loud.
David, can I, um-
speak to you privately?
For just a moment, please?
Excuse me Okay
Oh.
No, actually one of these is
supposed to be a light.
Oh, sorry.
So, the merger goes smoothly, or...
It did.
¡°Like butter.¡±
Mike Myers, SNL
You should ask Karen,
she was one of them.
I'm the only one left.
Everybody else
was either fired or quit.
And, there's one
in anger management.
Yeah, but you're great now, right?
We're all great.
Aren't we great?
We're good.
Michael, stop-
please stop that, okay?
Uh, can I get anyone anything?
I could go for
an appe-tease-er, yep.
- Martini, please.
- Bagel bites or something.
- Rachel, your house is beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
What's the square footage?
Uh, about 5,000
Does that include the garage?
Dwight, wow-
that's not appropriate.
- I don't know.
- It's a common question.
David, how much
did this house cost?
These old colonials are great...
when they're sound.
I'd love to, uh-
take a look around.
I'll show you around, sure.
Cool, let's start with the banisters.
Hey.
Do you see that guy behind you
in the blue blazer against the wall?
Yup
That's Drake.
And, just so you know,
I don't wanna be weird or anything
But, um- we used to date.
Oh.
Okay, cool.
Thanks for telling me that.
And, it didn't end well.
Gotcha.
All right.
This was a gift...
From Lee Iacocca.
20-year-old, single malt scotch.
Here is to Mr. Iacocca and his failed experiment,
The DeLorean.
Are you okay?
Yeah!
Do you have any ice?
Sure
How about some Splenda?
1, 2, 3, up Jenkins!s!
Down Jenkins!
Uh, I think I heard
the quarter over here.
- Where?
- On this side.
No, it is definitely
under one of these hands.
I kinda heard it on Roy's side too.
No, it is here.
Not here.
Good thing
you didn't listen to me.
Yeah, close one.
Not here.
Okay, it's either here or here.
Nice Job!
I can read you like a book.
Oh, yeah?
You can't keep anything form me.
Bottom's up!
Hey Creed. Hey
- What's up Creed?
- What are you guys up to?
Ah, hello.
You're the man, buddy.
I run a small fake ID
company from my car
With a laminating machine
that I swiped.
From the sheriff's station.
These studs are way too far apart.
What's in here?
Ah, it's a guest room.
Just the one window?
Oh, I must get that.
You'll have to excuse me.
Are those real pearls?
Uh, yes.
They're...
Good.
Well, it was nice meeting you guys.
Take care.
Well, if you're wondering
why his wife was staring daggers at me,
It's because I kinda
saw him for a little bit
When they were separated.
Didn't notice.
Really? I thought
it was so obvious.
I'm glad it didn't
make you uncomfortable.
No, it was before I knew you,
So, it's fine.
This one really smells like vanilla.
Check that out.
That's nice.
You and the Mrs. Should join us
at Sandals Jamaica next Christmas.
I... Michael, I think David provably wants
to spend Christmas here with his family.
Oh, yeah.
They don't allow kids at Sandals.
- They are- are persona non grata.
- Please stop.
They're...uh
But it's fun.
It is an awesome place.
You would not believe
how low this girl can limbo.
- It's crazy
- David, I'm sorry
You're just gonna
have to excuse us
for just a couple
minutes sorry.
Okay, Okay.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
What is it?
Sorry.
What- what's the matter?
- What's...
- Come here.
Just- just- just- just-
What are you doing?
Don't you know what I'm doing?
Yes, but you could tell me.
What are- what is that?
Why are you-
why are we going in the bathroom?
I thought this is
where you liked your privacy.
Shut up.
What has gotten into you?
No no no no! what?
Come on,
let's go back to the party.
Come on, wait,
let me just do my dress.
Don't take that- no!
Stop it! Stop it!
Jan, no, no, no! Michael!
No means please don't.
Slam me up against the wall,
right here.
I'm not gonna slam you
up against anything.
Oh, please,
- You're acting inappropriate.
- I want you so-
- I'm acting inappropriate?
- Jan- yeah.
Forget it, get out my way
- Here
- Hey
Where have you been all night?
I was looking forward
to hanging out with you.
I was...
Hey, don't you have a daughter?
Yes
Oh, good, you're up.
Hey, who makes this chair?
I don't know.
It was here when I was born.
I want one.
Really good,
solid construction.
It's comfortable.
What is this? Oak?
I don't know.
What do you know?
God, I hate these parties.
You wanna sneak out back
and shoot some hoops?
Meet me outside in two minutes.
You stay here and have fun,
'cause I'm gonna go out back,
And shoot hoops with David Wallace.
Okay.
Oh, um- don't mention that
you and I are dating.
'cause I think he might
still have feelings for me.
Wallace?
What the hell!
Have you dated
like every guy here?
Wow.
Okay.
You got me.
I so got you.
So, none of them.
Of course not.
I mean, you're kind of
like, my first.
Really?
- Oh, my God, it's so easy
- Okay.
It's not even fun.
Hey, Jan.
Not too good.
Did you get a chance to try
Michael's homemade potato salad?
Rachel thinks that
I brought homemade potato salad.
And I just picked it up
at the supermarket.
It's funny,
I wish I could make
potato salad that good.
It's just potatoes
and mayonnaise.
There's something wrong with Jan.
What's, uh-
what's with Jan and Michael?
I don't know.
Where to begin?
My ball.
The chimney is in decent shape.
Not great,
I found some termite damage
in a crawlspace
and some structural flaws
in the foundation
so all in all...
it was a pretty fun
cocktail party.
What?
I want us to make it.
I want a fresh start.
That's awesome.
That's what I want.
Okay, but
In order for us to make it,
There can't be
any secrets between us.
There- I didn't do anything.
Ask anybody,
I totally could've,
and I didn't at all.
Just listen.
Remember that casino night
about a month before
we were supposed to get married?
I kissed Jim.
What?
He told me how he felt,
and I guess I had feelings too,
and we kissed.
Jim came on to you?
Just listen.
No, I'm listening!
That's the problem I'm listening!
Don't yell.
Don't yell?
This is over.
Yeah, you're right,
this is so over.
You kidding me, Pam!
Come on!
God!
Damn Jet Skis!
Our first fight.
If this is about
what happened in the bathroom,
There was no place to cuddle.
I feel sick.
You didn't have
any of the potato salad, did you?
You know, we were good
when we were just running around.
You know, in secret.
It was wrong,
And it was exciting.
And maybe it was
a mistake to take it public.
Well, if that's the way you feel,
My lady, then you have hurt me greatly.
- Michael
- Greatly
Please don't cry.
I'm not going to cry.
I feel like it,
But I am not going to.
Why don't you just take
your stupid love contract
- And tear it up into a million pieces?
- It was never a love contract, Michael.
And, besides, I've already
given a copy to David.
And it would be just as embarrassing
- To get it back from him as it was handing it to him.
- I want the house, Jan!
I want the picket fence.
I want the ketchup fights,
And the tickling,
And the giggling.
I didn't mean it, okay?
- I was...
- Whatever.
I was tired, I am tired
And I didn't eat enough.
- You didn't mean it.
- And that's all.
- That's was it.
- That's it, you didn't mean it.
- No, I didn't.
- So...
That's all, I'm just saving
I didn't mean it.
I love you, Jan.
Okay.
Don't break up, you guys.
You're great together.
Are they gonna call the cops?
No, I paid them off.
Jet Ski money?
All of it.
I'm gonna kill Jim Halpert.
www.tvsubtitles.net