I'm not picking on you at all.
You're English, correct?
Yeah, big time, yeah.
I'm working
on an English character.
Would you mind gi...
it's called Reginald Pooftah.
David Brent, my liege.
How are you?
- Michael Scott.
- Oh, there you go.
I do characters as well.
I got a Chinese fella.
He's called ho me.
That's what it sounds like.
- Herrow! Herrow!
- I do ping.
Herrow. I ping.
You can't do that
these days. You can't.
No, no, no. And people
don't understand
that it has nothing to do
with making fun
of a different nationality.
No, no, no.
No, comedy is a place
where the mind goes
to tickle itself.
That's what she said.
That's good.
Pleasure to meet you.
- Where are you working?
- Dunder Mifflin.
- Any jobs now?
- No, not right now.
- Just let me know.
- All right.
All right.
See ya around.
Bye-bye.
What a nice guy.
Syn by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Your first student is here,
mister Bernard.
That's actually
"master of ceremonies" Bernard.
Last year, I went to a seminar
called "the ten secrets
of real estate."
Turns out it was just a ploy
to sell me
time-shares in Idaho.
Cut to, you know, I'm spending
a weekend in Boise,
terrible time, super lonely.
But I get to thinking
maybe I should put on
my own seminar
to lure clients.
Oh, it's...
Hello, I am here
for the small business seminar.
Michael?
Neii'm Greek!
My name is Mikanos.
Wait, Michael?
Michael?
Okay.
I am the plant.
Every great seminar has one.
My job is to make
the speaker look good,
and I do this
through the techniques
of leading questions
and laughing at all jokes.
And the character, Mikanos,
is just a little added Flava.
Mikanos is loosely based on
another character I do, Spiros,
who is more about the ladies.
Thank you so much, tuna Turner.
You are simply the best.
Listen, this isn't
a favor, all right?
This is a good idea.
We all win.
Go higher.
I get super flexible
when I'm nervous.
Wow.
Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
Hey, Andy, I'm really,
really sorry to do this to you,
but I have a meeting today
that I totally forgot,
so I can't be
a part of this seminar.
No. What?
You can't do that.
You are a critical part
of this seminar.
You're the charming warm-up guy.
- I know.
- If the seminar was a meal,
you'd be the amuse-bouche.
You, like, signal
the flavors of the whole night.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do it
you can't. You can't.
I can't have this go badly.
I'm a terrible salesman,
and I haven't been
making very many sales lately,
or ever.
This is my only idea
on how to turn things around.
If it goes badly,
I might lose my job,
which would suck,
because this is
the only job
I've ever been good at.
Will you let me know
when this
whole seminar thing's over?
What's going on?
Do you know that guy?
I just have a meeting,
uh, outside the office.
Hey.
How are the marks?
What are some
of your small business ideas?
I was thinking we could buy up
a bunch
of abandoned mineshafts.
That's great.
There's a big,
big future in that.
A lot of mines in Scranton.
Um, what about you?
- Uh, credit cards.
- Uh-huh.
My company will act
as an intermedium
for, like, 0.2 cents
off every transaction.
Wow!
Or something with cell phones,
like, every time
you make a phone call,
I'd make 0.2 cents.
Or anything... like,
any online shopping,
I get .2 cents basically.
Right.
Okay? Okay.
Great.
You promised us whales.
These are worms.
They're not worms,
Dwight, okay?
They're just people
with tiny businesses.
They're baby whales,
which is even cuter.
I'm out.
Stanley, you're
supposed to close.
I'm out, too.
What?
I already lost Jim.
Salesmen are supposed
to help each other out.
We're supposed to be a team.
We're no more a team
than the people staying
in the same hotel are a team.
You know
what might be kind of fun?
I was thinking, you know
Andy's having a seminar today?
What if we went in
as a Greek couple?
Mikanos and...
Oh, I don't know, Michael.
I'm not feeling up to that.
Okay.
Holly broke up
with a.J. Last week,
which is the greatest thing
that has ever happened...
To me.
To Holly, it's been
the worst week of her life,
and I know for a fact
that there was a week
for her in High School
when she got mono
and her first period ever.
Too much information?
That's what I thought.
But you know what?
Here I am using it.
If-a you change-a you mind,
why don't you talk to mikanos?
Is mikanos Greek?
He sounds Italian.
Ugh. You're the fifth person
to tell me that today.
Maybe mikanos ran away
to join the Italian circus.
Okay, yeah,
like a character history.
Good.
Tom Hanks does that.
Down...There.
Is "JLP" a word?
- "Jelp"? J-e-l-p?
- No, j-l-p.
Like, "I JLP...
I JLP you!"
I don't think that's a word.
I'm playing scrabble with Gabe,
and I've never won a game.
The winner gets to pick
the movie we watch.
I have won no games.
So far I've seen
the shining,
Rosemary's baby,
the ring.
Not really my thing.
Although, I...
I do like the early parts
of the movies
where they have
a perfect family and everything.
You want some help?
Really?
Yes.
- K-a. "Ka"?
What does "ka" mean?
It means you're playing someone
who's going to destroy you.
Why did you play "moo"?
Because I'm playing to win.
I'm playing "moo,"
I'm playing "milk,
whatever it takes.
Okay, but look,
you could have hit "mood."
Would have played a...
Uh!
A triple word.
Like the cow mood yesterday.
God.
Or moon.
The cow jumped over the moon.
No, it doesn't have to
just be cow stuff, right?
Kevin, Jim dropped
out of my seminar,
and I'm just...
I was wondering
if you could replace him
as my charming warm-up guy.
Andy, I'm no Jim.
The only way that I'm Jim
is in the movie version
when Jim sees
what his future would be like
if he never met Pam.
Hey, that's crazy talk.
I think you're great.
Then I won't let you down.
- Cake.
- In you go.
Hi, Ryan, you went
to business school, right?
- Yeah.
- I need someone
to talk to this seminar
about business.
- And?
- Can you do it?
Okay. I don't... I don't
like committing to things
just like that.
So no?
No, I don't like committing
to not doing things, either.
That's just
as big a commitment.
Oh, baby.
What do I put
you down for, bro hombre?
Yes.
- All right!
- Yes, I'll do it.
Okay, thank you so much.
It's gonna be awesome.
- And if I flake, I flake.
- What?
Kevin, you open it up.
Yep.
Ryan, you come in
with your small biz
expertise, right?
And then creed,
guest speaker extraordinaire.
And then I come in and just
close all the sales and stuff.
Um, okay, here we go.
One, two, three!
- Go.
- Creed!
Welcome everybody. Awesome to see
you guys. My name's Andy Bernard,
but you can call me
the nard dog.
Hi, nard dog.
I'm Lu Peachem.
Let's get things started,
shall we?
You guys ready to hear
from the dunder Mifflin
business experts?
Good. Well, as you can see
on your program,
first up is a speech called,
"don't just dream it,
do it."
Yes! Please give
a big hand to Mr. Kevin Malone.
All aboard!
Three, four, five.
Yes!
There are some people
who have charm
and some people who don't.
Guess which type I am.
Charm type.
Dream...Big.
Right?
So what I want you to do
is dream the biggest
that you c...An.
And then double it!
Are you okay?
No. Yes!
- Here.
- N...
I'm fine.
Okay, from here now.
The first lesson
that I'm gonna teach you,
right, is
about finding success.
And the key to finding success
is to picture a winner.
Okay, so then, what
are you picturing right now,
right this second?
'Cause the universe
is yours, people.
Get out of the way.
I'm really excited
to introduce you guys
to Ryan Howard.
He has achieved
a great deal in the last...
but perhaps
no achievement is greater
than his on-again,
off-again girlfriend.
What are you...
who am I?
I'm Kelly Kapoor,
the business bitch.
It is important
to brand yourself,
so I have a couple
of things in the works.
The business bitch,
the diet bitch,
the shopping bitch,
the etiquette bitch.
I could sit here,
and I could tell you
the ten secrets of business,
and you would have
a great time,
and you would learn a lot.
But who better to tell you
than the Yale university
adjunct Professor in management,
Professor Scott Powell,
who I have on my BlackBerry.
It's ringing.
Hey, Kelly Kapoor.
What a delicious surprise.
Professor Powell,
you are on speakerphone.
Uh, why?
Do you think you could tell us
the ten secrets of business?
Um, there aren't
really ten secrets.
Come on, Scott, please.
It's me.
Um, all right.
Well, um,
I guess know your market
would be key.
Practice fiscal discipline.
- Mm-hmm.
That brilliant little bitch.
A little treat
for our old friend, Gabe.
Put that "q" right there.
Wait. Why?
Put the "q" there, sweetie.
- I think there's better...
- Put the "q" there!
Sorry I yelled.
You could have just
told us what you were thinking.
There's no theater in that.
There's no yelling
in that, either.
Well...
What do you do
in your free time?
Practice Olympics.
Mmm.
Do you like movies?
I like
the musical grease,
or as we call it "home."
We have to try
this out on somebody.
Hello.
Look, you want
to order something?
She will have a greekaccino.
I don't know what that is.
It...
It's a very strong coffee
with milk from a goat.
I can't believe-ee.
It's a miracle.
She can talk!
No more brain damage.
No more brain damage!
I don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our special guest speaker
will provoke you.
He will inspire you.
He is...
Creed Bratton.
Two eyes, two ears,
a chin, a mouth,
ten fingers, two nipples.
A butt, two kneecaps, a penis.
I have just described to you
the loch ness monster.
And the reward for its capture?
All the riches in Scotland.
So I have one question:
Why are you here?
Okay!
All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
it is now time
for the rarest of things,
an actual free lunch.
There's sandwiches in the back.
Certainly help yourselves.
We'll meet back up in an hour.
I picked out our movie.
It's called suspiria.
It pushes all the boundaries.
All your preconceived notions
about what horror can be
come crashing down.
- When I win...
- Ooh.
- We're gonna watch wall-e,
where all the boundaries
of color are pushed.
It is hard to explain
why Erin is doing
so well today.
The only thing I can think
is Erin is living out
some slumdog millionaire
scenario,
where every word she's playing
has a connection
to her orphan past.
It's possible.
So what's your crazy
business pipe dream?
Well, I started
my own golf supply company.
Really?
It's taken off
faster than I expected,
so I came here to learn about
creating manageable growth.
- Phyllis?
- Hmm?
Some of these people
are for real.
Hey, friend.
How's it going?
Oh, you know what?
Let me steep that for you.
Thank you.
Hey, you know what?
Good news.
We're back in.
Let's go sell
some paper, buddy. Huh?
Really?
Ahem!
- Excuse me.
- I got it. I got it.
Hey, do you need a lozenge?
They're a bunch a jackals.
What?
They left you in the lurch,
and if they want to jump in,
it means you're almost there.
You did this.
Bring it home.
Let me tell you what you can do
with your offer to help.
You can table it
and offer it up another time.
Just know that I really
appreciate the gesture.
Hi. Hope you
enjoyed your lunch.
Welcome back.
Ooh. Well, hello.
Welcome to the seminar.
Hey, man.
What's goin' on?
You're gonna blow it.
Maybe.
Only maybe.
I got it.
Oscar, wait.
I think the victory
would be more meaningful
if Erin puts the last word
in herself.
Yes, Pam.
Yes, most definitely.
Yes.
Ah! No
Although I must say,
I will have apoplexy
if you lose.
Do you understand?
Apoplexy is what I will have.
Apoplexy.
- Yes.
- Got it.
Oh, Oscar.
Oscar?
I played "ape."
I just want to make
a point to that last caller.
I disagree.
I don't think it is
the running game at all.
I think we do have to make
a few moves in this off-season.
Wow!
What a day, right?
Guess you guys
are probably ready to go.
And you got
my business card, so...
Dah, dah, dah, dah, dah, dah.
You know, I like you.
I'm going to give you
my secret gyro recipe.
Come out here
since it's a secret,
and I'll tell you.
All right,
you have to close right now.
Yeah, I mean,
I'm getting to it.
No, you're not.
You're getting past it.
You have to close.
You can do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Andy, what's the problem?
This is hard for me.
I'm a nice guy.
You know,
Kelly and creed, Kevin,
they believe in you.
Don't let them down.
Don't let yourself down, Andy.
I'm gonna go back in.
I'm going to stall them
for a little bit.
I want you
to get your head together,
and then come back in.
I want you to close.
What is taking
that guy so long?
Psst.
You think this thing's
gonna go much longer?
I don't know.
They're still in there.
Ohh! Good-bye.
Stop.
Out with it.
Here's the story.
That guy in there
is Jim's childhood friend, tom.
Tom Witochkin.
One of my best buddies,
actually.
And when they were
both in the third grade,
Jim was placed
in the top reading group.
I was blue group,
so it was second from the top.
- And tom...
- Was in green group.
And Jim's mom suggested
that Jim spend time
hanging with the kids
in his reading group,
because she thought that
they would be a good influence.
And that's what I told him.
Right.
But how'd you say it?
"My mom thinks you're too dumb
to hang out with."
Okay, who would like
to purchase
this small business package
from me right now?
Yes, we got one.
Okay, the snowball is rolling.
Who else?
You can put it off
for a couple of days,
but I guarantee you,
eventually you're gonna realize
you need this.
So the only thing
that's gonna be different
is you'll be
a couple of days behind
where you would be if you bought
this from me right now.
So who's gonna
buy one right now?
I'll take one.
Yes! Awesome!
All right, anyone else?
Sold!
Anybody else?
Yes! All right!
- Yeah, bitch.
- Good choice.
The rest of you are dead to me.
You made the stupidest decisions
of your life.
No, no, no.
But it was
a pleasure meeting you,
and you've got my information,
so feel free to call anytime.
Hey, you think it's cool
if I grab a soda?
Yeah. Whoa.
Yep, absolutely, go ahead.
Hey.
How's it goin'?
- Pretty good.
- It's been a while.
It has been, yeah.
So you work here, huh?
Sales.
Must be a front
for some kind
of famous laboratory.
'Cause you're so smart.
Oh, man.
You remember that, huh?
Oh, barely.
I'm so dumb,
you know, stuff goes in,
stuff goes out.
Not like you probably remember
every paper sale you ever made.
Paper salesman genius.
- All right,
good catch-up.
- Yeah.
- See ya.
Where's your jetpack,
Zuckerberg?
Andy.
I didn't think
you had it in ya.
Well, I guess
when you looked in me,
you forgot about my balls.
They're on the outside.
Don't know how you missed 'em.
Wonderful seminar!
Almost as good
as the day when we first met.
You are the love of my life.
Come to me, necropolis.
Put your lips on my lips.
Come on.
Michael, I should
get back to work.
What? Come on.
It's time for grapes.
Real fun day.
- So, I won.
- I know.
You get to pick.
Well, that's actually what
I came to talk to you about.
I know how much
you want to watch wall-e.
Yes?
So I got us a compromise.
This movie is called hardware,
it tells the story of a killer
combat robot, just like wall-e
that the government invented
to destroy humans.
It's some of what you like
and some of what I like.
I heard you talked
about movies before
****
there's a Shrek 2?
Oh, yeah.
Nice guy.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net