Have you seen Darryl?
He's around here, somewhere.
Hmm.
Yeah, Darryl's here.
So is Santa Claus.
It's just a regular Thursday.
Neither guy is here.
And it's Friday.
Welcome to me and Darryl's
World of Lies.
Nobody knows it yet,
but Darryl already
started working in Philly.
So now he has to sneak
out of here
like the sneakiest
little sneaky sneak
you ever saw.
And I'm his helper.
It's so fun.
Darryl, meet Bear-yl.
How much did you pay for that?
Nothing.
Won him at the carnival.
Spent a ton on tickets, though.
Drive safe.
Everybody knows I go to Philly.
I've just been using sick days
I saved up.
But Erin was so excited
about being sneaky sneaks,
I went along with it.
Darryl, you are too much.
That guy's hilarious.
He's here today.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I've really been putting
in the hours
on this mural.
And my bs
is totally okay with it,
because he's in the Bahamas
and has no clue
what anybody's doing.
I'm usually very self-critical.
I hate what I paint.
But I don't know.
This time I feel
like it's...
it's really coming together.
Oh, my God!
What?
You've got to be kidding me.
What... are those...
are those butts?
Huh?
No way.
Excuse me, everyone.
Is it okay if I leave early
from work today?
It's Phillip's first birthday,
and the Senator and I
are hosting
a party at our house.
Oh, cute, so there'll
be a bunch of kids.
No.
No children.
Our house is not kid-friendly.
Most of our furniture is sharp.
Also ew.
It will mostly be
campaign donors.
Angela, I am prepared to donate
a whopping $8
to Lipton for America
- to have an invitation...
- No, no, please.
You know, actually none of you
could even really make the cut
for this thing.
Which I am so sad about.
Angela.
You're going to find out,
so I thought
I'd let you know
that Robert invited me too.
- What?
- He said he wanted me there
- for support.
- I'm...
his wife.
Angela's husband
and I are in love,
but as a politician
in this town
you still need
the conventional blonde wife
on your lawn signs.
He is risking everything
to have me there today.
Me.
We agreed
that you wouldn't be seen
with him in public.
It's humiliating for me.
Well, if you get
to bring a stud,
maybe I do too.
- Hey.
We are splitting a sublet
on a place near Philly.
Just a couple
of grown, sexy ass roommates.
And, as much as I miss
Pam and the kids,
it's kind of nice
to live the bachelor life again.
You know, let your hair down.
Jim was nice enough
to give me his bedroom.
I'm couching it.
Which usually means
there are clothes
all over the living room.
And this dude labels his food.
He's the clean one.
I'm the messy one.
How much fun is this?
I love Jim.
I love that he hooked me up
with a job.
It's just he uses
old T-shirts
as wash rags.
He doesn't wash his dishes.
Apparently,
they need to "soak."
He hooked me up with a job.
Attention, everyone.
Can I have your attention,
please?
Yeah, I don't know
everybody's name down here,
but, whoever did this,
will you please raise your hand?
Hello?
This is not over.
Okay?
I will stay up here all day
if I have to.
Is that what you want?
Yeah, I will also come down
if I want to.
It's my choice.
I don't demand justice often.
I'm not like Angela
who calls a lawyer
every time someone watches
a YouTube video of animals
doing it,
but someone should get fired
over this, right?
Val's no help.
Andy's gone. Jim's out.
I just feel
like I'm on my own here.
I mean, okay,
not completely on my own,
but in terms of people
who can do something.
Thank you, Brian.
Hey, so, Wade wants to send
people to the saloon conference.
We got to compile a list
of our target clients.
Already on it.
I ordered them
by their Google trend ranking
so we know who to hit first.
Who is this guy?
We are killing it.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Conference room,
everybody, now.
You don't have the clearance
to call
a conference room meeting.
Yes, but David Wallace does,
and he asked me
to gather everyone
to talk about stuff
that's gonna be revealed
once we're in the conference
room for the meeting.
You're telling me
David Wallace asked you
to call a super-secret
classified conference room
meeting?
Yeah.
Let's go, everyone.
Super-secret classified
conference room meeting now.
Let's go.
I have terrible news.
Someone defaced my mural.
They painted all over it.
I thought
that's what you were doing.
Yeah, but this is different.
Oh. They used worse paint
than your paint.
I don't think so,
but they put paint
where I didn't want paint,
so...
I thought you wanted paint
on the whole thing.
Different-colored paint.
I wanted different-colored paint
in the spots where they put
their paints,
so it just is... okay.
The point is these
warehouse guys are vandals,
and they need to be stopped.
Yeah, and somebody had
the balls to put my phone number
on the men's room wall,
which is so messed up.
It's 6782, not 83.
Uh, 6783's also a good time,
less mileage.
Pam, what can be done?
Yes, thank you.
Let's answer that question.
I was politely saying
nothing can be done.
- I thought I was clear.
- What?
Come on, guys,
we need to figure out
who did this and punish them.
This isn't just about me.
This is about all of us.
This is our mural.
Don't you see
how much we worked on this?
How much time and energy?
We put our heart
and soul into this thing.
David Wallace
called this meeting?
Sure did.
I was as surprised as you,
but apparently he is very
passionate about public art.
No, no, come on, guys.
Don't go.
- Pam, I'll help you.
- You will?
If there's anything
I hate worse than art,
it's crime.
- Thank you?
- I am in too, Pam.
- Yeah?
- Yes, of course.
I believe in you.
I believe in your art.
- And I am bored.
- Great.
I was hoping
for a righteous mob.
I ended up
with Dwight and Nellie.
But they both have
a mob mentality,
and I'm pretty sure Dwight
has a pitchfork in his car.
You need my pitchfork?
- Hey.
- What is it?
I have vengeance to exact.
Exciting news.
There's room for one more
at my son's birthday event,
- and I want you.
- I'm not interested.
But, wait, the State
Transportation Secretary
will be there.
You could sell
your bit salt idea
to the highway people.
If I get the deicing gig,
it's gonna be on merit,
not because I played politics.
Hey, so a little birdie
just told me
that Dwight can't come
to your son's birthday.
So do you want me
to go with you?
- No.
- Okay, I understand.
I'll just stay here then,
alone with the money.
Oh, crap.
I am handing out pieces
of paper
on which you will draw
one human butt.
What I do with said drawings
is no one's business
but my own.
You're gonna compare 'em
to the butts up there.
Incorrect.
It is my fetish.
Oh, also sign them.
My fetish
is signed drawings of butts.
I'm not drawing a butt.
All right, then no bottoms.
We should ask you
to do big rounded Ws.
Yes.
Or nipple-less breasts.
Okay, okay, I think it's time
to get back to work.
Come on, fellas.
Let's go.
Or melons like cantaloupes
with the halves are cut off
and then just the bottom parts.
Well, this is getting us
nowhere.
We need another approach.
We need to find the weakest one
and separate him from the group.
Yeah, I think,
if we could get Nate alone,
we could crack him.
We just need
a pretense to talk to him.
We could tell him
that his mother is dying.
That usually works on him.
Nate!
Your mother is dying.
See, I feel bad about that.
It's all right.
So she's gonna pull through
again?
That's great.
Can I talk to her?
No.
She needs her rest again.
Now, listen,
now that we have got you here,
let's talk
about this mural business.
You know who the vandal is.
Now I know a lot of these
warehouse guys are your friends,
but we've got chewing gum.
Gum's gotten mintier lately.
Have you noticed?
Like, some of it's
just too minty.
It's like they're literally
trying to hurt your...
Tell us who defaced the mural.
He did it.
All right. You can go.
Give him his gum.
There's no gum.
There never was any gum.
Wow, that's really rude.
Opening with puff pastries?
That's a bold play.
They're saying it's only
gonna get better from here?
Good luck.
That painting is just...
How can anyone that weighs less
than a Guinea hen
be so terrifying?
Ladies and gentlemen,
Senator and Angela Lipton.
Thanks, everybody.
Thanks for coming.
Phillip had no idea
he was so popular.
Oh, Robert, you're horrible.
Simon, Maxine,
who let you guys in here?
This is the team.
- Nice job, man.
- You too, Darryl.
What?
Oh, man.
I'm sorry about that.
It's cool.
Reading's tricky sometimes.
Oh.
Are you really mad about this?
That's my go-to thermos,
that's all.
Oh.
It's your go-to...
oh, man, that's a bummer.
- I'm sorry about that.
- No big deal.
- No, no, if it's a big deal,
it's a big deal.
No big deal.
No, no, no, no,
you don't have to do that.
Honestly, I don't mind.
Did you want me
to wash it for you or...?
I don't know.
Are you gonna wash it,
or are you gonna let it soak?
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
So, Frank, do you have
any thoughts
About what was done?
By you?
Maybe... maybe I could get
the ball rolling.
Frank?
Hi.
Pam.
I am so sorry
if I've done anything
to offend you.
I'm sure it isn't easy
for you guys
to have an upstairs person
coming down in your space.
So truly I apologize.
But enough about me.
Your turn.
Insert apology here, Frank?
I'm sorry I didn't like
your crappy doodles.
I drew a butt.
Big deal.
Butts are funny.
Well, I didn't think
that butt was funny.
Well, maybe if you got
the stick out of yours.
- What was that?
- You know what?
You people can't fire me,
so screw you.
Whoa.
Hey, that is not okay.
What are you gonna do
about that?
The first sorry
sounded sincere.
There were
two or three sorries in there.
- Mm, that's quite a lot.
- It's a lot.
That sucked.
He didn't apologize.
There's no talking to that guy.
Oh, your little feelings party
didn't work out, huh?
Who won the hugging contest?
No, let me guess.
Everyone tied for first.
We should just take him down.
Wait.
Are you saying...
I'm saying we should go
scorched earth
on that guy's face.
Normally I find Pam
to be a comforting
if unarousing presence
around the office.
Like a well-watered fern.
But today she has tapped into
this vengeful violent side,
and I'm like, wow,
Pam has kind of a good butt.
He messed with something
that was important to you.
We need to mess with something
that's important to him.
- A little eye-for-an-eye action.
- Yes, yes.
Go all Hammurabi on this clown.
We need an infiltrator.
I know just the man
for the job.
Clark?
He even looks like a mole.
One of his tee shots can wipe
out a whole owl population.
You two seem very close.
Yes, we're good friends.
Good friends.
- Yeah.
- And I suppose that may ruffle
a few feathers,
because for a long time
our party has turned its back
on the Hispanic people.
Well, that is not who I am.
I am a friend
of the Latino community.
And, if you ask me,
it's time that we bid bigotry
hasta luego.
Now does my embrace of Hispanics
make me more electable?
Given demographic trends,
I don't know.
And I don't care.
What I care about is Oscar.
My friend.
Mi amigo Oscar.
Maybe I should be insulted
that he only invited me here
to be his token Mexican friend,
but he could have invited
any number of Hispanics
that he knows...
his gardener Rohelio,
or he could have invited...
Rohelio.
But he chose me.
Rohelio's Malaysian.
The son of a bitch
is Malaysian.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Hey, I usually watch TV
during my lunch break.
- It's cool?
- Yeah, cool.
It's mine.
Don't worry.
I didn't say anything.
I don't think you had to.
Excuse me?
I think you might be going
a little crazy
with this labeling thing, man.
I mean, you put your name
on a five-pound bag of flour.
Are you honestly saying that,
if I needed flour,
I couldn't use that?
What you need flour for, Jim?
That's not the point.
- What you making, bread?
- No, I'm not making bread.
What kind of bread you making?
Pumpernickel?
It doesn't matter.
Darryl, I think you know
the point I'm trying to make.
All right, I'm being a jerk.
You got me this job.
I should be grateful.
I am, but just, you know, I get
a little finicky about my stuff.
That's all.
It's all good.
Are we all good?
We good.
What's that cooler?
Nothing.
It's mine.
What happened
to my Tavis Smileys?
Oh, crap.
Were those yours?
I never want to see you working
in the upstairs office again!
Do you hear me?
But my only crime was loving
the local sports teams
and trying to be
one of the guys.
Silence.
You'll now be working
in the warehouse
with the untouchables.
Now go make your hands
rough with work.
Okay, boss.
Pam, you know
this is ridiculous, right?
- Like, you're smarter than him.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- This is never gonna work.
- Shh, shh.
Remember your lines.
- What lines?
- Go move some paper.
Hey, you know that guy Frank
who works in the warehouse?
He's not my hire,
but I know who he is.
Okay, what is he like?
What's important to him?
Does he have, like,
a favorite pair of boots
or a lunchbox?
What, is he retiring?
You getting him a gift
or something?
Yeah, something like that.
I know he loves
his pickup truck.
Oh, great, his truck.
Great. Get the plate number.
Okay, do you know the plate...
never mind.
Why would you know that,
and why would I be asking that?
So we know which truck to fill.
While I got you on the phone,
your husband's like a sloppy,
homeless hobo.
- Can you fix that?
- Yeah.
I was kind of hoping you could.
I gotta go.
Bye.
Come on.
_
Hold on a second.
Sundeep, let's get you closer
to the Senator.
Just about there.
Great.
And, Oscar, I'm gonna need you
to step a little closer
to the Senator as well.
- Somewhere there.
- He's blocking me.
It's only a photo, honey.
Excuse me.
What's your name?
- Shawn.
- Lashawn, great.
You want to be in a photo?
Right this way.
- Not you. No.
- He put me here.
He put you
right in front of me?
He placed me there. He did.
He placed me here.
Let's just wheel Margaret
- right in front...
- Ow!
- Here. - Oscar... Angela.
- Robert.
Smile.
I'm done.
What are you...
is that supposed
to be my mural?
Yeah, Frank draws a butt
on your mural.
I'm drawing your mural
on Frank's truck's butt.
Eye for an eye, mamacita.
Aw, Dwight,
that's really sweet.
- Let's see yours.
- Oh, no.
I'm embarrassed.
It's stupid.
This is amazing!
Frank, and he's leaving a trail
of poops?
- Yeah.
- And he has saggy boobs.
I saw that.
It's great.
I feel better.
Good.
I'm glad you feel better.
This has been a wonderful day.
I have to say,
I like hanging out
with a vengeful bitch.
I know.
You miss Angela, don't you?
Ugh, don't sympathize.
You're ruining the mood.
Back to work.
Draw his penis.
I got back at Frank in
the most fitting way possible.
With my art.
You know,
the paints are water-based.
It's gonna come off
with a hose.
But I think the lesson
will last...
Lady, my truck?!
You had no right!
No, you had no right!
It's a $40,000 truck!
So?
You started it!
So? So somebody needs
to shut you up!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Whoa!
- Easy!
- Son of a bitch!
- Guys?
- You're gonna hit a woman?
Thanks so much for coming.
Thank you so much.
Well...
have we all calmed down yet?
Yes.
Sorry about that.
It was all my fault.
Let's all try
to do better next time.
Kevin, great to see you.
Thank you for the food.
And also you suck.
I beg your pardon.
You're, like,
a terrible person.
These guys care about you,
and you're just using them.
Again, the food was very good.
Well, I'm gonna say something
to the producers.
- No, no, it's...
- You shouldn't be fired.
I mean,
you were just protecting me.
It's all good.
I knew what I was doing. It's...
I'm sorry
about your mural, though.
I mean, because you put
so much into that.
Oh, no, forget about my mural.
It's stupid.
No, you worked hard on that.
That guy's an animal.
I'm glad they're firing him too.
It's crazy.
Brian, I'm so sorry.
Look, I don't... I don't want to
put myself where I don't belong.
If you ever need me,
you just call me,
and I'll be there for you.
Thanks, Brian.
See ya.
Wow, this whole Philly thing
has been so much fun
that I may have lost sight
of what really matters.
I mean, having fun
is not nearly as important
as being good to the people
you really care about.
I mean,
that's just Roommates 101.
- Oh, come on.
- Oh.
- Uh.
- Oh!
Damn.
You wins.
How good did that feel?
It felt really good actually.
www.tvsubtitles.net