Hello, son.
If you are watching this,
that means I'm already dead.
Life is...
How do you know
it's going to be a boy?
How... would you stop
interrupting, please?
Yesterday I was scraping some gunk off
my wall sockets with a metal fork,
and I gave myself the nastiest shock.
And when I came to,
I had an epiphery.
Life is precious.
And if I die,
I want my... son...
to know the dealio.
The dealio of life.
Here're some things
that I want to teach you.
That your mother
won't be able to.
To jump start a car,
First, pop the hood.
then you take these bad boys.
And clip them
anywhere on the engine.
Then, you take these...
And clip them wherever.
Number eight.
Learn how to take off
a woman's bra.
We will demonstrate
on Pam, and...
-No, no.
- Come on
You just twist your hands,
Until... something breaks.
Well, you get the picture.
Thanks, Pam.
And, remember.
No matter what,
I will always love you.
What if he's a murderer?
He's not going to be a murderer.
Maybe, that's how you die.
You know what, Dwight?
Do you want to this or no?
- I want to do this.
- Okay.
from the top, ready?
- Three
- Action
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL
(http://theoffice.tistory.com)
The Office 3x15 "Ben Franklin"
Original Air Date: Feb 1, 2007 (NBC)
Hello, everyone.
As you know,
we are six days away
from Philly's wedding
To get your suits
to the dry cleaners,
To get your hair did.
And, Karen, um...
you might want to invest in
a dress
or a skirt of some kind,
if you don't
or already have one.
This may be
Phyllis's only wedding ever.
It's my job to ensure
that none of you look like ragamuffins.
So... I am instituting
Primae Noctis.
I believe from the movie Braveheart,
and confirmed on Wikipedia,
is when the king got to deflower
every new bride
on her wedding night. So...
I'm sorry.
I had a very different understanding
as to what Primae Noctis meant.
I'm trying to get everyone
excited about Philly's wedding.
Because I want her to get people
excited about my wedding
...when the time comes
...which won't be hard
Because it's going to be awesome,
a lot better than hers.
That's for sure.
It will probably be on a boat.
Whazzup, spinstas?
Nothing.
You know,
this is a luncheon shower.
Girls only.
No problem.
The guys are having a little
Shindig in the room,
in the warehouse
From 2:30 to 3:15
And, this is the only time
that Bob is available.
Sort of a guy's night out.
A G-N-O, if you will.
A gno.
Actually, it's more of
a guy's afternoon in.
A G-A-I. A gai.
Not. Not... it's, uh... not gay.
It's... just...
it's a bridal shower for guys.
A guy shower.
An hour-long shower with guys.
Shit
I guess, Jim and I have had
a little bit of rough patch
for the past couple of weeks.
But, we had some really good talks.
And, actually now
I think that were better than ever.
Karen and I
had a long talk last night.
And, the night before that,
And... every night...
for the last five nights
Something's up with
Jim and Karen.
Not that I've been eavesdropping.
It's not really
any of my business.
But... I've gotten pretty good at
reading the back of Jim's neck.
Halpert!
Tall, queer,
handsome as ever.
Everybody, it's me, Jim.
Hello, Hello.
Todd Packer.
Karen Filippelli.
Jim's girlfriend.
Shut up! Shut!
That's rude
Either this chick is dude
or Halpert got scared straight!
Yes! Yes!
Ohhh... there...
- What happened? What?
- Oh, god...
Somebody help!
Help the man!
No! no!
I can't believe
you're not going to be there.
It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be
a great bachelor party, man.
- I have a full day sales call
- you should get out of them.
It's the only time
you can do it.
2:30 to 3:15
It's going to be great.
We are going to be
doing some darts.
There's going to be
a grilling up some stakes,
have some pies,
... going to be very delicious
and what kind of stripper
did you get?
I did not order a stripper.
You didn't order a stripper.
Have you ever been to
a bachelor party?
Not personally. No.
Mike, okay.
A stripper is ¡®Bachelor Party 101'
If you don't order a stripper,
your party is going to suck.
I can't get a stripper here.
Sexual harassment.
Just... Get one for the girls too.
That evens it out.
You know, separate but equal.
So that's what that means.
Okay everybody.
slight change of plans
We are still going to be having two parties
But each is going to get
a little extra dose of naugh-tay.
All right.
Okay, coed naked stripper
in this office. For realsies.
Under no circumstance
should a man strip off
his clothes in this office.
Shut up! Angela!
- Hey
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah. Why?
Well, you seem a little tired.
Oh, yeah. Well, I guess
there's been a couple of late nights.
Karen and I have been up talking.
You should get more sleep.
Yeah, I know I should.
Never underestimate
the power of a good night's sleep.
No, I'm sure you're right.
When I get eight hours,
compared to like, six hours...
it's like, big difference.
Really?
Oh yeah.
Gotta get your REM cycle,
going with the whole... sleeping...
better than not.
Good advice, Beesly.
Thanks. See you out there?
Yeah.
Don't fall asleep at your desk.
Okay, we are off.
Ryan and I are going
to get some supplies.
And, I need you to handle
hiring the strippers.
Absolutely not.
On it!
Go get on it,
and make it happen.
Ruddy chicks, thick calves,
no tats, no moles...
No tats. No, tats!
Of course, I ...
Stop. That's disgusting.
Leave me alone
and get the male stripper.
I knew you would, Nancy.
Sally.
No preference.
What do you think?
Redhead or blondhead?
Blond.
Nice.
Do you have
any blond women?
He hasn't even
said a word, yet.
Just giggling.
Yes ?
You okay?
I'm... I'm in the sex shop
Ah, gotcha.
Okay, so they had Albert Einstein,
Ben Franklin,
or Sponge Bob SquarePants.
SquarePants?
Yup. Sponge Bob SquarePants
And, you think that'd be sexy?
Michael referred me to a male strip club,
called Banana Slings.
Instead, I called
the Scholastic Speakers of Pennsylvania.
Oh, hold the door, please.
Thank you.
- Oh, hello
- Hello
You wearing a thong?
What?
Sparking cider is very good.
I think that's champagne.
Hello, ladies.
Who here is the history buff?
I.
Who's the fan of buff naked?
Without further ado
the one,
the only,
the sexy.
Mr. Benjamin Franklin.
Thank you for
the introduction, Mr. Scott.
And, good afternoon,
fine gentlewomen
of Dunder-Mifflin.
Half-pants.
Right, Mr. Franklin?
Knickers in fact, yes.
He says it is knickers.
Mr. Franklin,
I would say you were probably
one of the sexiest presidents ever.
Well, actually,
I never was president.
Yes, but Ben Franklin was.
Well, I'm here to teach you
a little bit about my life,
and, the era of founding fathers.
and, when they came
over on the mayflowers.
Wait, this is the entertainment?
Yeah, all right.
So, I want you to give him
your undivided attention.
And, Mr. Franklin,
if anyone of these ladies misbehave,
I'd give you a permission
to spank them.
Especially, that one.
Have you ever seen
a stripper before?
Yes.
Jennifer Garner
portrayed one on Alias.
It was one of
her many aliases.
Yeah. Me neither.
- Hey
- Hi
I'm Elizabeth.
I'm the dancer
that you guys requested
Okay, I specifically
ordered a stripper.
I'm the stripper.
Oh, okay, good.
Well, I'll keep your
'Please identify yourself', or such.
Oh, god.
"Is she hot?¡±
Text back, ¡°Kind of¡±
It was warm June evening in 1752,
the night of my faithful kite flight.
Mr. Franklin,
do you have a girlfriend?
I have a lovely wife, Deborah.
But don't you also have
girlfriends in Paris?
Like, a lot of them?
Ah, well, that is a gray area
of my life. Okay?
So, it was a warm June evening...
Look at that.
Nothing like grilling
in the great outdoors.
Is this the same grill
you grilled your foot on?
No.
Yes.
- Oh gross...
- But I got all the of the foot off of it.
Okay, Ben Franklin.
Oh, Ben Franklin tied
a cherry stem in his mouth!
Well, that is because
I am a renaissance man.
Ben Franklin?
Do you wear boxers,
briefs, or pantaloons?
Well, you're very saucy...
Guys, Beef!
It's what's for dinner.
Who wants some man meat?
I do! I want some man meat!
Michael, Dwight would
like your man meat.
Well, then my man meat
he shall have.
There you go.
- Dee-li-ci-ous-ity
- Of course
So, I guess
you have the Ben Franklin wig,
and a costume,
And you figure
how can I put those for practical use?
Well, I'd like to think that his dad
was a Ben Franklin impersonator.
And, he really pressured him into it.
Hey, um, I wanted to talk to you...
I know this is weird
or whatever, but um...
Jim told me about you guys.
What do you mean?
Well, that you kissed.
And we've talked it through,
and it's totally fine.
It's not a big deal.
It was just a kiss.
Wait, you're not still...
interested in him?
Oh, yeah.
Really?
Oh, no! I? I'm...
I was confused by your phrasing.
You should definitely
go out with Jim.
I mean, you're going out with Jim.
I¡®m not going out with Jim.
You're dating him.
Which is awesome because
you guys are great together.
Okay.
And I'm not into Jim. Yeah.
So, uh... we're good.
Yeah.
Sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Um... what?
Nothing.
I was just thinking of something else.
Okay, the game is 'No-limit Deuce-to-Seven Lowball'
Once 25/50,
nickels are worth 10, dimes 25,
and quarters 50, nothing wild
I'll go suffle
Here we go.
Mike
Ah, gentlemen.
The entertainment is here.
Everybody, I'd like to
introduce you to Elizabeth.
Hi, guys.
I hear there's
an important meeting here.
I'm not really into strippers.
You know what I find sexy?
Pam's art.
She's an artist.
And I appreciate that.
It's very moving.
And... sexy.
The art.
Hit it.
So, where's the groom?
He is right there.
- There he is.
- Absolutely not
That's all you need.
Okay, all right. I'll do it.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do this thing.
- Yeah, What am I...
- Sit down, down
Oh, here we go, alright.
Not bad, not bad.
You smell nice. Like Tide.
Um, What's that?
Smell like Tide Detergent.
Do you use Tide Detergent?
I have a girlfriend, so...
I bet she'd be jealous.
Yeah, she'd probably be.
Yeah, she'd be.
You know what?
Okay, excuse me.
Just... please
stop it, stop it.
Stop the music.
This is wrong, this is wrong!
This is wrong.
I have a girlfriend,
and, you are engaged.
and, I'm sure you have a boyfriend...
in prison or something.
So... let's just clear it out, okay?
Shame on you!
Go back to work!
Elizabeth, I want you to sit here.
When the phone rings,
answer it.
You want me to
answer the phones,
with my clothes on.
We hired you for three hours work,
and we are gonna get it.
Oh, I love your poster.
Thank you.
You know,
I invented electricity.
I know.
Well, I'm sensing
a little electricity here.
Didn't Ben Franklin have syphilis?
Yes.
But, I don't.
My name is Gordon.
On one hand,
I want to be honest with Jan,
and tell her the truth.
And, on the other hand,
I'm afraid that
she's gonna just dump me.
You know, Michael.
I fathered in illegitimate son.
Really?
But I've kept all this
from my wife, Deborah.
These things are only serve
to upset the women.
They are the gentler sex.
Wow.
Ben Franklin, you are really
kind of sleazebag.
Stripper,
Can I ask you a question
about women?
Um... should I tell my girlfriend
that you danced up on me?
Secrets, secrets are no fun.
Secrets, secrets hurt someone.
Wow.
Thank you.
Care for a piece of chocolate?
Chocolate!
Where did you acquire it?
That is a delicacy in the Amazon
but it has not yet been
imported to the United States.
- Who is the King of Austria?
- Joseph the Second.
- Who is the king of Prussia?
- Friedrich Wilhelm the Third.
Who is the king of England?
Why, the tyrant King George,
of course.
I don't care what Jim says.
That is not the real Ben Franklin.
I am 99% sure.
Michael, I left a meeting.
What is so urgent?
Are you... are you okay?
Not really.
Look, I don't know
how to say this,
so I just will.
Okay.
I... um... went to a bachelor party.
And, things got little out of hand.
Ah... when? When did...
When...last night?
No, today at work.
You went to
a bachelor party at work?
Yes, I kind of arranged it.
Well, I don't even think
the stripper was that hot.
Do you guys think
she was hot?
Kelly, don't do this.
Do what?
I just asked a question.
You know what you're doing.
Anyway, you know who was
totally flirted with Franklin?
Pam.
Really?
Looks like I hired
the right guy.
I'm glad.
And, you are the potential
Deborah Read?
Yeah, right.
God, I need a boyfriend.
Um, you know what, Ryan.
I'm totally ready to be set up with
one of your business school friends.
- Whenever
- Okay
Oh my god, I would get so fat
if I worked here.
Yeah? I lose my appetite
all the time.
You can stripe, you know.
Thanks.
So you don't want to end
our relationship?
I'm closer to firing you!
That is so sweet.
You are the best GD girlfriend in the world.
Do you know that?
- Thank you
- you are. you are.
So you know who turned out
to be kind of a creep?
Ben Franklin.
And Elizabeth, the stripper?
Gave me great advice.
Which rhymed.
Really makes you wonder
how Ben Franklin can become president,
but someone like Elizabeth can't.
Are you near-sighted or far-sighted?
Both
That's why I invented the bifocal.
www.tvsubtitles.net