Not again.
Bow down
before Recyclops.
Five years ago corporate
said we had to start
a recycling program
for Earth Day,
so Dwight took
the lead on that,
and introduced us to a very close
friend of his named Recyclops.
Happy Earth Day, everyone.
I'm Recyclops.
Did you know that
an old milk carton
can be sawed in half
and used as a planter?
JIM: The next year, he
really stepped things up.
Who has put a number seven
plastic in a number four bin?
A year after that, Recyclops
really began to take shape.
Recyclops will drown you
in your over-watered lawns!
Then tragedy struck Recyclops
when his fictional planet
was attacked by some other
fictitious thing, I can't remember.
Recyclops will have
his revenge!
I think this was also the year
that he renounced Earth Day
and vowed to destroy
the planet he once loved.
Oh, my God, you guys,
look! It's Recyclops!
Recyclops destroy!
(BELLOWING)
Oh, is today Recyclops Day? Yes.
I thought you were killed
by Polluticon or something.
Polluticon wishes.
That's aerosol spray. It's
terrible for the environment.
DWIGHT: Humans are terrible
for the environment.
(BELLOWING)
The thing I like most
about Recyclops
is that he's creating a
different world for our child.
Hmm.
A world where you truly
can be anything you want.
JIM: God bless you,
Recyclops,
and your cold
robot heart.
Okay. Okay.
How about this?
That's great.
I want it to be better
than great, Pam.
How about I remain seated and
I just do a little bit of a nod,
sort of a humble thing?
Sure.
No. Then my face is down.
They can't see my face.
And it looks like
you're taking a dump.
Alan Brand who's
the CEO of the company,
if title is important
to you,
has personally invited
moi to go to New York
to the shareholders'
meeting
and sit up on the stage
with the board of directors.
And at some point, they're
going to introduce me
as the most successful
branch manager that they have.
And then Michael Scott turns
and waves to the crowd.
And the crowd goes wild.
Ladies and gentlemen,
from Scranton, Pennsylvania,
please welcome
Michael "The Machine" Scott!
Oh.
Don't do the twirl.
Lose the twirl.
DWIGHT: Twirl sucks.
Michael, I hated the twirl.
Hate the twirl.
Okay, obviously I'm not
going to do the twirl.
I only did it because
I nailed the wave.
Yeah, good.
Don't do it.
(ENUNCIATING) I'm not going
to do the twirl, all right?
It's not even a twirl.
It's a spin.
I might do the spin.
The long-term problem is bad
investments that they need to dump.
And the short-term problem
is the company
has no cash and there's
nowhere to get it.
Okay, Oscar. I don't need the
whole enchilada, just bullet points.
Those are
the bullet points.
Well, could you
condense it, please?
That's as simple
as I can make it.
Michael, the limo's
here for you.
It's not a limo,
it's a town car.
Town cars are
actually better, though,
better torque,
better handling.
He said limousine, so...
Check it out, guys,
there's a limo down here.
Michael, look.
Oh, man!
It's a limo.
They sent a limo.
Town cars suck.
A town car
is something that a company
sends when they're in trouble.
A limousine is something
that a company sends
when they have cause
for celebration.
And in this case, I think
we are celebrating me.
KEVIN: Move it! Quick!
MICHAEL: (LAUGHS)
Wow! Wow!
ANDY: Oh, no way!
Yeah!
What kind of mileage
does this baby get?
It's like what high school
kids take to prom on TV shows.
So typical of management
to spend money on this.
(EXCLAIMING)
Bunch of boobs!
Hate to break it to you, Oscar,
but some of us like boobs.
Calves.
Calves all the way.
I'm so jealous
right now.
Hey, you know who you
should be jealous of?
Yourself.
Because you're invited,
and you're invited,
and you, and you,
and you and you and you
and you... Car seats eight.
What?
The car seats eight.
The limo seats eight.
Okay, then Jim and Pam
and Ryan plus a guest.
No.
No, thanks.
I'll use it
when you're done.
MICHAEL: Mmm.
Whoa.
The Dunder Mifflin
stock symbol is DMI.
Do you know what
that stands for?
Dummies,
Morons and Idiots,
because that's what
you'd have to be to own it.
And as one of those idiots, I
believe the board owes me answers.
MICHAEL: I wish the
windows weren't tinted
so people could
see us in here.
Hey, guys, do you think anyone
might have had sex in here?
Definitely. Definitely. Smells like it.
Look, they got pillows.
That, that's bigger
than my bed.
Word.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
MICHAEL: Who's playing
with the button?
Hey, Ryan, could you start consolidating
all our Rolodex
information into Outlook?
Doesn't seem like
there's much of a point
if the company's
going under.
But if the company
doesn't go under,
then we'll finally have all
our contacts in one program.
Company's probably going under,
though. It could go either way.
Seems like it's
leaning one way.
Maybe we should just
wait and find out.
Definitely.
Okay.
So should we wait to find out
before we start doing all this stuff?
Nah. Might as well
do it now.
Michael, what if somebody asks
you a question at this meeting?
Are you just
going to wave or what?
I will have to answer.
I'll ask you
a question.
Make it a softball.
Something he can, like,
crank out of the park.
Michael Scott, you run the most
profitable branch of Dunder Mifflin.
Yeah.
How do you do it?
No, no, that's too hard.
Say, your name is Zamboni,
and then I will say, "Well,
we're sort of on thin ice."
(LAUGHS)
Uh-oh!
I won't say that. I'll
say something like that.
ANDY: This is your big day. Come on.
Whoo. Oh, my God. This is it.
LAURIE: Mr. Scott?
Yes.
I'm Laurie.
Oh, hi.
Thank you for joining us. Come with me.
Well, thank you.
And please call...
Continue to call me
Mr. Scott.
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
If you just want to follow me
I'll take you up to the lounge.
Well, I guess this is as far
as I can take you guys, so...
DWIGHT: Good luck,
Michael. See you later.
Officers. Thank you.
After you, Mr. Scott.
Thank you.
Michael.
Hello.
So glad you could make it. Thank you.
How was the ride?
Oh. It was awesome.
Very, very sublime.
I'm glad. I want to
introduce you to everyone.
Okay. First we'll start with Alan Brand.
Alan, CEO.
Michael Scott,
Branch Manager, Scranton.
It's nice to meet you,
Michael. Nice to meet you, too.
It's an honor
and a privilege.
Seated, we have the former
congressman, Chris O'Keefe.
Your eminence.
For those of you with
questions, please line up
behind one of
the four microphones
that have been placed
in the aisles.
Coming through!
(SHOOING)
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(GRUNTS) Damn it!
What... Okay.
(GRUNTING)
I was hoping to lob Michael
a softball question early.
I wanted to swing by
the Garment District,
pick up a few crates
of my shirts.
I got a shirt guy.
OSCAR: Would you
believe this?
The money they spent
on this convention hall!
Excuse me, miss.
Just want to take this stupid
board of directors by their necks.
This is so simple.
Yeah.
Idiots!
Well, you should do that.
Get in line.
Oh, what a great idea, and
lose my job. No, thank you.
Look, do you want to be
able to tell your grandkids
you stood up
for yourself
during America's
biggest financial crisis?
How is he going
to have grandkids?
You guys ever
protect the President?
No.
What about Madonna or
Obama twins? Anybody famous?
Not supposed to
talk about it.
Nelly Furtado.
ALAN: All right, guys.
Are you ready?
Rock and roll.
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
Dunder Mifflin is
still a strong company,
and we are poised
to come through this
more streamlined and
profitable than ever.
(JEERING)
This is not as much fun
as I thought it would be.
It was fun when we weren't
on the brink of bankruptcy.
(OVER MIC) We're going
bankrupt, you think?
(AUDIENCE CLAMORING)
They are really angry.
The shareholders need to
empower our leadership...
I'm just going to
run to the bathroom.
Will you save my place?
Sure.
No. He will not.
Excuse me?
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you raised in
a household with no consequences?
Lt'll just be a second.
Oh.
If onlys and justs
were candies and nuts
then every day
would be Erntedankfest.
... and we're confident
there are many things
to be optimistic about
in Dunder Mifflin's future.
And one of them is
here with us today.
Michael Scott,
Scranton Branch Manager.
DWIGHT: (CLAPPING) Yes!
ALAN: In these
uncertain times,
Michael has managed to
maintain steady profits
from his Scranton branch.
We all thank you, Michael.
Another bright spot in the
Dunder Mifflin landscape,
our new waste pulp
repurposing plant in Milford.
(APPLAUDING)
Hey, Phyllis, are you just
getting back from lunch now?
Mmm. Bob took me
to Capello's.
We got a little tipsy.
Okay.
Shouldn't be
telling me that stuff,
and also shouldn't be taking
two-hour lunches without telling me.
Oh, it's okay. Michael doesn't
really care about these things.
I care about them. And I'm just
as much of a boss as Michael.
(BOTH LAUGH)
What's so funny?
I'm a co-manager.
That doesn't
make you a boss.
It's not like you can
fire people or anything.
(STUTTERING)
Who... How did you...
Who told you this?
We can't say.
Ryan.
Sorry. I'm plastered.
Okay, who else
has heard the rumor
that I am not as much
in charge as Michael?
Stuff gets around.
I don't participate.
Who here heard it
from Ryan?
Does an e-mail count?
Yes.
Then, yeah.
I am just as much
of a boss as Michael,
and I can do anything
that Michael can do.
All right?
Who here believes that I
have as much power as Michael?
I forgot I have to support
him, no matter what.
Close one.
These questions
are bush league.
You should get up
and say something.
You got to be true
to what's in there.
Don't be a wuss.
I've always been the guy who
can rally other people to rebel.
In high school I organized a
walkout over standardized testing.
Got over 500 students
to just skip the SATs.
At the last second, I
chickened out, took it anyway.
Got a 1220.
Always regretted it.
I feel lachrymose.
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
Believe me, everyone
is working very hard,
working weekends, struggling,
trying to right the ship.
You're criminals!
Hey, hey, hey, I'm sorry.
These are not criminals.
They're nice. They invited
me to come here today.
They invited me to
their hospitality suite,
where I had free food
and it was delicious.
Get this, you know
how nice they are?
They sent
a stretch limo
all the way to pick me up in Scranton.
Limousine?
Yes.
You're all corrupt!
You should be in jail!
(AUDIENCE AGREEING)
Quiet! Quiet, please!
Please, quiet!
Quiet, please! We want
to hear your questions.
Do you love her, or do
you love the idea of her?
I don't know, man.
I just don't know.
I've got to make an example out
of him. Should I just fire him?
Can you actually
fire people?
To be honest,
I don't know.
But maybe I could just yell
at him in front of people.
Well, I can't really imagine
you yelling at anyone.
Oh, I yell.
You've heard me yell.
Okay. I've
heard you exclaim.
Like the time you said, "Hey,
look, we parked over here!"
Well, that was
apple-picking day.
There was no need
to yell that day.
You know, I was just
excited to find the car.
Perfect end
to a perfect day.
Well, you'll
figure it out.
Okay, we're going to take
a 15-minute break,
and then we're going to
answer more questions.
You haven't said
anything yet
and we're headed
for bankruptcy!
ALL: Yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah, well, that's not going to
happen. That's not going to happen.
We'll be back
with some answers.
MAN: What?
WOMAN: What answers?
Okay, I know that
you're mad at me
and you're mad
at all of them...
How are you going to
fix the company?
Okay. All right.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
All right.
We are going to go out
there during this break
and we're going to
come back with a plan.
We're going to come back
with a plan for you.
It's a 45-day plan.
Forty-five days to
get us back on track.
(MAN CHEERING)
Forty-five points.
It's a 45-day, 45-point,
one point per day,
we get to 45 points,
we're back in business!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And you can take
that to the bank!
And, limo lady,
we are going completely
carbon-neutral!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
I love you, New York!
You! You!
Hey, Ryan,
how's it going?
Here's the thing.
I've tried it, like, five
different ways in my head and...
Oh. Got one.
I'm such a perfectionist
that I'd kind of rather not do it
at all than do a crappy version.
Simple data entry, though. So
there's really only one way to do it.
Sounds like you have a
really specific vision for it.
Do you want to maybe
just take a whack at it?
You know what?
What?
I think I know the problem. Great.
I think
you seem distracted.
Yep, that is
the problem.
And you know what, I
came up with something
that I think is
really gonna help.
Well, I'm glad you're
finally being proactive, Jim.
I am, too.
Let me show you.
Wow, things are
really picking up.
What was that about?
What?
You were supposed to wave.
I did wave. I did a lot more than wave.
What are we supposed
to tell them now?
Okay, you've dug us
quite a hole.
We tell them the plan.
Right?
There is no plan.
Here's what
we're going to do.
The 45-day thing that I
outlined, we go with that.
Day 45, company saved.
Day 44, go,
what have we got?
We have 15 minutes.
Excuse me?
Just whatever comes
to mind, shout it out.
Who the hell
is this guy?
I am the guy
who roused that crowd.
DAVID: Yes.
Got them on their feet.
They were so happy down there. Yes. Yes.
Who cares?
Okay. All right.
Well, I know a guy, this
Mexican guy, he's a math wiz.
He knows economics as well
as he knows bullfighting.
And I am going to
call in a little favor.
No, no, no.
Don't call anybody, Michael.
Well, I'm texting him, so.
Please do not text
anybody now, Michael.
It's done.
(VIBRATING)
Oh.
There he is. Come on in, come on in.
Gentlemen, I would
like you to meet Oscar.
Come on in,
don't be shy.
This is Oscar Martinez.
Oscar, why don't you come
over here? Let me present you.
Step up,
step up there.
Oscar is an accountant
extraordinaire at the Scranton branch,
and he has
a wonderful idea
as to how to get us out of
this murky, murky situation.
Take it away.
I think this is
really going to help.
If you could just
hold up here one second.
Hey, guys, just
a quick announcement.
If I could have
everyone's attention.
Just figured you needed a place
where you could concentrate.
And not be bothered
by bothering people.
Okay.
Let me show you
what I mean.
Your new office.
How great is that, right?
For a job well done.
Well, not done.
I will do my work
right now.
I will stay late tonight. Right.
I'm very sorry about
everything. (CHUCKLING)
You're a good kid.
You know what,
it gets bigger
once you're in there.
Enjoy it.
RYAN: Is there Internet?
Tell them what you
told me. This is genius.
Tell them about
the cash flow
and the dumping of
properties and...
This is all good.
It's all good stuff.
Lay it on them.
I feel,
as does Mr. Scott,
that we are in
the best of hands,
capable hands.
That wasn't what
you were saying to me.
He was much more
articulate
and that was better,
much better.
I think this has gone
very well and I thank you.
Okay.
(SIGHS) Oh.
Hey, hey.
What were you doing?
Michael, I didn't ask
to come up here.
Wow, man!
What?
That was embarrassing.
For me.
For me, too.
For you and me?
You embarrassed me.
(SIGHS)
Well...
That was a waste
of a text.
Let's get down
to brass tacks.
I think that we
might be in trouble.
We don't seem
to have a plan,
so I'm thinking
I go down there,
maybe rattle off a few jokes,
congressman can follow.
He's our best manager? Where's
the off button on this moron?
I'm not a moron.
Time after time, my
branch leads in sales.
I have personally won over 17
Dundie Awards, so I am not a moron.
And I'm just trying to help,
you know? So, you're the moron.
MICHAEL: Yes, it is a thrill
to be honored by one's company.
To have the people that you
work for stop for a minute
and say, "Wow, great job!"
That's what it's about.
He can take the bus.
He's had his limo ride.
That is what
it is all about.
Not the perks.
The perks...
The perks, I could
take or leave the perks.
Oscar, Oscar!
Come on!
But limos are for people
who make the company money,
not lose millions
and have no plan.
There he is,
there he is!
So we're leaving early.
(WHOOPING) Go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
Michael!
Oh, yeah!
(LAUGHING)
MICHAEL: After all, we are the only
ones with anything to celebrate.
Scranton! Scranton!
(MEN CHEERING)
MICHAEL: Dunder Mifflin!
The gentleman
in the glasses.
Dwight Schrute,
Scranton Branch.
I just want to say that I have
been standing in this line all day.
And if this line
is any indication
of how this company
is being run,
then we are
in big trouble.
(APPLAUDING)
Thank you.
Right, I know.
And I just
want to say that
I believe that there
are options out there.
A take-a-number option,
like they have in a deli.
(APPLAUSE STOPS)
What about
line varieties?
Like an express line for quick
comments of 10 words or less.
That could move
much more efficiently.
What about ropes along the
lines that you can hold on to?
ALAN: Thank you.
Thank you for
your suggestions.
Yes.
www.tvsubtitles.net