So, you found a band yet
for your wedding ?
'Cause I'm in a band.
We really rock.
Yeah, I mean, it's inevitable.
I definitely overhear some wedding
preparation, but I'm fine with it.
She hears me arranging
my social life...
and we both have to hear Dwight
order deer urine over the internet,
so it evens out.
So I got the Save The Date.
- Yeah ?
- Yeah, pretty stationary.
- Oh, thanks.
- I didn't get mine yet.
There are a few people
I decided not to invite.
And that might make things
kind of awkward, but...
it's my wedding.
And I don't want anyone there
who has called me a hussy.
Episode 21 - Season 2
Conflict resolution
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation: Catch-22 Team
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
Yes, thanks. Fantastic Sam's.
Adult cut plus.
Comes with a shampoo and blow dry.
We're doing I.D. photos today.
Gotta represent.
On or off ?
Off.
What is on your face ?
Is that a disguise ?
Excuse me.
Clown paint.
I.D. badges are long overdue.
Security in this office park
is a joke.
Last year I came to work with
my spud gun in a duffel bag.
I sat at my desk all day
with a rifle that shoots potatoes
at 60 pounds per square inch.
Can you imagine if I was deranged ?
That's a nice tie.
Thank you. That is...
- who makes that ?
- I don't know.
Do you mind if I wear that
for the photo ?
Let's... let's keep our clothes.
It's like child abuse!
I say, if Jesus saw that,
he'd freak out!
He'd freak out, Toby.
I mean, on so many levels!
And I'm supposed to work there!
- I'm supposed to...
- What's the deal... e... o ?
Just letting Oscar vent a little.
We would use the break room,
but the photographer's back there.
- What's the problem ?
- Angela.
It's just a little dispute over
a poster in their workspace.
- Since Christmas.
- So what, you're having a little spat ?
I forget, are you guys dating ?
Michael, can I talk to you
for a second, please ?
Here's how I usually handle this.
All I do is listen.
You know, these things just have
a way of working themselves out.
It's like if you write someone
a letter when you're really angry.
They say to keep it in your drawer
for a couple days,
and then you just never
end up sending it.
What do you know about
conflict resolution ?
Your answer to everything
is to get divorced, so...
- Okay.
- Okay, what ?
That was a right decision
for me and my marriage.
Well, that's not gonna fly here
because in this office
it is till death do us part.
Assuming that we don't get
downsized.
Pam,
would you get Angela and meet us
in the conference room, please ?
A Mediator's Toolchest.
Okay, well, before we get started,
you should know
that there are five
different styles of conflict.
My Shaolin Temple style
defeats your Monkey Style.
Can we go ?
I have a lot of work to do.
This is important.
- The first style is "lose-lose".
- What's the next one ?
Just, hold on, please.
Okay, if we do lose-lose,
neither of you gets what you want.
Do you understand ?
You... you would both lose.
Now, I need to ask you,
do you want to pursue
a lose-lose negotiation ?
Can we just skip to whatever
number five is ? Win-win or whatever ?
Win-win, is number four,
and number five is win-win-win.
The important difference here is
with win-win-win, we all win.
Me too. I win for having successfully
mediated a conflict at work.
Okay, so this is the disputed poster.
Now, one at a time,
I want you to express your feelings
using "I" emotion language and
no judging, or "you" statements.
I got this poster for Christmas, and
I feel I want to see it every day.
It makes me feel like the babies
are the true artists,
and God has a really
cute sense of humor.
Come on, seriously. That ?
I don't like looking at it.
It's creepy and in bad taste,
and it's just offensive to me.
It makes me think of the horrible,
frigid stage mothers
who forced the babies into it.
It's kitsch.
It's the opposite of art.
It destroys art. It destroys souls.
This is so much more offensive
to me than hard-core porno.
- I'm talking about the kind...
- Oh my God.
Let's see if we can't just brainstorm
and find some creative alternatives
- that are win-win.
- Win
Yes. Thank you, Pam.
How about, Angela makes the poster
into a t-shirt which Oscar wears.
That way he can never see it,
and whenever she looks at Oscar,
she can see it. Win-win-win.
- No.
- That's... no.
Well, brainstorm. Own the solution.
- How about I leave it up ?
- How about she takes it down ?
How about Angela can keep it up
on Tuesdays and Thursdays.
Okay, that is called a compromise.
And it is style three,
and it is not ideal.
To sum up, win-win,
make the poster into a t-shirt.
Win-lose, take the poster down.
Compromise, Tuesdays and Thursdays.
And the answer is...
make the poster into a t-shirt.
- Win-win.
- Win.
- Fine.
- But...
It is done!
- No, you're all good.
- Great.
Hey, Angela.
I didn't have your zip code.
Thanks.
It was hand-delivered.
but I did get a Save The Date
after all.
It's not my taste.
You solved it.
We can, throw that one out.
Are those all the other complaints ?
I would like to see those please.
- I can't do that.
- You can't do that, huh ?
Now you and I have a conflict.
I order you to give me that file.
That...
There! No more conflict.
I had to use the win-lose on that.
It was not pretty.
All right. Is that it ?
It's all Dwight's.
Every Friday at 4:00,  I have
a standing appointment with Dwight
for him to file a grievance
against Jim.
I tell him that I'm sending them
to a special file in New York.
That box is the special file
in New York.
Oh, God. All right.
Why do I have to do everything ?
Are you sure ?
Oh, he's sure. Just shoot.
This, is from Kevin.
He says Stanley uses his
Miracle Whip without asking.
Meredith complains that everyone
talks too loud in the morning
and the lights are too bright.
Creed...
Creed is sick of looking
at the redhead all day
and wants a seat
facing the receptionist.
Nice.
You will notice that not one
of these complaints is against me.
Actually, I have a separate folder
for complaints against Michael.
This is January through March
of this year.
How many of you have at one time
gone to Toby to complain
about another employee ?
And, did you get what you wanted,
or were you merely listened to,
you forget about your problem,
and you move on ?
That is outrageous!
I love this place...
and it pains me to see
all of the negativity...
festering...
Today we are going to get
everything out of these files
and into the open,
where it can be resolved.
All right, how about
the Phyllis-Angela dispute ?
- You already did me.
- That's what she said.
The thing is, Angela,
you are in here an awful lot.
You have complained about
everybody in the office,
except Dwight, which is odd
because  everyone else
has had run in with Dwight.
Toby, by the way,
what does "redacted" mean ?
There is a file full of complaints
in here marked "redacted."
It just means whoever complained
came to me later and withdrew it,
so I took their name off.
There were a bunch of complaints
about Dwight
that were put in the redacted file
about six months ago.
Wait! If someone has
a problem with me,
why would they withdraw it
six months ago ?
Let's move on. I volunteer.
Did anyone have a problem with me ?
All right, Pamela. Come on down!
Let's do it. And... okay.
Just one complaint.
Actually, it has been withdrawn.
So that is no help to us. Next.
Wait, what did it say ?
"Does she have to plan her wedding
on office time ?"
"Shouldn't she do that at home ?"
Who else ?
Why don't we just warm up first ?
Warm up emotionally, all right ?
I have this kind of big secret
about Angela.
And I've been really nice to her
and I haven't told anyone, and...
what the hell ?!
Here is a Kelly complaint.
"Ryan never returns my calls."
Ah, join the club.
My voice mail's real spotty...
sometimes.
I didn't file a complaint.
I was just talking.
To your HR representative.
To my friend, I thought.
I want that withdrawn.
Fine, I'll take your name off.
So no one will know.
Making progress.
- Dwight tried to kiss me.
- What ?
And I didn't tell anyone 'cause I'm
not really sure how I feel about it.
That is not true.
Redact it. Redact it!
Well, I'm not actually making
a formal complaint.
I just really think
we should talk about it.
Okay, question.
When a name is withdrawn,
does that also apply to the permanent
misbehavior file in New York ?
Sure.
Stanley.
Thanks for ratting me out.
I didn't do it.
I find that hard to believe
considering you have problems
with every single person
in this entire office
except Bobblehead Joe.
Someone complained that
the men's room is "whites only".
Stanley, you know that's not true.
I didn't say that.
Then why is there a picture
of a white man on the door ?
Okay, Phyllis. You complained
that Angela is giving you dirty looks.
And you tried to get off
the party planning committee.
No, I never said any such thing.
Angela and I are close.
And... also, Phyllis, Stanley says
that you cry too much,
and that bugs him.
Stanley and I are close too.
- We sit close.
- O... kay.
Just take it.
I can't believe Angela.
I went against my better judgment,
and I gave her a Save The Date.
And now it turns out
she complained about me to Toby.
Well, it was redacted.
Look, if she wants an invite,
maybe she's just trying to be friends.
Don't take her side.
Well, what does Roy
think about everything ?
I don't know. I try not to bother him
about this kind of stuff.
You mean like your thoughts
and your feelings ?
I know you keep
saying it's your space,
even though there's no assigned
parking, but I keep forgetting.
- Yes, that's the problem.
- I guess so.
Okay, well, all settled then.
I don't like you.
Okay, Ryan, you told Toby that
Creed has a distinct old man smell ?
I know exactly
what he's talking about.
I sprout mung beans on a damp
paper towel in my desk drawer.
Very nutritious.
But they smell like death.
All right, Kevin. You are accused of
making sexually suggestive
remarks to Angela
that made her feel uncomfortable.
Solution.
Angela, you are to make
sexually suggestive remarks
to Kevin that will make him
uncomfortable.
I accept your decision.
You know what, Dwight ?
Maybe we should get our photo I.D.
taken together.
That doesn't make any sense.
Well, it saves time, you know.
'Cause we could just meet
in the parking lot every morning.
Walk in together. Perfect.
- Smile.
- No.
I never smile if I can help it.
Showing one's teeth is a
submission signal in primates.
When someone smiles at me,
all I see is a chimpanzee
begging for its life.
This came out really well.
There you go.
This is humongous.
am not a security threat.
And my middle name is Kurt. Not Fart.
What did I write ?
I have another complaint
for Jim's permanent file.
Talk to Michael.
I gave him the box.
What box ?
- But I didn't report your snoring...
- Wednesdays, tearful. Tuesdays...
Four years of malfeasance
unreported. This cannot stand.
- Okay. Calm down.
- No! You calm down.
Whose side is Toby on ?
Whose side are you on ?!
- Him or me ?
- Stop.
Him or me ?
I cannot work with Jim anymore.
- Either he goes, or I go.
- Dwight...
- You choose!
- Stop...
One of us is out of here
by the end of today.
I am not bluffing!
Do the right thing here, Michael.
Okay, I have served you
loyally for years.
I deserve this, you know I do!
You know your I.D. says
you're a security threat ?
You have 'till 5:00.
Oh, look, Jim. There's a sales
manager position open in Stamford.
Want me to call Jan
and tell her you're interested ?
I could put in a good word for you.
'Cause I'll still be working here.
Transfer, transfer, everybody.
Transfer, transfer, transfer!
You two, in the conference room,
with me.
Nobody leaves until
we work this out.
Cage match.
Cage matches ? Yeah, they work.
How could they not work ?
If they didn't work, everybody
would still be in the cage.
Okay, so, Dwight, in your own words.
"Someone replaced all my pens
and pencils with crayons."
"I suspect Jim Halpert."
"Everyone has called me
Dwayne all day."
"I think Jim Halpert paid them to."
Yes, five bucks each.
And it was totally worth it.
"This morning I found a bloody glove
in my desk drawer"
"and Jim Halpert tried to convince me
I committed murder."
"I think he may be the real murderer."
"Jim Halpert said there was
an abandoned infant"
"in the woman's room.
When I went to save the child,"
"I saw Meredith on the can."
Gaaad.
"This morning I knocked myself
in the head with the phone."
That actually took a while.
I had to put more an more
nickels into his handset,
'till he got used to the weight,
and then I just...took 'em all out.
"Everytime I typed my name
it said 'Diapers'."
Just a simple macro.
You know, these actually don't
sound that funny one after another.
But he does deserve it, though.
"By the end of the day,"
"my desk  was about
two feet closer to the copier."
Yeah, I just moved it an inch every
time he went to the bathroom.
And that's how I spent
my entire day that day.
The Japanese have this thing
called shiatsu massage
where they dig into
your body very hard.
And it is very painful.
And apparently, some people throw up.
But the next day they feel great.
I've never had one.
They sound awful.
Maybe Stamford would be cool.
It's a good market.
Higher volume.
Maybe we should both go.
I have a girlfriend.
Sure you do, Dwight, sure.
Hey, there's like, 300 more of these.
Let's get to them later.
So you're gonna transfer Jim or not ?
Maybe, I haven't decided yet.
- Let's get to work.
- I want an answer by tomorrow.
Actually, tomorrow's not good.
How about later in the week ?
Fine.
Good. Okay.
Wait. How about a group
picture while you're here ?
I can't. I only get reimbursed
for the I.D. photos.
Well, that's, what,
a computer camera, right ?
- You mean, digital ?
- Yeah, it'll take, like, two seconds.
20 bucks.
All right. Everybody, come on.
Group photo for the newsletter.
You gotta be kidding.
Come on, everybody.
Come on, let's go. Creed, Kevin,
Oscar, andale, let's go.
One, two, three, smile.
- Try to smile.
- We resolved a lot today, everybody.
Think happy thoughts.
Alright, I'm just gonna take it
on three whether you smile or not.
Good, let's check that out.
All right. One more.
We'll take one more.
- That'll be another 20.
- What ?
Angela, I want to talk to you
about something.
- What ?
- No, Pam, don't.
- It's about the Save The Date.
- Pam it wasn't her.
What ?
I'm the one who complained
about you.
Alright, come on, one more time!
I didn't know that Toby
was gonna write it down.
I was just venting.
You know, it was one day.
That's terrible.
And I took it right back.
It was like...
Let's pay Mr...
Oh, dear.
Price gouger.
We can do this. Come on, everybody.
All right. Here we go.
It was really hard getting
a good picture of 15 people.
He would not give me a discount.
And eight tries added up.
One, two...
Didn't say three, did I ?
But I'm sort of an expert
at Photoshop.
So it turned out fine in the end.
When people work together
there is going to be conflict.
You can't outrun your problems.
Hey, Pam, it's Jim. I have
a doctor's appointment in the city.
So I probably won't be in
'till the late afternoon.
Just thought I'd let you know.
Okay, bye.
- Okay, Jan will see you now.
- Oh, thanks.
And that is why the idea of a cage
match is so universally appealing.
But here's the thing
about cage matches.
Sometimes you have to open the cage.
And that is something that
Toby will never understand.
www.tvsubtitles.net