Okay.
Well...
I did not get the job in New-York.
But I got the real prize...
domestic bliss.
Jan made me breakfast this morning.
Well, she bought the milk.
It's soy.
This is why I do it.
That's what I have to come home to.
She probably won't be up
for a few hours.
This is going be a very good year.
Very good.
Jan is at home.
Jim is back.
My protégé Ryan is at corporate.
Good stuff.
Andy and Dwight
are rocking the sales team.
I feel very blessed.
T
Tr
Tra
Tran
Trans
Transc
Transcr
Transcri
Transcrip
Transcript
Transcript :
Transcript : S
Transcript : Sw
Transcript : SwS
Transcript : SwSu
Transcript : SwSub
S
Sy
Transcript : SwSub
Syn
Sync
Transcript : SwSub
Synch
Synchr
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro
Synchro :
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : D
Synchro : Da
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : Dar
Synchro : DarK
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : DarKs
Synchro : DarKsh
Episode 4x01
"FUN RUN"
Generally it's not a good idea
to click on any internet offers
that you haven't requested.
What was the exact offer?
It was for a...
video.
Yeah, well, what kind of video?
A cebrity sex tape.
Really?
What kind of celebrity?
- Not relevant.
- How much you paid for it?
- You paid for it?
- It all happened so fast!
I broke up with Karen
after the job interview.
And, uh...
It was a little awkward
when she came back from the city.
She told me very clearly that just
because we were broken up doesn't mean
that she was going anywhere, because...
she had worked
really hard for her career.
But the next day, her desk was empty.
And as for me
and my current romantic life...
I, uh...
I'm single now and looking.
So if you know anybody...
Jim and I went to dinner a few times
when he got back from New York.
I talked him through his breakup.
It's really nice
to be good friends again.
Are you kidding me?
Pam and Jim are totally hooking up.
All they do is smile.
They're just keeping it a secret.
Right?
I don't know.
There is no evidence of intimacy.
They've been in remarkably good moods.
Could other things.
Are you kidding me?
And sunday, I'm thinking of going
to that flea market at the drive-in.
Oh, that sounds fun.
I'm mountain biking on sunday in...
montage mountain.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Well, have fun with that.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I have some bad news.
Meredith was hit by a car.
- What?
- Where?
It happened this morning
in the parking lot.
I took her to the hospital.
And the doctors tried to save her life.
They did the best that they could.
And she is going to be okay.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you have to phrase it like that?
- So she's really going to be fine?
- Yes. She has a slight...
pelvical fracture.
But people have survived far worse.
Thank God you were there.
Yeah.
Did you see who did it?
No need.
We can just check the security tapes.
Yeah,
kind of a good news/bad news there.
I was able to be on the scene so quickly
because I was in the car that hit her.
Who was driving?
Oh, Michael.
One day Michael came in complaining
about a speed bump on the highway.
I wonder who he ran over then.
- It's only Meredith.
- Yeah, it's only Meredith.
Thank God.
But did you see
the way they looked at me?
Like I was a murderer or something.
- Why did you it?
- It was an accident.
- Was she talking back?
- No.
Just got sick of that face?
Did she owe you money?
Is this downsizing?
Did she spurn your advances?
Hey, guys.
We're all gonna visit Meredith at lunch.
And we're kicking in $5 for flowers.
Who's we?
You and Jim?
No, me and Stanley and Phyllis so far.
I bet Jim goes too.
I haven't asked him yet.
- I bet you ask.
- I was planning on it.
I bet you were.
Angela?
Are you coming?
I can't.
Sprinkles is sick.
She's been sick for some time.
Thank you for asking.
No one asks about Sprinkles.
I have to give her her meds,
I have to pet her.
And who will she eat lunch with?
Can't your other cats keep her company?
There's bad blood.
Jealousies, cliques.
Angela, you're the chairman
of the party planning committee.
I shouldn't even be planning this.
It's your job.
All right!
- My lord, my lieg.
- Yes, Michael?
So Ryan got promoted to corporate
where he is a little fish in a big pond.
Whereas back here in Scranton,
I'm still top dog
in a fairly large pond.
So whos the real boss?
The dog or a fish?
So I need a little treat for the gang.
Something to win their affections back.
Back?
Why is that, Michael?
Well, I ran down Meredith in my car.
- Did you do this on purpose?
- No, I was being negligent.
But she's in the hospital,
she's fine,
recovering nicely.
Tiny little crack in her pelvis.
- But she will...
- It happened on company property?
Yes.
It was on company property
with company property, so...
Double jeopardy, we are fine.
I don't think you understand
how jeopardy works.
Oh, right, I'm sorry.
What is "we're fine"?
People keep calling me a "wunderkind."
I don't even know what that means.
I mean, I know what it means.
It means very successful for your age.
So I guess it makes sense, but...
It's a weird word.
- Hey, D.
- Hey monkey, what's up?
Can you do me a favor?
Go to my place
and give Sprinkles her medicine?
Sure.
I have to visit the alkie.
Check to see if she's faking.
If a car hit me,
it wouldn't crack my pelvis.
You know what?
I bet she cracked it at home.
Jumped in front of the car
to get some worker's comp.
I wouldn't put it past her.
- So what do you need me to do?
- I wrote it out.
There's a diabetes shot.
Roll the insulin in your hands,
don't shake it.
She gets an ace inhibitor with her meal.
But put her right in front of the dish,
or her cataracts won't let her see it.
Mix one capsule of omega fatty acid
in with her kidney medicine.
And you wanna give that to her
15 minutes after she's eaten.
And there's a fungal cream, because
she has this infection under her tail.
So you're gonna have to lift her tail
and put the cream right at the base.
Okay, I have an announcement.
You pushed Darryl out the window?
- You shot Dwight?
- No. No, that is not funny.
I love my employees.
Even though
I hit one of you with my car.
For which I take full responsibility.
Look, I'm just trying to take
everybody's mind
off of this unavoidable tragedy
and on to more positive things.
So I thought we should plant a tree.
Oh, good.
That means we don't have to work.
We're leaving for the hospital at 1:00.
So, like, a freedom tree.
- I can take 3 people.
- I can also take 3 people.
- Separate cars.
- Pam?
We'll get a card at the hospital,
and we'll sign it outside her room.
Sales people can go later in the day.
Hourly workers can go at lunch.
Okay, good, good. So we'll just
all go down there together at lunch.
- Excellent.
- I was thin...
- Good work, Pam.
- But if you...
All right, since im the boss,
I will drive as well. Who wants shotgun?
You can't be serious.
You ran a woman over this morning.
Everybody inside the car
was fine, Stanley!
Guess what?
I have flaws.
What are they?
Oh, I don't know.
I sing in the shower.
Sometimes,
I spend too much time volunteering.
Occasionally,
I'll hit somebody with my car.
So sue me.
No, don't sue me.
That's the opposite of the point
that I am trying to make.
I hate hospitals.
In my mind, they are...
associated with sickness.
She looks like an angel.
She looks awful.
No... okay. She always looks
like that, it was not my fault.
I think she's awake.
She's in the coma.
I brought all your friends
from the office.
- At the same time.
- Yep.
- Hello, Meredith.
- This is weird.
Brought you some balloons.
Why don't we...
Here you go.
Tie these up, cheer up your tubes.
Oh, for God's sake.
- Nurse!
- No, don't bother the nurse.
Just put it back in.
I am going to be sick.
I'm going to puke.
I wouldn't...
I wouldn't worry about it.
- Don't touch it.
- What are you doing? Just gimme that.
Thanks.
Does it hurt terribly?
No, it's not too bad.
They have me on a lot of painkillers.
Really?
What kind, codeine?
Vicodin?
Percocet?
Fentanyl?
Oxycontin?
- Palladone?
- I have no idea.
Well, it was really great of all of you
to come and visit me at the same time.
I'll see you guys at the office.
Okay, wait up, wait up, guys.
Guys, guys, hold on a sec.
You know what I was thinking
might be sort of fun?
Is if you forgave me...
in front of everybody.
I'm not gonna do that.
'Cause you know what they say
in the bible about forgiveness?
Forgiveness...
is next to godliness.
No, that's not...
- You cracked my pelvis.
- Look, I jus...
I don't understand
what is preventing you
from laughing this off
and giving me a big hug.
You're not forgiven.
Come on.
Do I need to be liked?
Absolutely not.
I like to be liked.
I enjoy being liked.
I have to be liked.
But it's not, like, this...
compulsive need to be liked.
Like my need to be praised.
Hey.
hey, monkey.
Any problems?
Well, you left the TV on.
And your cat is dead.
- What?!
- Sparkles, the white one, is dead.
Sprinkles.
That was the sick one, right?
But I thought she had more time.
Did she look...
When you saw her, how was she looking?
Really dead.
Like a, just a dead cat.
So...
Hey, come on.
Don't be sad.
Just...
Okay?
- She's in a better place.
- All right.
Actually, the place that she's in
is the freezer.
Because of the odor.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay, you know what?
Everybody, let's just get over
the whole Meredith thing.
She cracked her pelvis.
A tiny, little crack.
And she's gonna be fine.
So let just...
Michael, Angela's cat died.
Sprinkles?
I'm sorry, Angela.
Man, what a day, huh?
How could it get any worse?
Her computer crashes with the porn,
and then Meredith with the accident,
and then...
Sprinkles!
God!
That's three things.
I'll tell you what's going on.
This office is cursed.
And we need to do something about it.
Well, I am taking responsibility.
An it's up to me
to get rid of the curse
that hit Meredith with my car.
I'm not supersticious, but...
I'm... I am a little sticious.
Did anyone do anything
involving an indian burial ground?
- Like what?
- Like park on it.
Or dig up a body.
Toby?
Do you have anything you wanna tell us?
No, I did not violate
an indian burial ground.
In fact, I had some good luck recently.
Alfredo's pizza picked my business card
out of the basket, so...
I get a week of free pies.
- That's cool.
- Yeah.
Perfect.
So our tragedy is your good luck.
Satan.
Sprinkles never hurt a soul.
God, in your infinite wisdom,
how can you do this?
She wasn't ready.
She had so much left to accomplish.
It is only a cat.
You never...
You don't like them.
Cats do not provide
milk or wool or meat.
- Dwight, you haven't seen Meredith?
- No, I have not.
Well, I think you should go
to the hospital and pay your respects.
I do not respect her.
But I will go.
All right.
I would now like to talk about
each of your
individual religious beliefs.
Oh, Michael,
you can't ask about religious beliefs.
Satan is the master of lies.
Everything he says is the opposite.
All right, well, then you can ask
about religious beliefs.
Thank you for the permission.
Psych!
Alright, let's just go around the room,
and tell me what you believe in.
- Catholic.
- Okay.
- Presbyterian.
- Oh, me too.
- For real?
- Same religion.
I'm a lutheran, and bob is a unitarian.
It keeps things spicy.
That's why we're cursed.
I've been involved in a number of cults,
both as a leader and a follower.
You have more fun as a follower
but you make more money as a leader.
Kelly, you are hindu.
So you believe in Buddha.
That's buddhists.
Are you sure?
No.
What are you?
Well, if you're gonna reduce my identity
to my religion, then I'm sikh.
But I also like hip-hop and NPR.
And I'm restoring a 1967 corvette
in my spare time.
Okay.
So one sikh,
and...
As a farmer,
I know that when an animal is sick,
sometimes the right thing to do
is to put it out of its misery.
With the electricity
used to keep Meredith alive,
we could power a small fan for two days.
You tell me what's unethical.
Blink once
if you want me to pull the plug.
Don't pull any plugs.
How are you doing, miss Palmer?
- Better.
- Excellent.
Are you a doctor or a male nurse?
I'm an intern, which makes me a doctor.
Her chart doesn't indicate
that she had a hysterectomy,
but she did,
or at least, she got time off for one.
So that is where her uterus went.
Your last tetanus shot was when you were
bitten by a bat a few months ago?
Yes. Dwight here trapped it
in a bag against my head.
Just doing my job.
You also were recently bitten
by a raccoon?
And a rat.
Separate occasions.
Spend your whole life
trying to get people to like you,
and then you run over one person
with your car.
And it's not even
one of the popular ones.
Everybody gets on your case.
Doesn't make any sense.
God is dead.
If there was a god,
then Ryan and I would be married by now.
Maybe believing in god was a mistake.
What did people believe in before?
The sun?
Maybe there's some sort of animal
that we could make a sacrifice to.
Like...
a giant buffalo.
Or some sort of monster,
like something with the body of a walrus
with the head of...
a sea lion.
Or something with the body of an egret
with the head of a meerkat.
Or just...
the head of a monkey with...
the antlers of a reindeer.
With the body of...
a porcupine.
I will do some research.
- Okay.
- I can help you with that.
So just to be safe,
they are giving her the rabies vaccine.
God, rabies?
I was in the hospital room with her.
How contagious is that?
Is that like an STD?
- No. You gotta be bitten by something.
- This place is so cursed.
Actually, the doctor said she was lucky,
'cause the only way to beat rabies
is to start treatment
before the symptoms set in.
Lockjaw.
I know a lot of you
are very upset with me
for endangering Meredith's life
by hitting her
with my car.
But it may make you feel a little bit
better to know that before that happened
Dwight endangered her life
by putting a garbage bag over her head
and it had a bat in it.
Six of one, really.
Turns out, Meredith
has been exposed to rabies.
Which is, like, ten times worse
than a little crack in your pelvis.
Thanks to me, she went to the hospital,
and that saved her life.
Curse is broken.
Curse is broken, people!
Oh, there is a god!
And he has a plan for us after all.
So go home,
get some rest.
Very, very good work today.
Got a lot accomplished.
Is there a god?
If not, what are all these churches for?
And who is Jesus' dad?
Oh, well.
If they aren't together now,
then they probably never will be.
I thought they'd be good together.
Like PB & J.
Pam Beesly and Jim.
What a waste.
I told you I'm not dating anyone.
And even if I was,
I don't think it's anyone's business.
I mean,
when I do fall in love,
like, when it's for real,
the last person
I'm gonna talk about it to
is a camera crew or my coworkers.
Almost marrying Roy Anderson
was as close to Pamela Anderson
as I ever wanna be.
Trust me,
when I fall in love, you'll know.
Michael Scott's Dunder Mifflin Scranton
Meredith Palmer memorial
celebrity rabies awareness fun run race
for the cure, this is Pam.
Pro-am.
Pro-am race for the...
They hung up.
A woman shouldn't have to be hit by a
car to learn that she may have rabies.
But that is where we are in America.
And that does not sit right with me.
And that is why I'm hosting a fun
run race for the cure for rabies...
To raise awareness of the fact
that there is a cure for rabies.
A disease that has been
largely eradicated in the U.S.
But not very many people know that.
No, rabies.
Babies would be a good idea.
Can I put you down for a dime?
Hi, Stankley,
how many sponsors so far?
Zero.
Come on, man.
You gotta step it up.
It's for a good cause.
Jan called this morning
and pledged $500.
Isn't that your money?
That is for a good cause.
- Phyllis, how the rabies quilt coming?
- Oh, it's coming.
Oh, look at that! Three.
Way to honor Meredith, Phyllis.
You can't make me run.
It is not a real charity.
It's stupid, Michael
and I'm not gonna do it.
You didn't run for me
when I thought I had skin cancer.
I know that you're probably scared of
people seeing your fat legs in shorts.
Well, back in olden times,
a large, fat person like this
was a person of power.
A person who had money,
who could buy food.
A person of respect,
like the regional manager of the day.
Whereas someone athletic
and trim like myself
was somebody who worked in the fields,
and I was a peasant.
I just don't wanna run.
I didn't bring my sneakers
or my clothes.
You're gonna have to run
or you're gonna be in a lot of trouble.
It is not olden times anymore.
I'm petrified of nipple chafing.
Once it starts, is a vicious circle.
You have sensitive nipples, they chafe.
So they become more sensitive.
So they chafe more.
So...
I take precautions.
Hey, Angela.
I'm sorry about your cat.
This is Sprinkles.
She was my best friend.
I kept her
going through countless ailments.
I asked Dwight Schrute to feed her once,
and she is now deceased.
This is Halloween last year.
Just a couple of kittens.
Out on the town.
I'm having relationship problems.
And since you're always having
relationship problems,
I thought you could give me some advice.
What's wrong?
I have this crazy thought
that I know is crazy...
that maybe Dwight killed my cat.
When I got home,
Sprinkles' body was in the freezer
where Dwight said he left her.
But all my bags of frozen french fries
had been clawed to shreds!
Something's not right.
The vet's doing an autopsy.
Angela, I'm sorry.
Did Roy ever killed one of your cats?
I'm more of a dog person.
So what's your strategy for this race?
I'm gonna start fast.
Then I'm gonna run fast in the middle.
Then I'm gonna end fast.
- Why won't more people do that?
- 'Cause they're stupid.
What?
Oh, um, no, that's not...
- I mean, that wasn't...
- Yeah, that was, um...
I mean, I can see
how it would seem a bit like we, uh...
How it looks like, um...
But nowadays,
you can edit anything, right?
I mean, you can edit anything to...
Look like, um, anything.
- So...
- Yeah, I gave him a ride home
- because...
- Right.
We're dating.
There it is.
Uh, yeah.
We haven't told anybody,
but it's going really great.
Right?
It is going really great.
Shut up!
You're taking this out on me,
but I was only the messenger.
Oh, really?
You'll feel better after the 5k.
Exercise is good for depression.
I am not depressed.
I'm in grief!
We have raised almost $700,
most of it from me and Jan.
When do they put that
on the giant check?
Or is that something
that we write in later?
Well, a giant check costs
about $200 to make up.
I have a print shop standing by, but...
What do you think, Michael?
That's over 25% of our funds.
It's... a tough decision.
I always imagined it with a giant check.
Yeah, I mean, I personally am
definitely on board for the giant check.
Giant check it is.
I don't know. On the other hand, it does
leave less money for bat birth control.
Bat birth control.
This money's going to bat birth control,
right? That's what you told me.
You didn't contribute very much.
I was also hoping to hand
the giant check to a rabies doctor.
- How's that going?
- Not well.
A doctor won't come out
to collect a check for $700.
Or $500 if we go with the giant check.
- Which we are.
- And also...
There is no such thing
as a rabies doctor.
How about a rabies nurse?
- I don't think so.
- You know what?
I've actually seen ads for nurses
that you can hire by the hour.
For parties and bachelor events.
That's possible.
look into that.
Great, it's gonna cost 200 bucks.
And actually, more...
with tips.
Maybe we should skip the ceremony
and just set up
a college fund for Meredith's son.
Have you met that kid?
I'm not going to college.
5k means five kilometers,
not 5,000 miles.
Come in.
- My god!
- What're you doing?!
- You said, "come in!"
- No, I didn't. Just...
- Oh, my god.
- Please, get out.
So I closed the door
but the image of his...
- Baguette.
- dangling participle
still burned in my eyes.
I can imagine.
Come in.
May I enter the room?
Yes.
Or "come in."
See how I did that?
That's the way you should enter a room.
You knock and wait for the all clear.
You couldn't undress in the men's room?
Yes. But I have an office,
so why would I do that?
On average, how many hours a day
do you spend naked in your office?
- Just ballpark.
- European offices are always naked.
- They're so not.
- Besides, my shirt covered most of it.
I only saw where it ended.
- Gross.
- That's not gross!
It's the human body.
What is your problem?
Pam, you're an artist, right?
Think of me as one of your models.
Okay, you know what?
I don't want this to detract from what
we really need to think about today.
It's not fair to people with rabies.
And that's the point, right?
Okay.
Let's go have some fun all right.
They say if you're nervous around
someone, you should picture them naked.
I do not recommend this strategy.
Try picturing them with more clothes on.
Or a funny coat.
I'm sorry, is this a working office?
And not a french beach?
Okay, name, please?
Creed Bratton, 75+ division.
- You're over 75 years old?
- 82 november 1st.
- How much is the prize money?
- There's no prize money.
Well, is any of this real?
Check that out.
Look at me, I'm Toby!
I'm stretching.
I know what l'm doing.
Why is he even here?
So I heard
that you were peeping on Michael.
What?
No, it was not...
I don't know what your deal is,
but he's mine, okay?
So hands off.
Okay, everybody, listen up!
Thank you for coming.
Before we get started,
I want to say a few words
about this deadly disease called rabies.
And I'd like you to take a look
into the face of rabies.
That should scare you.
It scares me.
You people need to educate yourselves.
Meth: three americans every year
die from rabies.
Fact: four americans every year
How many of you
know someone who has been afflicted
or affected by rabies?
Show of hands.
One, two, three...
too many to count.
It is truly the silent killer.
No, it is the foaming, barking killer.
And it is something that...
Darryl!
- What're you doing?
- I give him a peanut.
No, don't give him...
Just...
Did you...
hear anything I said?
- Look how happy he is.
- He's happy because he's insane.
That's a perfect example
of the kind of awareness
we need to generate.
Where's the nurse?
- This is the reason we're here.
- Hello, Michael.
Oh, hey, I know you.
- Elizabeth, right?
- Yeah.
Very cool you went back
and got your degree.
I would like you to accept this check
for $340
made out to Science.
Make sure that
that gets into the right hands.
You got it?
Okay.
Fettuccini Alfredo.
Time to carbo load.
Just remember, folks, it's not
about winning, it is about finishing.
On your marks!
Get set!
On your left!
You're doing great, Michael.
Look at you go!
That's my boss!
- Yeah, baby!
- I'm fast.
I'm very fast.
I'm like Forrest Gump,
except...
I am not an idiot.
Oh, yes, I will work out today.
I will work out a way
to avoid running for a stupid cause.
I've walked 2 marathons.
Pretty sure I can handle a 5k.
The key is drafting
to eliminate wind resistance.
Yeah.
Oh, we're in last place.
- Oh, would you look at that?
- Darn it.
Water!
Water.
- Water, babe?
- No, no water for me.
Not while rabies causes fear of water.
Solidarity!
Michael, that's irrational!
Rabies victims...
have to live
with an irrational hatred of water
their entire lives.
So...
least I could do.
Oh, god.
My nipples!
It's starting.
- Can we get another round?
- Okay.
Thanks.
So we've got what?
Another 20 minutes?
More or less.
That fettuccini...
is hitting my stomach like a rock.
You got nothing to worry about.
I put imodium in Toby's coffee
before the race.
Excellent!
Simpsons!
Wait, imodium or ex-lax?
I'm making great time.
Usually I have to take a bathroom break
halfway through a race like this, but...
not today.
Ooh, an estate sale.
Want to go in?
I'm really committed to winning.
Okay, but what if I told you
that all the money you spend here
goes to preventing
a disease already cured.
- Yes.
- That's what I thought.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Let's do some good.
You have reached
the offices of Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
Currently the entire staff is out
doing the Michael scott D.M.S.M.P.M.C.
Rabies awarness pro-am fun run race...
For the cure.
Leave a message.
Oh, god.
Oh, Alfredo sauce.
I'm getting a stitch.
God!
Watch the nipples, Kevin!
Back off me.
You're feeling better?
No.
Well, you look cute as a button.
You've worked up quite a sweat.
The vet's removing
Sprinkles' organs right now
and sending them to the lab.
- I am a farmer, Angela.
- What does that mean?
When a farmer sees
an animal that is in pain,
that has no quality of life,
that has no utility,
a farmer does what city folk
don't have the stomach to do.
You did kill her!
I sang her her favorite songs.
You put her in my freezer!
It was beautiful
and gentle and respectful.
I fed her antihistamines
and she gradually fell asleep.
She barfed them up in the freezer
and tried to get out.
I'm not responsible for that...
- It's nothing!
- I'm robbing her!
- It's nothing! It's fine!
How could you do that
without telling me?
I thought I was helping you.
I expected a hug.
I took care of that cat
the best way I knew how.
Cat heaven is a beautiful place,
but you don't get there
if you're euthanized.
I know a great taxidermist.
I'll pay to have her stuff.
Well, he's not great,
but he's pretty good.
You don't understand.
Take bat bites seriously.
Don't get bit.
Or we can have her buried out
at the east field by mother.
- Huh, Angela?
- Don't touch me, Dwight.
You like it?
It's kind of designy and cool.
It was $8.
Oh, and I get to carry it.
And the winner is Toby Flenderson!
Have a seat.
I'll write it down.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Like five kilometers from the office.
He couldn't have made it circle?
I am not going to finish.
I can't beat rabies.
Nobody can beat rabies.
Rabies has been around
for a thousand years.
I was a fool
to think that I could beat it.
- Pictures of the dog all around.
- Yeah, probably...
What are you doing here?
Did you come back for us or...
I can't finish.
I feel so weak.
I just...
- You're probably dehydrated.
- What do you want me to do, Jim?
A glass of water would be a start.
There are people...
all over the world with all sorts
of problems and afflictions
and diseases.
They're deformed
and they're abnormal, and...
they're illiterate and ugly.
Symphonies don't have any money.
Public TV is bust.
I can't do anything about it.
I can't, you know...
There's just one of me,
and there's thousand of them.
And rabies wins.
You are a downer.
We were having a pretty nice day.
I'm still having a nice day.
- You are?
- Yeah.
Hey, Michael, look at this lamp.
$8.
That's a good deal.
And Michael, you don't have rabies.
And chances are
you're not gonna get it anytime soon.
So... you don't really have
to think about it too much.
Pam, if everybody felt that way,
nothing would get done.
Yeah, but there's other better people
out there who are helping.
You just don't think I am capable
of making a difference.
I know you, Michael.
I saw you naked.
You don't...
You don't know me.
You've just seen my penis.
I can make a difference.
Remember, I'm the one
who started this whole thing off
by hitting Meredith with my car.
And I owe it to her
to finish this G.D. 5k.
Finishing that 5k
was the hardest thing
I have ever had to do.
I ate more Fettuccine Alfredo
and drank less water
than I have in my entire life.
People always talk
about triumphs of the human spirit.
Today, I had a triumph
of the human body.
That's why everybody
was applauding for me at the end.
My guts and my heart.
And while I eventually puked
my guts out, I never...
puked my heart out.
And I'm very, very proud of that.
Hey, Michael.
Hey, Mer.
- How you doing?
- Better.
It's ironic, isn't it?
I mean, I'm in the hospital
for not getting enough water.
And you're in it for a disease
that causes a fear of water.
I'm in because you hit me with your car.
But I want to say...
I heard you were trying really hard,
so...
I'm not mad at you anymore.
Thanks.
Want to share?
Sure.
I'm not really sick.
I'm good.
www.tvsubtitles.net