Happy Halloween, everyone.
Oh, that's great.
Hey. Happy Halloween.
Jan called.
Ohh, 'kay.
I know, why she's calling.
It's the end of the month,
and I was supposed,
to let somebody go by
the end of the month.
And somehow I'm supposed
to put on a costume and smile.
- Okay.
- Jan Levinson's office.
Hey, Sherri, Michael Scott returning.
Oh, she's in a meeting.
She just wanted the name of
the employee you let go.
Well, I'm going to wait
'till the end of the day.
Because the book said it's best
to wait until the end of the day.
I just need the name of who
you're planning to let go.
I don't know yet.
I will have to call her back.
I know she wanted the name.
- Okay, Sherri ?
- Yeah ?
If you were getting fired,
how would you wanna be told,
so you could still be friends
with the person firing you ?
Jan wants the name as
soon as possible, Michael.
- Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
I'll call her back.
Wish I could fire Sherri.
- Hey, I'm still here.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
- No ?
- Bye
-Hanging up now.
Synchro: Occeane
Script : Nikki
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
I mean you hear about
lay offs in the news.
but when you actually have to
do it yourself, it is heavy stuff
It's, I mean, these are people's
lives you're talking about.
- You wanted me?
- Yes.
- Paper-mâché ?
- Hmm.
- Yesh
Pam, I have to let
somebody go, today.
This is, uh, the hardest
thing I've ever had to do.
Why did you put it off until Halloween ?
Because it's very scary stuff.
I think it's gonna put a
damper on the party a little.
You're worried about the party ?
There's a man's life at stake here.
- So it's a man ?
- No.
Or a woman. A human life.
If you had to guess,
ho it would be, based on,
their job performance ?
And who do you think deserved
to be fired? Who would that be?
I just answer the phone.
And, sometimes you just
let it go to voicemail.
Your costume, is fantastic.
I know. I sent away for
it in July from a catalog.
Oh no, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Aah !
- Okay.
- Oh, man.
Okay, I have to fire somebody.
What is that ?
What are you supposed to be ?
I'm a three hole punch version of Jim.
'Cause you can have me either way.
Plain white Jim, or three-hole punch.
- That's great.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, look, what about me ?
What are you ? A monk ?
I am Sith Lord.
Big deal.
Three round pieces of
paper taped to his shirt.
This cost me $129.
Ass.
Hey, you guys excited about the party ?
- It's going to be fun.
- Yeah.
Oh, looks at you.
Showing your colors.
Bet you wish you wore a dress every day.
- What are you implying ?
- All good.
Happy Halloween.
What  happened to all those
spooky decorations that we had ?
- The cobwebs and such?
- You know, I don't know.
We put them all up last night.
Well, you know what ?
Go buy some more.
I'll approve the overages.
- Sound good ?
- Yeah.
Good.
Oh, yeah, also, about budget stuff.
I going to need you to find, like
a full employee salary,
plus benefits, like fifty grand.
I'm going to need you to find
50 grand in the numbers.
- But we don't keep two sets of books.
- Well, that's not what I'm saying
Just, you know, find it.
Pretend that your jobs depend on it.
Interesting take on Dorothy.
I love it.
Hey, you know what would even be better?
- Soccer ball and cleats.
- Why is that ?
Bend It Like Beckham.
Oh, like the movie about the
Indian girl who plays soccer?
Yeah.
That would be perfect.
Yeah, I mean, I guess I could do that.
I don't really play soccer or anything.
Well, I don't really have two heads, so
Wait, what are you again ? Oh, right.
Three hole PUNCH !
- Okay, greatest strength.
- Okay, okay.
- A dog like obedience to authority.
- Nice.
- But that doesn't sound good.
- Okay, okay.
How 'bout, the ultimate team player ?
Dwight is special.
But, I don't believe his talents
are being used in this office.
So Pam and I have put his resume
on Monster.com, Google, Craig's List.
We're really interested most in
jobs that take Dwight out of state.
Preferably Alaska, or India.
He's a gun nut.
He sticks to his guns.
Well,  I looked through all the budgets.
- And there is one department...
- Yes ?
That has three people...
Yeah ?
...doing the work,
that could be done by two.
This is great.
Oh.
Yeah.
- Who do you think it should be?
- Jim.
- Definitely.
- No, Jim brings in money.
Phyllis.
Stanley. Pam. Oscar. Meredith.
Kevin. Angela.
It's not a popularity contest.
Although it does make sense
to fire the least popular.
Because, it has the least
effect on morale.
One of the warehouse guys.
What ?
There was someone left off that list?
Who is he saying?
You're right, I didn't
even think of him.
No, Michael.
- Yeah, that's actually a really good idea.
- No, not me.
- Yeah I could.
-  Not Dwight
- I'm not saying that's what he said.
- I know that's what he said.
What ?
Tell  him, not Dwight.
That is not a very nice thing to say about him.
- Tell him to stop.
- Are you kidding?
- Quiet you.
- I agree. He'd land on his feet.
Make him be quiet.
Those aren't chips and dip.
No, I made brownies.
What ?
I'm just trying to figure out
why you're sabotaging things.
- I made brownies.
- And I made cookies.
Same category.
I'm guessing Angela's the one,
in the neighborhood who gives,
The trick-or-treaters some toothbrushes
Pennies.
Walnuts.
Dunder Mifflin this is Pam.
Yeah.
Just one second. I will, uh, transfer
you to our manager, Michael Scott.
Michael Scott here.
Yes, I am regional
manager of this orifice
Dwight Schrute, is, amazing.
Yeah. No, he is actually the single
greatest employee of his generation.
You know what ?
I'm gonna tell you what.
You hire Dwight K. Schrute,
and he does not meet, nay, exceed,
every one of your wildest expectations,
well then, you can hold me,
Michael Gary Scott, personally
and financially responsible.
Okay. Okay. Okay-kay-kay-kay-kay. Okay
- Stanley, could you come with me, please.
- No.
As assistant regional manager.
- To the ?
- Look.
I've got some bad news.
You're fired.
You need to pack up
your things and go.
I'm serious, Stanley.
It's over, I'm sorry.
You're fired.
Get your fingers off my phone.
So, how did it go with Stanley?
How-how'd he take it?
- He wouldn't listen to me
- Oh, come on.
If you want to fire him, you're
going to have to tell him yourself.
I don't wanna fire Stanley,
I never said that.
I'm certainly not going to do it myself.
Get those big, baleful,
eyes staring at me. Yikes
Just, okay, just...
Cumberland Mills?
How did you get my resume?
Oh no, no. I'm very flattered.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just not sure that
it's my official resume.
or if it's something that maybe,
a satisfied customer posted online.
What does it say under
martial arts training ?
Oh, okay, I'm gonna
have to supplement that.
Could I have your fax number?
Would I ever leave this company ?
Look, I'm all about loyalty.
In fact I feel like part of what I'm
getting paid for here is my loyalty.
But, if there were somewhere else
that valued that loyalty more highly.
I'm going wherever they
value loyalty the most.
Oh, hey.
Oh, your dress is stuck in the back.
Kind of just...
Oh.
So you got the fax?
So why didn't you add it to the resume
What do you mean ? Of course martial
arts training is relevant.
Oh, excuse me! I know about a billion
Asians that would beg to differ.
get a little frustrated when
I'm dealing with incompetence.
Well, you know what ?
You can go to hell too.
And I will see you there...burning.
Fine! Okay, wait. So you'll let me
know when you've made a decision.
Jim is really talented.
And he should be the one who's
getting a better job offer.
Like, for real.
Don't take this the wrong way.
But, you should go for that job.
It's in Maryland
Yeah, but I mean,
look at the salary.
And it's definitely a step up.
And a challenge.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know what ? Maybe...
Maybe I will.
Jim...
This is called, leveraging an offer.
- Michael, can I talk to you for a moment
- Oh, God.
I just thought you should know,
that I was just offered
a job with better pay,
Better benefits and a better
title at Cumberland Mills.
- Fantastic.
- And I turned it down.
What ? That would've
solvedall my problems.
- Out of loyalty to this company...
- Oh, you idiot.
- So I was hoping to be made assistant
regional manager officially.
- If you left,
I wouldn't have to fire anybody
- But then you wouldn't have me here.
- Big deal, oh !
It would've worked out so well.
Can you get it back ?!
- It's in Maryland.
- You can call, can you call 'em?
I can't, I, I suppose, I could, no.
They never really made
me an offer anyway.
Why are you torturing me ?
G od.
Honestly, I don't think that Michael has,
the slightest clue of who
he's going to fire.
I think he keeps hoping that
someone's going to volunteer.
Or be run over by a
bus before the deadline.
But in the end, really,
what's going to happen is
It's gonna be the first person to
give him a dirty look in the hall.
And therein lies the true
essence of his charisma.
Yes.
Michael, I really didn't mean to.
Help, me.
- I'm sorry ?
- I want you to role play firing me.
I want you to fire me,
and I will take it.
- Oh, you want me to be you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I want you to be me, and I will be Creed.
- Oh, are you firing Creed?
- No, no. No, that's just the first,
Thing...can't, in head.
We should switch seats in order to..
- Yes, that's a good idea.
- Alright.
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry, but
I have to let you go.
And it's purely budgetary,
it's not personal.
- Wow.
- I'm going to kill myself,
- And it's your fault !
- That's an overreaction.
Corporate is really
breathing down my neck.
And they're saying this has to be done,
- by the end of the month.
- Is this you?
Is this you? Are you being you,
or is this Creed? Are you..
I,
- This is Creed.
- Okay.
I'm improvising, so just try to keep up.
- Hold that thought. Hold that thought.
- And I'm very angry, and I want...
- Michael Scott here. Toby ?
- I'm gonna kill you for firing me.
I really have to take this Creed,
so it was really worth...
- Get off, get off. No, no.
- Okay.
Just, just, yeah.
- What happened ?
- It wasn't me.
- Oh. That was like crazy. 'Cause I was
- Yeah, I know.
- Creed ?
- Huh ?
Could I talk to you for a second ?
You are great. Very ambitious.
And I feel like you want more
than this little office has to offer.
And I understand that you'd
wanna just spread your wings,
- And fly the coop.
- What are you telling me ?
I, we're gonna have to...
You, you want something better.
No, I don't. I wanna stay right here.
- No, you wanna leave.
- No, I wanna stay here
Why, why are you making this so hard ?
- I think there's a misunderstanding, Michael.
- I think you're right.
- Can I go?
- No, of course, you can't go
We haven't even started
this horrible process of.
Okay, Creed.
I need to let somebody go today.
They told me I need to let somebody go.
And as much as I think you're
a great guy, and I like you,
You're-you're, good-bye.
Let's fight it.
Let's  call Jan and fight this
thing together like the old days.
What old days?
What are you talking about?
Did you start the paperwork yet?
- It's right here on the desk, yeah.
- You don't have to do this Michael.
- I can't, I can't...
- Undo it!
I can't change anything.
- This is the way...
- No
Michael, undo it !
I don't...
- No, you have the
power to undo it.
Yeah, I went hunting once.
Shot the deer in the leg,
had to kill it with a shovel.
Took about an hour.
Why do you ask?
I have to fire someone today. Okay?
Fine. Fire someone else.
Fire Devon, he's terrible.
I am so much better at
my job than Devon.
Okay, well, I already picked you.
And you know that.
So, unless I just go through with this,
You're always gonna look at me
as the guy who almost fired you.
No, no, no, no, no,
I will forget so fast.
You will be my savior.
You're they guy who
gave me my life back.
Thank you.
I knew you'd see it my way Michael,
- God Bless you. You're a fine man.
- Don't...
Listen, you will not regret this either.
Devon's terrible.
No one's gonna miss him.
Good, good, good.
Devon, could I talk to you for a sec?
- Creed's an idiot, you know that.
- Well, he...
No, no, no, no, no.
You had it right the first time.
- Well, maybe I did.
- Exactly.
You gotta go with your gut man.
No. I can't, no. I can't go back.
I would look like an idiot.
- That's why I'm being fired?
- No.
So you might not look like an idiot ?
No. It was all the stuff that I said.
It was business downturn,
the cutbacks, and, and...
This is unbelievable!
I just hope that you and
I can remain friends.
Devon wait, please.
Look, look.
In addition to severance,
and everything, I want to give you,
This gift certificate to Chili's.
From me.
Okay? No hard feelings.
Kevin, Jim, Pam, Kelly, Toby,
Oscar, Meredith, Phyllis,
Stanley, or the temp.
If any of you wanna meet me for a drink,
I'm going to be a Poor Richard's
And the rest of you can go to hell.
What about the Halloween party ?
Hey, Jim. Wait, stop.
I'am sorry for pushing
you towards Cumberland.
Seriously, if you left here,
I would blow my brains out.
Come on.
That's just a figure of speech.
You know ?
Blow your brains out ? Come on.
All it really means is
that we're friends.
I mean, who else is she gonna talk to...
If I'm gone, right?
I mean, if she left, I wouldn't
blow my brains out.
Of course, I would take
that job in Maryland.
Because it's double the pay,
and soft shell crab just
happens to be my favorite food.
I love Halloween. You know,
it's just, it's just fun
Every year, it's just fun.
Last Halloween I came as
Janet Jackson's boob.
It was topical.
People got a big kick out of it.
The year before that,
I came as Monica Lewinsky.
And I wore a stained dress.
The year before that, I also
came as Monica Lewinsky.
And before that, I was O.J.
It was pretty funny.
Oh, I wish you were here last year.
Trick or treat !
Hey,  how you doing ?
Wow ! You guys looks great.
I'm a bumble bee.
You look great !
- And you're a princess?
- A fairy princess.
- A fairy princess, you're...
- I'm a lion.
You're a lion. Wow,
I want to hear your...Oh !
Oh, okay, that's all yours.
That's all yours.
Grab it, grab it. You know what ?
You guys are getting all of these.
www.tvsubtitles.net