All right, let's get started. Um...
Oh, first off,
we're supposed to be
pushing cardstock this week
so... let's push cardstock this week.
Uh, also? what is this?
Tape recorder.
For what?
For recording.
Michael is on vacation,
and he has asked me
to record all meetings
and to type up the transcripts.
Okay
Karen, any news
from that warehouse?
Yeah, the deal closed yesterday
with six-month commitment.
Oh my god, Dwight,
what are you doing?
What?
You're not allowed
to take off your pants
in the middle of the office.
I'm not...
Dwight, you know what?
Just back off,
Okay. It's making me
uncomfortable.
This is sexual
harassment, by the way.
Oh my god.
He's got a knife!
I do not have a knife.
No, let the record show
that Dwight K. Schrute is
now completely nude
and is holding a plastic knife
to Stanley's neck.
Let the record show
that Jim Halpert is a liar!
Dwight Schrute is now
wearing a baby's bonnet.
I am not!
Oh, Jim Carrey just walked in!
Dwight, get his autograph
for Michael, quickly!
Jim Carrey did not
just walk in. Okay?
Dwight, what is that
on your stomach?
- Is that a Muppet Babies tattoo?
- Oh my god, Karen, you're right.
- That is Animal from the Muppet Babies.
- You can't see my stomach...
I am now chopping off Phyllis'
head with a chainsaw!
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
µð¾¾ÀÎ»çÀÌµå ¹Ìµå°¶
The Office 3x12 "Back from Vacation"
Original Air Date: Jan 4, 2007 (NBC)
Hey mon!
Hey, you have
a bunch of messages.
And, that's nice.
Hannah quit while you're gone.
I guess she'd memo to file
some complaints she had
about being a working mother.
And- so, you might also
have to be deposed.
- Relax
- Okay
- Relax. Okay, I'll get to all of that later.
- It's kinda serious.
Aren't you going to ask me
how Jamaica was?
Say it. Ask me.
- How was Jamaica
- It was so good!
Hey Mon!
At Sandals, Jamaica,
when somebody says
"hey mon"
Everybody says
"hey mon" back.
Oh, Michael,
I'm glad you're here.
Stanley, you know what?
It is really good to see you, too.
My bonus check was
$100 less than you promised.
Okay, well, payroll is
in charge of all of that.
They said I should talk to you.
Well, I am just getting settled in,
so I am gonna...
I am not doing a lick more work
until I get my full bonus check.
You are not as much fun as
your Jamaican brothers.
Mon.
Don't you wanna talk about it?
Nope.
I still haven't found
an apartment yet.
I'm living in a hotel.
Yesterday I saw a "For Rent" sign,
down street from Jim's
And he said he didn't think
it would be such a good idea.
He said it would be like
we were living together.
In different houses.
Two blocks away.
"Feelin' hot, hot, hot!"
That's all I know so far,
but I'm gonna keep practicing.
It's good.
You know, I had never been
out of the country
before now.
Got to see how Jamaicans live.
It is great,
you know? They just relax.
They party all the time.
It's kind of
an impoverished country.
Yeah. Gosh... great.
You know what? Pam,
Make your note.
I want us all to start
having pina coladas
every day at three.
We can't today.
We're doing inventory.
Inventory was
at the end of December.
We couldn't do without you,
so we postponed.
I specifically went on vacation,
so I would miss it.
Inventory is boring.
In the islands,
they don't make you do stuff
like taking care of inventory.
Why do you think so many
businesses moved to the Caymans?
Tonight, we are going to have
an inventory luau.
I want to bring back a little slice
of paradise to the Dunder-Mifflin
warehouse inventories.
So, party planning committee.
Get on it.
By end of the day?
That's impossible.
The Jamaicans don't have
a word for "impossible"
Yep, It' English.
It's impossible.
Michael, there is no way
that we can do it in time.
How hard is a luau.
All you need are some grass skirts,
pineapple, poi,
tiki torches, sucking pig,
some fire dancers.
It's all you need.
Come on in.
Settle in.
Settling...
And... settled.
Good. There is something
I would like to show, everybody.
See this sign?
No shirt, no shoes,
no problem.
This is an attitude
I would like all of you
to have right here.
So what, if we have to say
like doing inventory
No, problem!
Oh my god, is that Jan?
What? Where?
On the left.
No, that's a German woman named...
Urkel Grue.
Jan told me to play it cool
and not tell anybody
because it could get us
both in trouble.
So officially,
I did not see her.
But I did see Jan there.
In our room.
At night.
And in the morning.
And that's all I'm gonna say.
Sex.
We had sex.
I had sex with her.
I had sex with Jan.
Hey dude.
Just got from Jamaica.
Big whoop.
I was in Hotlanta.
That whole town is whack.
Yea, that sounds amazing.
But you know what?
The lady, Jan Levinson
wanted go to Montego bay.
You took the ice cream?
I don't buy it.
Well, I'm looking at a photo,
right now.
And, I'm telling you,
it could be a Maxim.
They wouldn't give you
a subscription to Maxim.
- Oh, no?
- No.
Okay, well...
Check this out.
I'm sending you some e-mail.
You got it?
What a- No. I got nothing.
Check it again.
It'll refresh.
Yeah, Mike, still nothing.
Okay, wait a second,
I sent it to you at
Packer@Dunder-Mifflin.com
Packaging@Dunder-Mifflin.com
Wait, I just got it from
somebody else.
Wow! This is god damn!
I don't like
you've had this picture.
Darryl?
Hey. Hi, where is Darryl?
He's in the office.
Hey, man. How's it going?
Alright, what's up, Mike?
Yeah, it's great.
Okay- um-
So, did you get
any e-mail from me?
- Yeah
- Okay
Well, that was supposed
to go to Packer,
not "packaging."
Did you already forward it
to a whole bunch of people?
- Un-huh
- Okay
Um- well,
did you get the second
email that I sent,
explaining that the first
email was a mistake
and that you should delete it?
Yep.
And you sent that out to everyone?
Mike, I'm very busy down here.
Yikes.
Already sent it to you, my friend
Fantastic
Boring.
Call me if she rolls over.
Hey
You okay?
Yeah
You sure?
Yes.
Um- just- it's like-
it's stupid fight with Karen.
You want to talk about it?
Really?
I have a special
assignment for you.
Who's the target?
A sensitive email has been
released to the office.
It contains a file...
A picture...
the filename is "Jamaican Jan Sun Princess."
What's it of?
Not important.
Unless you're willing to
tell me everything,
- I cannot accept this assignment.
- Okay, forget it.
Okay, I accept it.
So, I don't know,
I just feel we've been
dating a month, right?
Same street?
I think that might be
a little close, a little bit much.
Hmm.
"Hmm," what?
How far away does she live now,
like ten minutes?
Yeah, I guess.
Honestly, I think
you should go easy on her.
No, I didn't mind helping
Jim with his problem.
That's what friends do.
I... help Phyllis all the time.
Just yesterday I untangled
a piece of tape from her hair.
So, yeah.
Hey. Thanks, a lot.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I mean, it's better than listening to
Michael play a conch shell,
which is what I was doing.
Oh, also?
Michael went to
Jamaica with Jan...
Yeah, how have we not
talked about this already?
I mean,
what happened there?
Kidnapping?
- Hey, I need to talk to you.
- Not now.
Not ever.
It's about you and Jan.
Oh, none of your business.
But so the truth is- um-
It seems from that photo
that you two have been
intimate relationship
That photo was
my personal property
And if you are  telling me that
you want my computer
to steal that photo,
And I'm going to call the cops.
I have nine different people
emailed me that photo,
including my ex-wife.
We wanna talk, you know
Well, this is probably the ice-breaker you need
You know,
for your own protection,
you should disclose
the relationship to HR.
I bet you'd love all of details.
Wouldn't you,
Skeevy little perv.
All right, if you are having
a relationship with your superior,
you must disclose it.
No, no, no.
I am not dating Jan.
She was very clear about that.
Just two like souls
having a romantic time
in the most romantic
place on earth.
Got enough? Weirdo?
- Alright. Thank Michael.
- Okay
Hey, we only have three hours, people,
to plan the whole luau
You're not helping.
What are the ingredients for poi?
I called every grocery stores
in Scranton,
and no one sells whole pigs.
Did you try to petting zoo?
Dunder-Mifflin, this is Pam.
Just a second.
Michael,
it's Jan on the phone waiting.
Oh, God! No, no, no, no!
Hang up. Hang up.
Tell her I'm not here!
Don't. Don't.
I ran out of gas.
I hit a deer!
I hit a deer with my car.
No, I hit a cat.
Tell her I hit a cat.
He'll call you back.
Okay. Great.
Do you think she bought it?
Okay. Okay.
Michael hit a deer?
Michael,
Michael, there's an emergency
in the warehouse.
An accident? Somebody hurt?
No, it's nasty photograph.
Oh, god. No, no, no.
Mike, you are a rock star, man.
You are the man!
Well done!
Alright, Okay.
- That corporate booty
- He likes to hit it!
Hello, hi. Attention everyone.
Um- apparently, there is an e-mail
circulating around,
That contains very
PG-13 rated picture of me.
And, a woman.
Jan
No, Kevin.
A woman.
Maybe, Jan. Maybe...
Urkel Grue.
My point is that,
If you get it, I would ask you
to just delete it.
sight unseen
Let's be very professional. Alright?
"Feeling... feeling hot hot hot."
What are you doing out here?
I live living, you know.
Jan calls, she's coming in here later to talk to you.
Did she say what's about?
That's all she said.
People in the party, ha-ha-ha!
I think you drop this.
You sure?
Definitely.
I have disconnected
the office T1 line.
I have ordered that
that can be taken down.
And destroyed all print-outs
from the bathroom.
There are copies in the bathroom?
Oh, well- a lot- of them.
I think I owe you one.
Sorry?
For taking sense into to Halpert.
The Day's Inn room 228
was starting to get really depressing.
Yeah, I know.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, he was being ridiculous.
Yeah.
But thanks.
Seriously.
Sure.
Oh, yes!
What did I tell you!
I knew he turned it off!
You see that?
This is the greatest time
of my life!
Who did this to you?
Where is he?
What?
No... it's not...
it's nothing.
It's hot in here.
- Yeah
Thanks.
- You don't need to stay here.
- I know.
So you're PMS-ing
pretty bad, huh?
Hello, everyone?
- Hello, Michael?
- Hello
Hi, Jan.
You look... tan.
I was in Scottsdale
visiting my sister.
Yeah? How was it?
Very sunny.
Family is important.
Michael, I would like to
speak with you.
- In your office
- Okay
Why am I here, Michael?
Uh, I...
In the last year
I've gone through a divorce,
an identity theft,
a husband who would not...
communicate.
This is neither here nor there.
My psychiatrist thinks that
I have some self-destructive tendencies
and that for once,
I should indulge them.
Are you following me?
Uh, uh, yes.
I think I owe it to myself
to find some kind of happiness.
You know, I mean,
I mean even if it means
lowering my expectations, or...
or redefining the word itself...
Okay, yeah.
This is the thing, you know.
I am attracted to you.
I- I don't know why,
but I am.
And I need to follow
my instincts.
At least that's
what Dr. Perry thinks.
Who's Dr. Perry? I...
This is the point, okay?
You're wrong for me.
- In- in... every way.
- Well, not...
But I still find myself wanting to...
be with you.
And I, to you, in addition,
feel, the same feelings,
that you are, as well.
Good, good.
So, um- thanks for coming by.
Thank you for taking your time.
Well, thanks for coming over.
I appreciate...
Wait 15 minutes,
find an excuse,
and meet me at your condo.
Jan.
You complete me.
Oh, God.
Hey.
Remember when we were
planning our honeymoon?
You wanted to go to Hawaii,
and I wanted to go to Mexico.
Yeah.
I was definitely right.
Oh brother.
What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna hang it up at home.
I don't have a lot of art.
Script & Syncronization : EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
Date: Feb. 11, 2007
drama forum in South Korea : http://kr.dcinside13.imagesearch.yahoo.com/zb40/zboard.php?id=f_drama
www.tvsubtitles.net