I really like Valentine's Day
in this office.
It's kind of like grade school...
everybody gives out little
presents and stuff.
Like last year,
Jim gave me this card
with Dwight's head on it.
It was horrifying and funny. And...
Phyllis.
You could just sign here.
Roy and I are saving
for the wedding, so...
I made him promise not to
get me anything too big.
Happy Valentine's Day, Darling,
love Bob Vance,
Vance Refrigeration.
- Isn't he sweet ?
- Yeah.
Such a sweetie.
All right, Dwight. As you know,
I'm heading to New York today,
doing a presentation on the branch
to the new CFO.
- And you want me to come with you.
- No. Opposite of that.
I will stay here and
run things on this end.
Very good.
Question. Will you be seeing Jan
when you're in New York ?
I probably will. Why do you ask ?
Well, it's Valentine's Day.
And you guys, you know...
Screwed.
What is your problem ?
This is a business trip.
I would have to be a raving lunatic
to try to talk to Jan about
what happened between us.
Her words, not mine.
She sent me an e-mail this morning.
But, it is Valentine's Day.
It's New York, city of love.
Hey, Pam, you heard NY, right ?
You want me to pick
you up anything ?
- That's okay.
- All right.
The best present would be,
you do a good job in front
of the new CFO.
Dude, I'm going to nail it.
Me in New York ?
Oh, I own that city.
Fuggit abat it !
See ya !
Saison 2 - Episode 16
Valentine's Day
Transcript par Nikki (twiztv.com)
Sous-titres par la Catch-22 Team
pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus
www.forom.com
Well, here we go
on our way to New York.
New York, New York.
The city so nice,
they named it twice.
Manhattan is the other name.
So, I broke up with Katy
and haven't been dating
anybody else.
So this year, I don't have to worry
about Valentine's Day.
It's gonna be good.
I invited a couple of friends over,
we're gonna play some cards.
And I'll end up winning
a lot of money,
because, they're idiots.
It's gonna be great.
What's this ?
What is this ?
I don't know.
It's on YOUR desk.
Yeah, but who put it there ?
And for what purpose ?
It was there when I sat down.
Happy Valentine's Day.
It's me.
I'm the bobble head.
Yes !
Yeah.
The meeting isn't till 3:00,
but I always like to come
to New York a little bit early
and hit some of my favorite haunts.
Like right here is my favorite
New York pizza joint.
And I'm gonna go get me
a New York slice.
Hey, Kelly.
- What's up ?
- Nothing.
Oh, except, oh my God, Jim.
Last  night, Ryan and I totally,
finally, hooked up.
- It was awesome.
- That's great.
I'm really happy for you.
I know. And it was so funny.
'Cause we were at this bar
with his friends,
and I was sitting next to him
the whole night.
And he wasn't making a move,
so in my head, I was like,
"Ryan, what's taking you so long ?"
And then he kissed me.
And I didn't know what to say.
So I said,
"Ryan, what took, you so long ?"
I mean, I just said it to him.
Can you believe that ?
Oh my God, Jim.
Is that embarrassing ?
- I'm embarrassed.
- No, don't be. No.
- Oh, thank God.
- All ri...
Because I was nervous, Jim.
You will not believe.
- I bet.
- I was so nervous.
But now, now I have a boyfriend.
All right.
I hooked up with her
on February 13th.
Here it is. Heart of New York City.
Times Square.
Named for all the good times
you have when you're in it.
Most people when they come
to New York,
they go straight to
the Empire State Building.
That's very touristy. I come here.
Great places to eat.
We have Bubba Gump Shrimp,
Red Lobster down there.
You know. This is...
this is the heart of civilization
right here.
Guess what ?
Really ?
- They're from Bob again.
- That's great.
Everybody takes the subway
in New York.
It's fast, it's efficient,
gets you there on time.
It's a way to... Okay.
There's a guy pooping in
a cardboard box down there.
This is the world-famous
Rockefeller Center.
Founded  of course,
by Theodore Rockefeller.
This is the skating rink.
And I think they Rangers,
practice there sometimes.
And, it's... that's Tina Fey.
That's Tina Fey
from Saturday Night Live.
Hello, hello. Hi.
Oh, I'm s... I'm sorry.
I thought you were... okay.
I thought that was...
She looked like...
she looked a lot like Tina Fey.
Hello, hello. I thought that was
Tina Fey, but it wasn't. So.
Are you serious ?
He was here ?
When ? When I was talking to
the fake Tina Fey ?
Come on ! No, are you s...
Hello, Angela. Did you hear ?
Somebody totally rocked the house
and got me the best present
I've ever gotten.
Really ?
I wouldn't know anything
about that.
- But I'm glad you enjoyed it.
- Oh, I did. I did.
I didn't get anything
for Valentine's Day.
Oh, I bet you will before
the day is over.
Really ? Well, I hope I do.
I would love to live
in New York some day.
It's a big dream of mine.
Work corporate, with Jan.
It'd  be awesome.
Go to Broadway shows, eat hotdogs.
Scranton is great, but New York...
is like Scranton on acid.
No, on speed. Nah.
On steroids.
Okay. Um, I think...
that's either the Hudson or the East.
So, we're back...
should be back this way.
There is a lot of pressure
on me right now.
It's like Michael Jordan
in the NBA finals,
or like
Stormin' Norman Schwarzkopf.
And this presentation
is Desert Storm.
And soon as it's over,
we will not have to deal
with those Iraqis anymore.
Let's do it.
No, that's alright.
Spend the money on her
instead of giving it to us.
That's fine.
No, I didn't even have
a seat for you anyway.
Yeah.
All right, man.
Okay, have a good night. Bye.
Phyllis Lapin ?
- Holy God.
- It's from Bob.
Man, that thing's bigger than I am.
- No, it's not.
- Oh, zip it.
There they are. What's up ?
-Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- Michael Scott.
- Josh Porter. High five.
- You know Dan Gordon from Buffalo.
- Yeah, how you doing ?
Nobody needs to introduce this guy.
Craigers.
- What's up, buddy ?
- You have been kicked out
of every strip club in Albany.
- Is that true ?
- Guilty, yeah.
So what's going on,
what did I miss ?
No much. They're,
I guess running late upstairs.
So we're just waiting
for the presentation.
Cool. Good. Good. Good.
Give us some time
to catch up and...
Pam, hi. How you doing ? Good.
Listen, may I speak with you...
privately ?
You can't fire me, Dwight.
Just 'cause Michael's not here.
No, Pam, just,
Just...
Please.
You need to get something
for your... girlfriend ?
Girlfriend. Yes.
And the reason I didn't get
anything for this particular person,
who shall remain nameless,
is that she's not really
the kind of person
you'd think would be
in to Valentine's Day.
- She's kind of...
- Tightly wound ?
Exactly.
Okay. Well, sometimes the gift is
really about the gesture,
you know, like what it means
instead of what it is.
You mean, like a ham ?
No. Not like a ham.
It's about doing something,
so that the person knows
that you really care about her.
- Okay, I get it.
- That you remember her.
That's great. Okay, shut up.
I know exactly what to do.
How about you, Craig ?
Did you lose anyone ?
Oh, man. Jan called me
in September.
And she's like,
you gotta fire four people.
And I was just like, what ?
You know.
- Did you ?
- No, I just ignored her.
She's the worst.
Well, she's our boss.
She ain't my boss, dude.
I don't work for that bitch.
Hey, come on.
- You know, that's not...
- What ?
- Just cool it.
- You like Jan ?
How can you like Jan ?
Maybe because she's my girlfriend.
Was, or not my girlfriend.
She's...
- we hooked up and...
- You hooked up with Jan ?
That was just, you know,
months ago.
It was just once.
God, it's just stupid.
Just... forget it.
- Yeah, let's change the subject.
- Yeah, yeah.
I don't know what he's thinking,
but I would just be so psyched
if we just dated forever.
Well, take it slow.
'Cause it seems like
a lot of the time,
things like that need to...
Soda.
Cool.
Hey, so do you want to do
something tonight ?
Oh, no, not while I'm here.
I mean, I know that
it's Valentine's Day or whatever,
but there's totally no pressure
at all of any kind, whatsoever.
- So...
- I can't tonight.
I have plans with my friends.
Okay.
- That's cool. I...
- Okay.
- I completely understand.
- Cool.
Okay.
- Josh Porter, Stanford.
- Nice to meet you.
And  Michael Scott, Scranton.
- Ditto.
- How are you, Jan ?
- Fine, Michael, thank you.
Okay, so we are in the process
of doing a complete review of
the company's financial strength.
All I'd like to do today...
Nervous ? No, I'm not nervous.
Well, I mean, I guess I'd be lying
if I didn't say
I was a little nervous.
The new CFO is judging me
on this too.
And, well, it is Michael. So...
yeah, I'm very nervous.
So with the 12 new local accounts,
we had a total of 4% organic growth.
Which was just above
our pre-year targets.
- Thanks very much.
- Thank you.
Okay, Michael.
What is a business ?
Is it a collection of numbers
and sales reports ?
Sure. But as you know,
David and Jan, it is much more.
Life moves a little slower
in Scranton, Pennsylvania.
And that's the way we like it.
'Cause at Dunder Mifflin Scranton,
we're not just
in the paper business.
We're in the people business.
Let's meet some of the folks
who make Scranton branch so special.
This is Stanley Hudson,
one of our talented salesmen.
An African-American
father of two...
Stanley's dedication is no doubt one
of the hallmarks of the foundation
of the business we're hoping
to build our basis on.
Yeah, I shot a bunch of footage
around the office,
edited it together on my Mac.
Was thinking about entering it
in some festivals.
Probably won't.
You know, not what this is about.
And finally, Pam Beesly.
Look at her. Look how cute.
Not bad at all.
As the receptionist, Pam is truly
the gateway to our world.
Well, I hope this gave you
a little taste of what life is like
here at Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
What it's like to walk
a mile in Oscar's shoes.
Or try on Phyllis' pants.
Next time you're in town,
give us a call.
Stop on by.
I'm sure you'll be greeted
by a big smile
and a "How you doing, pal ?"
Maybe even one of
Angela's famous brownies.
And you'll know that you're home.
Great Scott !
Questions ?
Okay, okay, thank you, Michael.
That was great.
Yes, thank you.
But, for right now, what I'd really
like to know about
is the branch's performance.
So do you have
that information as well ?
Yes, absolutely, David.
Get that for you. I...
-  Can you sign ?
- Yeah.
Oscar.
- Nothing for me ?
- Join the club.
- Who's it from ?
- My mom.
It's frustrating 'cause
we'd be so perfect together.
You know what ?
Here's the deal, Kelly.
It would be really nice
if he was into you, right ?
It would be great. But he isn't.
- You know.
- Yeah, but it would be so great
- if he was...
- Well, he's not, though.
So you just gotta suck it up.
You just gotta move on.
Try to have some fun.
Come to my poker game tonight.
Okay, cool.
Is it okay if I invite Ryan ?
And that about does it. Thank you.
Okay.
Craig.
Yeah, here's the deal.
I did not understand
this was supposed to be a...
full on, like, report or whatnot.
I'm sorry, what did you think
"financial presentation" meant ?
I was under the impression
this was more of, like,
a meet-and-greet type of deal.
So, does that mean that you don't
have the numbers on your branch ?
That is correct, yes.
Craig, you realize that we are trying
to decide whether drastic steps
need to be taken.
Look, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Well, the point is that this doesn't
exactly bode well for your branch.
Oh, man. You know what ?
Michael made that stupid movie.
He doesn't get in any trouble.
Maybe I should've slept
with you too.
- Okay, okay.
- No, no, no.
- All right.
- I'm not, I just...
I just don't know what to do
anymore, Michael.
I mean, I'm probably
going to get fired.
- No, you're not.
- Yeah, I...
Michael, the CFO thinks
that we slept together.
Don't you understand ?
People get fired for much less.
And I just can't believe
that you told everybody.
And we didn't even sleep together !
Technically, we fell asleep
in the same bed.
- So...
- Oh, God.
Michael, it was months ago.
It was once. It's over.
Do you understand ?
Yes. I'm sorry.
I'll, fix this. I'll talk to him.
I'll talk to David.
Surely, you cannot be serious.
I am serious,
and don't call me Shirley.
Airplane.
Women, are like wolves.
If you want a wolf,
you have to trap it.
You have to snare it.
And then you have to tame it.
Keep it happy.
Care for it. Feed it.
Lovingly, the way an animal
deserves to be loved.
And my animal deserves
a lot of loving.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey.
- You almost ready to go ?
- I guess, yeah.
- What's wrong ?
- Nothing.
It's just that I had to sit here
all day while Phyllis got,
like, an entire garden
delivered to her.
What, you're mad at me ?
I mean, I know that
we said no big gifts,
but I was kind of hoping you'd get
me something for Valentine's Day.
Well, Valentine's Day isn't over.
Let's get you home, and you are
gonna get the best sex of your life.
You understand this is
a very serious situation.
No, no, no. Yes, I... Okay, well...
All right, here's the deal.
This is my fault.
This is totally on me.
Before you guys came in,
I was talking to the guys,
we were all chatting.
And I made a joke.
A really dumb joke.
And Craig the idiot
took it seriously.
-  You made a joke ?
- I did. It was stupid.
And Craig, you saw him,
he's not the sharpest tool
in the shed.
Although, he is a tool.
Well, I don't need
to explain to you
that even a joke about sexual
relations with your boss...
I know, it was borderline at best.
And... and Jan
is a fantastic executive
and has all the integrity
in the world.
And, I'm really sorry.
It'll never happen again.
It's fine. Let's just...
just forget it.
Good.
- Heading out ?
- Yeah.
All right, Beesly.
Hey, Happy Valentine's Day.
Bye.
- Good night, Pam.
- Night, Phyllis.
Thank you again, for that, really.
- It was very nice.
- No big deal.
- Really, sorry again.
- Oh, no. It's... it's okay.
It's okay.
So... Happy Valentine's Day.
Yeah, Happy Valentine's Day.
Oi vey...schmear.
www.tvsubtitles.net