I got a delivery for you.
Leave it at reception.
I'm supposed to deliver this one
in person.
Clean up on aisle five.
After three years of writing,
one year of shooting,
four years of reshooting,
and two years of editing,
I have finally completed
my movie,
Threat Level Midnight.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- Erin, Erin...
- Yes?
- What are you doing?
- Guys...
Did you guys know
that our own Michael Scott
has made a movie
and that he maybe
will let us watch it,
but only if everybody's
dying to see it?
That's... Well,
don't put words in my mouth.
Threat Level Midnight
is the great lost film
of Michael Scott.
We're all in it,
from, like, years and years ago.
It's like a home movie.
Yeah, if Michael Scott
did your home movie.
Michael screened
a work in progress for us
years ago, and it didn't go well.
We thought it was a comedy.
Everything pointed
to it being a comedy.
- Yep.
- We'd love to see it.
Sweet.
I will go invite Holly.
Okay, everyone,
I know we're really excited
to see this movie
that everybody's in,
but we have to remember
that Michael is sensitive.
So let's stay positive...
And no laughing, no comments,
just positive energy,
and we'll have
a pure fun day, okay?
Thanks, mom.
You never told me
you made a movie.
Mm-hmm.
It's got action. It's got heart.
It's got symbolism.
- It's got you.
- It's got a lot of me.
I can't wait.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Threat Level Midnight.
♪
Michael Scarn?
Well, that
is an interesting story.
He was once the best
secret agent in the business.
That was years ago.
Where is he now?
Well, that's also
an interesting story.
Master Scarn.
Master Scarn!
I play Samuel,
Michael Scarn's robot butler.
I wanted Samuel's voice...
To be like this.
But Michael
thought that Samuel should be
a very advanced android,
almost indistinguishable
from a real person.
Dwight does not play a robot.
- I'm up.
- It's the president.
- He needs you for a mission.
- Tell him I'm retired.
It's Goldenface.
Goldenface...
This makes it personal.
♪
Scarn, you're right on time.
- Hail to the chief.
- I gave up a lot of weekends
because I thought it
would be good for my daughter
to see a black man as president,
even in a silly home movie.
What a stupid waste of time.
It's your old enemy, Goldenface.
He's after
the NHL all-star game.
He's hidden a bomb
somewhere in the stadium.
Scarn...
This one is personal for me.
I own the stadium.
I can't see it blown up.
It's my retirement plan.
We have to search the stadium.
Not so fast...
Goldenface has taken
all of the concession-stand
workers hostage.
Scarn, will you find these
hostages and save the game?
Heads I do it, tails I don't.
Best out of seven.
Heads.
Tails.
♪
Heads.
Tails.
Looks like there's gonna be
a clean up on aisle five.
Well, the hostages were scared.
Don't you guys get it?
Nobody's coming for us.
Oh, someone's coming, all right.
The only man who would care,
Michael Scarn.
See, I'm gonna lure him here.
Then I'm gonna kill everybody.
Then I'm gonna dig up
Scarn's dead wife,
and I'm gonna hump her real good.
I did not love the dialogue...
Or the character.
I took the role
to impress a receptionist
who will remain nameless.
Well, the all-star game
was three days away.
The only way Scarn was getting
in was in a uniform.
Just one problem with that...
Scarn didn't know
a hockey stick from a slim Jim.
So he went to meet
with the famed trainer,
Cherokee Jack.
Mop the ice.
I'm not here to learn how to mop,
I'm here to learn
how to play hockey.
Mop it.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I get no traction
'cause I'm running on ice ♪
♪ it's taking me twice as long ♪
♪ can't have a reaction
'cause I'm running on ice ♪
Come on.
♪
♪ You got to run, run, run, oh ♪
♪ oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ you run, you run,
you run, run, run, oh ♪
♪ oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
- Now take this.
- ♪ Running on ice ♪
What am I supposed to do
with this?
- ♪ Running on ice ♪
- Mop.
♪ Running, running on ice ♪
♪ running on ice ♪
Well, Michael Scarn
was quickly becoming
one of the hottest
hockey players in the country.
Each year
the national hockey league
accepts one civilian amateur
to play in the all-star game.
It's down to the three of you.
The final test is speed skating.
On your marks...
Get set...
Die.
♪
Nice try, Goldenface,
except you forgot one thing...
to kill me.
Oh, I wasn't trying to kill you.
I was trying to slow you down.
No!
- Oh, by the way...
- Yeah?
How's your wife doing?
Congratulations.
Hey, you came in second...
Not bad either, champ.
I'm so sorry I have to do this.
Shh! Shh, shh!
I'm so sorry.
I'm intercepting a name...
Jasmine Windsong.
She works for Goldenface.
But what I can't figure out is,
who is the Funky Cat?
Not who, what.
The Funky Cat is
the hippest jazz club in town.
Oh!
Oh, n...
♪
He cut the part where
my circuit board malfunctioned?
Then what was the point
of spilling the drink on me?
♪ They call me ♪
♪ Jasmine Windsong ♪
Bingo.
He finished his movie?
No kidding.
Wow.
That's great.
Yeah, good for him.
♪
♪ The hostages are under the stadium ♪
Ooh, ugh!
Ugh.
Check, please.
You have to let us go,
Goldenface.
- We have families.
- Ha, this is gonna show them...
That I mean business.
See ya.
Far and away the most
expensive shot of the movie,
but it was "intregral"
to the story.
Ha!
It's Scarn!
Sorry about your friend, Scarn.
The joke's on you, Goldenface.
That man was
a wanted animal rapist.
We've searched
the whole building, Goldenface.
- Where is the bomb?
- Hmm?
We've searched
the whole building, Goldenface.
- Where is the bomb?
- Hmm?
We've searched the... Okay.
He said,
"Where is the bomb?"
In the puck.
But why are you telling me this?
Because I'm going
to kill you, unless...
You forgive me
for murdering your wife.
♪
- Hey, Goldenface.
- Yeah?
Go puck yourself.
No!
That was not scripted.
More Tylenol.
You've already had four.
Oh, God!
So good.
You're lucky to be alive.
It'll take
a lot more than a bullet
to the brain, lungs,
heart, back, and balls
to kill Michael Scarn.
Let's just make sure
that everything's...
working properly.
You just said
the bomb is in the puck?
Yes.
Is that where
you hid the bomb, Goldenface?
But why would you blow up
the stadium?
You own the stadium.
For the insurance money...
I knew it all along.
You will never get away
with this.
Where had I gone wrong?
All I wanted was to start
a family with my beautiful wife.
But somewhere along the way,
things got messed up.
It wasn't easy for Scarn to admit
that he'd lost
his self-confidence.
And he hadn't, of course.
He just wasn't using it
right now.
Mike!
Beer me, Billy.
You don't look so good.
What's got you down?
I got problems, Billy,
big problems.
You got problems?
My TV don't work.
I pay 30 bucks a month for the
damn satellite "Whatsahoozit."
I can't even get the damn game.
Now, you tell me,
what's worse than that?
Don't ever change, Billy.
Goldenface is going to blow up
the NHL all-star game tomorrow.
I see what you mean
about problems.
I know what'll cheer you up.
That table
of bachelorettes over there
bought you this drink.
Hey.
Ever banged an entire
bachelorette party, baby?
Why are you singling my line out,
like, a million years later?
I'm too depressed
to save the big game, Billy.
I'm gonna cheer you up
the only ways I know hows.
Hey, kid...
Hit G-9 on the jukebox.
No, Billy, I haven't done
that dance since my wife died.
There's a whole crowd
of people out there
who need to learn
how to do the Scarn.
♪
♪ Well, my name's Michael Scarn ♪
♪ and I'm here to say ♪
♪ I'm about to do the Scarn
in a major way ♪
♪
♪ you jump to the right,
and you shake a hand ♪
♪ then you jump to the left,
and you shake that hand ♪
♪ you meet new friends,
you tie some yarn ♪
♪ and that's how you do
the Scarn ♪
♪ You jump to the right,
and you shake a hand ♪
♪ then you jump to the left,
and you shake that hand ♪
♪ meet new friends,
tie that yarn ♪
♪ that's how you do the Scarn ♪
♪ you jump to the right and... ♪
- Shh. Stop.
- ♪ And you shake that hand ♪
♪ meet new friends,
tie that yarn ♪
- ♪ that's how you do the Scarn ♪
- Boom!
If doing the Scarn is gay,
then I'm the biggest queer
on earth!
You guys, I think I have...
- I'm really sorry.
- My self-confidence back.
- Hey, hey.
- Michael!
Michael, I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
I think I was just relieved
to see that Michael Scarn
got his confidence back.
Yeah, Michael,
the movie's amazing.
It's, like,
one of the best movies
I've ever seen in my life.
You should enter it in festivals.
- Or carnivals.
- Yeah.
Well, that's
a pretty good reaction.
That's pretty cool, right?
Did you like it?
Did you like that?
Which part?
Okay.
- All right.
- Oh, come on.
- No.
- Michael.
- No, come on!
- We have to see the end.
No, it's not good enough.
It's not good enough.
Some people
are really popping on-screen.
- Hey.
- Good movie.
- Mm, good?
Everybody out there says
it's great.
- I loved it.
- Did you?
- What did you love about it?
- Um...
I loved that you got to work
together with all your friends.
- Mm-hmm.
- Isn't that so great
when you can all work
together like that?
No, no. Holly, this isn't
Oean's Eleven,
where you get together
with all your friends,
and you just have fun,
and you don't care
about how it turns out.
What'd you really think,
honestly?
Um...
Is it... is it
because you're afraid
of where this is gonna take me?
Because, see, I need you
to keep me grounded.
I'm not worried about that.
This is 11 years, okay?
This has been my dream
for 11 years...
And if you don't think
it's great,
then you're basically saying
you don't believe in my dream.
It's your dream? You never
even mentioned it before.
We talk
about a lot of things, Holly.
You know, I was eventually
going to get around
to my dream, obviously.
11 years
that I could've been working
on the Scarn Nebulus.
Well, why do you have
to make a movie at all?
Because if I don't have this,
what do I have?
- I have nothing.
- Really?
You can't think of anything else
that you might have?
I have my book on business,
somehow I manage.
I have my HBO Comedy Special,
here I go again, dot, dot, dot.
But you know what?
When I think about it,
when I really think about it,
none of those things
are as real to me as my movie.
I'm real.
Yeah, you're
a real pain in the ass.
And now I'm gonna go
watch the movie
with people who think it's great.
And I'm sorry I called you
a pain in the ass.
I'm angry, and I love you.
I love you too.
I'm a huge Woody Allen fan...
Although I've only seen Antz.
But I'll tell you something...
What I respect about that man
is that when he was going
through all of that stuff
that came out in the press...
About how Antz was just
a rip-off of A Bug's Life,
he stayed true to his films...
Or at least the film that I saw,
which, again, was Antz.
Thing is...
I thought Bug's Life was better,
much better than Antz.
Point is,
don't listen to your critics.
Listen to your fans.
Who likes Threat Level Midnight?
Okay, well, then who wants
to watch the rest?
Michael, you have to get
to that puck before halftime,
or the whole stadium
will explode.
I know. It's a good thing
my trainer and mentor
- is here to cheer me on.
- Cherokee Jack?
Michael, he died.
♪
This one's for you,
Cherokee Jack.
We filmed this during an actual
Scranton High School hockey game.
They were trying
to qualify for States.
Shh.
It's fine. It's great.
No, no, actually
it was really screwed up,
because they...
they were trying to qualify.
They were disqualified.
They had to forfeit the game.
Undefeated season...
That's why there were
so many people there.
- Why is your face gold?
- Why do you care?
I'm just making conversation.
I worked in a gold factory.
We had a boss
who only cared about money.
He wouldn't give us
lunch breaks, so we had to...
- Hey.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
- It is good.
- No, no, it's not.
It's not.
But they really
seem to be enjoying it.
Come on.
Please, Goldenface, let us go!
Cherokee Jack.
I want you to take
all your frustrations...
with women, the system,
with everything...
take it out on the puck,
all on the puck.
♪
- Yah!
- Aah!
- Oh!
- Yay!
- Yay, they're saved!
- Whoo!
♪
Hey, we got sports games again.
Oh, sh...
Some breakfast for me,
some breakfast for you.
Aw.
Oh, yeah, I guess
I did let him be a robot.
I'll get it.
Man, I love being retired.
Scarn here.
- Michael, it's the president.
- Hello, sir.
I need you for another mission.
Uh...
Yeah, I'm in.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Isn't the president evil?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, he is.
No, no, he's doing it
to catch the president.
No, no, Dwight,
he's just being stupid.
Well, Michael Scarn was
back in the game.
And I bet you're wondering
why do I know so much
about Michael Scarn?
Well, because I am Michael Scarn.
Oh!
That was so good.
Aw, yeah!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net