(IN KEVIN'S VOICE) Oscar, Toby said he
left my Girl Scout cookies on my chair.
Have you seen them?
Wait, I'm sitting on them.
This is awesome.
Thank you. It didn't
even take that long.
What's the difference
between a chimichanga,
a chalupa and a tostada?
Call me back ASAP.
It's urgent.
Wait, this isn't funny.
I don't talk like that.
Say, "Me eat cookie."
No. I won't say it.
Why is everyone
clumped around accounting?
Break it up, you clique.
It's Kevin as Cookie
Monster from Sesame Street.
Is that the program where all
those puppets live in the barrio?
MEREDITH: Mmm-hmm.
I love that show.
This is Kevin.
OSCAR: Thank you.
That is an amusing link.
I'd like it sent
to me, please.
Me, too, Oscar, please send
it to me. Yeah, totally.
Yeah, me, too.
Angela,
this is inappropriate.
This is my favorite day.
It's Secretary's Day.
And it is Erin's and my
three-week anniversary,
so perfect storm
for a romantic gesture.
Want to make sure the whole office
remembers it's Secretary's Day.
I sent an email blast, a text blast,
a good old-fashioned talk blast.
I sent a snail-mail
blast a week ago,
and a stern reminder via fax
at 7:00 this morning,
so people better step up and
appreciate the crap out of Erin.
Oh, thank you.
ANDY: I do.
Thank you.
If it wasn't for secretaries,
I wouldn't have a stepmom.
Welcome back.
Hey, thanks.
PAM: It's my first day back after
maternity leave, and I miss Cece, of course.
But we need the money.
What was maternity leave
like? Oh. How do I explain it?
It rocked.
It rocked my ass off.
Oh. You couldn't
have watered it?
I literally did not know that
existed until this moment.
Well, I knew it existed,
and I chose to let it die.
It's nice to see
you again, Dwight.
Hello, Pam.
I was just wondering what you
had planned for Secretary's Day.
I'm going to give Erin $15.
I know that Erin would be so
psyched if you took her out to lunch.
A one-on-one
lunch with Erin?
Yeah. She really
looks up to you.
There's only so much we
can do as her coworkers.
Secretary's Day is really
kind of a boss-secretary thing.
She's kind of a rube.
That's my girlfriend
you're talking about.
Okay. All right. All right.
Okay, I'll take her to lunch.
She's gonna be so psyched.
Hi, Erin.
Happy Secretary's Day.
Well, happy boss's day.
There wouldn't be a secretary
if there was no boss.
I wanted to know what
your plans for lunch were,
because I was hoping
to ask you to lunch.
I got a picture of you
asking me to lunch.
I was thinking we could go to
Hayworth's, just the two of us.
(GROANING) Well, Hayworth's
is more business-casual,
and they always screw
up your order, so I'm...
Oh. Yeah, okay. Yeah, that
was a stupid suggestion.
I was thinking someplace special,
so I thought Hayworth's, but...
Okay, well, we'll figure something out.
Okay.
Okay, let's go
to Hayworth's.
Okay!
Have a cookie, Kev.
Yeah, ha, ha, tray of cookies.
I'm not falling for that.
I brought those in.
It's my birthday.
That's some stone-cold
narcissism right there.
Man, Darryl, I'm sorry.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
(MIMICKING COOKIE MONSTER)
(MEREDITH LAUGHING)
KEVIN: They're making fun of
Cookie Monster. I get that.
But in a strange way, it feels
like they're making fun of me.
(IN KEVIN'S VOICE) Oscar, did you
eat some of my M&M's? The level...
This is violent
and offensive.
Thank you.
And it really makes me
self-conscious about my voice.
That's awful.
I'm not crying.
You have some
food on your face.
Do my hands feel
sweaty to you?
GABE: The beginning here has
been a little bit of a fiasco.
Either they don't respect me,
or they respect me too much.
And some of them still think
that I'm the IT guy.
This Cookie Monster thing is
an opportunity to show people
that I'm an authority figure.
Hello, everyone. If I might
have a moment of your time.
It's come to my attention
that people have been watching
and laughing at
a hurtful parody video.
It is now forbidden to talk,
joke about, or email this around.
Yeah.
And that's straight
from corporate, so...
Not to be scary, but,
yeah, I would listen to me.
And that's all.
(BIDDING FAREWELL IN ITALIAN)
Would you mind if I
listened to my book on tape?
I'm kind of a bookworm.
This is a novelization of the movie
Precious, Based on the Book Push by Sapphire.
I was thinking it would be
fun to talk on the way over.
What decade would you have
chosen to be a teenager?
I don't know.
I would have
chosen the 1490s.
(EXCLAIMING)
'Cause America
was discovered.
Right.
(SIGHS)
And then my last job was
at a Taco Bell Express,
but then it became a full Taco Bell
and, I don't know, I couldn't keep up.
My favorite part about being a receptionist
is that I get to have my own desk.
At my foster home I never
had a desk, so it's like...
I don't mean that I didn't like
my foster home. I did like it.
I just didn't have
a desk there.
Did you have a favorite age? Or month?
An age or month?
Yeah, like a favorite month. Like,
I liked April when I was seven.
I've been trying. I've been
trying to keep it going.
Erin is just weird.
How many pillows
do you sleep on at night?
So how are
things going with Andy?
He's the best boyfriend
in the world.
Tell me about him
before I met him.
Well, let's see...
Andy plays the banjo.
Yeah, I love that.
Other than the fact that he dated Angela,
I don't think he is a snappy dresser.
What?
I don't think he is the best
dresser. Reminds me of Easter.
Sorry. About Angela.
Did you say he dated Angela?
Mmm-hmm.
You didn't know that?
WAITER: Here we go.
Hot plate.
Oh, okay.
WAITER: And your
salad, miss.
Why wouldn't
he tell me that?
I don't know.
Probably didn't want you
to have a mental image
of him having sex
with somebody else.
They had sex?
They were engaged, so...
Okay, you know what, sir?
WAITER: Yes?
Yeah, I asked for pickles on my burger,
and there are only, like, five or six.
Can I get some
more pickles?
Of course. I'll get
you a bowl of pickles.
MICHAEL: Thank you.
(GROANING)
They were engaged?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
Well...
(GROANING)
What are you doing?
In the foster home,
my hair was my room.
(PANTING)
(SHOUTING)
Okay, okay, you know what?
You know what? You know what?
Everybody's looking
at you right now.
(PANTING)
I'll have what
she's having.
Did you have a...
Did you like your lunch?
Did you have a good lunch?
Did you like that?
Did you enjoy your food?
It was good.
I liked my lunch.
(GROANING)
What's up?
Her milk is coming in.
She's getting uncomfortable.
Dwight, don't be gross.
No, no, he's right.
Same thing happens with my cows if
I don't tend them frequently enough.
You gotta milk them, or
else they'll moo like crazy.
That's weird,
my breast pump is missing.
Have you seen
my breast pump?
All right, this is
gonna traumatize me
a hell of a lot more
than you, believe me.
You know what, Dwight? Let me just
check the bathroom first. Okay?
Really? Fine.
Let your breasts explode.
Three squeezes
and I would drain you.
PAM: Mmm.
Meredith! MEREDITH: I
just like the way it feels.
PAM: What are you doing?
MEREDITH: Just relax, okay?
Relax?
This is like
the Cadillac of pumps.
Give it
back to me, now!
Okay. I was just
warming it up.
That's...
It's disgusting!
It's not a big deal.
It's not sterile!
We're both girls.
Who cares?
So, how was lunch?
Lunch was fine.
Was it everything that you
hoped and dreamed it might be?
I don't know.
It was lunch, Andy.
Well, I know, I'm...
That's what I'm...
Just wondering...
I mean...
Erin, I think we're
out of fax cover sheets.
God, Oscar, will you keep
your pants on? It's easy.
(MIMICKING KEVIN) My name
is Kevin. I'm an accountant.
You see?
I did the voice.
It's a little derivative.
But parody is
always derivative.
It's not organic.
Do you know what I mean?
Jim does a really good one. Do yours.
Oh, guys, I really
refuse to participate.
(MIMICKING KEVIN) "Michael, can
I have an advance on my paycheck,
"because a Mrs. Fields Cookies
just opened up at the mall!"
Guys, why don't we leave the
parodies to the pros at MADtv?
"Sorry, Gabe, but that show
hasn't been on in many cookies."
Okay.
Hey, can I have
your attention, please?
First of all,
thanks to everyone
for helping put this
awesome party together,
and a very special shout-out to the
chair of the party planning committee,
Miss Angela Martin.
You have outdone yourself.
Yeah, you know what?
I think we can all agree that
Angela's not so great, so...
I'm saying the exact opposite.
Angela is fantastic.
No, no, no.
ANDY: Specific shout-out.
Stop talking.
Okay. As some of you may know, I have a
very special connection to Secretary's Day
in the form of that 115-pound
moonbeam over there named Erin Hannon.
To a lot of you she may just be the person
who brings you your fax confirmations,
but to me,
she is my girlfriend,
in addition to being the person
who brings me my fax confirmations.
So, I wrote
a little ditty
that I would like to play
for all of you right now.
It's a little tune called
Secretary of Love.
One, two, one, two, three...
(ALL GASPING)
I know about Angela.
I know that you
were engaged to her
and that you were
sleeping with her.
Michael told me.
Oh, God.
Erin, can we talk
about this in private?
I don't want it to be in
private. Is it true or is it not?
Yes. Who else did you sleep with?
Did you sleep with Phyllis or
Kelly or Pam? Maybe all together?
PAM: No. No. No. No.
Did everyone know? Was I
the only one who didn't know?
Yeah. Pretty much.
KEVIN: Pretty much.
Yeah.
Who are you? I don't know you. Get away!
I should probably
get involved in this,
but I think my energy is better
spent on the Cookie Monster issue.
Erin, you know, if I had been
engaged to anybody before you,
I would have told you.
Thanks.
So if you need anything,
I'm right over there.
(MIMICKING KEVIN) "Hey, Erin, you
look delicious! I mean, beautiful."
Okay. Okay.
There, I heard that.
So, I'm sorry, Pam,
but that's it.
I'm going to have to suspend
you without pay for two days.
What? What do you mean, suspend me?
I think you need
to go a little easy.
You can't just suspend
someone from work.
Yeah, you're right. You know
what? You're suspended too, Jim.
Okay.
Fine. You too, Dwight.
Wait, what? I was just slow-clapping
your no-nonsense decision-making.
I don't want to hear it.
Suspended.
"C" is for suspension.
Why would that be something that you
would talk about on Secretary's Day?
Andy, she's not the easiest person in
the world to have a conversation with.
All right? And besides, who
doesn't tell their girlfriend
that they were engaged to someone
who works four feet away from them?
That's like... That's... That's
like Mr. & Mrs. Smith crap.
I was gonna tell her,
just on my own time.
You know what? I resent the implication
that I would keep that secret.
Everyone here knows that I
can't and won't keep a secret.
ANDY: Who cares?
I mean, it's not like I killed
somebody. Big deal, right?
This is gonna blow
over in two seconds.
She never asked me, so if you
think about it, it's kind of...
I probably should have told her, I
guess. Everybody does stupid things.
Psst.
Hey. Erin.
You want to talk to me,
come to my desk.
You embarrassed me earlier.
Take it up with
the chief of police.
You think I want people remembering
I had sensual relations with Andy?
It's the kind of thing you
wish you could have annulled.
I want to throw up
just thinking about it.
You are throwing up
for the wrong reasons.
I don't think this
fax is going through.
Oh...
Is there a different... I guess
put it through again, you know?
Hey.
You know,
I was engaged before Jim.
Really?
Yeah. And he
worked here, too.
It was Andy,
wasn't it?
No, no, it wasn't Andy. It wasn't.
It doesn't matter.
It's not about
who you've been with.
It's about who
you end up with.
Sometimes the heart doesn't know what
it wants until it finds what it wants.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
Thank you.
So I can reprimand them,
but I can't suspend them?
Oh, I can't do either?
Uh-huh.
Fair enough.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Toby.
TOBY: I called Tallahassee.
Now, he can ask you not to come in, but
he can't dock your pay. It's not legal.
Very interesting.
I also learned some interesting things
about how they structure their...
Thanks, Toby.
GABE: Hey, everyone. Hi.
Quite an afternoon, huh?
Cathartic, in a way. I'm glad
that I got to share it with you.
Makes you think about
what's really important.
It's not about showing you're in charge
or flexing some sort of authority.
It's about forgiveness.
And, yes, I'm talking about you
three in this desk clump right here.
I think that if you
were to apologize to me,
then I would revoke
your suspension.
I don't think
an apology is enough.
I really think the only way for me to
learn my lesson is to take my suspension.
And I gotta take
this bad attitude
and I gotta go home
and I got to adjust it.
DWIGHT: Oh, come on. I hope
the suspension does that.
PAM: Yeah.
Prideful idiots.
Watch how it's done.
Gabriel, I apologize.
Great.
I kneel before you.
Guys, I would even take a
contrite look as an apology.
Humbly taking your hand upon
which I kiss to show my contrition.
Guys, to...
To err is human.
ERIN: Trust is the most
important thing to me.
Is your name
Andy Bernard?
What's your real name?
Lionel Frankenstein?
Will you stop walking
for one second?
That's it. There's no
other secrets, okay?
I mean, yeah, my chest
is not naturally hairless,
and my parents pay
my credit card bill.
How long were
you guys together?
A year.
A year?
You were together
for a year?
Yeah. But that's it. Now
you know everything about me.
I promise. And if I
think of anything else...
I think I have to be on
my own for a little bit.
Like that girl Precious in Precious,
Based on the Novel Push by Sapphire. Okay?
I didn't see that movie.
(ALL CHATTERING)
That was ugly. I'm sorry
that you had to see that.
Well, do they
still get paid?
It's tacky to
discuss finances.
It's best to pretend
that this never happened.
Sounds like they just got
to go home with pay.
ANGELA: Yeah.
Pathetic.
Can I buy
everyone coffees?
(MIMICKING KEVIN)
Or cookies!
DWIGHT: What was that?
KELLY: So gross.
Are you kidding me?
Was that an impression?
All right.
(MIMICKING GABE) "Guys, I'm now going
to apologize for the mess that we're in,
"because corporate
told me to.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"I just want you to know,
I laugh like a crazy person."
Okay, you gotta
be able to...
You gotta be able to laugh at
yourself here. One of the gang.
"I have to go back to the zoo
to the stick insect exhibit."
(ALL LAUGHING)
Yeah.
"Ciao. " Right? "Ciao.
"I say ciao 'cause I'm
fancy from Tallahassee."
Why don't we say
ciao to the impressions?
ALL: Ciao.
DWIGHT: Stick insect.
God.
Erin?
Oh.
Sorry. I thought
everyone was gone.
No, no. I was just watching Cookie
Monster. It finally downloaded.
Do you mind
if I sit down?
Yeah.
What's...
I can't trust
Andy anymore.
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry about that.
I feel... I'm sorry I caused that.
It's Andy's fault.
Well, yeah. Yes. So...
But I still feel sorry.
(SIGHS)
You know what? I wouldn't
worry about Angela. She's...
She doesn't hold
a candle to you, Erin.
She's old enough to be
your mom, for one thing,
and she's, like,
three feet tall,
(BOTH LAUGHING)
And she wears
pioneer women clothing,
and I don't think she's
ever pooped in her life.
And Andy? You know... Come on. Andy,
his butt looks big in those khakis.
Oh, I like his butt.
You said butt.
You tricked me.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
You'd love...
This... This guy in my
neighborhood, Tom Dizemore.
This is him. (GRUFFLY)
"Hey! Hey, Scott..."
ANDY: Sometimes telling
someone something is hard.
Well, at least somebody made
her happy on Secretary's Day.
(IN OSCAR'S VOICE) Hey, Kevin, it's Oscar.
I'm looking at the sheet you sent me,
and I can't seem to find the
column for shipping costs...
I made the most
brilliant retaliation video.
It is so awesome.
I don't get it.
Yeah, I mean, the Count
has a very distinct voice.
Thank you.
Yeah, "I want
to count to 10."
OSCAR: Yeah.
But Oscar is
an accountant,
and the Count
counts numbers.
You're an accountant,
too, so it doesn't...
Why didn't you do
Oscar the Grouch?
That would have been funny.
But the Count is purple,
and Oscar wears purple.
Oh! Oh! I was just watching
that. Did you do that, man? Oscar!
And the Count! Nailed him. Nailed
him! Good work, Cookie Monster.
Thank you.
www.tvsubtitles.net