Oh, hey, Kevin.
Nice of you to join us.
Where were you?
My tire blew out
on the way here, Michael.
I almost died.
I went into this skid-
Pop quiz.
What?
- Why is today special day?
- I almost died...
Today is a special day
Because I am being honored...
As a visiting professor...
Special lecturer emeritus...
How did you-
How did you put it?
You will be a quest speaker.
In my Emerging Enterprises class.
In business school, Kevin.
Business school
If you bring your boss to class,
it automatically bumps you up
a full letter grade.
So...
I'd be stupid not to do it, right?
A boss is like a teacher.
And I am like the cool teacher.
Like Mr. Handell.
Mr. Handell would hang out with us.
And he would tell us awesome jokes.
And he actually hooked up with
one of the students.
Um- and then,
like 12 other kids came forward.
It was in all the papers.
Really ruined eighth grade for us.
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
µð¾¾ÀÎ»çÀÌµå ¹Ìµå°¶
The Office 3x17 "Business School"
Original Air Date: Feb 15, 2007 (NBC)
Here we go.
College road show.
Gotta bring our a game,
What is the most inspiring thing
I ever said to you?
"Don't be an idiot"
Changed my life.
Whenever I'm about to
do something, I think,
"Would an idiot do that?"
And, if they would,
I do not do that thing.
- Will they throw their hats, you think?
- What?
A lot times at a school
or naval academy,
after a rousing speech,
the crowd will throw its hats
high into the air.
You... you understand
nobody's graduating.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm just saying,
if they did throw their hats,
I've got a great line for that.
May your hats fly
as high as your dreams.
Thought it was a pretty good line.
it doesn't apply.
I understand. Wow.
Relax, spazzy boy.
Sometimes you're such a little spazz!
God, I'm driving!
Quit it!
We have fun
I can't wait for your art show tonight.
Okay, just so you know,
It's just the students
from my class in a little studio.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Thanks.
I'm really happy
to be back with Roy.
I think it shows maturity.
Maturity and dignity.
Is that braggy?
I don't mean it to be braggy.
Love you.
You too.
Pam's with Roy.
I'm with Karen.
And Brangelina is with Frangelina.
Moving on.
I can't believe
you're back together with Roy.
Oh, yeah.
We have such a
solid foundation, you know.
Oh, my God.
You're so in love now.
Yeah. Oh, you should come to
my art show, by the way.
Oh, art show.
I mean. It's not a big deal.
But I think a lot of people
from the office are gonna be there.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely I'll be there, for sure.
Campus.
Brings back so many memories...
That I would've made.
Hey, Frisbee.
Check that out- oh!
What do you say
we get out Fris on before class, huh?
Dude
Oh, my God.
Animal stool.
Dwight, what are you doing?
Solving a mystery,
if that's quite all right with you.
Come to papa.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
What we have here is a bird.
That has been trapped in a vent.
Fortunately, I have found it before-
Bat! Bat!
Oh, my God.
Bat!
No, everyone remain calm!
There it goes!
Good bye!
Okay, this is it.
Ryan is doing
my intro right now.
Dunder-Mifflin can't compete
with the modern chains,
And management is unwilling
or unable to adapt.
Their customers are dying off...
I can't here
what he's saying.
But he looks like
he's really into it.
We have a bat in the office.
The simple solution
would be to open a window.
If we had windows
that could open.
Poop is raining
from the ceilings.
Poop!
Okay, thanks.
Animal control
will be here at 6:00
At 6:00?
No, that is unacceptable.
Okay, Jim, you are the number two in this office.
You need to step up and show some leadership.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
So weird.
What? What's so weird?
The bat.
I mean I know
I felt it bite me.
But look. There's no mark.
I feel so...
Tingly.
So strangely powerful.
Oh, well.
And now,
without further ado,
I present the regional manager
of Dunder-Mifflin, Scranton,
Michael Scoot.
Hello everyone. I am Michael Scott.
Hello, I'm Tom Rollins,
CEO of the Teaching company...
And, I'd like to start today
by inspiring you.
May I borrow
someone's textbook, please?
Thank you.
What have we here?
Oh, economics.
Very very interesting.
You cannot learn...
from books.
Replace these pages...
With life lesson.
And then...
You will have a book...
That is worth
its weight in gold.
I know these are expensive,
But the lesson is priceless.
Good.
All right,
I think you're inspired.
Shall we proceed?
There are
four kinds of business.
Tourism.
Food service.
Railroads.
And sales.
And hospitals/manufacturing.
And air travel.
This is your job, Halpert.
What happened?
That bread on your desk?
I just picked it up.
It's white-hot.
But, Jim...
This garlic bread is cold.
What?
No.
It burned me. I-
Bizarre.
No.
One crisis at a time.
If a vampire bat was in the U.S.,
It would make sense for it
to come to a "sylvania".
Like Penn-sylvania.
Now, that doesn't mean
that Jim is gonna
become a vampire.
Only that he carries
the vampiric germ.
So... you want to start a business?
How do you start?
What do you need?
Well... first of all...
You need a building.
And, secondly,
you need supply.
You need something to sell.
Now, this could be anything.
It could be a "thingamajig"
Or a "whosi-whatsi".
Or... a "whatchamacallit"
Now, you need to sell those
in order to have
a "PayDay"
And, if you sell
enough of them,
You will make
a "100 grand"
"Satisfied?"
Oh, this looks great.
I'd love to be there.
But my daughter's play
is tonight.
Damn it.
You know one of the other
parents will probably videotape it.
Oh, no. you should go.
Well, it's important
to support to local art.
And- and what they do
is not art.
Okay, I'm seeing some
confused faces out there.
Let me slow down
a little bit.
Break this down.
Okay.
The more stickers you sell,
the more profit...
Fancy word for money
You have to buy Playstations
and Beanie Babies.
Michael.
- And products!
- What we normally do here is
More of a question
and answer type thing.
Well, okay.
I was just kind of getting going.
Yeah, I know.
Um- alright.
Okay, well,
we can do questions. Okay.
Very good. First hand up.
Sir, as a company
that primarily distributes paper,
How have you adapted
your business model
To function in an increasingly
paperless world?
We can't overestimate
the value of computers.
Yes, they are great
for playing games,
And forwarding funny emails.
But, real business
is done on paper, okay?
Write that down.
Hey, Jim. Here's
the aspirin you wanted.
Oh, thank God.
I have such a headache
from that glare.
What glare?
The glare of
Angela's crucifix.
It's blinding.
I don't have a lot of
experience with vampires,
But I have hunted
werewolves.
I shot one once,
But by the time I got to it,
It had turned back into
my neighbor's dog.
Extraordinary events
Call for extraordinary actions.
- We form an allegiance...
- Sure.
- To use sudden violence.
- Okay
Do you have the tools to turn
a wooden mop handle into a stake?
What size?
What do you say
to a customer
Who wants to leave you
for the convenience
and savings of
a nationwide chain?
I say,
"You will miss our service."
"And, I absolutely guarantee
you'll come back."
Has anyone ever come back?
We don't want them back.
They're stupid.
How far has your Herfindahl Index
declined since the merger?
Nice try.
How's your
Polack-says-what index?
What?
Thanks, Kowalski.
Can we get back on track here?
By your own employee's calculation,
You'll be obsolete
in the next five to ten years.
Wait, Ryan said that?
What are you doing?
You better not hurt
that little bat.
Animals can't feel pain.
Don't hurt that bat, Creed!
It's a living thing
with feelings and a family.
Flush him towards the door.
On my go... now!
Bat!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
I...
am a hero.
Yeah, sure,
you know business.
Sitting up here
In your ivory tower.
And your ebony tower.
But you know what?
I tell you one thing.
Dunder-Mifflin is here to stay.
But, how can you compete
against a company
With the resources of
a nationalwide chain?
David will always beat Goliath.
But there's five Goliaths.
There's Staples, OfficeMax...
Yeah, You know what else is
facing five Goliaths?
America.
Al-Qaeda.
Global warming.
Sex predators.
Mercury poisoning.
So do we just give up?
Is that what we're learning
in business school?
But in the big picture...
Dunder-Mifflin is the big picture.
Can't you understand that?
No, you can't.
You're too young.
Ryan
has never made a sale.
And he started a fire
trying to make a cheesy pita.
And everybody thinks
he's a tease.
Well, you know what?
He doesn't know anything,
and neither do you.
So, suck on that!
It wasn't personal.
Business is always personal.
It's the most personal thing
in the world.
When we get back to the office,
pack your thing.
- Pack my...
- You heard me.
Pack your things.
I really wanna come out!
Good night, Mary Beth!
So, you're cool to just wait here
for animal control?
Animal control?
I've been controlling animals
since I was six.
Cool, okay.
I'm gonna go home
and lie down.
Draw the shades.
There's just
so much sun in here.
Bye, Dwight.
Good bye, Jim.
And good luck.
Jim is on a path now.
An eternal journey.
And I wish him well.
But I have a destiny
in this realm.
Specifically
in the kitchen.
And it's all
from the same series.
Oh...
Called "Impressions,"
Not that I would call myself
an Impressionist, per se.
But maybe one day.
I  hope so.
I still need, you know
my breakthrough
or whatever.
Hey, babe, how are you?
Good.
Look who I brought.
My brother, huh?
- Hey, Kenny
- Hey, Pam
Hey...
How about this, huh?
I show up with my brother,
And no one from work is here?
That's pretty cool, huh?
Magic time.
My hair! Ah- get off!
Get off me!
Hold still, woman!
Oh, my God, oh my God!
You're welcome.
It's cool if I go, right?
I mean,
I looked at all of them.
Yeah, I'll just-
I'll drive myself home.
To my place?
Maybe. I'm a little tired.
Your art was the prettiest art
Of all the art.
Thank you.
Look...
I'm sorry, okay?
I was just trying to do
my presentation.
And... of course
I was wrong to suggest
that Dunder-Mifflin might
ever go out of business.
But you don't have to fire me.
Fire you? No, no, no.
You are moving to the annex.
To the annex?
Where Kelly is?
A good manager
doesn't fire people.
He hires people
and inspires people.
People, Ryan.
And people will never
go out of business.
You're the one who said
we needed more culture.
This is culture to you?
It's her first try.
Yeah, on Van Gogh's first try,
he drew the hands of
the peasants.
Meaning what?
Meaning real art
takes courage, okay?
And- and honesty.
Well, those aren't
Pam's strong points.
Yeah, exactly.
That's why this is motel art.
Thanks for coming.
Pam-casso!
Sorry I'm late.
I had to race across town.
Oh, Michael.
Wow!
You did these freehand?
Yep.
My God,
these could be tracings.
Look at this one.
Wow!
You nailed it.
How much?
What do you mean?
I don't see a price.
Um, you want to buy it?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, we have to take it
for the office.
I mean,
there's my window.
And, there's my car!
Is that your car?
That is our building.
And, we sell paper.
I'm really proud of you.
Thank you.
What?
Do you have something
in your pocket?
Chunky.
Do you want half?
No, thank you.
It is a message.
It is an inspiration.
It is a source of beauty.
And, without paper,
It could not have happened.
Unless you had a camera.
Oh, my God, Oh, my God, Oh, my God, Oh, my God
It's only temporary, okay?
Don't get excited.
I won't, I won't, I won't, I won't
Script & Syncronization : EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
Date: Feb. 11, 2007
drama forum in South Korea : http://kr.dcinside13.imagesearch.yahoo.com/zb40/zboard.php?id=f_drama
www.tvsubtitles.net