Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
I feel so lucky
we're in the same city
for Valentine's Day.
It's like magic.
Or it's like me
getting on my hands and knees
and begging my partners to
switch a Tuesday for a Thursday.
Alakazam.
By the way, they do need
an extra day next week.
And poof, he disappears.
Hey.
Wanna play hooky today?
Oh, maybe.
What do you got in mind?
We can do anything you want.
I really wanna have fun today,
because tomorrow
is going to be a nightmare.
Andy's coming back
from his stupid, dumb boat trip.
He's been rude,
he's been selfish,
I think he's a big jerk,
and I'm breaking up with him.
Bam, Andy!
How do ya like me now?
I hope as a friend.
Erin says she's gonna break up
with Andy, but I'm not sure.
He's coming back tomorrow,
and surprise,
today she wants to do
whatever I'd like.
You know, when I was a kid
we had a dog who got real sick,
and we had to
send him to a farm.
And on his last day,
we did everything he loved.
Wanna play catch
in the parking lot?
- Sure.
- Great.
- Get my coat.
- Perfect.
Come in.
Andy, hi, I just made
another huge sale
for the company
that you manage,
so I need you to authorize
that expense report
and sign off on that contract.
I would be happy to.
It would be
my pleasure, Mr. Schrute.
Rink-a-dit doo, rika-doot-deet
doo, rika-deet-doo.
I really like Andy these days.
He's pretend, and he does
exactly as I tell him to.
All that will change when
real Andy comes back tomorrow.
Unless he comes back
as pretend Dwight.
In which case,
we're in for an epic,
confusing showdown.
Andy left a carton of milk
in the fridge,
so I've been
sneaking a little bit
every day
for the last three months.
It's been yummy.
But now Andy's coming back.
So, I guess it's
good-bye, chunky lemon milk.
Okay, I'll say it.
I wish Andy had stayed
on his trip.
I say we all have
one last fun, boss-less day.
Yeah, let's get some booze
and some cocaine
and just blow it out,
no consequences.
Or the mini-mall.
They have all these
Valentine Day deals.
And you get 20% off
if you come in
with your husband
or your boyfriend.
But I mean, if you don't
have one of those,
you can probably just bring
whoever it is you use
to kill your loneliness.
Phyll, I'll pretend
to be your husband.
I'm already sick of you,
so it'll seem realistic.
- Oh...
- They have a nail salon there
where I get my feet detailed.
They use a watch repair kit.
Ooh!
I'll be your foot buddy.
Everyone, it is our last day
here with no manager.
I say we go
to the mini-mall.
Clark, you will be
my fake boyfriend
- so I can get the discount.
- That's what I do.
Let's do it.
Darryl, everyone
seems to be pairing off.
Do you want to pretend to be
a couple so we get the...
No.
Yes. Yes. Why wouldn't I?
I wanna pretend to be gay.
I got no problem with that.
All right, it'll be easy.
Don't be nervous, just follow--
Stop talking about it.
I said I'm fine with it.
These are gross.
They are terrible.
Oh, hey, don't fill up
on chocolates.
I made us a lunch reservation
at State Street Grill.
Oh, my God.
That's so romantic.
It's with Brian and Alyssa.
Oh, my God,
that's less romantic.
I know, but we should go.
We need to thank him
for, you know, saving my life.
Yeah, yeah, no, totally.
That's good.
So should we just get a bottle
of wine later and celebrate?
That sounds nice.
I'm very excited to see Brian.
Brian's a great guy,
and Pam and I have
gotten really close
to he and his wife Alyssa
over the years, and...
he got fired
for protecting my wife
from a jerk in the warehouse.
I'm sorry, but you know him.
He's a good guy.
Oh, tiny foot lady is back.
Oh...
Oh, get the baby clipper.
Oh, so cute.
You take off your glasses.
Okay.
What?
Your boyfriend.
He look like a pretty girl.
My boyfriend does look like
a pretty girl, doesn't he?
Yes, a very little pretty girl.
And you know what?
I think you are developing.
We should go
and get you a training bra.
Oh, you guys
both think this is funny?
Well, you know what?
No more discount.
- Excuse me!
- What? Shush!
Full price.
- We're not together.
- Oh, come on.
She's living a lie.
Turns out I can't even
be in a pretend relationship.
Hi. We'd like
the couples discount
on a pair of foot massages.
No, no discount for two men.
Two men are not a couple.
We are together, romantically.
Two men.
Doesn't work. No discount.
Oh, it works.
Him and me, all right,
we are crazy in love.
More in love than your
small mind can comprehend.
And we have two disposable
incomes and no kids,
and we're taking
our business elsewhere.
Oh...
- Hey.
- Hey, Brian.
Hey.
Sorry we're late.
Oh, uh, no problem.
I finished all the bread.
- Oh.
- Yeah, okay.
What?
He's on a no-carb thing,
supposedly.
Oh.
It's great to see you guys.
Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding?
Thank you, man, I mean,
I've wanted the opportunity
to say thanks for...
everything, and I'm really
sorry about the job.
That just seems crazy.
It's fine.
What are you gonna do?
But if you guys know of
any work, I'm fully available.
Well, my dad
can't hear a thing.
You could boom
his whole life for him.
That-- okay, great.
Does he pay well?
Where's Alyssa?
Uh, yeah.
Um, you know, Alyssa's--
she's not gonna make it today.
Oh.
Actually,
we're not gonna make it.
We're splitting up.
I have yet another
sales order for you to sign.
Why, thank you, Mr. Schrute.
I don't know how you do it.
You're a God.
Rink-a-dink,
deet, deet, doo.
Hi, Dwight.
You're back.
And you're disgusting.
Oh, geez, my nails
aren't dry yet.
I don't think I can work
for at least a couple hours.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, well, well,
look who it is.
Andy.
I guess I can cancel
my order from zappos.com
because, oh,
the loafers have arrived.
- Andy.
- Hey! Sweetheart!
I missed you so much.
Yes. Oh.
Welcome back, buddy.
I have been dreaming
of this moment.
Me too. So much.
I'm so happy.
I am really,
really bad at breakups.
Technically, I'm still dating
my first-grade boyfriend.
I mean, we just had
our 20th anniversary.
And I forgot
to get him something.
What happened? We thought
you were coming back tomorrow.
Well, Valentine's surprise
for Erin.
Hello. Super romantic.
And I got you something.
Oh, it's a couple of pieces
of bamboo, big deal, right?
No, these are
musical instruments.
It's so we can play
island music together.
'Cause I have this.
Clop the cloppers.
Yeah, clop 'em.
It's called bembe.
♪ Yoruba yoruba ♪
♪ aruba yoruba ♪
♪ yoruba yoruba ♪
♪ aruba raruba ♪
Hey, burning man, if it's not
selling out too much,
you might wanna throw on a tie.
David Wallace is gonna
be here in an hour.
Obviously, that's why I'm here.
I mean, I came back early
to surprise Erin.
Happy Valentine's Day,
sweetheart.
But I'm just saying
I'm also excited
about the Wallace meeting.
Why?
Isn't he just coming in
to rip you a new one
for being gone three months?
No, please, come on, Clark.
Wallace knows that he's been
gone for the last three months.
Right?
Wallace does know
that you've been gone
for the last three months?
I have no idea. I don't know
what he knows or doesn't know.
But we've been in touch
the whole time.
I mean, it's not hard
to get high-speed internet
in Turks and Caicos, people.
It's in every bembe cafe.
He only emailed me four times.
Question. Where's Jim?
He and Pam are having
their Valentine's Day lunch.
For two hours, really?
So, you're concerned
about peoples' long absence
from their place of work.
If the shoe fits...
♪ Yoruba yoruba ♪
♪ Ruba yoruba ♪
We were telling two different
versions of the same story,
and then everything
just went numb.
Well, I mean, that's okay.
It doesn't mean
that it's over, right?
I mean, couples fight.
Yeah, and that's the thing.
When we were fighting,
it weirdly felt like the
relationship was still alive.
And it wasn't until
we stopped fighting
that we realized it was over.
It's over.
I'm sorry, this is--
oh, my God, okay.
We have to stop
seeing each other like this.
Uh, we have to find a different
way to communicate
other than breaking down
in front of each other.
- Yeah.
- What?
At least my crying
won't get you fired.
Crying?
I notice that you landed the
Scranton White Pages account.
That is tremendous.
Thank you.
And you sold it
to Jan, too, I mean...
Yes.
- I'm impressed.
- Yeah.
Well, there's one problem.
Couldn't help but notice
that you offered a price point
that was not approved
by the head office.
So, gotta run that stuff
by me, Dwight.
You were on a boat.
I was...
On a boat in the ocean.
Okay, the issue is that you
need to run this stuff by me.
Coolio?
Are we coolio?
- Just say the word "coolio."
- I'm not gonna say it.
- Say it.
- Not a word.
- Coolio.
- No.
What do you think you're doing?
Just gonna call
the Scranton White Pages
- and clear this right up.
- Don't you dare, Andy.
Hello?
- Oh...
- Hey, Jan. Nard Dog here.
Oh, Andy...
I was just looking over
the paperwork.
- I found a little hiccup.
- Really?
Yeah, it appears my employee
offered you a price
that he was not authorized to.
- Hmm.
- Coolio.
Seriously?
You're calling me a few weeks
after finalizing our contract
to gouge me now for more money?
- Is that what you're doing?
- Coolio. I'm coolio.
No, no, no, Jan,
I think you misunderstood.
- Yeah.
- I'm coolio.
It's-- it's actually
just an issue--
You know what, uh, Nard Dog?
There is an option
in the contract
that allows me to back out
within 30 days of signing,
so I would like
to exercise that option.
No, Jan, please do not
listen to this boob!
Remember Clark. He gave you
everything. Everything.
Jan, I don't know
what he's talking about, but--
Tell Angela to send me
a final invoice.
Uh--
- Please, Ja-- Ja--
- Ooh...
Oh...
that was not...
how I had hoped that would go.
Hey, everybody.
Great job.
Listen, we're a smidge behind
on my paychecks.
Yes, well, as you know,
we get paid on Fridays.
And you haven't been here
for 12 Fridays.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Looking good.
Who's that little fella?
It's a bonus check
for you from Wallace.
Because the branch exceeded its
targets over the past quarter.
- Wow, that's wonderful.
- Quarter's three months.
That's how long
you've been gone.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Great, well,
we're all up to speed.
Two seconds of the turd dog,
and he loses the biggest sale
this branch has ever seen.
Do you have any idea
what I had to do
to get that sale from Jan?
I mean, I went all out.
All out. I mean like everything
was out the whole week.
He just waltzes back in here
like he owns
the chunky lemon milk.
Who needs him, right?
God, I just don't know
what we do.
I mean, short of
telling David Wallace
that he was gone
for three months...
I'd like to rat out Andy,
but unfortunately I have
a bit of a "boy who cried wolf"
dynamic with David Wallace.
Except instead of
a boy I'm a man,
and instead of a wolf, I cried,
"genetically-engineered
monster wolf."
I'm not gonna rat on him.
Andy gave me a second chance.
So the least I could do
is let somebody else rat on him.
Meredith, why don't you?
Meredith Palmer ain't never
been called no narc.
Floozy? Yes.
Alkie? Check.
Einstein sarcastically?
You bet.
But never no narc.
Vomit mop? Sure.
Floor meat? That's me.
- Flesh hoover? Hi.
- Hey--
- Meredith, that's plenty.
All right?
That's more than plenty.
Why does no one stop her?
Guys, I know that a lot
of people are mad at Andy,
and believe me, I am too.
But he has been through a lot,
and we all used to
love him, right?
So, if he's gonna
get in trouble,
just let it be his fault,
not ours.
I don't want that on my hands.
Fine.
The state he's in, Wallace will
take one look at him
and probably fire him anyway.
What's going on in here,
dirty players?
Let's get back to bustin'
some paper rhymes.
Come on.
♪ Who's that girl? ♪
It's Andy.
All right.
Back to work.
Okay, I can tell
you're mad at me.
Do you wanna just, um,
I don't know, tell me why?
I don't know.
I thought that was
a little weird.
You told me Brian got fired
for the whole warehouse thing.
And you intentionally left out
a kind of major
intimate detail.
I don't know, Pam, I guess
I just feel like a chump...
who knows less about
his marriage than the sound guy.
I didn't tell you
about the crying
because I didn't want you
to know how upset I was.
Because it would've
stressed you out,
and you're always saying how
much you don't want more stress.
Yeah, well, yeah, okay.
Well, then thank you.
Thanks to both of you.
- It's not Brian's fault.
- No, you're right.
And I'm not mad at Brian.
And to be honest,
I probably don't have
any reason to be mad at all
because I wasn't there.
So let's just forget about it.
Okay.
I need you guys to tell me
all the highlights
from the last three months
in case David asks.
Just a few things I could
sprinkle into conversation.
Any big sales or office gossip?
Well, we had
the Scranton White Pages.
Not helpful.
Let's stay positive, people.
- Okay?
- Hey, guys.
Hey, David, how are ya?
We were just having
our weekly round table
where we motivate each other.
I'm not gonna lie-- I get
as much out of it as they do.
Sounds great.
Don't let me interrupt.
Whatever you guys have been
doing this last quarter,
I couldn't be happier
with the numbers.
- Thank you.
- Well, finish up.
I'm gonna meet with Val
about that warehouse guy
you had to let go,
and you and I
will talk in 15 minutes?
- Great.
- Great job, everybody!
We had to let
a warehouse guy go?
You know Pam's mural?
Well, Frank--
Lit the whole thing on fire.
It was crazy.
- What?
- Yeah.
There was a fire
in the warehouse?
The whole thing is in ashes.
Fire department was here.
It was in all the papers.
Oh...
This is what I'm talking about.
This would be good to know.
All right, what else?
We started selling balloons.
- What?
- Yeah.
And, uh, Kathy Ireland
signed on
as the official spokesbabe
of Dunder Mifflin.
No kidding.
Yeah,
in the European billboards,
- she's gonna be topless.
- Wow.
Go, Kathy.
She's like 50.
- They're tasteful.
- Good, good. What else?
And who knew the balloon game
would be so lucrative?
And thank God, right? We needed
the income after the fire.
What fire?
The warehouse fire.
Weren't you just down there?
It's like burnt to ashes.
It looked fine to me.
I am speaking metaphorically,
of course.
You know I have lots of irons
- in the "fire."
- Mm-hmm.
Well, that's one of 'em,
you know.
Making sure that
the warehouse logistics
is a well-oiled,
properly-stoked fire.
Okay.
Think you'll agree
I explained that pretty well.
- Thanks, Andy.
- Thank you.
All right. Everyone.
The fish sounds great.
Yeah, I guess.
Really playing the scales, huh?
Yeah, I don't know,
it just sort of sounds like
noise to me now.
You think I need a new fish?
I don't love you anymore.
- What?
- I still like you.
But you were gone
a really long time,
and you didn't really
email me all that much.
You re-tweeted me a lot,
to be fair.
But I don't love you.
Okay, I get it.
You're unhappy.
I've been gone a long time,
and we lost
a little bit of juju,
but you and me,
we have a future.
There is a lot of love here.
I just said there isn't love.
On your side.
But there's tons on my side.
It's gushing.
We're just outta sync
right now.
But that's just timing,
and what's timing?
I mean, my parents
lasted 30, 40 years.
They were never happy
at the same time.
I guess.
I mean, what do we have left?
35, maybe 40 years,
if we're lucky?
I mean, I have spent
a lot of time in the sun.
You got really sunburned.
I'm gonna be a prune
in like three years.
Ugh...
I know you may not be
feeling love for me right now,
but if you fake it,
I won't be able
to tell the difference.
So I'll feel good.
And then eventually, maybe,
you'll actually
start to love me again.
You really think
we can get that back?
Yes.
Come on.
Totally.
You know what?
Maybe we should cancel
that bottle of wine tonight.
Oh?
Yeah, I just feel like
I got a bunch of stuff to do
in Philly,
and I'm sure you have
stuff to do, so we can just...
Drop me at the bus station?
Are you sure?
I just feel like
we're gonna fight.
Yeah.
So...
how 'bout let's not?
Okay.
Oh, um...
happy Valentine's Day.
Sorry. I didn't
have time to wrap it.
Wow.
I didn't know you kept this.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Thank you.
No problem.
I don't think you should
go to Philly tonight.
I think that you should stay,
and I think we should fight.
You really want to fight
on Valentine's Day?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
All right,
put your dukes up, Beesly.
Hi.
Hey, you okay?
I couldn't do it.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you don't
have to apologize.
I just-- I just want you
to be happy, okay?
We're breaking up.
And just so you know,
I was worried
that you were dead.
You were gone for three months.
Andy? David. Still here.
What was that
about three months?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net