Let's think this through.
If we ask corporate for that, then...
They are either gonna say yes... or no.
Could go either way.
We don't know what
they are going to say.
- Think it through !
- Have to think it through.
Because if they say no...
Can we not ?
No, yes we have to.
You know why ?
Cause I don't like to be
cooped up in that office.
In that box all day long.
Heisman !
Because I need to think. Okay, Jim ?
Oh, Kevin !
Nice catch.
Oscar !
Intercepted. Right here.
- Right or the left.
- Give it to me.
Phyllis, give me the ball.
Okay, give me the ball.
You guys...Creed. Give me the ball.
Right now.
- Give it to me.
- Ryan.
Fumble ! Yeah !
All right, hey, Dwight !
- You all right, Ryan ?
-  Yeah.
Pam !
Episode 217 - Season 2
DWIGHT'S SPEECH
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation: Catch-22 Team
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
They're having a sale on TiVo.
Maybe I should get a TiVo.
DVD burner.
Maybe I should get one of those.
You are so lucky, Jim.
You are so lucky you
don't have this problem.
What was the ninth place prize again ?
A loaf of bread ?
Cojino's pizza.
Great. Tasty terrific pizza.
Question, do their pizza play DVDs ?
Dwight was the top salesman
of the year at our company.
He wins a little prize money and
gets honored at some convention
It is literally the highest possible
honor that a Northeastern, Pennsylvania;
based, mid-sized, paper company,
regional salesman, can attain. So...
- What did I do to deserve this ?
- Are you sad that Dwight beat you ?
- No.
- Are you gonna cry, Jim ?
- Do you need a tissue ?
- I heard that you got a wedding dress.
- Do you have pictures ?
-Yeah. I'll show 'em to you later.
I should get back.
- Talk to you guys later.
- Okay, cool.
I have a ton of stuff
to do for the wedding.
And I have to do it in the office.
And that can be kind of awkward.
Just because people, can get all
weird about wedding stuff.
I just don't want to offend...
Angela. Or someone.
- That's what she said.
- I don't get it.
Grapes, seductive.
So, you ready for the big
speech this afternoon ?
Well, it's not really a big speech.
You're still coming, right ?
Abso-fruitly.
Fruit, grapes. Nailed the joke.
Matter of time.
And yes, it is a big speech.
Biggest of your life.
Speaker at the sales convention.
Been there, done that.
Went there again, did it again.
Two years in a row. Consecutive.
I just I miss the feeling of knowing
that you did a good job.
Because somebody
gives you proof of it.
Sir, you're awesome.
Here's a plaque.
What, a whole year has gone by,
and you need more proof ?
Here's a certificate.
They stopped making
plaques that year.
What if I give a really
long extended thank you ?
For instance, thank you, Mr. Blank.
- Thank you, very, very...
- That would look terrible.
These are mostly salesmen, and
salesmen expect to be entertained.
And  you are the main act.
When I was in the sixth grade, I was a
finalist in our school spelling bee.
It was me against Raj Patel.
And I misspelled,
in front of the entire school.
The word "failure".
I can't do this.
That's because you're
incapable of doing it.
Because you don't know how.
Because you have no skills.
Dwight, there's no way
I can possibly teach you,
you need to know about
public speaking by speech time.
Okay.
But, I can teach you enough so that
you don't embarrass me or the company.
Okay, deal. I'll do whatever you say.
No questions asked.
Well, if you have a question,
you should ask me.
I'll try to think of one...
Don't-don't try to think of
a question to humor me.
Just try not to be such an idiot.
Is that an insult or is that part
of the public speaking advice ?
Insult.
Mom, I'm sorry. I know you and dad
are chipping in for the wedding.
But I do not want
orange invitations.
Yes.
Well, if you really want...
Hi, yeah, can I talk to one
of your travel agents ?
I'm gonna take a trip.
I'm gonna get out of town for a while.
And go someplace...
Not here.
Where do I want to go ?
That is an excellent question.
And one I probably should have
thought about before I called you.
I get here early every morning
so I can set the thermostat.
I like it a little cooler,
around 66 degrees.
I'm more productive.
Maybe some people don't
like it as cold as I do.
But I don't care.
But  seriously, what's the difference
between a salesman and a saleswoman ?
- A saleswoman has a vagina.
- It's a joke, Dwight.
- It's not a sex ed class.
- But I'm right.
Yeah, you're right about the difference
between a man and a woman.
But not about the punchline
to the joke, all right ?
The difference between a salesman
and a saleswoman is boobs.
Hey, do you remember
the speeches that you gave ?
I do. Both of them.
- Could I have a copy of one of them?
- No, no, they would remember.
Look, it doesn't matter what you say.
it just matters that you're saying
something that people care about.
Yeah? All right, here we go.
Watch this.
Attention everybody !
Attention please.
I have some very great
news from corporate.
We had a wonderful quarter,
and as a result,
all of you are getting
bonuses for $1,000.
- Yeah !
- Congratulations.
You see that ?
You see how they responded to me ?
In that moment, I had them.
- That is so great about the bonus !
- No, no. It's not true.
I was just talking.
So, just go out there and say anything.
They'll eat it up,
they're a great audience.
Go ahead, get the wallpaper.
Wallpaper the ceiling if you want.
Excuse me ?
May I have your attention please ?
There has been an accident on 84 West.
Cars have skidded off the
road into the safety railing.
Several  cars have flipped.
There is broken glass everywhere.
Several people are injured.
Do we know anyone who
was injured in the accident ?
Brad Pitt.
Also, there will be no bonuses.
- Why would this affect our bonuses ?
- They're unrelated.
Is Brad okay ?
He will never act again.
Also, this branch is closing.
What the hell is going on here ?
- Are we out of jobs ?
- Yes.
This is karma for what he
did to Jennifer Anniston.
He's kidding. Dwight was kidding.
And I don't know why
because it wasn't funny.
And it was just horrible.
- Michael ?
- Yeah ?
You said we were getting bonuses.
All right. Everybody in
the conference room now.
Let's go ! Let's do it.
Cancel the wallpaper
As your leader and your friend,
I sort of demand that you can
all speak in public as I can.
And did, twice.
You saw the plaque, right ?
All right, we're all gonna go around the
room and we're going to make toasts.
And that way we will overcome
or fear of public speaking.
- You mean toastmasters ?
- Pam !
I'm public speaking.
Stop public interrupting me.
Actually, this would be good
practice for your wedding toast.
Yeah, the bride doesn't really do,
have you ever been to a wedding ?
- Can I go ?
- Yes
Good. Jim taking the initiative.
So, I am going on a trip.
But I'm not really sure
where I'm going yet.
It'a kinda open ended.
So I was hoping maybe you guys
would have some suggestions.
You should go to Hedonism.
- What is that ?
- It's like Club Med.
But everything is naked.
I was thinking more like Europe.
Or something like that.
But good second choice.
Been to Amsterdam.
Okay, you know what ?
That's not a toast.
You're not standing up.
- To Amsterdam.
-  When did you go there ?
After my divorce.
Really? For like, how long ?
About a week or...maybe or month.
- I can't
- Jimmy, listen to me
You do not want to go
to Amsterdam, trust me.
- Where do I wanna go ?
- I'd send you to Hong Kong.
I'd like to say hi to
my friends in China.
Wode Zhongguode Pengyou Nihao.
Okay. Dwight.
Show us what you have learned today.
Good morning, Vietnam !
Okay, you know what ?
This isn't working.
Because, I'm not
nervous in front of them.
- They're my subordinates.
- No, we're not.
Yes, you are. I am the
assistant regional manager.
- Which means absolutely nothing.
- Michael, can you explain ?
- Well, it's mostly made up. So...
Dwight is not going to
do a good job, it's sad.
And they're expecting excellence
because I did do such a great job.
Two years in a row I killed.
It was amazing.
Confidence, Dwight !
Dwight.
If you could travel anywhere
in the world, where would you go ?
I can travel anywhere, except Cuba.
And I WILL travel to New Zealand.
And walk the Lord of the
Rings trail to Mordor
And then I will hike Mt. Doom.
So, you know, just leave me alone.
Okay, just trying to get
some advice on my trip.
Oh please, you're not taking any trip.
You know, I majored in
public speaking in college?
You did ?
And the first thing
that they teach you
is that you've gotta
be true to yourself.
And you are all about authority.
Yes, I am.
The great speakers throughout
history were not joke tellers.
They were people of passion.
So, if you wanna do well today,
you gotta do what they did.
- Which is?
- You gotta wave your arms.
And you've gotta pound your fists.
Many times.
So as to emphasize your point.
Okay, I didn't actually major
in public speaking.
But I did download speeches from
some of history's famous dictators.
Like this one.
Originally given by Benito Mussolini.
Okay, look, I know you're giving
this speech on your own.
But I wrote up a few talking
points for you to look at.
- Hope you don't mind.
-  I'll glance at it.
It's time, Dwight.
The grim reaper is here.
The very best of luck to you, Dwight.
Thank you, Angela.
Why'd you pick the
VR for the reception ?
Roy has a connection.
It's nicer than you think.
You're  inviting Jim ?
Of course, he's one of
my closest friends.
All right.
Ready ? Here we go !
Wow, it's a little bit bigger
than I remembered.
Come on, we're down here in the front.
I am just feeling under the weather.
And, I think that I will
go home and rest.
I've never ever seen
you take a sick day.
Well, I've seen you take enough
for the both of us.
Next, I'd like to introduce the
Dunder-Mifflin salesman of the year.
Dwight Schrute !
Dwight, how we doing ?
- Okay, you know what ?
- Okay.
You know what ? Okay. No, no problem.
You're lucky you have me,
- I am going to cover for you.
All right !
Good morning Vietnam !
I am not Dwight Schrute.
Not at all. I am Michael Scott.
His mentor and boss.
And until Dwight comes up,
if he ever does,
I wanted to say a few words
about excellence.
What makes a work
environment excellent ?
Well, there are many things.
I believe, that do such
a thing of that... nature.
And one would be humor.
What is the difference between
a salesman and a saleswoman ?
I always set it at 69.
Maybe we'll use a DJ.
That's the one thing Roy's in
charge of for this wedding,
but all he's managed
to do is set a date.
Well, he did a great job.
June 10th is perfect.
I want a June wedding.
I've always wanted one.
Ryan, do you know when you
would want to get married ?
Actually, I don't see
ever getting married.
Ryan, you should be more sensitive.
It's obvious she likes you.
- And comments like that, they just...
- I know what I said.
I'm very sorry, I did not know that
you were wearing a hearing aid.
And I just thought you were speaking...
Abnormally.
And now, the black guy from
the Police Academy movies.
A robot.
Michael Winslow. Anyone ?
Car starting.
All right, Dwight Schrute, everyone.
Good luck.
That is a tough crowd.
Blood alone moves
the wheels of history !
Have you ever asked yourselves
in an hour of meditation,
which everyone finds during the day,
How long we have been
striving for greatness ?
Not only the years we've been at war,
the war of work.
But from the moment, as a child,
when we realized that the
world could be conquered.
It has been a lifetime struggle.
A never-ending fight.
I say to you, and you will understand,
that it is a privilege to fight !
We  are warriors !
Salesmen of Northeastern
Pennsylvania, I ask you.
Once more, rise and be worthy
of this historical hour.
I got a time share on Key West
that might be available.
Maybe, thanks.
- You really think you're gonna go?
- Yeah, I'm definitely going.
Nice, send me a postcard.
Jim has worked at the same
place for five years.
Jim eats the same ham and cheese
sandwich everyday for lunch.
I don't know,
if I were a betting man,
I'd say he will have a fun
weekend in Philadelphia.
No revolution is worth anything
unless it can defend itself !
Some people will tell you
salesman is a bad word.
They'll conjure up images
of used car dealers...
...and door to door charlatans.
This is our duty to change
their perception.
I say, salesmen...
and women...of the world, unite.
We must never acquiesce.
For it is together !
Together that we prevail !
We must never concede control
of the motherland, for it is...
Together that we prevail !
Australia ?
I've always wanted to go there.
I'm going.
I'm a little nervous to run into Dwight
on his connecting flight to Mordor,
But, other than that...,
Yeah, I bought the ticket.
Non-refundable.
That's awesome.
Where are you staying ?
I don't know.
I feel like I have plenty of time
to figure out the details, but.
When are you leaving ?
I'm leaving...on June 8th.
Yeah.
And I'm really sorry about that.
I just...
Yeah, that's too bad.
Yeah.
Do you want me to take
these on my way out ?
It's okay, I got it.
Alright.
Ok. Thanks.
- There you are. What happened ?
- I got thirsty. How it go ?
It was amazing.
I wish you would have been there.
You would not believe
what happened here.
What, did something happen ?
This woman came in.
Sat down. Ordered a drink.
The bartender asked for her ID,
which I thought was odd.
- Because I pegged her at, like, 35.
- Weird.
Yeah, really weird.
So, she's like, I don't have my ID.
Please, give me one.
And he's like, I can't do that.
I can't serve you.
- Con artist.
- She might have been.
So she says fine,
I will go to my room.
I will get my purse,
I will come back.
I'll show you my ID.
She hasn't come back yet.
She's probably in the room
drinking from the minibar.
Right ?
Dwight gave a great speech.
That's the word on the street, anyway.
And I entertained Dwight to no
end with my bar story.
I captivated the guy...
who captivated 1 000 guys.
Can you believe that ? 1 000 guys.
www.tvsubtitles.net