Oh, yeah! I've got a big box, yes I do!
I've got a big box,
how about you?
I've got a big box, yes I do,
I've got a big box, how about you?
I think you don't know
what you're saying.
It is "from Sah-bray," our new
owner, and it is "to Sah-bray." Us!
I wonder what's inside.
Scissor me.
Dunder Mifflin was
recently bought
by an electronics
company named Sah-bray.
They stepped in at the eleventh
hour and they saved our asses.
Although David Wallace said
that we were the one branch
that was actually
working right,
so we probably could've
saved our own asses.
We didn't need them
touching our asses.
(SHOUTING)
Wow!
Awesome.
For Accounting,
a brand new printer,
and for the sales staff,
a new fax machine.
This cord has
Creed written all over it.
And whoever would like
a brand new scanner
can come visit it
in my office. Thank you.
Here we go.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
Cool. What next?
Guys, um, who's Gabe?
This note says to
put the box aside
for a Gabe Lewis,
who's coming tomorrow.
Okay, everybody, listen up.
I have some bad news.
Due to circumstances
beyond my control...
Impulsivity and
inattention to detail...
Hey, hey.
I have opened a box which
should not have been opened...
Terrible mistake.
...and distributed things
which should not
have been distributed.
Un-distributable.
Well, maybe we can
put the box back together.
Impossible.
He opened it like an ape.
I think we can do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Did we try printer first,
shredder at an angle?
Yeah. Fax cable, then
the scanner upside-down?
Yes.
Have you tried
making everything smaller?
And...
Wow! Really nice job!
This group of people, when
they put their minds together,
they can do
something great.
And I think that you should
all be proud of yourselves.
(CELL PHONE RINGING IN BOX)
Oh, Michael!
All right, relax. We can
do it. We just did it.
So, we can do this again.
Erin, scissor me, please?
No, don't!
Thank you. Oh!
Got it. Okay.
(RINGING CONTINUES)
All right, he's on his
way up. Okay, we ready?
What do you want us to do?
Why do I have to
explain everything?
Because we're usually
not on the same page.
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh. Okay.
And to you.
Gabe seems tall.
Hope we get along.
I had a very good thing going
with David Wallace.
He was a good guy. He was
somebody I could trust.
There he is.
You can really see
that he is okay
taking a picture with me,
even though I was there
for disciplinary reasons.
Welcome. Scranton hotdog from Scranton?
You know what, Dwight? Let's
give him a minute to settle in.
Shall we?
Okay.
Hi. My name
is Gabe Lewis.
I am Coordinating Director
for Emerging Regions.
Hello, Gabe. I am
Michael Scott, co-manager.
This is my protégé,
Jim Halpert.
Co-manager, actually.
In training.
Trained. Loving it.
Good at it, so...
We are very impressed
with this branch,
and we are so excited
about this merger.
We're very excited,
too, aren't we, guys?
Right?
ANDY: So excited.
We have a little song
prepared for you.
Actually,
if you don't mind,
I would love to put this
on the Sabre website.
Sabre.
Sabre. Sabre.
It's Sabre.
ANDY: It's Sabre.
Oh. Of course.
Sabre.
MICHAEL: Good.
Take it away, guys.
Okay.
BOTH: (SINGING) Hopped off
the train in Scranton, PA
Another cloudy gray afternoon
Jumped in the cab Here
you are for the first time
Look to the right And you
see the Electric City sign
This is gonna be a good day
For Dunder Mifflin and Sah-bray
(ANDY CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Sabre.
It's Sabre.
Dunder Mifflin and Sabre
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Dunder
Mifflin is a part of Sah-bray
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Dunder Mifflin is a part of Sabre
Dunder Mifflin
is a part of Sabre
You sure it's Sabre?
Hey.
Thank you.
Hey, we should be fine
if we leave around 11:20.
Oh, you MapQuested it.
It's four blocks away.
Well, now we
won't get lost.
Or we could drive,
and that takes one minute.
We found a great
local daycare.
It's rated really high by all
the local parenting websites,
but that means it's also
really hard to get into.
Turns out a lot of parents want
the very best for their children.
That's weird.
We're hoping our interview
seals the deal.
But if not,
there's always the Army.
The infantry.
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
So you've just
been bought by Sabre.
You've probably got
a lot of questions.
Hi, I'm Christian Slater.
What's it like to work for Sabre?
Let's find out together.
Working at Sabre means
taking on the challenge
of the road that
rises to meet you.
Sabre is respecting the past, but
opening the window to the future.
Have you ever tasted a
rainbow? At Sabre, you will.
You'll find it easy to embrace
the Sabre spirit. Welcome.
We're very excited to go
on this journey with you.
JIM: So, you've been shown
a nonsensical video.
You're probably wondering, "What's
going on?" Well, you're not alone.
Wow. Really terrific.
Most of our business comes
from selling printers,
so don't think of yourselves
as paper salesmen anymore,
but as printer salesmen
who also sell paper.
Perfect.
No. Don't like that.
At Sabre, we really encourage
honest communication.
You should always feel free
to express your thoughts...
Talk about vacation days!
We have a policy
here at Sabre
where we are allowed
to take two weeks.
But I banked six weeks.
I already booked
a Great Lakes cruise.
Hey, who the hell's
going through our stuff?
Actually, that's Nick.
He's your new IT guy.
He's setting up
a site blocker,
mostly blocking
the inappropriate sites,
and then there are the time-wasting
sites like Twitter, YouTube.
We are blocking
those as well.
No. Don't like that.
Okay, did everyone get one?
With these bottles, we eliminate
the need for plastic water bottles,
which are the scourge
of the environment.
We will still get to use the
little cups, though, right?
Little cups?
Like paper or plastic?
I don't know what
they're made of.
They're two-ounce paper cups dipped
in plastic. He goes through 20 a day.
Okay. Well,
I bet you could fit
20 little cups of water
in your aluminum bottle.
You know what
can't fit in a bottle
are the 20 little trips
I take to the cooler,
and the 20 little scans
I do of everybody
to make sure everything's
running smoothly,
and the 20 little conversations
that I have with Stanley.
That's okay.
There is a small part
of me that is actually
very excited about
this new company.
But 70% of me is water, and
the other part, the real part,
the part that has
feelings and emotions
and thoughts and
makes decisions,
and, if I can be crass,
makes babies,
that part thinks that
all of these changes suck...
Really?
You don't have enough water
in there? Your stomach?
(EXCLAIMS)
What?
Looks like we kicked it.
MICHAEL: I miss the old
Dunder Mifflin. (INAUDIBLE)
Too much change is not a
good thing. Ask the climate.
I don't want to
appear ungrateful
for everything
Sabre is doing for us.
I don't get that sense
at all from you, so...
Well, you should
have a little,
but it's great
that you don't,
because I am trying to
embrace all of these changes.
But I'm... I'll be honest,
I'm having trouble
wrapping my head
around a couple of them.
Which ones?
(SIGHS) All of them.
Well, I wish that
I could do something,
but it's kind of policy,
you know?
Above my pay grade.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, maybe we should call.
We should call someone.
I could help. I'm good with
bosses. Call one of the higher ups?
You know what?
Let me see what I can do.
(BOTH GASPING)
Okay, this is officially the
cutest thing I've ever seen.
Cubbies! I totally
forgot about cubbies.
There's a finger-painting
station and a curly slide.
Am I too old to go here?
Oh!
Adorable, right?
I walked in on someone
in the bathroom. What?
I just walked in on
someone in the bathroom.
Who?
I don't know.
The guy we're meeting with?
I don't know,
I don't know.
I am telling you, there
are no strawberries in here.
Well, I saw them in there.
Well, maybe they ran away
'cause the pizza was, like,
(IN ITALIAN ACCENT) "Hey, get out
of here, you stupid strawberries."
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I think when Andy
finally asks me out,
he's gonna try to top what
he did with the drum line.
I can't wait to see
what he comes up with.
The ball is totally
in Erin's court,
after the whole
drum line thing.
First let me say, I told them
everything that you wanted me to say
in just the way you
wanted me to say it, so...
Gabe, honey, I love this, I
love the sound of your voice,
but I really need
some new information now.
Okay. I told the story
of your uncle,
and I have a feeling
that you would've really,
really been proud
of the way... Okay.
Wait a minute, who is
it? Who's there? What?
Is there somebody
in the room with you?
I want to see who it is.
Turn me around.
I don't. It's just...
Turn me around. Now.
(WHISTLES) Hey, buddy?
Was it something I said?
Hello. No. My name's
Michael Scott. Hello.
Well, hello, Mr. Scott,
pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you. We are very
excited about the merger with Sabre.
I think you have
a great accent.
Thank you. I've been working
on it since I was a little girl.
To what do I owe the pleasure
of this video chat?
Well, I am a little concerned about
all these changes, to be quite frank.
I think we have done things a
certain way here at Dunder Mifflin
for quite some time.
Pardon.
Pardon me, Mr. Scott,
but the last time
I saw a company
as mismanaged
as Dunder Mifflin
was my grandson's
snowball company,
so you'll excuse me
if I'd prefer
that you all adapt to
the way we do things.
Okay. I feel very strongly
that you can't just come in here
and change everything that
people have been doing forever.
Is Christian Slater back
there? Because he knows...
He'd know what to do.
So listen,
why don't you tell Gabe
if by the end of the day
you can't handle the changes?
I've already told him, but I will tell
him again, if you think that'll help.
I would take until the end
of the day if I were you.
(GRUNTS)
(CLATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Pam and Jim?
Hey. I'm Jerry.
Hi, Jerry.
Jerry.
Good to see you.
Come on in.
My office is
right back here.
This is the playroom.
This is great.
Gotta confess,
we came a little early,
so we got a quick
look around, but...
So you saw it already.
No. Yes, we saw this, yes.
No, it wasn't like
a look around,
we really just had a peek. Quick peek.
Didn't focus on anything
in particular. It's lovely.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Gotta take this, sorry.
JIM: Do it.
Hi, this is Jerry.
Okay, you've gotta
pull it together.
We should just go.
He's really uncomfortable.
He's uncomfortable
because you're acting weird,
so you have to
stop acting weird.
What if we just bring it up?
We'll just put it out in the open?
That's the weirdest possible
solution to the problem.
Sorry about that.
Right this way.
All right.
I have come here today
to talk to Mr. David Wallace
about this whole thing
going on with Sabre.
He will know
exactly what to do.
He is not a big fan of me
dropping by unannounced,
but then again, who is?
(DRUMS BEATING)
Hey. Hi.
Michael!
Sorry, I hope you're
not busy doing something.
No, you kidding? Come on
in. Come on in. You sure?
You look great.
You look great, too.
You hungry?
I'm just having lunch.
Oh, yeah,
that sounds good.
Teddy, look who
just stopped in.
Hey.
MICHAEL: Hey.
Hey! Wow. That's very
loud. Keep it up, son!
Wow. Oh, yummy!
You have got the life, my friend. Yeah.
Can I just stay here
and never go back?
Things not going
so well over there?
Oh, man!
How much time do you have?
I have a doctor's appointment
next Thursday.
Yeah?
Hey, honey, how's your day
going? Did you do anything cool?
No, sweetie,
I just hung out.
'Cause I saw
you had shoes on,
so I didn't know
if you did anything.
No, just hanging out, hon.
You remember Michael?
Hi. Sorry, I was just
in the neighborhood
and thought
I'd come by and say...
No problem at all.
This is great.
So, what are
you guys up to?
I don't know. Maybe...
Actually, you know, I think
maybe we'll go outside.
Maybe... We'll go outside? Go outside.
There was one thing
we were curious about.
Your flexibility on things
like Easter or Memorial Day,
because we might want to change
our days around a little bit.
That seems a bit premature,
don't you think?
I don't even know if I
have a space for you yet,
and you're already lining up
your holiday plans.
No, sorry, we're kind of planners,
but we're also flexible, too,
so you know what?
Maybe we can just discuss it
when the time comes.
Yeah. If the time comes,
we can discuss it.
Is this because Jim walked in
on you going to the bathroom?
What?
Seriously? You told her?
Did it...
It might have come up
while we were
waiting for you.
And you thought that
might have something
to do with how
the meeting is going?
No, I didn't... Maybe,
because it doesn't seem
to be going super well.
You didn't consider the fact that
it might not be going super well
just because it might
not be going super well?
No, 'cause we're
really nice people,
but you don't
seem to like us.
I'm being
perfectly pleasant.
Did you ever consider
that you might not be
as charming as
you think you are?
This coming from the guy who
still uses a children's toilet.
Why didn't you just
lock the door, man?
It doesn't lock for
the children's safety.
Anybody could have walked in.
It was story time.
Sabre is changing everything. Site
blockers, they don't let us use cups.
So I started thinking,
who could handle this?
Who would know what to do?
David Wallace
would know what to do.
What should I do,
David Wallace?
I don't know.
What can you do?
Mmm! Exactly.
What are you thinking?
It's a tough one.
It is a tough one.
I don't have
any ideas for you.
Yeah,
but one would be good.
Hey, okay, wait.
Okay.
I want to tell you about
a business idea I have.
Okay.
You know how kids leave
their toys everywhere? Right?
So this is a vacuum. It's
like a Shop-Vac type of thing.
(EXCLAIMS)
Teaches kids how to pick up
their own toys. Right?
Baseball gloves,
Hacky Sacks,
drumsticks...
(EXCLAIMS) Picks it up.
So the kid's making
the noise to pick it up?
Yeah. No.
No, no,
that's the vacuum noise.
Okay.
You don't like it.
No, I think it's...
No, it's okay.
Another guy from Dunder
Mifflin, Arnie from Research,
he's gonna draw up
the prototype, and...
It's like a Shop-Vac.
Did I say that?
Yep.
It'll be okay.
Hey, any fun
weekend plans?
No. You?
No, actually.
So, nothing?
No movies or parties
or anything you might
want to invite someone to?
Nothing. It's wide open.
Okay.
That's as hard
as I can hint.
Hey, you know, if you want, I'm
sure I could get Arnie onboard,
if you want to join us
for Suck lt.
Work together again.
The what?
"Suck lt."
That's what it's called.
Oh! Okay.
Huh? Catchy.
Kid's will love it.
I like it.
There are very few things
that would make me
not want to team up
with David Wallace,
and Suck It
is one of them.
See you later.
Oh, Michael.
I know.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for having me.
Well, that's not the David
Wallace that I remember.
That was some sort
of weird creature
that lives in
David Wallace's house.
Oh, my God. All right!
Just get me out of here.
Hello! Is anybody home?
Thank you, Erin.
Now, if everyone would
please ready their canteens
so I can fill them
with the sweet, sweet
nectar of Gabe's homeland
and then propose a toast.
Here we go.
You know when people
say getting fired
was the best thing that
ever happened to them?
I feel sorry
for those people.
That?
The best thing? Really?
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
Well, I'm not really one
for making speeches.
Yes, you are.
Since when?
You make a lot.
MICHAEL: But I feel
pretty good right now.
I really do. A lot better than
I did earlier, let me tell you.
That's your toast?
No, this is my toast.
I think this whole thing
with Sabre is gonna work out.
I have a very good
feeling about it.
Michael, this isn't a toast,
you're just thinking out loud.
Here's my toast.
Orange juice is in here,
and like Sabre, it is from
Florida, and it is good.
Just 'cause you have liquid,
that doesn't make it a toast.
Here's the toast.
I'm gonna do it now.
Raise your container
to us and to Sabre.
PHYLLIS: To us and to Sabre. Hear, hear.
Mmm.
Wow, that is metallicy.
That's like drinking a battery.
Really gets you in the fillings,
doesn't it? Okay, anyway, welcome.
Well, it's a mess,
what a mess
What you gonna do
You're gonna take out your Suck
It And you'll suck it, suck it
Take out your Suck It
and you'll suck it
Suck it
Yeah
Take out my Suck It and we'll Suck it
Suck it
Yeah. Take out my Suck It and
we'll suck it Take out, suck it
Yeah
(WHOOPS)
Teddy!
Dad!
www.tvsubtitles.net