Hey, Ryan.
Can I get you a pencil
from the warehouse?
Uh, no thanks.
I'm good.
Oh, it's okay.
I'm going down.
Um...
Oh.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
All right,
I'll be right back.
Whoo!
There you go.
Awesome!
Thank you.
You're welcome!
Michael, could you
get me a pen
from down in the warehouse?
Don't mind if I do.
See you in a minute.
Okay!
Whoo!
There you go,
fresh from the warehouse.
Hey, Michael.
Would you get me some coffee
from the warehouse?
There's coffee
in the kitchen, Pam.
But the warehouse coffee
tastes so much better.
Yeah, it's better.
All right.
Okay.
I am like Bette Midler
in For the Boys.
Gotta keep the troops
entertained.
With cream and sugar?
All right.
www.1000fr.com present
sync:FRM@¹¾ßË
So I wanted to let you know
that we lost Ed Truck.
Oh...kay.
Let me see
if I have his cell.
Is this the only reason
you are calling, Jan?
Or does somebody miss me?
Michael...Ed died
over the weekend.
Oh, wow.
Attention, everybody.
I just received a call
from corporate
with some news that they felt
that I should know first.
My old boss,
Ed Truck, has died.
Oh, Michael,
that's such terrible news.
You must feel so sad.
Yes, I am.
It's very sad.
Because he was my boss.
Oh, that's a shame.
Ed was a good guy.
That's right.
You worked with him.
So did Creed.
Well, I'll be
in my office.
In case anybody
wants to drop by.
Cheer me up.
So did you hear the news?
The news that you
just announced?
That Ed died?
Yeah.
Is there anything I can do?
Oh, gosh, what can
anybody do, really?
Just...psh.
He was almost 70.
Circle of life.
Yeah.
Oh. Okay.
Mmmmm.
Okay.
What's going on with
Fairfield County Schools?
Karen, did you generate
that price list?
Um...shoot.
Uh, I will. Sorry.
Okay, just get it done.
Jim, will you make sure?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Suck up!
Ahem!
Josh, did you hear
what I said?
Thank you, everyone.
Damn it.
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
They're just out
of Herr's Chips.
Oh.
But don't worry about it.
My snack food
doesn't fall
under  the umbrella
of your authority.
Mm, that's where
you're wrong.
I'm your project
supervisor today.
And I've just decided
that we're
not doing anything
until you get the chips
that you require.
So I think we should
go get some.
Now, please.
It's a real shame
about Ed, huh?
Yeah. Must really
have you thinkin'.
About what?
The older you get,
the bigger the chance is
you're gonna die.
You knew that.
Ed was decapitated.
What?
Really?
He was drunk as a skunk.
He was flying down Route 6.
He slides under
an 18-wheeler.
Pop, it snaps right off.
Oh, my God.
That is the way to go.
Instant death.
Very smart.
You  know, a human can go on
living for several hours
after being decapitated.
You're thinking
of a chicken.
What'd I say?
That is just not the way
a Dunder Mifflin manager
should go.
I'm sorry.
Alone, out of the blue.
Not even have his own head
to comfort him.
So I'm not exactly...
sure how to say this.
Ed was decapitated.
What are you doing?
You said you didn't
know how to say it.
He...
was driving
on the road.
And he went under a truck.
And that's when his
h-h-head was...
separated from...
the rest of him.
And I will
let you know more
as soon as I find out.
Hey.
Hi.
If my head ever comes off,
I would like you
to put it on ice.
I do not want
to talk about this.
When I die,
I want to be frozen.
And if they have to freeze me
in pieces,
so be it.
I will wake up
stronger than ever,
because I will have
used that time
to figure out exactly
why I died,
and what moves
I could have used
to defend myself better
now that I know what hold
he had me in.
I don't understand.
We have a day honoring
Martin Luther King.
But he didn't even
work here.
I understand
how you feel, Michael.
I really do.
So would it be helpful
to give everyone the day off?
You really don't get it,
do you?
You don't understand
these people.
That is the last thing
that they would want
is a day off.
Well, what would you
suggest?
A statue.
Of Ed?
Yeah.
I'm not sure
that's realistic.
Well, I think it would
be very realistic.
It would look just like him.
No, that's not--
We could have
his eyes light up.
You could have his arms move.
That is not a statue.
That is a robot.
I think that is
a great way to honor Ed.
And how big
do you want this robot?
Life-size.
Mm, no.
Better make it 2/3.
Easier to stop
if it turns on us.
What the hell
are you two talking about?
Well, we are talking
about how to properly honor
a man who gave his life
as regional manger
of this company, Jan!
You know what, Michael?
I've really
tried with you today.
And I have to get
back to work.
Oh, do you?
You know who wished
they could get back to work
is Ed Truck!
But Ed Truck can't
because he is--
Good-bye.
dead!
Look...I gave him
a six-foot extension cord,
so he can't chase us.
That's perfect.
Okay, that is a no
on the West Side Market.
Okay, great.
I think that's enough.
Can I...get back
to work now?
Wow. Never pegged you
for a quitter.
I am not a quitter.
I will do this
all day, if you want.
Really?
Yeah, all day.
Hey.
What are we doing?
What's the game?
want in.
Oh, there's no game.
We're just trying to get
these chips for Karen.
Did you check
the vending machine?
Oh, the vending machines?
How did we miss that?
I have no idea.
We went right
for the copier.
Mm-hmm. And then we
checked the fax machine.
Yeah, nothing there.
Did you check your butt?
Ooh, can you imagine
how much blood there was?
If it happened right here,
it would reach
all the way to reception.
Probably get on Pam.
Okay, that's enough.
What?
We do not want
to hear about this.
Well, you know what?
I didn't wanna
hear about it either, Stanley.
But I did, and now I can't
stop picturing it.
He leaves work.
He's on his way home.
Wham! His cappa is detated
from his head.
You have just
spit on my face.
Well, you know what?
There's something wrong
with you.
There is something wrong
with everybody in here.
Because we have lost
a member of our family.
And you don't wanna
talk about it.
You don't wanna
think about it.
You just wanna
get back to work.
There are five stages
to grief.
Which are denial,
anger,  bargaining,
depression, and acceptance.
And right now, out there,
they are all denying
the fact
that they're sad.
And...that's hard.
And it's
making them all angry.
And it is my job
to try to get them
all the way through
to acceptance.
And if not acceptance,
then just depression.
If I can get them depressed,
then I'll have done my job.
I'm going to throw you
this ball.
When you catch the ball,
I want you to say
the name of a person
very important to you,
somebody really special,
who died.
d then I want you to say
how they died.
And you may cry,
if you like.
That is encouraged.
Let me just start.
Let me show you how this works.
I catch the ball.
I lost Ed Truck.
And...it feels like somebody
took my heart
and dropped it into a bucket
of boiling tears.
And, at the same time,
somebody else
is hitting my soul
in the crotch
with a frozen sledgehammer.
And then a third guy
walks in
and starts punching me
in the grief bone.
And I am crying.
And nobody can hear me,
because I am terribly,
terribly...
terribly alone.
Excuse me, I'm sorry
to interrupt.
I need to see Pam.
There seems to be, like,
something wrong
with the radiator
in her car.
Okay.
Fine.
Hurry back.
There's nothing wrong
with your car.
I just thought you might
want a break
from the grief
counseling session.
Oh...I would
like a break.
How are you liking
the new car?
Great.
Yeah?
It sure is small.
Got air bags?
I think so.
I don't know, I was mainly
focused on the cup holders.
Well, you're still not
driving so fast, are you?
Yeah.
Hi, yeah, this is Mike
from the West Side Market.
Well, we added a shipment
of Herr's
salt and vinegar chips.
And we ordered that about
three weeks ago, and have--
Yeah.
You have 'em
in the warehouse?
Great.
What is my store number?
Six.
Wa--no.
I'll call you back.
Shut up.
Six?
Okay, we can start.
You waited for me?
Y eah.
Pam, you're a member
of this family.
So we will wait
for our family members.
Phyllis, you wanna
give it a shot?
I got it.
When my mother
was pregnant with me,
they did an ultrasound
and found she was having twins.
When they did
another ultrasound
a few weeks later,
they discovered that
I had re-sorbed
the other fetus.
Do I regret this?
No.
I believe his tissue
has made me stronger.
I now have the strength
of a grown man
and a little baby.
Okay, why don't you
throw the ball to somebody else?
Nope.
Oh, yes, Stanley,
Come on, your turn.
You have to go.
I will not!
Okay...
I'm going to
toss the ball
to Pam.
Let's see.
I had an aunt
that I was really close to.
She was this amazing
female boxer.
Um, anyway,
she was injured in a fight,
and she was paralyzed.
So you can imagine
how upset I was...
when I found out
that she asked her manager
to remove
her breathing tube
so she could die.
Wow.
If you want to cry,
that's okay.
Thanks.
Um...
A few years ago,
my family was
on a safari in Africa.
And, um, my cousin...
Mufasa...
was, um, he was
trampled to death
by a pack of wildebeests.
And, um, we all...
took it really hard.
All of us kind
of in the audience...
of what happened.
Do you wanna
talk about it anymore?
Oh, it would probably
take me, like,
an hour and a half
to tell that whole story.
Me me, me me me.
Yes. Okay.
Um...I was trying
to throw this party once.
And everyone was over
for the weekend.
And then
my Uncle Bernie died.
And so me and
my best friend,
we had to pretend
like he was alive.
So...
Wait a second.
That's Weekend at Bernie's.
Do you think that this
is a game?
Well, there is a ball.
All right,
we're starting over.
No, I'm done.
You are not leaving!
No, we are not done.
We really have
a lot of work to do.
Yeah, well,
you know what?
The guy who had my job
has died.
And nobody cares.
And he sat at my desk.
Michael...
Look, I know
this is hard for you.
But death's just
a part of life.
I mean, just this morning,
I saw a little bird
fly into the glass doors
downstairs and die.
And I had to keep going.
How do you know?
What?
That that bird was dead?
Did you check...
its breathing?
It was obvious.
Was its heart beating,
Toby?
Did you check it?
No, of course you didn't.
You're not a veterinarian.
You  don't know anything!
Michael!
Michael...
Oh, God.
Ohh!
Oh, my God!
Come on.
Poor little fella.
Oh, shoot.
He's a goner.
No, he's not.
Yeah.
Michael, get him
away from your head!
He is covered
in germs and bacteria!
You can't get
diseases from a bird!
That bird should not
be in the kitchen.
We don't know
if it's dead.
Uh, no, that thing is dead.
You want me
to flush him?
Attention, everybody.
This will only
take a second...
of your time.
Today at 4:00 p.m.,
we will be meeting
in the parking lot
to have a funeral service
for this bird.
I have a lot
of work to do.
Well...I'm sorry
to inconvenience you,
Meredith.
But that is what you do
when things die.
You honor them.
Toby killed this bird.
And now we are going
to honor it.
But--
No! No! No!
That's enough.
You know what?
This bird is dead.
It died alone.
The least you can do
is be there for him now.
Find a box for him.
I'm calling a supermarket
in Montreal.
Nice.
Bonjour, je cherche
de chips
de la marque Herr's.
Non?
Oh, merci comme même.
Au revoir.
Nope.
Sounded good.
Thanks.
It's okay.
Shh.
Yes, I know.
I know it's been
a tough day.
But it's good
to let it show.
I mean, how many times
do I have to confirm plans
with Ryan for him to know
that we have a date tonight?
God.
What are--
What are you doing?!
What?
No, this is
about the right size.
No, God, no!
It's not!
What is the matter
with you?
Is that the beak?
I'm sorry,
I grew up on a farm.
We slaughtered a pig
whenever we wanted bacon.
My grandfather was re-buried
in an old oil drum.
It would've fit if he had
given me another minute.
I need a box.
I need a box,
a small box.
Not too confining.
Is it for the bird?
Yeah.
I have it covered.
Oh, thank you.
If you want to do something
for the funeral--
Yes, please.
Maybe you could play a song
on your recorder. Excellent.
Do you have it with you?
Always.
Did I wake up this morning
thinking I'd be
throwing together
a bird funeral?
You never can tell
what your day here
is gonna turn into.
Where'd you find them?
Where'd I find what?
I called the manufacturer,
who referred me
to the distributor,
to the vending machine company,
who told me that
they sell them in the machines
in the building next door.
Glad you could all make it.
You told us
we had to.
Dwight,
do you have the box?
Actually, I have it.
You made this?
Wow.
That's...
that's very nice.
When Ias five,
my mom told me
that my fish
went to the hospital
in the toilet.
And it never came back.
So we had a funeral for it.
And I remember thinking,
"I'm a little too old
for this."
And I was five.
I'd also like
to say a few words,
if that's okay.
Yes.
What do we know
about this bird?
You might think,
"Not much, it's just a bird."
But we do know
some things.
We know it was
a local bird.
Maybe it's that same bird
that surprised Oscar
that one morning with
a special present from above.
Oh, I remember that.
That was so funny.
And we know
how he died.
Flying into
the glass doors.
But you know what,
I don't think
he was being stupid.
I think he just...
really, really wanted
to come inside our building
to spread his cheer
and lift our spirits
with a song.
It's not a songbird.
Shh.
An impression, then.
Lastly, we can't help
but notice
that he was by himself
when he died.
But of course,
we all know
that doesn't mean
he was alone.
Because I'm sure
that there were lots
of other birds
out there
who cared for him
very much.
He will not be forgotten.
Amen.
* Just smile for me
and let the day begin *
* You are the sunshine *
* That lights my heart within *
Society teaches us
that having feelings
and crying
is bad and wrong.
Well, that's baloney,
because grief isn't wrong.
There is such a thing
as good grief.
Just ask Charlie Brown.
Les get back to work.
Guys, get a broom.
Let's clean this up.
Grab a broom.
You heard me.
Mush.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net