It's kinda blurry.
That's better.
Question.
What kind of bear is best?
It's a ridiculous question.
False.
Black bear.
Well, that's debatable.
There's basically
2 schools of thought...
Fact.
Bears eat beets.
Bears.
Beets.
Battlestar Galactica.
Bears do not...
What is going on?
What are you doing?
Last week, I was in a drugstore,
and I saw these glasses.
$4.
And it only cost me $7
to recreate the rest of the ensemble,
and that's a grand total of...
$11.
Imitation is the most sincere
form of flattery. So I thank you.
Identity theft is not a joke, Jim!
Millions of families suffer every year!
- Michael!
- Oh, that's funny.
Michael!
T
Tr
Tra
Tran
Trans
Transc
Transcr
Transcri
Transcrip
Transcript
Transcript :
Transcript : S
Transcript : Sw
Transcript : SwS
Transcript : SwSu
Transcript : SwSub
S
Sy
Transcript : SwSub
Syn
Sync
Transcript : SwSub
Synch
Synchr
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro
Synchro :
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : D
Synchro : Da
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : Dar
Synchro : DarK
Transcript : SwSub
Synchro : DarKs
Synchro : DarKsh
The Office US - 3x21
Product Recall
Yes, I understand.
Can I transfer you
to Customer Relations?
Absolutely.
I couldn't be
I know, I know. We're all trying
to get to the bottom of this.
Yes, I am upset.
Don't I sound upset?
It's disgusting.
I totally agree.
Well, we're going to be
recalling all of that paper.
We have a crisis.
Apparently,
a disgruntled employee at the paper mill
decided that it would be funny
to put an obscene watermark
on our 24-pound cream letter stock.
500 boxes
has gone out with the image
of a beloved cartoon duck
performing...
unspeakable acts upon a...
certain cartoon mouse
that a lot of people like.
I've never been a fan.
Everybody in here, STAT.
No time to lose.
Cry-Man Squaw, F and C, double time.
Cry-Man Squaw?
Crisis Management Squad.
F and C, double time?
Front and center,
twice as fast as you'ld normally go.
- Other questions?
- One more.
- Why are you talking like that?
- To save time, Jim.
I think you could make
the argument that it wastes time.
Yeah, she has a good point.
For example,
with the last thing you said,
by the time you explained it,
it actually took up more time.
Forget it.
Where's Creed?
- Creed,
- Here.
quality assurance.
Your job.
I really think you screwed
the pooch on this one, Creed.
Because of you, the entire
company is in jeopardy.
Every week,
I'm supposed to take 4 hours
and do a quality spot-check
at the paper mill.
And, of course, the one year
I blow it off, this happens.
We have a lot of angry
customers out there.
This puts us
at threat level Midnight.
Accounting, you are on customer
service duty today.
- That's really not our job.
- Midnight, Oscar!
Don't worry,
Kelly'll be training you.
Kelly's training us?
This day is bananas.
B-A-N-A-N-A-S.
B-A-N-A...
I don't have a headache.
I'm just preparing.
Jim, big fire in your house.
Your client, Dunmore High School,
sent out their prom invitations
on this paper. To all the kids.
- Yeah, I got a call out on them.
- No, no.
Not good enough.
This is a keystone account.
I want you in the school.
In person.
- Sure.
- Bring a partner.
- I'll go.
- No.
We need somebody who's actually
made a sale. Andy, you go.
William Dolittle, at your service.
AKA, Will Do.
Yeah, I'm definitely gonna go alone.
No, no.
I need two men on this.
That's what she said. No time!
But she did. No time!
Guys, get on this!
Dwight,
you're in charge
of the press conference.
Yes! You're entering
the "No Spin Zone."
We're having a press conference?
No, the press is just
gonna find out by themselves.
Not.
Here's the thing.
When a company screws up,
best thing
is to call a press conference.
Alert the media,
and then you control the story.
Wait for them to find out,
and the story controls you.
That's what happened to O.J.
I have invited Barbara Allen,
one of our oldest clients,
to come in here
and meet with me
for a personal apology.
The press wants a story.
I will give them a story.
- Did the press ask for a story?
- Here
is your headline.
"Scranton-area paper company,
"Dunder-Mifflin,
"apologizes to valued client.
"Some companies
"still know how business is done."
Okay?
Battle stations, everybody.
Let's go, go, go, go, go!
Yes, hello. Creed Bratton, Quality
Assurance. Dunder-Mifflin, Scranton.
I was supposed to meet
with one of your floor managers
last week for a quality inspection,
and he or she wasn't there.
And I'm trying to remember who it was.
Mm-hmm.
Who wasn't there last week?
Debbie Brown.
And which day was that?
Wednesday the 11th.
Perfect.
The difference between me
and a homeless man is this job.
I will do whatever it takes to survive.
Like I did...
when I was a homeless man.
I know the reason
that you guys became accountants
is 'cause you're not good at interacting
with people. But guess what?
From now on,
you guys are no longer losers.
So give yourselves a round of applause.
I wonder how many
phone calls you're missing
while you're teaching us to answer it.
I know.
Probably a lot.
Can you just tell us
what we need to do so we can go?
Okay, Angela.
I love your enthusiasm.
All you need to do
is pick up the phone and say,
"Customer Service.
This is Kelly. "
Except don't say Kelly.
Say your own name.
Or, if you're bored,
just make up a name.
Like one time
I said I was Bridget Jones,
and I talked like this
for the whole conversation.
Ooh, can I be...
Australian, mate?
- Absolutely!
- 'Ello, mate.
I like ice cream.
I need a boyfriend.
I like ice cream, too, mate.
Alli-gators and dingo babies.
Beer me.
What's that?
Hand me that water.
I always say, "Beer me."
Gets a laugh, like,
a quarter of the time.
So how's what's-her-name?
You know her name.
Who, Karen? Yeah, she's only
one of my oldest friends.
How's the apartment hanging?
It's fine.
Nice.
Check out this sunshine, man.
Global warming, right?
Today was supposed to be
really cold, I bet.
What about music?
Do you have any music?
Uh, yeah.
Should have said so.
I was thinking more like a CD or...
a CD?
Your call, dude.
My girlfriend made
an awesome mix. Beer me that disc.
Lord, beer me strength.
So, Tuna, when we get in there,
let's do a really good job, okay?
Did that really need to be said?
Well, not everything
a guy says needs to be said.
Sometimes it's just about
the music of a conversation.
Whoa, what the...
why is my girlfriend here?
Oh, is she that
teacher in the white?
No, she's a part-time
frozen yogurt chef.
Which one is she?
The one in the green hoodie.
I wonder if she's, like,
- a guidance counselor or something?
- No.
I don't think so.
- She's probably a tutor.
- Nope.
- She's probably a te...
- No.
- She's...
Okay, press conference in 45.
Dwight, make sure
this place looks nice.
On it.
Okay, Karen, Ryan, Pam.
Center stage.
Pam, run a comb through your hair.
First rule in roadside beet sales:
put the most attractive beets on top.
The ones that make you pull
the car over and go,
"Wow, I need this beet right now.
"Those are the money beets."
Hey!
Look sharp.
Hey.
Hu, hi!
Hello. Dwight Schrute.
And you must be, uh,
from The Washington Post.
Scranton Times.
Chad Lite. "Lighter Side of Life. "
- And "Breaking Corporate News."
- And obits.
Oh, dear God.
Okay, here are your credentials.
You've been granted
level 3 security clearance.
Don't get too excited.
That's out of 20.
Right this way.
Regional Manager Michael Scott
will address the client
in the press room shortly.
Have a seat.
Can I get you a beverage?
- Uh, yeah, I'd like a...
- Great.
Andy, you know what?
We don't have a lot of time,
so we should probably...
Jamie.
What are you doing here?
Are you a student here?
Oh... yeah.
You never told me
you're in high school.
This is weird.
I gotta go to Spanish.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
I had no idea.
Well... that's not gonna
hold up in court.
We didn't do anything illegal.
Except knock over a mailbox
with her friends.
Sir, yes, you have a valid point.
I'm sorry.
No, I am so sorry.
Really?
Dickson City.
Excuse me?
Well, I don't see how that's our fault.
And I've already told you the official
position of Dunder-Miflin is apologetic.
So I don't know what you want from me.
Okay...
First,
I just wanna say
that you are doing so good.
You have so many good qualities
that the one that you
might wanna work on is...
apologizing?
When I went over Wednesday
for the spot check,
I got a call from Debbie Brown
saying she has an emergency
dentist appointment.
Emergency dentist appointment.
Now I'm told
she told her manager she had the flu.
I'm a trusting guy, but, uh...
I just wish Debbie Brown had been there.
We would have caught this.
Yes.
I'll be sure someone returns your call.
I'm so sorry.
Bye.
Hello.
I'm looking for Michael Scott.
Mrs. Allen
is our most important client.
Because every client
Even though she's a pretty
unimportant client, really.
And so,
with the eyes of the nation upon us,
I would like to say
that Dunder-Mifflin truly regrets
this unfortunate incident.
And,
as a gesture of gratitude
for your continued loyalty,
Mrs. Allen,
I would like to present you
with this novelty check
for six months of free paper,
or 25 reams,
whichever comes first.
- You look good in this.
- So...
let us consider this matter ended.
Well, it isn't ended.
I'm very angry.
I could have lost business.
I know.
I know you're angry.
And we are truly, truly sorry.
I don't accept your apology.
The watermark
was obscene and horrifying.
Well...
we are extremely sorry.
I don't accept.
I'll be with you in a moment.
All right.
Who was that guy she was talking to?
At her locker?
Not important.
Because you're not dating her.
Because it's a felony.
But who was that guy?
Probably another high school student.
The issue with the watermark
is very serious.
- Absolutely.
- We teach our students
- that character counts.
- And you should.
You don't teach it well enough.
One of your students is
- a bitch.
- Andy is having a real rough day today.
I wanna take out an ad
in your yearbook.
- A full page, two words.
- "Good luck."
That's not what I had in mind.
Ask where he's from.
Where are you from?
Ohio? That's nice.
So what do you want?
He's upset about the watermark.
Okay, great. Now tell him
that it was an unfortunate error,
and we're doing everything we can do
to fix it, and that you're sorry.
It was an unfortunate error.
We're fixing it.
- And you already got your money back...
- And you're sorry.
And the company has already apologized,
so you can take that apology or not.
I think he had Tourette's or something.
We are going to do
everything humanly possible
to ensure that this
never happens again.
Well, it doesn't help.
Because it already happened to me.
The watermark...
it's a one-time thing.
I don't care.
It was disgusting!
Cartoon characters having sex?
May I point out that the sex
appeared to be consensual.
- Both animals were smiling.
- Okay.
I grew up on a farm.
I have seen animals having sex
in every position imaginable.
Goat on chicken,
chicken on goat.
Couple of chickens doing a goat.
Couple of pigs watching.
Whoever drew this got it exactly right.
What...
can I do for you?
For starters,
I think that you should resign.
Okay.
Well...
Um, wasn't really my fault.
- The guys at the pape...
- You're the head...
- It's a guy at the paper mills.
- You're the head of the company!
The head of the company?
I'm a regional manager!
- And you should lose your job!
- What? Okay,
this is insane.
You can get out of here.
- Get out! That's insane.
- Fine.
Somebody else will appreciate it.
- It's nontransferable.
- Doesn't matter. Out, please!
I'm calling the Better Business Bureau.
Yeah, well, I'm calling
the Ungrateful Bee-otch Hotline!
Did you get all that?
Everything.
We gotta do something.
This is spinning out of control, Pam.
- This is just not...
- It's just the Scranton Times.
No, then Newsweek picks it up.
And then CNN does a story about it.
- And then... YouTube gets a hold of it.
- You know what?
I really think the whole thing is just
gonna blow over in, like, a week or two.
You're right.
It will blow over.
But it's not
going to take...
a week or two.
Do you know what this is for?
Yes.
Michael likes me to run the camera
when he makes his apology videos.
He says he needs a woman's touch.
I think that's good.
"Hello, I am Michael Scott,
"Regional Manager
of Dunder-Mifflin, Scranton.
"By now, you are probably
sick of hearing about
"Dunder-Mifflin and our
embarrassing watermark boner.
"Let me tell you something.
Something from the heart.
"I am not leaving this office.
"It will take a SWAT team
"to remove me from this office,
and maybe not even that. "
You'ld never withstand a SWAT team.
That's how devoted I am to this job.
- I'm just saying.
- I know.
They would flank you,
throw in a concussion grenade.
You'd be on the ground...
Do you think you're taking it
a little... literally, Dwight?
And now we're wasting tape.
I'm gonna have to cut this all out.
- Can you say "cut"...
- Cut.
- So I know where...
I'm asking Pam to do it.
- Cut.
- Okay, ready?
Kevin, what's four plus seven?
Eleven.
Well, you didn't know that
when you filled out this payroll form.
Yeah, well, at least
I didn't suck at customer relations.
Yes!
Facial!
You two are apes.
I expect you
to apologize for that, Angela.
I'm sorry.
That you're both morons.
But you still said,
"I'm sorry."
I called you morons.
Still said it, so...
Five, four, three.
"There is no way
"I will resign.
"It wouldn't be fair.
"Not to the good workers I work with,
"not to my clients,
"and especially not to me.
"Let's not forget who this whole
"resigning business is about, anyway.
"If I could leave you
"with one thought, remember...
"it wasn't me.
"They are trying
"to make me an escape goat.
"If I am fired, I swear to God
"that every single piece
"of copier paper in this town
"is going to have the F-word on it.
"The F-word.
"You have one day."
One day for what?
That's... they always
give an ultimatum.
Okay.
- Good? Cut?
- Cut.
That was your best apology video ever.
I thought so too.
Got a farewell card for Debbie Brown.
I thought maybe you'd like to sign it.
Maybe throw a couple of bucks in there
for her. She's got children.
I feel terrible about Debbie Brown.
She got fired because of Dwight.
So I thought I'd pass around
a good-bye card.
Maybe everyone
could put in a couple of bucks
to help her through
these difficult times.
Why do bad things
always happen to the good people?
It's tragic.
Just tragic.
- You want music?
- I don't care.
Come on, man. Just give it a couple
days. I think you'll be all right.
Yeah.
You know what?
I don't...
Hey, Dwight.
You look really nice today.
Psh!
I look like an idiot.
Hey, Karen.
Hey, Dwight.
Lookin' sharp.
Yeah, that's 'cause I'm...
your boyfriend, Jim Halpert.
Wanna get together later
and have sexual intercourse,
'cause you're my girlfriend?
- Do you?
- No.
- Okay.
- I'm good. Thanks.
Look at that.
I'm Jim Halpert.
Spot on.
Blah, blah, a little comment.
Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net