What about this one?
It's kind a bad ass, right?
Just seems kind of crazy in the way I
****
I don't know...
That's not yours.
*****
and didn't seem to realize that
wasn't his hot coffee,
so the question has to be asked...
Is there no limit to
what he won't notice?
What's a seven letter word
for ***
- ***
- No, starts with an H.
Handbag.
Hmm, thank you.
Okay.
All right, everybody.
Take a seat.
As you may have heard,
our branch on the planet Jupiter
Is up 8,000% in sales.
Hold up.
That clock is slow.
It is 5:00.
I will see you all tomorrow.
Bye, Stanley.
Love you.
So long, Stanley.
Good night, everybody.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
So what kind of statement
Are you making with
that costume, Kevin?
Well, the statement
that I'm making, Oscar,
Is I kind of look
like Michael Moore.
- Dunder-Mifflin,
the is Erin.
Happy Halloween.
How can I haunt you today?
A lot of people are really
Getting into Halloween
this year.
Six seconds, MacGruber!
Pam's got a lot of fun stuff
planned...
two seconds, MacGruber!
Including a costume contest
and bobbing for apples
And a Ouija board.
Oh, boom!
Ohh, explosion!
MacGruber!
People are really into
the costume contest this year.
Might have something
to do with the prize.
Maybe you've heard of it.
The 2011 Scranton/Wilkes-barre
coupon book,
Worth over $15,000 in savings.
Stop.
Too late.
If I was the real
Scranton strangler,
You'd be so strangled by now.
And if you're out there,
strangler,
You will get caught.
By me.
Sounds like someone's
really trying to convince us
That he's not
the Scranton strangler.
To my chickens,
I'm the Scranton strangler.
Oh-ho.
That's very funny.
Looks like someone
decided to dress up
As ol' Dwight Schrute's mom.
- What?
- You're only 1/3 as beautiful
And about half her height.
I am supposed to be olive oil.
And it makes more sense when
I'm standing next to Popeye,
But Jim doesn't want
to put his costume on.
I am Popeye.
I've never really been
a costume guy.
Even when I was a kid,
it just felt like something
I was too old for, heh.
And then, this morning,
Pam hands me
this little number.
No.
- In case you can't read
my-my-my poker face...
We will be reviewing
our sales policies.
I have ten seconds
to explain them
Or this whole place blows up.
MacGruber!
Lame.
Why don't witches wear panties?
Oh, here we go.
Because they need
to grip the broom.
- Oh! Who likes to water-ski
on Lake Erie?
No, what...
Where does Dracula
like to water ski?
Lake Erie.
When our warehouse workers
make deliveries,
They're gonna be
encouraged to offer clients
Extra products.
And then they will split
those commissions with sales.
Wait, so drivers are gonna
be able to sell paper
On the road?
That is correct.
- Has anyone started
calling you Gabe-wad yet?
Not here, no.
- Gabe-wad.
Okay, guys, fun is fun, but...
Blacula.
Dracula.
Oh, so...
I almost forgot.
You'll find this hilarious.
Apparently, corporate
is going to have
Drivers sell paper
on their routes now.
That's like exactly sort of
the idea that you had.
Yes, I do remember saying
something like that to you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I blew this.
You should have gotten
credit for that, man.
I'm just glad we're
gonna try it out.
Really? We're good?
We're cool.
Okay.
What's that in your shirt?
Oh, that's a ream of paper.
Thought you might hit me.
Darryl Philbin
is the greatest guy
In the world.
And you know what I'd like?
I would like to have
all the racists
Brought together
And take Darryl Philbin
out to lunch.
Just to see
what they're missing.
It's a great stick, right?
It's really good.
Classic.
I feel like you might
win the whole thing with that.
Thanks.
Everyone realizes
this coupon book
Is not actually worth
$15,000, right?
You'd have to spend $200,000
on crap you don't even need
To get $15,000 worth
of benefits.
Heh, I'm not the only one
who sees this, right?
No.
- No, it...
- no.
I get that.
Um, excuse me, everyone.
I want to invite you all
to the Halloween party
I'm having at my bar.
You own a bar?
Public school at exit 11?
That's a great...Name.
You're hilarious.
A-plus.
So...You're all
on the list.
- Hey, man, can I get
a plus-five?
It's all guys.
Hey, what's the crowd
like, Danny?
Our age?
Okay.
I don't
think that she would leave Jim
For Danny.
I don't know.
They're both handsome.
Pam is gonna choose
whoever has a scent
Most like that of her father.
Does anyone remember
what her dad smelled like?
- I think he...
- hey, hey, gang, quiet.
Here she comes.
Did you hear about
that Danny guy?
Heard he used to date Pam.
So, four years ago,
When I was in Stanford,
Connecticut
And dating someone else...
- Mm-hmm.
Pam went on two dates
with Danny.
Which was obviously
The greatest love story
ever told,
Given how much people are
walking on eggshells around us.
We were basically
Romeo and Juliet.
- That's right.
- Except where Juliet
Doesn't have that great a time,
And Romeo doesn't call back
after two dates.
Yikes.
But I've learned to love again.
He's a cartoon sailor.
no.
And he looks so handsome
in his uniform.
Please.
No, I'm not gonna... no.
Tuna.
If you want us
to skip this party...
I don't care.
I am never gonna forget
What Danny did to Pam.
I forget nothing.
I'm like an elephant
in that way.
You know what eleph...
buh... this...
This sucks for Jim, right?
But it also sucks for us,
Because we don't get invited
to a ton of Halloween parties.
Yeah, and, like,
everyone's gonna be there.
Stanley, Phyllis, Angela,
Darryl, creed's a maybe.
Creed's going?
Madge from the warehouse
Just made her first sale.
Madge.
We should have been doing this
a long time ago.
Erin, would you please
do me a solid...
And get Darryl Philbin
on the speakerphone.
Hello.
Hi, Darryl.
Come out here, please.
I'm good.
You need to stop being so shy.
Come out here and embrace
who you really are,
Superstar.
This is embarrassing, Michael.
Yeah, I bet it is.
If you're gonna do your job
well here...
You gotta get used
to being embarrassed.
Let me put my shoes on.
Um, hit
the speakerphone button.
The speakerphone button?
Same button as you hit before.
Or sit on it.
This whole delivery/sales idea,
You know whose that was?
That was Darryl Philbin's.
He thought of that way before
the corporate fat suits.
So what happened?
I got in the way.
I said no.
And it just stopped.
But then, corporate
comes up with this idea.
But you know what?
They need to know
that it was yours.
And I don't care
if I take a bullet,
We're going to call them.
We're going to put them
on speakerphone right now.
And we are going
to straighten this out.
Screw corporate.
They probably stole
the idea anyway.
Corporate stole nothing.
Okay? Darryl brought
this idea to me,
And then I told them,
giving Darryl full credit.
So no need
to "screw corporate."
Everyone, let's give Darryl
a round of applause
As planned.
I'm a little peeved
at Darryl right now.
He went to Gabe
behind your back.
No, he didn't
go behind my back,
He went over my head.
He went over your head
to go behind your back.
What is taking someone
from behind?
No, shh, Michael, listen.
This cannot stand.
We can't have workers
going straight to corporate.
It makes your job superfluous.
It was a good idea, though.
Yeah, here's another good idea.
Corporate chain of command.
We need to strangle
Darryl's idea.
- Hey, Danny.
- Hey.
I'm really sorry,
But we can't come
to your party tonight.
Ah, I was looking forward
To throwing some darts
with you guys.
- Well...
- Okay, well, then,
Maybe we could do it...
Like next Halloween.
- Oh, for sure.
- We're just, like,
Totally caught
in the middle here.
What are you talking about?
Well, Jim and Pam basically
begged us not to go.
Jim and Pam really
don't want you to go?
They're really upset
About the whole
Danny situation.
I'll talk to them.
Yeah, but just don't tell them
That we said anything to you.
Okay?
Okay.
Or you're dead.
Kelly.
Great costume.
- Thanks.
- Oh...
Kelly! You cannot
change costumes
In the middle of the day!
Pam, she's out.
Um, if I'm out,
I'm gonna Sue
this entire company
For discrimination!
Guys, you're arguing over
a 1 in 16 chance.
Over a prize worth...
40 bucks.
Um, 15,000 bucks, Oscar.
Yeah, shut it, Oscar.
Pam.
This is an amazing prize.
I mean, I don't even want
to give Pam a compliment
'cause she's so blech.
But she did a good job.
I really want that coupon book.
Garbage magnet.
God, magnets
are interesting enough.
You don't need to tart 'em up
with some design.
I can't believe
this doesn't make you mad.
What the hell
are they talking about?
Hmm, Kevin and Gabe.
Probably about the extremes of
the human physique.
Do you think Kevin
is going over my head?
I don't... oh, my God.
Okay, all right!
All right!
All right, you know what?
That's inappropriate, Kevin.
I am your boss, and if you
have something to say,
It goes through me,
And then I take it to Gabe.
Chain of command.
Do you understand?
- I am so sorry.
- Oh, you're sorry?
- I just thought...
- what did you just thought?
Well, Gabe asked me
if there were any really cool
Lady gaga moves that
he could do for the catwalk,
And so then I told...
All right.
I told him that there
was this one cool move
Where she powers down
like a robot.
Okay.
Okay? But I'm so sorry
that I didn't tell you first.
Well,
don't let it happen again.
You think that I
would let this happen again?
No way, Jose!
I'm...
you, Gabe.
Okay.
Can you imagine?
It's just crazy.
That is crazy.
We would never care if Andy
or Kevin went to your party.
Look, I'm just glad
we can laugh about it,
Because I was a little nervous
about coming to work here
With, you know, our history.
Oh, my gosh.
Everyone keeps blowing
that out of proportion.
It's not even a history.
Exactly.
It's not like you guys had
some long relationship, right?
Big, painful breakup
I don't know about?
- Two or three dates.
- It was two.
Was it two?
I thought it was three.
No, we, um...
We had plans for a third,
But then, I don't know,
You never called me back, so...
Ooh.
You can't handle the truth.
Well,
that does not sound like me.
Yeah. It was, though.
That's what happened.
Well, great.
I just wanted to make sure
things weren't weird.
Okay, this whole
"going over my head gate"
Is making people act weird.
Chain of command is crumbling.
Do you know what just happened?
I just made Kevin cry.
And Gabe looks like lady gaga.
That's not Halloween.
Halloween should be a day
in which we honor monsters
And not be mad at each other.
I'm not mad.
Are you mad?
You went over my head,
and then you lied to my face,
So my head and my face
have taken a beating.
Well, I'm sorry
if it seems that way to you.
Okay, that might help,
If you said "I'm sorry"
in front of everybody...
- Mike.
- In front of me.
You made a bad call.
And I fixed it.
So I'm not apologizing.
So that's it?
- That's it.
- Is it?
Yes.
Suck it.
Bill Compton
from true blood.
How many freakin' vampires
Am I supposed
to care about these days?
I guess you could say
I'm still in costume.
I'm a rational consumer.
Oh, yeah.
Stupid coupon booklet.
You see my costume?
I'm a rational consumer.
Yeah, I heard you say it
to Phyllis.
That's a good line.
Okay, everybody,
after you walk the runway,
Everyone has to vote
for who gets the coupon book,
And you can't
vote for yourself.
Pam, can you vote
for other people?
Got to get in on this.
Hey, it's cool, man.
I work in the warehouse.
I'm cool!
I'm hip and I'm jive,
But I don't care about nobody!
Do you know who I am?
Happy Halloween, jerk!
Still don't know who I am?
I'll give you a hint.
I go over other people's heads.
Michael, this is a bad idea.
What's a bad idea?
Dressing up as somebody...
I mean, when has that
ever worked for you?
Never!
Okay, you know what?
Fine.
I'm not Darryl.
And thank God I'm not Darryl.
Could you for once
just let us enjoy a party
Instead of making it
about all your issues?
♪ get a jolt
from my electrode ♪
♪ they did the monster mash ♪
♪ the monster mash ♪
He's a warrior.
♪ they did the mash ♪
Yes. Yeah.
♪ they did the monster mash ♪
I present to you
the "rational consumer."
As it were.
♪ Igor on chains
backed by his baying hounds ♪
Slow.
Nice and slow, honey, yeah.
Angela as a nurse.
Don't... slow it down.
There it is.
I don't like your tone.
Look, they were sold out
Of all the other costumes,
okay?
Think we all live
in the real world here.
Let's not pretend to be unaware
Of what sells in this office.
What should we ask?
Hey, can I play?
Why don't you ask
if Darryl is a bad friend
Who backstabs people
in the back?
We have one question
to ask the spirit world,
And you want us to ask that?
He says no.
Ah, Darryl moved it.
You moved it.
No.
Hey, Dwight,
you saw Darryl move it, right?
Let's just say I saw
Exactly what the two of you
wanted me to see.
I know how to sit on a fence.
Hell, I can even
sleep on a fence.
The trick is to do it face down
With the post in your mouth.
If you had one word you
would use to describe Darryl,
What would that word be?
"a"...
"s"...
"s".
"h".
No.
"e"...
"t".
An asset.
Aah!
That's enough.
I don't think it's gonna
work out the way you think.
I don't think you get it.
- Hey.
This is some party, huh?
When you work hard,
you play hard around here.
Even if you don't work hard.
Oh, here's something.
Mm?
Uh, why didn't you
ever call Pam back?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not saying
that everybody
Has to fall in love
or anything.
I'm just saying,
but to, you know,
To not even call her back is...
Know what it was?
I think she gave me her number,
But then, like, her fours
looked like eights, and then...
Could be.
But you also
called her the second time,
So you had the number right.
Halpert, you looking
for someone to bang your wife?
- Nope.
- Okay.
You want to know?
I didn't call her back
Because she spent the whole date
talking about you.
She was obviously
in love with you.
♪ grooving from side to side ♪
57, 58.
Wait, she hasn't moved
in a while.
Erin. Er...
Two.
I got two.
I ate two whole apples.
I'd remember talking about Jim.
That wasn't it.
Just tell her the real reason.
You honestly want to know
Why I didn't call her back
on a date over four years ago?
Hey, she had a nice time.
It seems rude.
I did. Yeah.
And it's one of those things
That's just gonna keep
gnawing at me.
Like gnaw, gnaw.
"why? Why didn't he?
I have no idea why."
okay.
Honestly,
I didn't call you back
'cause I thought
you seemed a little...
Dorky.
- Hey, man...
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I got it.
Now I know.
You thought
I was a little dorky.
You know?
Okay.
Well, excuse me.
In the future, you need
To get Michael's approval
On anything
before coming to me.
Thank you.
You're gonna miss out
on some good ideas.
Okay, well, obviously,
If it's a really...
really good idea,
Then my door is open to that.
If they're good ideas,
I'm not gonna say no.
- You said no to this one.
- That's... okay.
I make one mistake in 15 years
And you drag me over the coals.
After everything I did for you?
- What have you done for me?
- Oh...
- Well...
Ed truck hired me.
Jo promoted me.
Gabe listened to me.
All you've ever done
was say no to me.
I have ambition.
And you kept me
at the same level for years.
Oh, dropping bombs, right?
Must really make you think,
Michael.
Stop it. Stop. Stop.
We're thinking.
We're thinking about it.
Yeah.
You don't have to point
to the fact
That we're thinking about it.
Stop it.
Just let us think.
Okay, next time you have
a really great idea,
We will put it in a hat
And then we will have Erin
pick it out of the hat
And let her decide.
I don't understand the point
of the hat.
You're right.
We don't need a hat.
I am not budging
on the hat issue.
Okay, we're gonna table
the hat question.
The best ideas
are gonna come to me.
I make the final decision.
Period.
Okay. We both reserve
the right to go to Jo
If we disagree with Gabe.
- Okay.
- Fair enough.
Why don't we simplify this?
Darryl brings it to Michael.
Michael brings it to me.
No one calls Jo.
Unless you and I decide
we want to talk to Jo.
Then we'll give her a call.
Cool.
Yeah. I'm sorry I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
I was a jerk.
Friends fight.
What's up, man?
Sometimes it seems like
It was better down
in the warehouse, you know?
When I was a freshman
in college,
I worked
at the student newspaper,
The Cornell daily sun.
This was at Cornell.
I had to write an op-ed column
Bernard's regards.
This was your freshman year?
I started to ask myself
"do I have big plans here?"
I didn't want to become editor
of that paper.
So I got up and walked right out
of Walter Bernard hall.
And that's actually
when I heard
Eight male voices singing,
Unencumbered by instruments.
I was hooked.
So is becoming CEO
of this company
Your a cappella group?
Come on.
We're going to Danny's bar.
Public school.
No, I got some work to do.
I do have big plans
at this company.
To be honest,
I still can't believe
He didn't call her back.
Who doesn't call a dork
like that back?
Spinach in a can.
Powerful spinach.
A-gah-gah-gah-gah.
- Aw, my hero.
Okay, everyone,
I've tallied the votes.
And the winner of the costume
celebration spectacular
And the Scranton/Wilkes-barre
coupon book, Oscar Martinez.
Really?
If I have to vote for someone
I don't want it to be
someone who can be me.
Shake things up.
I'm an inner guy.
Best Edward James ** costume
I've ever seen.
Like freaky good.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net