Yeah, I'm not a temp anymore.
I got Jim's, uh, old job.
Which means, at my ten-year
high school reunion,
it will not say,
"Ryan Howard is a temp."
"Ryan Howard is a junior sales associate
at a mid-range paper supply firm."
That'll show'em.
You have no idea how
long I've wanted to do that.
Me too.
I think we're just drunk.
No, I'm not drunk. Are you drunk ?
No.
Jim.
You're really gonna marry him ?
Okay.
Jim is gone.
He's gone. I miss him so much.
Oh, I cry myself to sleep. Jim !
False. I do not miss him.
The Office US 3x01
"Gay Witch Hunt"
Transcript : Nikki
Subtitles be the Catch-22 Team
EZtoms, Keyshawn, Occeane, Titus Pullo, Unfold.
pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
No, that is the fun of this place.
I call everybody "faggy."
Why would anyone find that offensive ?
Okay, I think Oscar would just like if
you used "lame" or something like that.
- That's what "faggy" means.
- No, not really.
- Apparently, you called Oscar faggy.
- Yeah.
For liking the move "Shakespeare
in Love" more than an action movie.
It wasn't just an action move,
it was "Die Hard."
All, all right,
Michael, but Oscar's really gay.
- Exactly.
- I mean for real.
- Yeah, I know.
- No, he's attracted to other men.
Okay, little too far. Crossed the line.
Okay, I am telling you,
Oscar is an actual homosexual.
Yeah, he told me this morning.
And obviously he hopes
he can count on your discretion.
I would've never called
him that if I knew.
You don't...
you don't call retarded people retards.
It's bad taste. You call your friends
retards when they're acting retarded.
And I consider Oscar a friend.
Listen man, I am so sorry.
I had no idea.
- Oh, it's fine.
- No.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- No, it's not. I just-
I feel terrible about it. I...
I have been calling people
faggy since I was in junior high,
and I have never made this mistake.
If I don't know how to behave,
it is because I am just
so far the opposite way.
You know ? I'm just- I-I
can't even imagine- the... thing.
Maybe we could go out for a
beer sometime, and you could tell me...
how you do that to another dude.
That sounds like a great,
wonderful idea. Let's do that.
It explains so much.
No, I'm not gay.
And I don't understand why
anyone would think that I'm gay if...
Yeah, I'm gay.
I can't say whether Dunder Mifflin
paper is less flammable, sir, but
I can assure you that it
is certainly not more flammable
Why did I transfer to Stamford ?
I... think that's pretty obvious.
I got promoted.
And you can't beat that view. Right ?
Hey, Big Tuna. You're single, right ?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I am.
Pretty hot, huh ?
She's completely crazy.
Steer clear, Big Tuna.
Head for open waters.
Okay.
I ate a tuna sandwich on my first day...
so Andy started calling me Big Tuna.
I don't think any of them
actually know my real name.
Big Tuna is a super ambitious guy,
you know ? Cut-your-throat-to-get-ahead
type of guy. But,
I mean, I'm not threatened by him.
I went to Cornell.
You ever heard of it ?
I graduated in four years,
I never studied once,
I was drunk the whole time,
and I sang in the a capella group,
"Here comes Treble."
So, end of day, we are going to have
a little diversity policy freshener,
because of some more problems
at the Scranton branch.
And I have a list of business
startups I got from the Chamber.
Yes, I am going to need
someone to cold call them.
Oh, I can do that.
Tuna's  nice enough
I don't-I don't know
how well he's fitting in here.
He's always looking
at the camera like this.
What is that ?
Can you tell who's gay and who's not ?
Of course.
What about Oscar ?
- Absolutely not.
- Well, he is.
Well, he's not dressed
in women's clothes, so...
There could be others. I need to know.
I don't want to offend anybody else.
You could assume everyone is,
and not say anything offensive.
Yeah. I'm sure everyone would appreciate
me treating them like they were gay.
Hey, what about Angela ? She's hard
and severe. She could be a gay woman.
- I really don't think so.
- I don't know.
I can imagine her with another woman.
Can't you ?
Do some research. Find out if there's
a way to tell by just looking at'em.
Jim told me you could by gaydar online.
That's ridiculous.
Yeah, probably.
He didn't tell the truth a lot.
- Let's call him and get the website.
- Definitely.
What's gaydar ?
Oh, oh, gaydar, yes ! No, uh,
I think they have it at Sharper Image.
Oh, you know what ?
I can check for you. No problem.
It's sold out.
Yeah, sorry about that. That's a bummer.
- Well, they're sold out.
- Damn.
Try Brookstone.
I miss that.
Chicken or fish ?
chicken.
- So, you, uh, having a good day ?
- Excellent. Thanks.
Good. I'm glad.
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't go
through with the wedding.
I got cold feet a few days before,
and... I can't really explain it. I just
had to get out of that relationship.
We still had to pay for all the food.
So we froze it.
But I'm... I'm doing well.
I have my own apartment,
and I'm taking art classes,
and I have lunch
for the next five weeks.
After Pam dumped me, I, um...
I kind of stopped taking care
of myself for a while there, and, uh...
I hit bottom when, uh...
I had a drunk driving arrest.
I've  been working out, and, um...
you know,
I'm not gonna take her for granted.
I gotta win her back.
I got them a toaster.
They called off the wedding
and gave the toaster back to me.
I tried to return
the toaster to the store,
and they said they no longer
sold that kind of toaster.
So now my house has got two toasters.
It is so cool that you're gay.
I totally underestimated you.
Yes, I am super cool.
I am an accountant at a failing
paper supply company. In Scranton.
Much like, uh, Sir Ian McKellen.
Sure, sometimes I watch "Will & Grace."
And I want to throw up.
It's terribly loud.
I do like it sometimes,
when Harry Connick Jr. is on.
He's so talented.
Okay. Who put my calculator is Jell-O ?
Good one.
But, uh, seriously. Guys, who did this ?
Seriously, guys. Who did this ?
I need to know who
put my calculator in Jell-O
or I'm gonna lose... my freakin'mind !
You know, it-it's amazing to me that
in this day and age, you could be so...
obtuse... a-about sexual orientation !
I watch "The L Word,"
- Okay ?
- Good, good.
I watch "Queer as [beep]."
- That's not what it's called.
- So...
Okay, Michael, are you aware
that you outed Oscar today ?
What ? What does that even...
Coming out is a significant
moment for a gay person.
And they should be allowed to select
the timing and manner of announcing it.
Well, gay pride, right ?
Gay pride parade ?
It's not like... Gay Shame Festival.
All right, now Oscar's feeling
discriminated against by his coworkers,
primarily Angela, and, um...
that's your fault.
I think Angela might be gay.
Could Oscar and Angela
be having a gay affair ?
- No.
- Maybe. Is that what this is about ?
- I don't.
No. It's not possible.
- Anything's possible.
- Okay, you know, imagine...
you were gay.
Well, I'm not gay, Jan, and you
should know that better than anybody.
Michael !
Your immaturity is
extremely disappointing
and may even lead to a lawsuit,
which is the absolute last thing
this company needs right now,
- Do you understand ?
- I know.
The company has made
it my responsibility today
to put an end to 100,000
years of being weirded out by gays.
Am I the first gay man you ever knew ?
Trick question.
Because you can't always tell,
so how would I know ?
Was that the right answer ?
- Yep ?
- Michael,
Dwight's looking at gay
pornography on his computer.
Uh, Michael knows, Pam.
Okay, he asked me to do this
just for him. He has his own reasons.
Okay.
Nothing  wrong with this stuff.
At all. This is fine.
You know what ? Gay porn, straight porn,
it's all good.
I don't particularly get into this,
but, uh... You know what ?
I totally see the merit.
And, actually... It is quite beautiful.
- Oh, damn popups.
- What are you doing ?
- Watching some of your friends.
- This is stupid.
- Excuse me.
- Don't touch me. Help ! Ow.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop it !
All right,
everybody in the conference room.
I don't care if you are gay
or straight or a lesbian, or overweight.
Just get in here ! Right now !
Did you know that "gay"
used to mean "happy"?
When I was growing up, it meant "lame."
And now it means a man
who makes love to other men.
We're all homos. Homo sapiens.
Gays aren't necessarily
who you think they are, people.
I mean, anybody can be gay.
Businessmen. Like antique dealers,
or hairdressers, or... accountants.
Oscar, why don't you take
this opportunity to officially come out
to everybody here,
however you want to do it.
Go ahead.
Stand up. I'm doing this for you.
Yes, I'm gay.
And...  I didn't plan on sharing that
part of my life with you today, so...
Whatever. Can I sit down now ?
I am not offended by homosexuality.
In the'60s, I made love to many,
many women. Often outdoors.
In the mud and the rain.
And it's possible a man slipped in.
There would be no way of knowing.
Who, should be the judges
and juries of our society ?
Judges and juries.
Yes, that's a good point.
She has a good point.
Because  gay marriage,
currently, is not legal under U.S. law.
I bet a lot of straight
men wished that applied to them.
So they could go out there and
have some torrid, unabashed, monkey sex.
As much as they could. You know,
that sounds pretty good, right ?
That sounds great.
Yeah, Dwight ?
I think all the other office gays
should identify themselves,
or I will do it for them.
- No one else in this office is gay.
- What about Phyllis ?
She makes absolutely
no attempt to be feminine.
I'm getting married to Bob Vance.
- You are ?
- Congratulations !
- When did you get that ?!
- That's great.
Congratulations, Phyllis. That is great.
And frankly, kind of amazing.
See ? Everybody has a chance.
- Thank you.
- But still, Phyllis...
In college, did you ever experiment
with other women ? A lot of women do.
No, and you know me in high school.
Of course, we all thought
you were gay in high school.
Yeah, right. Ha, ha !
And I take that as a compliment.
Well, with your ties
and your matching socks-
Well, I just liked to look good,
okay, so-
You sound pretty defensive, Michael.
No, I am just coming out myself.
I am coming out hetero.
I think the problem with this office is
that YOU are sending mixed signals
about my being here.
No, no, no.
The only signal that I am sending is,
"Gay good." Look, if I was gay,
I would be the most flamboyant
gay you've ever seen.
I would be leading the
parade covered in feathers, and
just... I'd be waving that rainbow flag.
I don't think I can
work here any longer.
This has been the worst,
most backwards day of my life.
You misunderstand-okay. All right.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-bop. You know what ? Okay.
Okay. I, uh... I'm gonna put
my money where my mouth is. You ready ?
- What are you doing ?
- I am going to embrace Oscar.
You might want to watch this, Angela,
because you can't catch anything.
Here we go.
- No.
- We are going to make a statement.
You and I are going to
make a statement together.
- Oscar is my friend.
- I'd rather not.
- And I just don't care who sees it.
- I...
- Doesn't bother me.
- I really would-
would-I'd really rather not.
Come here, friend. You're my friend.
No, NO !
I don't want to touch you !
Ever consider that ? You're ignorant.
And insulting. And small.
Okay.
All right.
I'm sorry, Michael. Michael. I'm sorry.
That was a good idea. Come on.
Come on. All right.
- I'm sorry I called you "faggy."
- I know, I know.
- You're not faggy.
- I know you are.
- You're a good guy.
- You too.
Michael appears to be gay too.
And yet, he is my friend.
I guess I do have a gay friend.
You know what ?
I'm gonna raise the stakes.
- You don't... really don't...
- I want you to watch this.
And I want you to burn
this into your brains.
- I don't think we need to-
- Because this is an image
that I want you people to remember.
For a long time to come.
Whenever you come into the office,
I want you to think about this.
We don't need to-
- Yes, we do.
- What ?
I did it.
- Thank you.
See ? I'm still here.
We're all still here.
Oh, come one, Dwight ! Come on, man !
We're not in the playground anymore.
There are new rules.
We have to be mature
, but we can't lose the
spirit of childlike wonder.
What is love, anyway ?
Maybe it's suppose
to break all the rules.
Like me and Jan.
Or Oscar and some guy.
Life is short.
When two people find each other...
what should stand in their way ?
It is very easy for you to be a hero.
All you need are honesty,
empathy, respect, and open-mindedness.
I'm glad today spurred social change.
That's part of my
job as regional manager.
But you know what, even if it didn't,
at least we put this matter to bed.
That's what she said. Or he said.
Oh, there's Gil, Oscar's roommate.
I wonder if he knows.
I was going to quit, but Jan offered me
a three month paid vacation
and a company car.
All I had to do was sign
something saying I won't sue.
Gil and I are going to Europe.
Kids, sometimes it pays to be gay.
"Hope this helps, Jim."
Nice.
- What are you doing ?
- Shh. Don't be scared.
It works. Heh.
Oh no.
www.tvsubtitles.net