- Hey.
Who are you faxing
so early in the morning?
Kinda hard to explain.
I don't have a ton of contact
with the Scranton branch,
but before I left, I took a box
of Dwight's stationery.
So from time to time,
I send Dwight faxes.
From himself.
From the future.
"Dwight, "At 8:00 A.M. today,
someone poisons the coffee.
"Do not drink the coffee.
"More instructions will follow.
"Cordially, Future Dwight"
Nooo!
You'll thank me later.
Episode 7
"Branch Closing"
The catch 22 team
Raceman
http://www.theofficeus.fr/
http://www.1000fr.com/
There she is.
- Jan Levinson. First thing in the morning.
- Michael.
I love to start my day
with a hearty bowl of Jan.
- Michael.
-"Just call me Levinson"
- "In the morning Baby"
- Michael.
Yes.
I'm here to tell you that we are
closing the Scranton branch.
I don't understand.
The board voted last
night to close your branch.
- On whom's authority?
- The board's.
- W-what?
- I'm very sorry. I-I...
I don't relish telling you this.
You've been a big part of this company.
And the board asked me to thank you
- for your years of service.
- You're welcome.
A small number of people will be
transferred to the Stamford branch,
and the rest will be
getting severance packages.
Am I a small number person
or a severance package person?
Well, we haven't made final
decisions about personnel yet.
- But you're a severance package person.
- Oh, no.
Oh, my God!
- I don't really get it.
Because we're not doing that bad,
and our numbers are gonna come up.
Yeah, but it's not all
about numbers, Michael.
- Well
- It's, it's about talent.
Oh, you gotta-- Josh?
- Yes, really.
- King of the stupid universe?
It is an outrage.
That's all.
It's...
They're making a huge, huge mistake.
Let's see Josh replace these people.
Let's see Josh find another Stanley.
You think Stanleys grow on trees?
Well, they don't.
There is no Stanley tree.
Do you think the world is
crawling with Phyllises?
Show me that farm.
With Phyllises and Kevins sprouting up
all over the place,
ripe for the plucking.
Show me that farm.
Pictures.
Memories.
Look at that.
They grow up so fast.
- Hey, stranger.
- Don't say that.
That just sounds weird. Please.
Sorry, I just feel like we
haven't talked in a while.
Well, we have nothing
to talk about, Dwight.
Just do your work.
While you still can.
When you become close with someone,
you develop a kind of sixth sense.
You can read their
moods like a book.
Right now, the title
of Michael's book is
Something Weird Is Going On.
Colon: What Did Jan Say?
The Michael Scott Story.
By Michael Scott.
With Dwight Schrute.
Hey, did you hear about
your friends in Pennsylvania?
Really
Wow, that's too bad.
Sorry. Scranton branch is closing?
In your face.
Well, I work here now.
Sucka!
- Are you okay?
-Yeah. Great, amazing.
Best physical condition of my life.
- What did Jan want?
- Nothing. Just checking in.
I can't tell you, so.
- What can't you tell me?
- Nothing. Pam.
What difference does it make?
We'll all be gone in a few weeks anyway.
- What?
-What?
-  You just said that we're gonna be gone
- Do I have any messages?
- Michael, what's going on?
- Okay.
Listen up, everybody.
I have some news.
We are screwed.
Dunder-Mifflin Scranton
is being shut down.
Michael, We shouldn't
be talking about this
until all the decisions have been made.
You knew about this
all along, didn't you?
Jan told me just a few
minutes before she told you.
Traitor.
You are a traitor.
What about us, Michael?
Do we still have jobs?
I don't know.
Probably not.
This is the worst.
It makes perfect sense
that it would happen today
because I just received
this in the mail.
1,000 business cards with this
address and phone number.
I don't want to blame
anyone in particular.
I think everyone's to blame.
If I get to stay and Ryan is laid off,
I will kill myself.
Like Romeo and Juliet.
The Claire Danes one.
Stamford Connecticut
I worked in Scranton
for a really long time. And...
It's gonna be weird
that it's all disappearing.
I mean, I always knew that the branch
would shut down someday.
I just figured it would
be because Michael...
sold the building for some magic beans.
I couldn't be happier.
I'm gonna take the
severance and retire.
My wife and I are gonna travel.
I really couldn't be happier.
It's a blessing in disguise.
Actually, not even in disguise.
Sometimes at home, I answer the phone,
"Dunder-Mifflin. This is Pam."
So...maybe that'll stop now.
What does that mean?
Well, some of us are fired,
and  a few are going to Connecticut.
I don't know if I really
wanna work here without Pam.
You know that Cinderella song?
You Don't Know What
You Got Till It's Gone?
That pretty much says
it better than how I know
how to say it in words.
Hey, Mike.
Darrel. Noble Darrel.
Look, I heard about the office.
- tuff break???
- I know. I know
Well, I'll land on my feet.
- Yeah. Don't worry about me.
- I wasn't.
So you'll be okay too.
You're warrior, you're smart.
Capable. You'll find
something else, and...
Actually, Bob Vance
bought out the warehouse.
- So he's keeping on the whole crew.
- So we're good.
Awesome.
This is my house.
The CFO's taking away
my house and giving it to Josh.
And Josh is giving the
garage to Bob Vance.
All right, listen up.
Some of you may have heard some
rumors about the branch closing.
But I am not going
to take this lying down.
I have a plan,
and I am going to save our jobs.
So  just hang in there. Let's go.
- Yes!
- Oh, good. You're bringing Dwight.
Yes. This might get ugly.
I'm gonna need backup.
-What's the plan?
- Go to New York.
Confront the CFO. Show him he's
making a mistake. Save the branch.
Can I drive? No way.
- Shotgun!
- No, there's no one else.
Still.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Secretary says Wallace
is away for the day.
and won't be coming
back into the office.
Okay.
But... Do not worry.
I have his home address...
Right here.
- Why?
- Christmas card list.
You send him cards?
You've never met him.
Well, when I do,
we'll have something to talk about.
Hey, do you have a second?
Sure, what's up?
I know it's not definite,
or whatever, but
but, uh, do you know who's
coming over here from Scranton?
I honestly don't. I don't know.
So is it, like, sales or
accountants?
You know what, Jim?
I wouldn't worry about it.
What does that mean?
- Hi.
- Come in, hey.
Oh, good, you're both here.
Ready to talk logistics?
I just feel like it could
have been something special
if we could have kept working together.
But...
I'm gonna go someplace else,
and you're gonna go someplace else.
It just doesn't make sense.
This kind of worked
out perfectly for me.
I got some good experience.
Michael's gonna write me
a great recommendation.
And as far as me and Kelly goes...
I think it's for the best.
Okay.
This is it.
This is exactly what Michael Moore does.
Famous documentarian.
He goes up to people with a camera,
and he's like,
"Why did you do this?
"Why did you pollute?
"You are bad. You're a bad person."
Very dramatic.
Although I can't say I was a big fan
of Bowling For Columbine.
Because I thought it was gonna be
a bowling movie.
Like Kingpin.
And it wasn't. It was something else.
So.
Josh will be running what is now called
Dunder-Mifflin Northeast,
which is all the
offices north of Stamford.
And Jim, if you want the job,
you'll be his number two.
Wow. sure. Absolutely.
Awesome. 'Scuse me, Jan. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to stop you there.
I...
will not be taking the job.
Excu--why not?
As of today, I have accepted a
senior management position at Staples.
Today.
You leveraged your new
position with us into another offer?
Damn it, Josh.
This whole restructuring thing
was based around keeping you.
I'm sorry, all right? It's done.
It's time.
I gotta make some calls.
Excuse me. I'm sorry, Jim.
Say what you will
about Michael Scott.
But he would never do that.
So.
Do you know what you're gonna say
when he shows up?
I will improvise.
- I will speak from the heart.
- No. Bad idea.
You need an attack plan.
Here, I'll be him. You be you.
- Let's practice.
- All right.
- Coming home from work.
- 'Scuse me.
- Mr. Wallace? David Wallace?
- Yes.
What is the meaning of this?
Can  you tell us why you
are shutting down Scranton
and putting 15 people out of work?
Well, the branch is
no longer financially viable.
It's simple dollars and cents.
Yes, but these are employees, sir.
- These are human beings.
- Listen, Scott.
We're losing money, okay?
It's not a charity.
It's a business.
- And it's a dying business.
- Stop--stop it. Just...
- Okay, he's not gonna say any of that.
- It-- Wh--hey, why not?
Because he'd be
intimidated. And I just--
- Let's start again.
- Just be more scared of me, okay? Okay.
Don't touch me this time.
Dum dee do dee do dee doe
- Excuse me, Mr. Wallace?
- Coming home from w-- Agh!
So we are still
scrambling here, but,
It looks like Scranton is
going to absorb Stamford.
Wow.
And I know that you just left there
couple of months ago,
but we would like to offer
you the number two position
- at that branch.
- Thank you.
No, it's just, I'm not sure if I...
Well, to be quite honest with you, Jan,
I have a few unpleasant
memories of Scranton.
- Michael.
- No, no, no.
Just,some personal stuff.
And I'm not really
ready to revisit that,
I don't think.
Well. Please think about it.
And call me.
We  will do whatever we
can to get you to stay.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
I'm trying to organize a little group
lunch for everybody, since, you know,
we're never gonna see each other again.
Where are we going?
I thought maybe DJ's?
How 'bout Cugino's?
I don't wanna go all
the way to Dunmore.
How 'bout Cooper's, then?
No seafood.
Well, I don't want to go to DJ's.
Oh, now, all of a sudden, you get picky?
Okay. Forget it.
Hooters.
No.
Ah! Here.
Replenish your fluids.
Where's Michael?
He's not here.
I don't know where he is.
What...
What's going on here?
We know the branch is closing.
Michael told us.
Oh, God.
Okay. You know what, everybody?
I'm sure there is
a better way to do this,
but I've driven something like 400 miles
today, and I'm completely exhausted.
So I'm just gonna tell you.
Your branch is not closing.
Stamford is closing
for the time being, it seems
that all of your jobs are safe.
Yes.
Stanley.
Is it because of Michael?
Did he actually do something?
Well, reasons are not important.
Would you just call him,
please, wherever he is,
- And tell him?
- Sure. Jan.
Do you know--is anyone
coming back to Scranton?
Back?
Coming to Scranton.
Is anyone coming to Scranton?
- We don't know.
- Probably a few.
- Who is it?
- The office.
Are you gonna get it? No.
Not until I have some
good news for them.
Not until I have some good news.
I guess new people might
be coming from Stamford.
Should be fun. New blood.
Is Jim coming back?
That's,
I hadn't thought about it.
I don't know.
I just don't want it to be weird.
You know?
I mean, I took his old job
- And his old desk.
- Yeah, yeah, that might be weird.
Overall, though,
we still all have our jobs,
so good news, right?
- Oh, yeah. Totally.
- I'm so happy!
We don't have to break up now, Ryan!
It is the best day of my whole life.
- What are you gonna do?
- I really don't know.
- How you doing with all this?
- You know, I'm fine.
I'll be better when
I know if I have a job.
You'd actually move to Scranton?
Yeah, if they let me.
I think I-- I think I would.
New York City is 45 minutes
down the road from here.
And you wanna move to Scranton.
If I were you, I'd move to New York.
Yeah, you know, I-- I might do that.
I'm who knows?
I might do that.
- Hey Andy!
- What's up Josh ?
Hey, man, just wanted to say thanks.
Good luck.
- Thanks, man. You, too.
- Totally.
- Anything?
- Nothing.
What if this doesn't work?
What if the office actually goes under?
Then it was an honor
to have worked with you.
All right.
Favorite moments
in Dunder-Mifflin history.
Go.
My first day, when you hazed me
by spraying me with a fire extinguisher.
That was hilarious.
The foam.
My first sale.My promotion to
assistant regional manager.
Our basketball game.
And when you took me to the hospital...
and told me that you cared about me.
- Oh, right. Okay.
- That's enough. That's good.
What were your favorite moments?
All of 'em. I loved 'em all.
Every single one.
What about when Jan
said the branch was closing?
- God, Dwight.
- Well, I just...
Hey, Pam.
We're going to Poor Richard's.
- Creed's buying shots.
- No, thanks, guys.
- All right.
- Have fun, though.
- Cool.
- Hey, I hear Jim's coming back.
Really? Where did you hear that?
- Ryan, are you coming ?
- Well, I was.
Yeah, we'll meet you there.
Awesome.
- Let's go.
- I'll tell you later.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Crazy day, huh?
- Yeah.
- Man.
I'm...
I'm really glad you're
still gonna be working here.
Yeah, me, too.
Maybe this is good.
Finding another job is a pain.
There's another annoying boss,
another desk.
I'd have to learn
everything all over again.
So...
there are reasons to stay.
Hey...
I think I am gonna take that job.
And Scranton?
It's not that bad.
So...
If they offer you a job there...
I think you should take it.
- Okay, yeah. Maybe I will.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'm happy he said that.
I mean, I don't think he's
into me or anything. But...
I'm kind of into him.
So...there you go.
What are we still doing here?
It's over.
Let's go home.
Get the car.
This was such a stupid idea.
This was so stupid.
I'm such a stupid idiot.
I  let everybody down.
Everybody hates me.
I lost everybody's jobs.
- Nobody likes me anymore!
- Oh, my God!
- What?
- Stamford is closed!
Michael, we're not closed.
Stamford is closed!
- Stamford is closed! We did it.
- We did it?
- We did it!
- Yeah!
Yeah! Right here, right here.
- Yeah, baby!
- In your face!
- We did it.
- Oh, man.
- How did we do it?
- I don't know. I have no idea.
I don't understand.
www.tvsubtitles.net