Go, in the door..
Push !
No no no! Turn it around.
Turn it around, you're breaking.
Shove it, breaking !
You shove it! Shove it back !
Here we go.
Don't break the branches, Dwight.
Ah, I got a splinter.
Well, suck it up, we all have problems.
Hey everybody.
Look what we have !
Nice, huh ?
- I've got it leveraged. Push !
- One three.
- Straight up.
- Ready, one, two, three.
Merry Christmas !
Episode 210- Season 2
CHRISTMAS PARTY
Catch 22 team :
El uploador, Keyshawn, Occeane, Unfold
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
Did it work ?
Well, sort of.
Why did you get it so big ?
'A', that's what she said.
And 'B',
I wanted it to be impressive.
he biggest day of the year deserves
the biggest tree of the year.
But what are we going to do
with this hacked off part ?
Well, that is a perfectly
good mini tree Kevin.
And we are going to
sell that to charity.
That's what Christmas is all about.
So this year,
for the first time ever...
I got Pam in Secret Santa.
And I got her this, teapot.
Which I know she really wants.
So she can make tea at her desk.
but I'm also gonna stuff
it with some inside jokes.
Like...
This is my high school yearbook photo.
She saw it at the party,
and it really makes her laugh.
I'm not sure why.
What else?
This is hot sauce packet.
She put this on a hot dog
a couple of years ago.
Because she thought it was ketchup
And, it was really funny.
So I kept the other two.
This would take a little
too long to explain.
So I won't.
And this is a card.
Because Christmas is the time
to tell people how you feel.
Is there anything we're missing ?
Phyllis, you got the lights ?
Yes, I got those cute little ones.
Do you think I should have
gotten the big ones ?
We'll see.
Angela, drafted me into the
party planning committee.
Her memo said that we need to
prepare for every possible disaster.
Which to me seems...excessive.
Merry Christmas !
Pimp !
I'm kidding.
What do we got ? What do we got ?
How many plates are we getting ?
Fifty.
Double it. Double everything.
Double ice cream.
Double napkins. Double it.
On me.
It was a tough year
I had to fire somebody this year.
This party has to really rock.
Check it out.
Christmas bonus.
Three-thousand G's.
I got this for helping save
the company money
So I guess some good came
out of firing Devin after all.
Maybe  I should call him, tell him that.
I want people to cut loose.
I want people...making out in closets.
I want, I want people hanging from
the ceilings, lampshades on the heads
I want it to be a Playboy Mansion party.
And also, I want you to know,
and spread the word, that
I will have my digital camera.
And I will be taking
pictures all along the way.
And the best and craziest
thing that happens,
will be on the cover of the newsletter.
Incentive.
You do realize that we can't
serve liquor at the party.
Yeah, I know. Dammit.
Stupid corporate wet blankets.
Like booze ever killed anybody.
One, two, three.
You guys should use a hand truck.
Do we have one ?
No.
Will you help me ?
No. No way.
It- no.
Come on, Mike. Let me borrow the hat.
For just a couple of hours.
- You wanna be Santa ?
- Yeah.
Have you ever seen Santa ?
Yeah, I've SEEN Santa. Who cares ?
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
It just doesn't work.
Michael !
I would like to be the elf.
That makes sense, because
he has elfish features.
Okay, everyone, listen up !
It is time, to get your presents.
Wrap them, and place them under the tree.
Like so.
If you do not get your present wrapped,
and under the tree within
the next five minutes,
you  will be disqualified
from Secret Santa.
All right ? No exceptions.
Except Michael.
I got Angela.
She's into these posters of babies...
dressed as adults.
I got her one of those.
I felt kind of weird buying that.
I got Creed.
And to tell you the truth,
I don't know anything about Creed.
know his name's Creed.
I know he works right over there.
I think he's Irish and I...
I got him this, uh, shamrock keychain.
I got myself for Secret Santa.
I was suppose to tell
somebody, but I didn't.
You get something good this year
I think I did a pretty good job.
Who'd you have ?
I can't tell you, 'cause it's a secret.
think I got something
pretty nice for my guy.
- Yeah ?
- Spent a lot of dough. A lot of dough.
Wow.
Well, there, there's
a $20 limit, right ? So.
Yeah, I wanted this party
to be really special.
So I sorta went above and beyond.
hat's great, well, don't
tell me who it is, 'cause...
It was Ryan ! Yep.
I  have Ryan.
Gather 'round.
Secret Santa, let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Stanley, no. I'm gonna handle the cord.
Kay ? Safety reasons.
I know how to plug something in.
I wanna do it.
All right !
Let's count it down.
Like Rockefeller Center.
Ready ?
Three.
Two.
One.
Yeah !
Not great.
Sorry, everybody.
I think the tree looks nice.
- I could get some flares from my car.
-  No, no
Shake it off, everybody.
Just, let's do Secret Santa.
Presents are the best way to show
someone how much you care.
It is like this tangible thing
that you can point to and say:
"Hey, man, I love you this
many dollars worth."
First present, Oscar.
A shower radio, neat.
Oh, great. That was from me.
hanks, Kelly. You know, I was
gonna get one of these.
Okay, that's enough.
Let's keep it moving on. Jim.
Ah, cool.
That's from me.
Great.
Where'd you get it ?
I don't know, it was so long ago.
He obviously forgot to get me something.
And then he went into his closet
and dug out this little number.
And then threw it in a bag.
Yep, that's exactly what happened.
Pam.
Oh, my God !
Thank you very much, Santa.
Whoever you are.
- It's awesome.
- There's a little more to it.
All right, next. Ryan.
Don't !
A video iPod.
omebody really got carried away
with the spirit of Christmas.
It was me. I got carried
away with the spirit.
Wasn't there a $20 limit on the gift?
This is 400 bucks.
- You don't know that.
- Yeah, you left the price tag on.
I did, what ? Oh, shoot. Wow,
Well, who cares?
It doesn't matter what I spent.
What matters is that
Christmas is fun, right ?
Michael.
For me ?
What is in here ?
- Come on.
-  I-I knitted it for you.
An oven mitt ?
Okay.
So Phyllis is basically saying :
"Hey Michael, I know you did
a lot to help the office this year."
"But I only care about you...
a homemade oven mitt's worth."
I gave Ryan an iPod.
Should we just keep
opening up the presents ?
We don't do anything until Michael
gives us further instructions.
I got it !
We are going to turn Secret
Santa into Yankee Swap !
What is, Yankee Swap ?
One person chooses a gift.
The next person can
either choose a gift.
Or steal that person's gift.
If your gift gets stolen, then you
can steal someone else's gift
Or choose a new gift.
I thought that was
called nasty Christmas.
Yeah, we call it White Elephant.
Well, I call it fun !
Why are we doing this ?
Because it's better.
Because it's more special.
- I sounds mean.
- Shut...
No, it's not. Okay, just give it a shot.
Michael should have asked the
party planning committee first.
He's not supposed to just spring
things on us out of nowhere.
Okay, Meredith is up first.
Here's the deal.
You can either pick a new gift,
OR, you can steal somebody
else's gift they've already gotten.
Like the oven mitt.
I'll take the teapot.
Oh, shouldn't we...
I bought that specifically for Pam.
Yaaankee Swap.
That's what makes it fun.
- Pam, you can steal the oven mitt now.
- I'll take the iPod.
And I have to give it to her ?
I don't have a choice ?
Yes, now you can steal the oven mitt,
the old shirt, the shower
radio or pick a new gift.
- That was meant for Kelly.
- Yeah, I figured.
I think this is going great.
- Yikes.
-  Well, it's for Angela, so...
That's like the creepiest
thing that I've ever seen.
Angela, you're up.
I'll take the poster.
Some  people like these.
I will steal the iPod.
Everyone wants the iPod.
It's a huge hit.
It is almost a Christmas miracle.
Ah, well, Oscar, you little gourmand.
You have the next turn.
I'll take the teapot.
Dammit.
Okay, moving along,
Meredith, let's go.
I really want the iPod.
It's already been stolen this round.
Pick something else.
I hope nobody takes this baby,
'cause this is great.
Wow, look at that fine craftsmanship.
Somebody really put a lot of
work into that. It's beautiful.
I'll take the oven mitt.
See, I wanted somebody to take it.
Boom.
Reverse psychology.
Reverse psychology is an awesome tool.
I don't know if you guys know about it.
But, basically you make someone think
the opposite of what you believe.
And that tricks them into
doing something stupid.
Works like a charm.
In addition to these paint
ball pellets your gift includes,
two paintball lessons
with Dwight Schrute.
You and me, Michael. Yes !
Who wants to take
paintball lessons ?
How is that better than an iPod ?
I never said it was better than an iPod.
Michael keeps bragging about his iPod.
But, you know what ?
Two paintball lessons with
someone as experienced
as I am is worth easily like two grand.
Take that Saddam.
Last gift, Kevin.
I want the footbath.
That's the thing I bought myself.
I'm really psyched to use it.
Maybe I should have taken the iPod.
Shoot.
Pam, steal something
or pick the final gift.
I want the iPod.
- Dammit.
- Sure you don't want the teapot ?
I mean, it's an iPod.
- Right.
- Sorry.
No, no, definitely.
Okay, well, I guess I will take,
that book of short stories.
Yes! There you go.
I want the teapot.
Gracias.
You gotta be kidding me.
Yankee Swap is like Machiavelli meets..
Christmas.
What is she so upset about ?
Maybe because you hated
her present so much.
I think Yankee Swap was a big hit.
I think it was a success.
And I'm the one who ended up with
Dwight's stupid paint ball pellets.
Yeah, but Michael, the point is that
we all bought gifts for specific people.
And  you should have just bought
a $20 gift like everyone else.
Well, I didn't! I got a big bonus
because I fired Devin,
And I used the money to buy
something awesome. Sue me !
You got a bonus check ?
How much ?
It wasn't...It wasn't that much.
It was 3,000.
All right, I'm done now.
Unbelievable. I do the nicest thing that
anyone's ever done for these people.
And they freak out.
Well, happy birthday, Jesus.
Sorry your party's so lame.
That comes to 166.41.
All right, now you're the expert.
Is this enough to get
20 people plastered ?
Fifteen bottles of vodka?
-Yeah, that should do it.
- Cool, cool. Box it up.
We wish you a Merry Christmas
And a Happy New Year
I bought this teapot for Pam,
and I know she really wants it.
- So can I trade you for it ?
- No trades.
Come on. It's a shamrock keychain.
Good luck.
A real man makes his own luck.
Billy Zane, "Titanic".
Look, it has sentimental value, Dwight.
Can I buy it from you ?
- No, I want it. I'm going to use it.
- You don't even drink tea.
- True.
But I get sinus infections.
And sinus infections can be cured by
making a tea, from green tea leaf stems.
And pouring it directly
into your nose like so.
To think that my gift to
Pam will be used for that...
It's a little too much to handle.
- This is awesome.
- I know,
It's totally going to change
the way I workout.
Yeah, and I was going to get
you one of these for Christmas.
Now I don't have to.
I'm gonna save a ton of money.
So what are you going
to get me instead ?
I don't know.
Probably like a sweater or something.
Looks like Santa was a little naughty.
What is that ?
This is Christmas spirit.
As in spirits. Booze.
We can drink ?
We're really not supposed
to serve alcohol.
Zip it! Toby.
Just, I mean, it's a party, come on.
If I can't throw a good party for
my employees, then I am a terrible boss.
- Who wants a drink ?
- Me, please.
Here we go !
The deal is that this is my last hurrah.
Cause I made a New Year's resolution
that I'm not going to drink anymore.
During the week.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
Does everyone know
my boyfriend, Bob Vance ?
- Kevin Malone.
- Bob Vance, Vance refrigeration.
- Stanley Hudson.
- Ryan Howard.
- Bob Vance, Vance refrigeration.
What line of work you in, Bob ?
I got, I lost Culpepper
at TO, it was over, man.
Oh yeah, I need McNabb and Deon Branch
to have big games or else I'm done.
It's possible. I can't believe you
traded Sean Alexander, man.
- I had to I need a defense.
- Come on! Sean Alexander ?
- He's the best back in the league !
- Defense.
- Oh, no, it's-that's not worth it.
- It is worth it.
- Never.
- Are you kidding ? You wait.
Anybody making out in here ?
Not yet, give it time
Oh hey, Ebenezer. Boink.
Okay, how's it going in here ?
We're running low on cups.
Do you want me to just run out and
- Yeah, there should be some
- No, no, no.
We'll find some, don't leave the party.
One, two, three !
Kudos to Ryan, king
of the party committee !
Oh, no, I REALLY did not do anything.
No false modesty, my friend.
You know, you don't have
to answer calls during a party.
- Just thought you should know.
- No.
I was just, checking out my present.
I traded with Dwight.
I figured, you know, you went to a lot
of trouble and that means a lot.
And  also Roy got me an iPod or,
was going to get me an iPod, so...
Well, either way. This is an amazing
gift because it comes with bonus gifts.
Look inside.
Oh my God !
The yearbook picture !
Yeah, I think I made the right choice.
Oh, my God.
This is incredible.
Is this the Boggle timer ?
I didn't think you were going
to get that one. I really didn't know.
This is so awesome.
Not bad- and if it couldn't go to Ryan,
you are the guy I'd want it to go to.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Merry Christmas asswipe.
No way! Oh, you're kidding me.
Packer !
Yes! Todd Packer, ladies and gentlemen !
What's up, my nerds ?
- Check it out.
- Oh no, no.
Oh, look at that !
Icing on the cake !
Pac man need a drinky.
Let's fix you up.
Who wants to fix up- Toby?
Toby's gonna fix you up.
- Whoo!
- Yeah.
Darryl !
Here you go. You earned it.
- That's okay Mike.
- No no no no no
I really want you to have it.
All right, thanks, man.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
Whose butt is that ?
Mine.
How did I not guess that ?
Lampshade on the head !
It's happening !
Ho, no !
Hey.
Hello there.
- What are you doing ?
- I don't know.
You shouldn't do things like that.
The man is supposed to do that.
Thanks for the party Michael.
Listen up, we're going
to Poor Richard's.
- Who's in?
- I'm in.
- Yes !
- Michael ?
Poor Richard's ?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Christmas is awesome.
First of all...
You get to spend time
with people you love.
Secondly...
You can get drunk and
no one can say anything.
Third, you give presents.
What's better than giving presents?
And fourth, getting presents.
So four things.
Not bad for one day.
It's really the greatest day of all time.
Hey Meredith, heading
over to Poor Richard's ?
Yep.
Cool, cool, cool.
You need a ride ?
All right, let's head out.
Sounds good, do you have a coat ?
- Yeah.
- Oooh-kay.
www.tvsubtitles.net