David!
- Oh, Michael?
- Are we all set?
Isn't our interview tomorrow?
Yes. I just happened to be
in the neighborhood,
thought I'd drop in and say hello.
You happened to be in midtown Manhattan?
Thought I'd catch a show.
In the middle of a work day?
No.
You know what?
Since I'm here,
let me ask you
a few questions about the job.
Okay.
How many people are you interviewing?
We're only interviewing
the branch managers and
some other
upper level company people.
Ah, well, good.
Out of curiosity
are you interviewing anyone
who has been here
longer than I have, or
manages more people?
- I don't think so.
- Great.
One more question.
When you merged those branches
who did you put in charge?
I believe we put you in charge.
Great. No further questions.
- Okay, Michael.
- Okay.
I'm really looking
forward to our interview.
And I'm really looking
forward to working with you.
I have got it made in the shade.
I know this company.
The other branch managers
are total morons.
Hey, Pam yeah-
I forgot what day the interview was
and I drove to New York accidentally.
I'll be like three hours late.
[새 자막]
Script: easyL
Sync: easyL, nemameya
http://theOffice.tistory.com
3x24-25 The Job
Original Air Date: May 17, 2007 (NBC)
- See, I have 600...
- Yeah, I don't have...
Hey.
Hey, Kev.
What's different about you?
- You look worse.
- Thank you.
You got a haircut.
It's sexy, hot.
Turn around.
No.
Come on.
No way.
Do it!
What's up, Big Haircut?
You are no longer Big Tuna.
From henceforth,
you shall be known as Big Haircut.
- Andy...
- What is it, Big Haircut?
- Nothing.
- Sorry, I can't hear you Big Haircut
- Yup.
- What?
Karen suggested that I get a haircut
before the interview tomorrow
so that I could look presentable
and not, as she so lovingly puts it,
homeless.
Hey.
I think it looks great.
Thanks, Pam.
After I had my little
outburst at the beach,
Jim was really nice about it.
He just basically said that
he missed my friendship, too
and I would always
mean a lot to him
and I understand
where he's coming from.
For the record,
I am not embarassed at all.
It needed to be said,
and I said it,
and it only took me three years
to summons the courage,
so thank you.
Yeah.
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
The time has come to
name my own replacement.
So please hand this
letter of congratulations to
Dwight K. Schrute.
But that's my name.
"Dwight, congratulations a wipe."
"Don't screw the pooch."
Thank you.
Okay.
- Thank you, Michael.
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
- Stop crying.
- Thank you
Hey.
About the beach-
It's okay,
we all say things without thinking.
Oh, no it's not that.
I've actually been thinking that
for a long time.
And I'm glad I said it.
I just- I'm sorry
if it made you feel weird.
Okay.
Pam is kind of a bitch.
Hey, what if we leave tonight?
Grab a bite, get a hotel room,
enjoy the city a little bit.
I just have so much paperwork to do.
Wow. Done. Okay, let's do it.
So I was wondering if Karen and I
could get off a few hours early
'Cause we want to
spend the night in the city.
Why, so you could do it?
No, well- I was thinking that uh-
Actually, we could all leave
tomorrow and do a convoy, you know?
Convoys are really fun.
Pull up next to each other.
Give each other the finger.
Moon each other.
We're gonna go tonight,
But we're gonna see you there
tomorrow morning, right?
Alright.
Alright. Your loss.
Wait, how would you moon us
if you were driving?
Cruise control.
So Jim,
Who do you think is hotter?
Pam or Karen?
Yeah, I'm not going to
talk about this now.
Pam is taller.
You sure?
Yes.
She has bigger breasts too.
I think Karen has
a prettier face.
What else?
I mean Pam's face is
really pretty too.
It's a very tough call.
Really tough call.
You know what?
Why don't you take the rest
of the day to figure it out,
and then come back
and tell me what you got.
- Will do.
- Alright.
Hey, Pam.
I've been meaning to
say something to you.
I really miss our friendship.
It's very funny.
I've never heard you talk that much.
I thought it was Kelly.
Are you kidding?
I would have never done that.
It was patheticville.
No offense, Pam.
You know what?
Don't even worry about it.
Everyone was so drunk,
I bet no one even remembers
what you said.
I remember.
I blogged the whole thing.
www.creedthoughts.gov.www/creedthoughts.
Check it out.
Last year Creed asked me
how to set up a blog.
Wanting to protect the world
from being exposed to Creed's brain
I opened up a Word document
on his computer and
put an address at the top.
I've read some of it.
Even for the internet,
it's pretty shocking.
There they are.
The Accounting Department.
I shall miss your humility
and your promptly printed checks.
Do you think it's gonna to be weird
working with Jan in New York?
No. Not at all.
I haven't talked to Jan
since we broke up.
And I think if she had something
to say she would have called me.
Maybe you should talk to her, before...
No, no, no. You know what?
It's a done deal.
I basically have the job already.
There's nothing
she can do to stop it now.
I already sold my condo.
Michael... / What? / Why?
I'm sorry.
That just doesn't make sense.
- Yes, I-
- What? Who gave you that advice?
Yeah, Michael you should
never sell your condo...
I have to buy another place.
- But you said you were in debt.
- You're not sure that you have the job.
I sold it on eBay.
The buyer was
very motivated, as was I.
It went for eighty percent of
what I paid.
Sold in record time.
How would you like to
spend the night with
the Regional Manager of
Dunder-Mifflin, Scranton?
No Dwight.
I don't care if that is how
they consolidated power in ancient Rome.
No, no, not, not, Michael.
Me.
I'm taking his job.
Not now.
Goodbye, Kelly Kapoor.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim.
Oh, hey, Dwight.
I am gonna be your new boss.
It's my greatest dream come true.
Welcome to the Hotel Hell.
Check in time is now, check out time is never.
- Does my room have cable?
- No.
And the sheets are made of fire.
Can I change rooms?
Sorry we're all booked up.
Hell convention in town.
Can I have a late checkout?
I'll have to talk to the manager.
You're not the manager
even in your own fantasy?
I'm the owner.
The co-owner with Satan!
Okay, just so I understand it.
In your wildest fantasy,
you are in Hell
and you are co-running
a bed and breakfast with the devil?
Yeah, but I haven't
told you my salary yet.
Go.
80,000 dollars a year.
Once I'm officially
Regional Manager,
my first order of business
will be to demote Jim Halpert.
So I will need a new number two.
My ideal choice?
Jack Bauer.
But he is unavailable.
Fictional.
And overqualified.
I will see you at the interview.
Yes you will.
Who is D. Abramson?
He's from that company in Pittsburgh...
Michael.
Why-
are you here?
How are you?
I'm good. How are you, Janet?
- It's good to see you.
- I'm- I'm great.
Can we- can we talk
privately for a minute?
Why privately?
I just- I uh- I don't uh-
I- I don't- I don't like
the way that we left things.
Okay, sure, fine.
Why don't you wait in my office?
I have some important
business matters to take care of.
- Okay.
Pam, Defcon 10.
- Houston, we have a problem.
- What do you want me to do?
I may need some
immediate assistance.
If you would slowly and quietly
gather the ladies in the conference room.
Phyllis, Angela, Karen.
- What about Meredith?
- No.
She's an alternate.
- So, how you been?
- I've been good.
- Good.
- Good. Yeah.
Sorry to drop by unexpectedly.
I- I tried calling,
but I kept getting voice mail.
Weird.
Yeah, I didn't get
both of your messages.
So- Michael needs us
in the conference room.
‘Cause of Jan again?
Hey, uh- before I leave tonight,
would you mind making a half a dozen
copies of Jim's and my sales reports
for our interviews tomorrow?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I really hope you get the job.
Thanks.
After you ended everything with us,
I went on a vacation.
To kinda clear my mind.
Sound good. Sounds fun.
It was. Yeah, it was good.
I think I- just-
get right to the point, you know?
I- I feel good about myself for the
first time in a really long time, and-
I've made some big changes in my life and-
I miss you.
I want us to get back together.
Would you excuse me for a second?
Defcon 20.
She wants to get back together.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know. That's why you're here.
- Help me, please.
- Would you want to get back together with her?
No, no. What do I do?
Just don't get back together with her.
What if she makes me?
How can she make you
get back together with her?
She made me do a lot of things
I didn't wanna do.
This was a terrible relationship.
You were not happy
when you were with her.
I wasn't.
You're so much happier now.
Just go in there and be strong.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
I need to go in there
and tell her that we can't be together.
Right.
Do it.
I'm in a very good place right now.
Thank you.
Okay. Jan.
We need to talk.
Jan is in a different place right now.
And it is a sign of maturity to give people second chances.
So I am going to hear her out.
Oh my God.
Huge!
Yeah, bigger actually.
That's crazy!
Oh, my God. Can you believe that?
Unbelievable.
- She could put the cup right there.
- I know.
No, it's fine.
I'm sure it must've been weird for Jim
when Roy and I were
joking around-
that one time.
I would never do that.
Waste of money.
In my experience,
guys are way more attracted
to the back of you than the front.
I love fake boobs.
Often times,
you find them on strippers.
I find it offensive.
Au naturale, baby.
That's how I like'em.
Swing low, sweet chariots.
So...
There are a lot of things that
I would like to do differently / Yeah.
I feel like when we first got together,
that I had a problem
with my priorities.
First got priorities.
And if we could talk about a way
to approach a possible reconciliation...
Let's get back together.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll tell you this,
it is not because of the boob job.
Excuse me,
boob enhancement.
That would be shallow.
And this is the opposite of shallow.
This is emotionally magnificent.
Okay, everyone, listen up!
Time to begin the interview process
Andrew Bernard.
Saving the best for first.
Alright, you guys. See you later, wish us luck!
No! Hey, hey, hey, hey! Do not wish them luck.
All luck must be wished unto Michael.
- Good luck, you guys!
- What did I say!?
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
I'm happy for him.
I hope he gets the job.
I really just want him to be happy.
And I know that sounds cliche.
And I know saying it
sounds cliche, sounds cliche.
Maybe I'm being cliche.
I don't care.
Because I am what I am.
That's Popeye.
I am going to begin this process
with a simple test of
intelligence and mental dexterity.
What is the best color?
White,
because it contains all other colors.
Wrong. Black.
It is the most dominant.
How do you make a table?
You make a chair,
but you don't sit on it.
What is the capital of Maine?
The capital of Maine is
Montpelier, Vermont,
which is near Ithaca, New York,
where I went to Cornell.
Okay, also,
moratorium on Cornell talk.
Don't wanna hear about it.
Forget your personal history
and learn the history
of this company.
Should not be a problem.
I minored in history in the
Ivy League school which I attended.
You're not off to
a very good start, Bernard.
I agree.
But in another way,
I am off to a very good start,
wouldn't you say?
I am a great interviewee.
Why? Because I have
something no one else has.
My brain.
which I use to my advantage,
when advantageous.
Time! No, you failed.
Damn it!
This interview is over.
I'll let you know.
Hey, thank you so much for
driving me down for my interview.
Totally, no problem.
What are you
interviewing for by the way?
my assistant, or?
Oh, you know I'm gonna have
a congratulations Karen party
Tomorrow night at my friend's house.
Oh wow, that sounds like fun.
Is your friend name Karen, too?
What did she accomplish?
No.
I'm sorry.
I should have been clearer.
It's for me.
'Cause I'm going to get the job.
How remarkable.
Thanks.
Wait- Wait a sec.
- Check one more time.
- Okay.
Very good
Alright, well-
I- I have to get back.
- But I will see you in New York tomorrow, right?
- Yes indeed.
- Good luck with your interview.
- Thank you.
Bye.
So, I guess
we're getting back together.
What happened?
Your advice was good,
but Jan's was bigger.
Here's the sitch.
Two weeks ago, I was in
the worst relationship of my life.
She treated me poorly.
We didn't connect,
I was miserable.
Now, I'm in the best
relationship of my life
with the same woman.
Love is a mystery.
So we have all night.
Where do you want to go first?
I don't know.
How about the U.N.?
How often do you come here?
Every time my sixth grade
class has a field trip.
I think you'll really
enjoy this, adult Jim.
Hey, everybody.
The next time you see me,
I'll be working for corporate.
Starting tomorrow, Dwight Schrute
will be running the branch.
So, without further ado,
I would like to start
saying my goodbyes
♬ For everything you've done ♬
♬ You know I'm bound ♬
Okay.
♬ I'm bound to thank you for it ♬
Goodnight
and good luck.
Who's ready to work?
Yeah, we went to
the Spotted Pig for dinner.
It's in the Village.
Karen knew it.
And then we second acted Spamalot.
That's when you sneak in
at intermission with all the smokers.
And then we went to a bar
that used to be a church.
Oh and at this one bar,
I swear I saw Lorne Michaels.
That wasn't him.
So what's going to happen
to us when I get this job?
Oh do you mean when I get the job?
Well, if you get the job
then I'd move here with you.
Would you move with me?
I'm not stupid, okay?
I was at the beach.
We won't have a future in Scranton.
There's one too many people there.
You mean Kevin?
Exactly.
But you get it, right?
Can't stay there.
Yeah, I do.
Come on.
How are you guys doing?
Need anything?
Uh- no, we're good. Thanks.
I have been here a bunch of times.
So I know where everything is,
know everybody's names.
If you need to know
somebody's name, just ask me.
Who's that?
That is Beardy.
Beardy?
I'm gonna introduce myself.
No, no, no, just-
that's not his real name.
That's just what I call him, so...
I am by far the most qualified
person they're interviewing.
Jim and Karen are here,
which is cute.
They're like, kid actors
tagging along with daddy
on the big audition,
hoping to be discovered.
Except daddy is
the best actor around.
Daddy is Meryl Streep.
Michael is gone.
Hail to the chief!
My first order of business?
Make Andrew Bernard
my number two.
My first order of business?
Accept.
As if you had a choice.
Duh. Opportunity of a lifetime.
Three months ago, I was nowhere.
I was just a Cornell grad,
in anger management.
Look where I am now.
Not bad.
Hey! Hunter!
What's up my brother?
This is Hunter,
secretary extraordinaire.
Uh- administrative assistant.
Jan in yet?
I think she's coming in later.
Could you give her a message
for me, when she gets in?
Sure.
Just say,
"I want to squeeze them."
It's code. She'll
know what it means.
Okay.
Oh, Hunter?
Could you tell her, also?
You showed great leadership
potential at the coal walk.
Even if you did follow it with that
embarrassing personal confession.
Thank you.
I had to make Andy my number two.
It's political, complicated,
you wouldn't understand.
I want you to be
Assistant Regional Manager.
Really?
Well, in a sense.
Although, publicly I am going to retain
the Assistant Regional Manager position.
You will be your own assistant.
Correct, I need
someone I can trust.
But I would also like the title
to be secretly applied to you.
Just stripped of
its pomp and frills.
Okay.
So, you would be
the Regional Manager,
and the Assistant
Regional Manager.
Andy is your number two.
I would be the Secret
Assistant Regional Manager.
Let's call it Secret Assistant
to the Regional Manager.
Do you accept?
Absolutely, I do.
I learned from Jim.
If Dwight ever asks you to
accept something secret,
you reply, "Absolutely, I do."
Hello, hello!
- Michael, good to see you!
- Good to see you.
Here are the post-merger
performance stats that you asked for.
Great. I've been meaning
to thank you by the way.
You didn't lose a single
customer during the merger.
And you still managed
to trim the budget.
That is nice work.
So, let me ask you a question
right off the bat.
What do you think are your
greatest strengths as a manager?
Why don't I tell you what
my greatest weaknesses are?
I work too hard.
I care too much.
And sometimes I can be
too invested in my job.
Okay.
And your strengths?
Well, my weaknesses are
actually strengths.
Oh. Yes. Very good.
- Thank you.
- Very good.
Dwight is our new boss.
Oh, Michael's not going anywhere.
Then who do you think will get the job?
Karen.
She looks corporate.
Those little pants suits.
I think it's gonna be Michael.
Do you really think he's qualified for that job?
No, but he wasn't qualified for
the job he has now, and he got that one.
Yeah.
Listen up! Come to the
center of the room, please.
This is a Schrute Buck.
When you have done
something good,
you will receive
one Schrute Buck.
One thousand Schrute Bucks
equals an extra five
minutes for lunch.
What is the cash value
of a Schrute Buck?
Excellent question, Pam.
1/100th of a cent.
So ten thousand of your dollars
is worth one real dollar?
Just- zip your lid!
Another announcement.
Michael wasted an enormous amount
of the group's time and
patience with non-work related
ethnic celebrations and
parades of soft-minded
dogoodedness.
No longer.
No more meetings!
Amen.
Instead, today I will begin my first
lecture in a long series of lectures
designed to increase your
knowledge on the world of paper.
Do we have to?
Yes! Michael is gone.
There's a new sheriff
here in these offices,
and his name is me.
Conference room!
10 seconds!
All of you!
I literally cannot wait until
I see what Dwight has planned.
And I wish Jim were here.
What do you think we
could be doing better?
I've never been a big fan
of the name Dunder-Mifflin.
I was thinking we could name
the company something like,
"Paper Great.”
“Where great paper
is our passion.”
“We're GREAT!"
I don't know, could be good.
Or, "Super Duper Paper."
"It's super duper."
I don't know,
something like that.
- Okay.
- Thanks for coming in, Michael.
- Thank you.
It is always a treat
when our paths cross.
So, oh! Before I forget,
I wanted to let you know,
if you hadn't already heard,
Jan and I are back together.
So, I may need to fill out
one of those love documents again.
You're back together.
Yes. And I am very excited about
the prospect of working under her,
or on top of her.
That's not sexual, just-
we're all professionals.
Okay, well-
I thought it was clear
in the description of the position.
The job you're applying
for is Jan's job.
I don't understand.
So, we're gonna tag team it?
No, we're letting Jan go.
Listen up. Let's start
from the ground up.
Where does paper come from?
- Trees.
- Trees!
And where do trees grow?
- Forest.
- Soil.
Right. We have in
front of you here,
7 different types of
Pennsylvania top soil.
Now, what would you say-
is the most important element
in the production of above
ground leafy growth?
Probably phosphorus, right?
Wrong! It's nitrogen!
Absorb this information.
Good!
Now, let us discuss precipitation.
Stanley? When rainfall occurs,
does it usually fall in a liquid,
solid, or gaseous state?
Liquid.
Very good!
You have earned one Schrute Buck.
I don't want it.
Then you have been deducted 50 Schrute Bucks!
Make it 100.
Don't you wanna
earn Schrute Bucks?
No. In fact, I'll give you
a billion Stanley Nickels
if you never talk to me again.
What's the ratio of Stanley
Nickels to Schrute Bucks?
The same as the ratio of
unicorns to leprechauns.
- Okay...
- That's it!
- What-
- Class is canceled, everybody out!
- No wait, what are you doing?
- I'm punishing them.
No, no, no, wait!
Class is not canceled.
Hey! Come on!
Let's listen to
Dwight's presentation!
- What- What are you winking for?
- Zip your lid!
So, that's...
my basic 5 year plan.
And after that, who knows?
- Okay. Uh- now, this may seem like an odd question, but...
- Yeah?
What do you think
about Michael Scott?
He's a very nice man.
And he's very well suited
for the job he has now.
This is off the record.
He would be disaster.
Hey you!
Hey.
How was your interview?
- Pretty good.
- Yeah?
Could have gone better I guess.
I'll put in a good word for you.
Cool.
Maybe you should do it
sooner rather than later.
What?
Let's just run away together.
Let's just run away to
Jamaica and live in a bungalow.
You have some savings right?
You could pay off my debts.
It would be fine. We'd have fun.
What's- what's the matter?
What- what happened in there?
I can't tell you.
Tell me what?
You son of a bitch!
Jan, this isn't the time,
- You're firing me?
- we're in an interview...
Where the hell do you get off?
Frankly, it's overdue.
Your behavior in the last two years
has been completely erratic.
Erratic?
Recently, you don't even
show an interest in your work!
You smoke constantly
in your office.
You spend most of the
day online shopping.
You disappear for hours
at a time, sometimes days.
Always saying you're visiting
your sister in Scottsdale.
You go to Scranton far more
often than you used to...
Is it because of these?
- Hey, whoa, Jan, not-
- No, I wanna know. I wanna know!
Because if it is, then- then-
then- I will see you in court!
It's not.
- No?
- It's not.
'Cause he likes them.
Okay? He likes them.
And- and that is-
that is all I care about.
The time has come for you to end your
professional relationship with this company.
You are clearly unstable.
- Hey! You're unstable!
- Yeah!
No, we're all unstable...
Okay, you know what?
I'm just not leaving.
Not leaving.
David, I did not tell her.
It's like staring into my soul
when I look at this wall.
It's like outer space without
the stars. It's so black.
This is gonna look so awesome!
It's so intimidating!
Anyone who comes in here
is gonna have to take me seriously.
Abandon all hope,
you who enter here!
Totally!
- Bye Hunter.
- Bye.
Good luck with your band.
- Oh, thank...
- Don't let them change you, okay?
So long, xxx!
So, I am gonna
give her a ride home.
Let me know about the job.
Actually, Michael,
I think we're gonna take it
in another direction.
Good, I'm glad we're
on the same page.
I have a lot of ideas
for new directions.
No.
We're not giving you the job.
You know what?
That is actually good
Because-
I don't think I could take
my girlfriend's job.
That's not being
a good boyfriend.
So, I respectfully withdraw
my name from consideration.
Do you accept my withdrawal?
- I do.
- Good. Very good.
I'm glad we are finally
on the same page.
Still have my job
in Scranton, though.
- Yes.
- Good.
That's all I ever wanted.
These two.
Either one of them,
excellent candidates.
Wow. That was some serious,
hardcore, self destruction.
Yeah. Kinda feel bad
for her though.
Don't. She's nuts.
Oh, man.
You know what?
This might take a while.
You really don't have to
stay, if you don't want.
Okay, good, because-
a bunch of my friends are meeting downtown for lunch.
- And, I was gonna meet them, so...
- Okay.
- Just call me when you're done.
- Sure.
Good luck, Halpert.
Thank you.
Dunder-Mifflin, this is Grace.
Sure.
Oh, God! I mean,
I just don't understand!
It's just so rude, you know?
I mean the absolute
nerve of that guy!
I know. I know, I'm sorry
about that. That was terrible.
Oh, just- No, actually
I think it's good.
You know? It's fine, actually.
I do. I really think it's great
that it happened, because,
you know, my work has always been the thing
that has gotten in the way of my happiness, so...
No, don't cry,
it's gonna be okay.
Oh, I know, I know.
It's just- I'm sorry.
It's just these painkillers that
I started taking since the surgery.
They make my moods
totally unpredictable!
What am I gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, I guess you could come
and stay at my condo.
I think I could
back out of the sale.
Probably get some negative
feedback on my eBay profile.
Live together.
Actually, wait a minute!
This could be great!
This could be perfect!
You know, my full-time job
could be our relationship.
I could wear stretch pants and
wait for you to come home at 5:15.
It could work. This
could work, really!
I'll be back!
And I am back!
How'd it go?
No. No, Pam. I'm back!
For good!
Kevin Nealon.
Everybody, may I have
your attention please?
It is with great honor and
privilege that I announce to you
that I have officially withdrawn my name
for consideration from the corporate job.
I know, I know, I know.
"Michael, what are you
thinking? You were a shoe in."
Well, got down there.
I nailed the interview.
And the strangest thing happened.
Why is my office black?
To intimidate my subordinates.
That's stupid.
It was Andy's idea.
You shouldn't have taken it.
Bad management.
Good thing I'm back.
Ryan, coffee.
I don't do that stuff anymore.
No, it's for me, bimbo. Kids.
So I'm back.
And I am never,
ever going to leave.
I am going nowhere.
This place is like the hospital
where I was born,
my house,
my old age home,
and my graveyard for my bones.
Did Karen get the job?
Back to work.
Still waiting on that coffee.
Pam, hello.
Dwight, hello.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me,
when you held the title of Secret
Assistant to the Regional Manager.
You served the office
with great dignity.
No, I don't know
what the future holds.
But, I'm optimistic.
And, uh- I had fun goofing
around with Dwight today.
Jim and I are just too similar.
Maybe one day I'll
find my own Karen.
But- that is a- um-
you know, not-
A man.
A man version.
But uh- until then,
I can hold my head up.
I'm not gay.
I don't know how I feel about
hiring a Sixers fan.
I should leave.
Uh, let me ask you
a question, Jim.
- You're clearly a very bright guy.
- Thanks.
Always hit your
numbers, personable,
you make a great impression
on everyone you meet-
I'm sorry, wait,
so is the question
How'd I get to be so awesome?
Because, I don't have
an answer for you.
Uh, oh, hey, do you have
your quarterly numbers?
- Sorry to make you fill that thing out.
- Oh, no, absolutely.
That's a HR formality.
We have this very
irritating HR guy here.
He's probably the only person
you're not gonna like. Kendall.
- So, first up...
- There you go.
How do you think you
function here in New York?
What's that? Oh, great.
You know? I just-
I really appreciate the
buildings, and the people,
and there's just a energy
that New York has.
Not to mention, they have
places that are open past eight.
So that's a bonus.
You've been in the Scranton
branch a long time.
What have you liked
most about that place?
The friendships.
Okay.
Well, we want the person who takes
this position to be here for the long haul.
So, long haul. Where do you
see yourself in ten years?
How are your feet?
Medium rare. Thanks.
The real reason that
I went to Stamford
was because I wanted
to be not here.
I know.
And even though I came back,
I just, I feel like
I've never really come back.
Well, I wish you would.
Dunder-Mifflin, this is Pam.
Just one moment,
I'll transfer you.
I haven't heard anything,
but I bet Jim got the job.
I mean, why wouldn't he?
He's totally qualified, and smart,
everyone loves him.
And, if he never
comes back again,
that's okay. We're friends.
And I'm sure we'll stay friends.
We just- we never
got the timing right.
You know? I shot him down, and then
he did the same to me, and-
But you know what? It's okay.
I'm totally fine. Everything
is gonna be totally...
Pam. Sorry.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Yes.
All right. Then, it's a date.
I'm sorry, what
was the question?
So, I know we left the other
day on a note of uncertainty.
But, after some more thought,
I'm very pleased to be able
to offer you this job.
Great, I'm so glad.
We're all very excited
you're going to be joining us.
It'll be nice to have
another MBA around here.
I'm excited, too.
Okay. Bye.
- Who was that?
- Nobody.
You and I are done.
What?
www.tvsubtitles.net