All right Jim, your
quarterlies look very good.
How are things
going at the library?
Oh, I told you
I couldn’t close it, so…
So you’ve come to the
master for guidance?
Is this what you’re
saying, grasshopper?
Actually you called
me in here, but yeah.
All right, well let me
show you how it’s done.
Yes, I'd like to speak to
your office manager, please.
Yes, hello, this is Michael
Scott, I am the regional manager
of Dundler Mifflin
Paper Products.
Just wanted to talk to
you "manager-a-manager".
All right, done deal!
Thank you very much sir,
you’re a gentleman
and a scholar.
Oh, I’m sorry, OK,
I’m sorry, my mistake.
That was a woman I was talking
to... she had a very low voice.
Probably a smoker. So...
So that’s the
way it’s done.
I’ve been at Dundler
Mifflin for 12 years,
the last four as
regional manager
If you want to
come through here,
See, we have the
entire floor
So this is my kingdom,
as far as the eye can see.
Ah, this is our
receptionist, Pam.
Pam, Pam Pam! Pam Beesly.
Pam has been with us for…
for ever, right Pam?
Well, I don’t know...
If you think
she’s cute now
you should have seen her
a couple of years ago!
What?
Any messages?
Yeah, just a fax
Pam, this is
from corporate.
How many times have I
told you that there’s
a special filing cabinet
for things from corporate?
You haven’t told me!
It’s called the
waste paper basket.
Look at that!
Look at that face!
People say I’m
the best boss.
They go, "God, we've never worked
in a place like this before,
you’re hilarious, and you
get the best out of us.”
I think that pretty
much sums it up
I found it at
Spencer Gifts.
My job is to
speak to clients
on the phone
about quantities
and type of copier paper.
You know, whether
we can supply to them
whether they can
pay for it and...
I’m boring myself just
talking about this.
I still love that
after seven years!
What?
Nothing
Ok, all right.
See you later
All right, take care.
Back to work.
Corporate really doesn’t interfere
with me at all, Jan Levinson-Gould
Jan, hello!
I call her Hillary
Rodham Clinton, right?
Not to her face, because
not because I’m scared
of her, because I’m not...
but...
yeah.
All right, was there anything you
wanted to add to the agenda?
Me no get an agenda.
I’m sorry, what?
I didn’t get any agenda.
Well, I faxed one
over to you this morning.
Really? Cause I didn’t… did
we get a fax this morning?
Yeah, the one…
Why isn’t it in my hand?
Because a company runs on
efficiency of communication, right?
So what’s the problem
Pam, why I didn’t get it?
You put it in the garbage can
that was a special filing cabinet.
Yeah, that was a joke, that
was actually my brother's,
it was supposed to be with bills
and doesn’t work great with faxes.
Do you want to
look at mine?
Yeah. Thank you.
OK, since the last meeting,
Alan and the board have decided
that we can’t justify the Scranton
branch and the Stanford branch
Oh, ok…
No, Michael don’t panic
No no no no, this is good,
this is fine, excellent
Michael, listen,
don’t panic
- Although the alarm bells are going off...
- We haven’t made any decisions yet,
I’ve spoken to Joshua in Stanford
I’ve told him the same as you
and it’s up to either you or him to convince
me that your branch can incorporate the other
OK, no problem
This does, however, mean that
there is going to be downsizing
Me no wanna
hear that, Jan
because downsizing
is a bitch,
it is a real bitch,
and I wouldn’t wish
that on Josh’s men,
I certainly wouldn’t
wish it on my men,
or women - present
company excluded... sorry.
is Josh concerned about
downsizing himself?
Not "downsizing himself", but is
he concerned about downsizing?
Question: How long
do we have to...
Oh, Todd Packer, terrific
rept, do you mind if I take it?
Go right ahead.
Pac man!
Hey, you big queen!
Oh, that’s
not... appropriate
Hey, is old Godzillary
coming in today?
I don’t know
what you mean
Look, I've been meaning
ask her one question
Does the carpet
match the drapes?
Oh my god!
That's horrifying!
Horrible
Horrible person!
So do you think we can keep… a lid on this for
now? I don’t want to worry people unnecessarily.
No, absolutely. Under this regime,
it will not leave this office.
So what does downsizing
actually mean?
Well...
You guys gotta update your
resumes, just like I’m doing.
I bet it’s gonna
be me, probably.
Yeah, it’ll be you.
I have an important
question for you.
Yes?
Are you going to Angela's
cat-party on Sunday?
Yeah, stop.
That’s ridiculous.
Am I gonna tell them? No I’m not going to
tell them, I don’t see the point of that.
As a doctor, you would not tell
a patient if they had cancer.
This is Mister Scott.
- Guilty, guilty as charged!
Ryan Howard, from
the temp agency
Deniqua sent me down
here to start today
Howard, like Moe
Howard, "Three Stooges"?
Right here, high five! Oh
Pam, that’s a guy thing, Pam.
I’m sort of a
student of comedy.
I’m Hitler, Adolf Hitler
I don't think it would be the
worst thing, if they let me go.
Because, then I might...
It’s just, I don't think it's many a
little girl's dream to be a receptionist.
I like to do
illustrations,
mostly water color,
a few oil pencil.
Jim thinks they’re good.
Dundler Mifflin,
this is Pam.
Sure. Uh, Mr. Davis, let
me call you right back.
Yeah, something just came up,
2 minutes. Thank you very much.
Dwight, what
are you doing?
- What?
- What are you doing?
Just clearing my desk,
I can’t concentrate.
- It's not on your desk.
- It’s overlapping.
It's all spilling
over the edge.
One word, two
syllables: demarcation.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Safety violation, I could
fall and pierce an organ.
We'll see.
See, this is why the whole downsizing
thing just doesn't bother me.
Downsizing?
I have no problem with that. I have been
recommending downsizing since I first got here.
I even brought it
up in my interview.
I say, bring it on!
You just still have 8 messages from yesterday.
- Relax, everything's under control.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh
that’s important, right.
Oh, this is so important,
I should run to answer it.
What?
Come on. Six Million
Dollar Man! Steve Austin!
Actually, that would be a good salary for
me, don’t you think? Six million dollars?
Memo to Jan: I
deserve a raise.
Don’t we all?
I’m sorry?
Nothing!
If you're unhappy with your compensation, maybe
you should take it up with HR [Human Resources]
OK? Not today, OK, Pam?
Just... be professional.
I think I’m a role model here, I
think I garner people's respect.
Attention all Dundler Mifflin employees, please
we have a meeting in the conference room ASAP
People I respect, heroes
of mine, would be: Bob Hope,
Abraham Lincoln,
definitely,
Bono,
and probably God
would be the fourth one.
And I just think all those people
really helped the world, in so many ways,
that it’s, it’s
really beyond words.
It’s really uncalculable.
Now, I know there are some rumors out
there, and I just kind of want to see…
I’m Assistant Regional
Manager, I should know first.
Assistant to the
Regional Manager.
OK. Can you just
tell me, please?
Just tell me quietly.
Can you whisper it in my ear?
I'm just about
to tell everyone.
Please, OK.
Do you want me
to tell them?
You don’t know
what it is!
OK, you tell them,
with my permission.
I don’t need...
Permission granted.
Go ahead.
Corporate has deemed it appropriate
to enforce an ultimatum upon me,
and Jan is thinking about downsizing
either the Stanford branch or this branch.
I heard they might be
closing this branch down,
That's just...
That's just the rumor going around,
this is my first day, I don’t really know.
Yeah, but Michael, what
if they downsize here?
Not gonna happen.
It could be out of
your hands, Michael.
It won't be out of
my hands, Stanley, OK?
I promise you that.
Can you promise that?
On his mother's grave.
Well, yeah, it is a promise, and frankly I’m a little
bit insulted that you have to keep asking about it.
It’s just that
we need to know.
Hold on a second, I think Pam
wanted to say something. Pam?
You had a look that you wanted
to ask a question, just then?
I was in the meeting with Jan and she did say
that it could be this branch that gets the axe.
Are you sure about that?
Pam? Maybe you should stick to the ongoing
confidentiality agreement of meetings.
Pam, information
is power.
So you can't say for sure whether
it's gotta to be us or them.
No, no, no, Stanley, no, you did
not see me in there with her.
I said, if corporate wants to come in here and
interfere, then they’re gonna have to go through me, right?
You know, you can go
mess with Josh’s people,
but I’m the head
of this family,
and you ain’t gonna be
messing with my children.
If I left, what would I do with all
this useless information in my head?
You know... tonnage
price of manila folders?
Pam’s favorite flavor of
yoghurt, which is Mixed Berries.
Jim said Mixed Berries?
Yeah, he’s onto me.
Watch out for this guy!
Dwight Schrute in the building!
This is Ryan,
the new temp.
Nice to meet you.
Introduce yourself, be polite.
Dwight Schrute, Assistant
Regional Manager.
Assistant to the
So, Dwight, tell him about the kung-fu
and the car and everything.
Yeah, I got a '78 280Z, I bought it for 1200,
fixed it up, it's now worth three grand.
That is his profit!
New engine, suspension, I got it
re-sprayed, I’ve got some photos
Damn it!
Jim!
OK, hold on,
Judge is in session.
What is the problem here?
He put my stuff
in jello again.
That’s real
professional, thanks.
That's the third time and it wasn't
funny the first 2 times either, Jim
It’s ok here, but people sometimes
take advantage because it's so relaxed.
I’m a volunteer sheriff's
deputy on the weekends,
and you cannot
screw around there.
It's sort of one of the rules.
What is that?
That’s my stapler.
No no no, do
not take it out!
You have to eat
it out there.
Because there are starving
people in the world,
Which I hate, and it is
a waste of that kind of food.
OK, you know what?
You can be a witness.
Can you reprimand
him please?
- How do you
know it was me?
- It's always you.
- Are you gonna
discipline him or not?
Ooh, discipline, kinky!
All right, here’s
the deal, you guys.
The thing about a practical joke, is that you have
to know when to start, as well as when to stop!
And yeah, Jim, now is the time to stop
putting Dwight’s personal effects into jello.
OK, Dwight, I’m sorry, because
I’ve always been your biggest *flan*
Nice! That’s the
way it is around here.
You should have put
him in custard-y!
Yes, new guy!
He scores!
OK that’s great, I guess,
what I’m most
concerned with is...
damage to
company property.
That’s all.
Pudding... putting...
I’m trying to think of
another dessert to do.
Do you like going out at
the end of a week for a drink?
Yeah!
Well, that’s why we're all going out, so
we can have an end-of-the-week drink.
Well, then when
are we going out?
I don’t know,
tonight, hopefully.
OK, yeah.
Hey, man.
Hey!
What’s going on?
Hey baby!
Roy is my fiancé, we’ve
been engaged about...
about 3 years, and we were supposed
to get married in September,
but I think we’re gonna
get married in the spring
Do you mind if I go out
for a drink with these guys?
No, come on. Let’s get
out of here and go home.
OK, I'm gonna be a few minutes,
It's only twenty past five, I’ve
still got to do my faxes.
You know what, you
should come with us,
because we're all going out and
it could be a good chance for you to
see what people are like outside
the office, I think it could be fun
No, it sounds good but
seriously we gotta get going
Yeah, yeah.
What's in the bag?
Just tell her I'll
talk to her later.
No, definitely, all right
dude, awesome, will do.
Do I think I’ll be
invited to the wedding?
So, have you
felt the vibe yet?
We work hard,
we play hard.
Sometimes we play hard when we
should be working hard, right?
I guess the atmosphere that I've
created here is that I am a friend first,
and a boss second.
Probably an
entertainer third.
Just a second!
Right?
Oh, hey do you like the
Jamie Kennedy Experiment?
Yeah
Punk'd, and all
that kind of stuff?
You are going to be my accomplice,
just go along with it, OK?
All right
Just follow my lead,
don’t pimp me all right?
Come in!
So corporate just said
that I don’t want to…
You got a fax.
Oh, thank you, Pam.
Pam? Can you come
in here for a sec?
Just have a seat, I was gonna
call you in anyway... You know Ryan?
As you know, there is
going to be downsizing
and you have made my
life so much easier,
in that I’m going to
have to let you go first
What? Why?
Why? Well, theft,
and stealing
Stealing?
What am I supposed
to have stolen?
Post-It notes.
Post-It notes...?
What are those worth,
like 50 cents?
You steal 1000 Post-It
notes at 50 cents apiece,
And, you know, you’ve
made a profit... margin.
You know... gonna run us
out of business, Pam.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
I can’t believe
this, I mean,
I have never even stolen as much as
a paper clip and now you're firing me.
And the best thing
about it is that
we are not gonna have to
give you any severance pay,
because that is
gross misconduct, and…
Just clean out your
desk. I’m sorry.
You’ve been X'd, punk!
Surprise! It’s a joke, we
were joking around, you see?
OK, he was in on it, he
was my accomplice, and
There was, it was kind of a
morale booster thing, and...
We were showing the new guy around,
kind of giving him the feel of the place, so…
God, you were, we
totally got you…
You’re a jerk!
Well, I don’t
know about that.
What is the most important
thing for a company?
Is it the cash flow?
Is it the inventory?
Nah-uh, it’s the people.
The people.
My proudest moment here was not
when I increased profits by 17%,
or when I cut expenses without
losing a single employee.
No, no, no, no.
It was a young
Guatemalan guy.
First job in the country,
barely spoke English,
Came to me and said:
"Mr. Scott,
would you be the
Godfather of my child?"
Didn't work out in the end. We
had to let him go. He sucked.
Hey.
Hey, how are you?
Good, I thought you were
going out for a drink with…
Oh, no, no, just
decided not to, uh...
How’s your headache?
It's better, thanks.
Good, good, that's great.
Are you...
Am I walking out?
Yes.
Yes. Do you wanna... ?
Yeah.
Great, let me just...
Oh, Roy.
Yeah, listen, have
a nice weekend!
Yeah, definitely,
you too! Enjoy it.
You know what, just...
Come here.
WORLD'S BEST BOSS
www.tvsubtitles.net