I'm taking some time off
from work...
well, my other work...
because we needed it.
It's great.
The phone's been ringing
off the hook.
The guys in Philly
are kind of going nuts.
But that doesn't matter.
This does.
It's the only thing
that matters.
We've had some
really nice days together.
Mm-hmm.
Nice morning, too.
Beesly.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Which tie makes me look
like a guy who likes sofas?
My agent's putting me up
for a furniture commercial.
Ah.
Definitely blue.
Totally, right?
So, big tuna, what's up?
Back in the small pond?
For now, yeah, yeah.
I was just spreading myself
way too thin...
Thin-sliced tuna.
Carpaccio.
Go on.
Uh, well, it took me a while.
But I finally realized
that I can't give 100%
to two things at once,
you know?
Yeah.
Tell me about it.
I've been trying to act
and manage this branch.
Half the time,
I don't know if I'm wearing
my stage makeup
or my work makeup.
Huh.
Well, you know,
you can't have everything,
so you gotta ask yourself
what makes you the happiest.
You just go all in
for what's most important.
That's my new thing.
Is everything okay?
No.
Everything is not okay.
The county took my cats.
Wait, all of them?
Two sacks' worth.
Apparently, my apartment
complex has rules
about how many pets
are too many for a studio.
And while I was out
picking Philip up
from daycare, they came.
They came into my house.
That's... that's awful, Angela.
I'm so sorry.
It's the bitch
that lives downstairs.
She's this uptight,
judgmental shrew.
You know the type.
I've never met anyone
like that.
And they're gone.
And I have no one left.
Without my cats, I am
utterly and completely alone.
Angela, you still
have your son.
I guess.
Attention, everyone.
May I have your attention?
There are four new
deadly weapons in this office.
Basher, thrasher,
crasher, and...
Smasher.
"Smasher"? No.
Where'd you get that?
Fireball.
Cut!
This morning,
after hours of combat
with some of the city's
best teenagers,
I earned my black belt
in goju ryu martial arts.
I had to find a new dojo
after Sensei Ira and I
parted ways.
My new sensei, Sensei Billy,
thought I had
more than enough training
to take the test.
Turns out Sensei Ira
was a bit of a shyster.
Sensei Billy says most students
don't spend $150,000
over 20 years
to get their black belt.
I would like to invite you all
to my black belt ceremony,
right here in the office
at lunch,
lunch not provided.
- Fireball!
- Ahh!
That's how it's done.
That's pretty good.
I feel safe.
Hey, Erin.
Is Andy in?
Oh, is Andy in?
Sorry, I-I thought
you said "is Indian?"
And I was like,
"is Indian what?"
Is Indian food good?
Is Indian jewelry pretty?
Is Indian hair
an expensive kind of wig?
Yes to all three, by the way.
Lately, I've been
having a lot of trouble
keeping track
of Andy's calendar.
His student film audition
schedule is crazy hectic.
Yes.
There's Andy.
Andy is in.
I'm a good receptionist.
I know he's in.
David Walrus
in his native habitat.
Hey, Andy.
Can we go in your office
and talk?
Yeah.
This isn't gonna
be an easy conversation.
I told Andy that he was
on very thin ice
when he snuck away for three
months to the Caribbean.
Then last week,
he used company money
to buy a top-of-the-line
photo printer.
In his words, "the kind
that's good for head shots. "
And yesterday, he asked me
to pay for cheek implants.
Claimed it's going
to boost office morale.
Now, he's a good guy.
But honestly,
at a certain point,
the ice gets too thin,
and you fall through.
And that is when you get fired.
- Andy.
- I'm gonna stop you right there.
David, this documentary
is going to air in two weeks.
I feel like it's a once
in a lifetime opportunity
to pursue my dream.
Uh-huh.
But...
Every minute that I spend here
is time not spent
making audition videos
for reality dating,
cooking, or singing shows.
I got a real shot here.
And I'll never be able
to forgive myself
if I blew it
because I was too focused
on my stupid paper company job.
No offense.
So you think you've been
too focused on your job?
At my last head shot sitting,
I was so distracted
wondering what I was
missing at work
that I came across
totally manic.
And I was going for zany.
So you... you want
to quit Dunder Mifflin
to pursue acting?
Well, no, actually.
I see no reason to
limit myself to just acting.
I am pursuing fame of any kind.
Could be singing.
Could be dancing.
I don't... it just...
I owe it to myself
and my future fans.
Uh, well, I guess I can't stand
in the way of a man's dream.
And it seems
like you have the gift.
Thank you, David.
There's probably no way
I can talk you
into staying
at this point, huh?
Nope.
I have made up my mind.
I'm really sorry.
Well, good luck.
Hey, thank you.
Not gonna need it.
Okay.
Well, that kind of worked out.
I think just about anybody
could be a star.
My postman,
the night janitor here...
but Andy?
No, definitely not.
Charisma black hole.
Oh.
Clark.
I'm actually here today.
Surprise.
So I was wondering if maybe
I could have my desk back.
Right.
Yeah.
But, you know, I've actually
been working
pretty hard here
on a daily basis.
So I kind of feel
like I've earned this.
- I mean, you know?
- You totally have.
You have earned it.
But maybe I could be
with my wife.
It's kind of the whole reason
why I'm here.
Right.
Well, I'm here to sell paper.
- Burn.
- Wow.
All right, Jim, look.
I just got made junior salesman.
Right?
And... and Wallace is here today.
And I don't want him
to just think of me
as a customer service rep
that sits in the annex.
I mean, you can
get that, right?
Right?
And what do you need
more face time with Wallace for?
You trying to get a...
a second second job here?
It's okay.
You can sit in the annex.
- What?
- I'll come visit you.
Okay.
The annex it is.
I'll be sitting at your desk,
if that's okay with you.
It's fine with me.
Have fun.
But be careful.
It is very easy to get lost
in Pete's beautiful, dead eyes.
Everyone,
a little breaking news for you.
Just had a little chat
with David Wallace.
And, um, I'm taking
a leave of absence
from Dunder Mifflin forever.
I can't say
we didn't see it coming,
but it's a sad day
when anybody is fired.
We're so sorry, Andy.
Uh, uh, uh, uh,
Andy was not fired.
I wasn't fired.
What are you talking about?
I'm fired up. Yes.
Guys, I'm...
I'm leaving to pursue
my lifelong dream
of being famous.
Oh, Andy.
Yeah, so I'll see you
on the red carpet.
'Cause see,
that's how it works.
Andy sings beautifully,
and he's really good
at dancing.
He's a good speaker.
But there's just something there
you don't want to look at.
Hey, how am I doing
it as your desk mate, by the way?
You probably miss Clark.
Yeah, a little bit.
Oh, wow.
But, um... oh, I get that...
Oh, no, no.
No, it's cool.
- I get it.
- It's cool, man.
I'm sure you and I
will have our own thing.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Go Phillies, right?
You don't watch baseball.
I keep forgetting that.
I just think you're going
into this a little fast.
I'm 38, Darryl.
How much slower should I go?
Show business is cold.
Let's say you get a job,
which you probably won't.
They're not gonna cut you
any slack.
You're meant for a job
with lots and lots of slack.
All right.
I get it.
The male is a funny species.
We don't just tell each other
how we feel.
That's chick stuff.
So instead of saying,
"hey, Andy, I love you, man.
I don't want you to leave,"
you say something like,
"hey, Andy, you're making
the worst mistake of your life.
You're not talented. "
Well...
right back at you, Darryl.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Mmm!
Andy's from the generation
that thinks
they should all be famous.
What happened to the generation
that knew you shut up,
did your work,
and died quietly
from a heart attack?
Could Andy make it
as an entertainer?
I don't know.
You know who's really funny?
This bird in the park
that can't fly right.
I'd pay to see him.
But I don't have to,
'cause the park is free.
- Hyuh! Hyah!
I will now perform
the ceremonial changing
of the belts.
He will now perform
the ceremonial changing
of the belts.
It's not a large room.
I think they heard me.
Take my belt, master.
I now submit to you
every part of myself.
That's really okay.
I'm mostly focused
on the belt here.
Just slip it off my...
slip it off my hips.
Hold it...
take a step back.
Take a step back.
Okay, okay,
I can't...
I can't do this if you're gonna
be thrusting like that, okay?
I think we're gonna have
to cut this off.
He will now perform
the ceremonial cutting off
of the belt.
He... oh.
Gah! Hyah!
Dwight has been
practicing karate for years.
When we were dating,
I would help him
with his strength training.
He would strap me to his chest
in a Baby Bjorn
made for fat children
and do lunges across the farm.
I felt like I was flying.
There it is.
- Congratulations.
- We did it, we did it.
- I love you.
- Okay.
Thanks.
I will now perform
my final kata forms.
- You're going to watch me, right?
- Yes, I will.
- Sensei, you're not watching.
- Yeah, I'm watching.
Just do it.
Ho!
Ha!
- Watching?
- I'm watching.
Watch this part, okay?
Huh, gah!
Gah!
- Ha, ha, whoo.
- Oh!
Sensei, do you generally
do house calls like this?
Uh, you can just call me Billy.
And no.
No, but Dwight insisted.
He wanted
to receive his black belt
in the place
he loves most in the world.
He said that?
- He's an odd guy, isn't he?
- Yes.
Irritating?
Also yes.
But I've got to hand it to him,
he is one of the most
tenacious and determined men
I've ever met.
Hyuah! Hah!
Hut!
Ha... ah!
Unh! Kyah!
Ha! Ahah! Aah!
Oh!
I am so proud of you,
schrooberry blue.
I really felt like
I almost lost her.
And... and nothing
is worth that.
Well, I tell you, Jim,
a lot of guys in my circle?
They wouldn't even
change their golf schedule
to shore up their marriage,
let alone
their professional goals.
Dude, there is no way
that Jim is just back here
to "hang out with Pam. "
You did not just say that.
You don't know Pam.
She is really cool.
All I'm saying is,
forget about my chair.
He wants the manager's chair.
And I thought
you wanted that job.
Yeah, I did.
But I made too many mistakes.
It's out of my reach now.
Besides, I think Jim
would be a fine manager.
I'd be happy
to see Jim as manager.
So the reason
I called you in here
is because Andy is moving on.
Again.
And I'm looking
for a new manager.
And with his performance
this year,
I have been considering Dwight.
Am I crazy?
Not at all.
It should be Dwight.
You sure?
You're going to want to invest
in a lot more
liability insurance,
- but, uh...
- Yeah.
Hey, if there's someone who
loves paper more than Dwight,
I definitely don't want
to meet that person.
Andy, we just wondered
if we could have a word.
It's now or never.
Well, we just had
a quick question
about this decision of yours.
You know, to leave a stable job
and pursue a career
in the entertainment business
in your late 30s
with no savings to fall back on
and no real connections
in that business,
which can be competitive.
Yeah, sure.
What's your question?
Our question is...
it seems dumb.
Well, it's better
than sticking around here
and half-assing it,
right?
Of course.
But what if you were
to stay here,
you know,
and "full-ass" it?
- Yeah.
- Um, really give it a go?
Be the greatest manager
in the history of this branch
and in that way,
achieve the fame
and immortality that you seek?
Hmm?
Nah.
I like my plan better.
Well, Andy,
your plan sucks, okay?
Nobody is going
to hire you ever.
You're too character-y
to be a lead,
and you're not fat enough
to be a great character actor.
What?
No, I don't think
he can make it as an actor.
But he also can't make it
as an employee in an office,
so, you know,
why not go nuts with it?
Hey, are you still in charge
of office supplies?
Yes. Yeah.
I seem to have
a sticky note emergency,
where I grab it
on the wrong end,
and then, this happens.
Oh, boy, um...
If you could
help me out, that would be...
- I could give you
some beginner stickies?
- Anything would help. Thank you.
- Okay.
Here you go.
Oh, also, while you're at it,
if you did have a salt packet,
three tacks, and some aspirin,
that'd be great.
- Oh, wow. You have that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow, that's...
- It's all yours.
You come so prepared.
Aspirin.
If you want to get rid
of a headache,
you sit on something sharp.
Any sensei will tell you that.
Hey, congratulations
on that black belt, man.
It's really great.
Thank you.
So I saw you talking
to Wallace earlier.
Is he going to offer you
the manager's job?
No.
He was maybe thinking
of you for it.
Yeah, right.
I'm afraid that ship
has sailed.
I wouldn't be too sure
about that.
Just saying.
- Hello.
- Well, hello.
Big day for you.
- Big day for you.
- Thank you.
- Love the belt.
- Oh, yes.
You know, I don't know
anything about karate,
but I have broken
a few boards in my day.
Hi-yah.
Diving boards
at my family pool in Redding.
I was an obese child.
I never talk about that here,
but nard-dog's outta here,
so lettin' it all hang out.
This is exciting.
You're finally gonna get
to go out and flap your wings.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
'Cause a lot of people
are saying I might not make it.
Oh, I doubt you'll make it.
Very few do
who try to be a star.
But listen,
you've saved up enough money
to take a couple of years off,
and pursue your dream,
and have some fun, right?
No, I just applied
for more overdraft protection.
Andy, I have nothing to gain
from getting you to stay,
and everything to gain
from you leaving.
But please,
I have known you for years.
I have seen you perform.
Dear God,
don't quit your day job.
Nothing is impossible
to him who will try.
Alexander the Great,
if he were Cockney.
You're bad.
I'm gonna make it.
Every person
who's been on Conan
has a crazy story
about how they made it.
Every person.
Erin.
Honest Erin.
Cannot tell a lie.
- Oh.
- We lay together.
That's something
you can't take back.
So true.
Is there a question,
or are... what?
Will you tell me bluntly?
Do you think I'm making
a terrible mistake
quitting my job
to become an actor?
Bluntly?
Yes.
Huge mistake.
Andy, honestly, I think
you might become homeless
or maybe even starve.
Thank you.
You can stay on
as a salesman, Andy.
Thank you.
Dwight, could you come in here
for a second, please?
- Say it again.
- Will you be the new manager?
Where?
- Where?
- What branch?
Here. Scranton.
Come on.
Come on, Dwight.
Get up.
Let's go.
It's good news.
I'm sorry.
I've just waited for this moment
my entire life.
I mean, I was
interim manager once,
but then I shot that gun.
What?
But this isn't interim manager.
No.
It's Dwight K. Schrute...
Manager.
Why do you already have this?
In case Michael or Andy
ever got killed
in a traffic accident
and there was a trade show
on the same day.
You will not regret
this decision, David.
I know.
I will never,
ever let you down.
I know, Dwight.
I know.
Okay.
All righty.
You're gonna do great.
- Hey.
- Wow, hey.
Hi.
What's up?
- Um, I have a question.
- Okay.
Oh, I had a question.
Really?
- I did!
- Yeah, totally you did.
Super important.
I need you to stay right here
while you think about it.
- Okay.
- All right? I'm gonna wait.
All right.
I did not come back here
just to see you.
No, I'm sure you did not.
What was your question?
I don't know,
but it might take me
a long time to figure it out.
Well, then, I should figure out
things to do while I'm waiting.
Exactly.
Hey, everybody.
I changed my mind.
Not leaving.
I'm gonna stay on in sales.
Oh, thank God...
because sales could be
your best role yet.
Hey.
Good choice, man.
Seriously.
Don't wanna see you
in a porn next year.
Okay.
Ooh, there's a great play
about a salesman.
Death of a Salesman.
I don't think so.
Sure,Death of a Salesman
by Arthur Miller.
It's a great play
about crushed dreams.
Mm, no, this one was written
by Spongebob Squarepants.
Got any hot leads?
See, so you just push
from under,
and turn it around, and boom.
Now, the staple crimps outward.
I had no idea.
And here, I've been stapling
the same way for 20 years
like a frickin' sheep.
- Look who's back.
- I'm back.
Oh! Hey, look, and now,
it's like a double date.
Wow.
'Cause, uh...
bop, bop.
Tweedle-lee-doo.
Actually, maybe we should
go on a double date sometime.
That'd be fun.
Yeah, we should do that
for real sometime.
Well, how about Thursday?
Oh, well,
Thursday's tough because...
Weeknights are actually tough
just because...
They are.
That's true, yeah.
Just forget it.
- Forget I said anything.
- Oh.
Attention, everyone.
Just a quick announcement.
Little reconfiguration
to the staff.
- Dwight Schrute...
- David.
Can I just do one thing
while you're making
this announcement?
And then, I'll never,
ever do it again.
- I don't think so.
- But it's just one thing.
- Just let me... let me do this...
- Dwight... Dwight... Dwight.
Come on... what I was
about to say is Dwight...
Oh.
I- I'm sorry,
I gotta...
this'll be a second, sorry.
Just wait
and send it to voice mail.
Yeah.
Come on.
Then we'll get him
a new set of drums.
Oh, my God.
Dwight Schrute is manager!
Oh, yeah!
Whoo!
Brava.
- Way to go, Dwight.
- Whoo!
Creed Bratton
is the new manager!
Congrats.
- What's going on?
- Dwight's the new manager.
He freaking did it.
Congratulations, Dwight.
Pam.
Congratulations, buddy.
Thank you, Jim.
Congrats, Dwight.
Get out of Jim's seat.
Wha... but I fought
for this seat.
You're an annex kid.
You might be bullpen.
We'll see.
Give it a couple years.
Scram.
It's nice to have you back.
- So...
I wanted to offer you
a new position.
Let's hear it.
Assistant regional manager.
Nope.
Can't accept that job.
- It's not a real job.
- Jim.
I'll tell you
what I could accept
is assistant
to the regional manager.
That is a real job,
and one I'd be proud to take.
Shake on it?
Done. Way to negotiate, idiot.
Don't get me wrong.
I am definitely here for Pam.
But this is
an awesome added bonus.
So... all the numbers adding up?
Hey, I didn't get a chance
to say it, but...
congratulations, Dwight.
Thank you.
Ahem.
Yes, congratulations.
Yeah, and, Dwight,
I'd like to be
the first
to say congratulations.
This is a big day for you.
Hmm.
Yes, it is.
Carry on.
How did I just abandon
my dream so quickly?
It's 'cause I had a fallback.
That's the problem.
When you have fallbacks,
it's just easy to give up.
When Cortez landed in Mexico,
only way he got his men
to defeat the Aztecs
was by burning
all of his own boats
so they could never
return home.
Huge dick move,
but very effective.
I need to be that same kind
of dick to myself.
Everyone!
- Changed my mind again.
- Which is it now?
- Dream or no dream?
- Uh, dream.
Goin' with my dream.
Gotta go all in.
Ain't that right, Jim?
Oh, don't look at me,
'cause I think you're making
a terrible choice.
All in!
Whoo!
Toby!
Hey.
I changed my mind again.
I am gonna leave Dunder Mifflin
to pursue acting after all.
- Okay, then, Andy.
- Yeah.
But here's the thing.
I can't have good old
Dunder Mifflin to fall back on,
or else I'll never succeed.
Gotta burn those boats!
So I need you
to go into my file
and put down
that I was fired for theft
and/or groping wieners.
A- Andy, you know
I can't do that.
- It'd be lying.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, I'm...
- Come on, just do it.
- I can't.
- All right, fine.
Just know
that you made me do this.
Oh, come on.
Andy, no.
God, Toby, don't...
stop blocking my hand.
No, no.
This is your...
you brought this on.
No, no.
Andy.
Okay, all right.
Groped you good.
Off to Hollywood!
This is Angela.
Oh.
Hello, Miss Polodnikovski.
Uh, how can I help you?
Did my rent check not clear?
Because I just transferred
another $25 to that account.
So if there's a problem,
it's clearly on your end.
And... oh.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Good.
Then, um...
what is this about?
No, no.
Hey, hey.
No, you are out of line,
Miss Polodnikovski.
No. No, you are.
No, you are!
Evicted? Fine!
I don't want to live
in that cesspool anyway.
Listen, I get
my security deposit back.
Yes, I do.
Ye...
That is not fair!
Well, you know what?
You have so many hairs
on your chin,
Animal Control
should've taken you away.
That is very unladylike.
You are disgusting!
What do you think
that was about?
David.
I lost the Scranton
White Pages account.
Do you have any idea
how much paper that is?
And I'd just like to point out
I was mad at Dwight.
I did it out of spite.
We put the past
behind us, though, Andy.
When have I told you
I hate you and this company?
Enough, Andy.
Enough!
Just stop forgiving me, David.
Please?
This is my last chance to honor
what is best inside myself.
What if I took a dump
on your new car?
Oh, my God.
Eleanor Roosevelt once said,
"The future belongs to those
who believe in the beauty
of their dreams. "
I think she's right.
- I feel calm now.
- Get out!
Get out!
I feel, like,
for the first time
in a long time,
I'm doing the right thing.
- Andy.
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
Uh, heavy stuff
like books on the bottom.
So it won't squash
my knickety-knacks on top.
Yeah, okay,
that's not what I mean.
You don't have to leave
because you said you would.
Don't let pride ruin
your whole life.
Okay?
It's not worth it.
Wow.
Angela.
What we had was great,
and, honestly, I think
about it a lot too...
Ugh.
But I just...
it's in the past.
- And I feel like we shouldn't...
- No, that's not...
- Rehash...
- No, none... no, stop.
It's just...
- Exactly.
- Okay.
Well, have a good trip.
Good luck, Andy.
Thanks, Angela.
You too.
Thanks.
A- bridge a-burnt.
No turning back now.
Everybody, Lorelei and I
would like to say thank you
and good-bye
the only way we know how.
- Oh, good lord.
- Can't you just leave?
You know, Andy, you could just
say a really nice good-bye.
Tuna, I'm a performer,
and perform I shall.
* I will remember you *
* Will you remember me? *
* Don't let your life *
* pass you by *
* and weep not for
the memories *
* Remember all the good times *
* that we had *
* I let them
slip away from us *
* when things got bad *
* How clearly I first saw you *
* smilin' in the sun *
* Want to feel
your warmth upon me *
* I wanna be the one *
* I will remember you *
You okay?
It's just a really nice song.
* Will you remember me? *
* Don't let your life *
* pass you by *
* and weep not
for the memories *
* Don't let your life *
* pass you by *
* and weep not for
the memories *
Awesome.
Nice!
Thanks, Meredith.
- Mm.
- Who knows?
Maybe Andy will make it.
- He's not terrible.
- Yeah.
And people worse than him
make it all the time,
like Lil' Romeo.
No, he's good.
Hewasgood.
- Good night, Kevin.
- Night, Oscar.
Tents?
Are you thinking
of going camping?
I thought you found
nature vulgar.
Well, I've changed my mind.
Wait a minute, Angela.
You're not thinking
of living in a tent...
Oh, God, would you just mind
your own business?
Okay, listen.
I'm just gonna say this.
You are not going to live
in a tent.
- Oh, God.
- Come stay with me.
You don't want me
at your place.
I do. Yes.
Not forever, but u-until
you get back on your feet,
which won't be long.
It's the least I can do.
Well...
Separate bathrooms.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's go get Philip.
- Then, we'll get your stuff...
- Okay.
And you get the hell out
of that place.
Okay.
Are you allowed to have pets?
Oh, Angela.
Yesterday, I was just your
average, ordinary paper salesman
with a farm and a bunch
of pipe dreams about beet fuel.
Today, I leave here a regional
manager with a black belt.
Ah!
It really is amazing
how your life can change
in one day.
You talk to Wade and Colin?
No, I just saw
I missed their call.
Why? What's up?
We got an offer on the table.
- What kind of offer?
- A buyout.
- What?
- We're in play, baby.
- Oh, my God.
- We did it.
- We did it!
- Ah, ha, ha, ha, ho!
Hey, and look.
The buyers wanna make sure
it's not just a Philly play.
- Okay.
- So get this.
They're gonna pay for us
to go pitch out west.
We talking spurs,
the jazz, cowboys.
Blake Griffin, baby.
- Wow, that is...
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- We did it.
Yeah, we did it.
Hey, how long... how long do
we think that's gonna take?
Wade said we could do the
whole country in three months.
Oh, man.
Yeah, I can't do it.
Can't do what?
This, man.
I- I can't do this to Pam.
No, no.
Jim, this is different.
This is everything.
I know.
And I...
and I can't do it.
So is your place all bachelor,
slobby, and gross?
Nope, it's neat
and tastefully appointed
like most gay men's homes.
The stereotype holds up.
I wouldn't know.
I never lived with a gay guy.
Angela, you just were...
I love him.
I know.
I understand more than most,
but we both have to move on.
You... you can't... c...
No, not the Senator.
I love Dwight.
www.tvsubtitles.net