Tonight, the Scranton Business Park
is having Casino Night.
And we are converting our warehouse
into a full-blown gambling hall.
And I know it's illegal in
Pennsylvania,
but, it's for charity.
And I consider myself
a great philanderer.
It's just, nice to know
at the end of the day,
I can look in the mirror and say,
"Michael, because of you,"
"some little kid in the Congo
has a bellyful of rice this evening."
Just...
makes you feel good.
Excuse me. How long is the wait
for a table for two ?
I would never, ever serve you.
Not in a million, billion years.
It's a nice tux.
I know.  It belonged to
my grandfather.
He was buried in it.
So... family heirloom.
So, what's the deal ? We've gotta pay
for our own drinks ? That's lame.
Come on, it'll be fun.
And besides, I'm a roulette expert.
Impossible. Roulette is not a game
of skill. It is a game of chance.
- I can always kind of win at roulette.
- Oh, really ?
How would you do that ?
Mind control.
You can't be serious.
Are you serious ?
Ever since I as a little kid,
like eight or nine, I could...
sort of control things with my mind.
I don't believe you. Continue.
It was just little things, you know.
Like I could make something shake.
Or I could make a marble fall off the
counter. You know, just little things.
That's ridiculous. You know what ?
Why don't you move that coat rack ?
Excuse me, everyone!
Attention in the office, please!
Jim is about to prove
his telekinetic powers.
And he needs absolute silence.
Go ahead.
Okay, I'll try.
Oh, my God.
Episode 22 - Season 2
Casino night
Script: Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation: Catch-22 Team
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
www.forom.com
I try not to think of it
as lagging behind.
It's more of a David
and Goliath thing.
Well, the fact of the matter is,
that your branch
is currently number four
of the five branches
that I oversee and...
- Top 80%.
- Michael...
You know that I'm very serious here.
Jan, listen. I promise
I will kick it up a notch.
What ?
Emeril. Oh, actually,
while I have you...
Not that I have you
or have ever had you.
But, we're having our
Casino Night tonight,
and I think everyone would love
to see their fearless leader here.
I thought that you were
their fearless leader ?
I am, but your are the Eva Peron
to my Cesar Chavez.
- I think you can handle it...
- Oh, come on...
- probably, Michael.
- Come on! It'd be fun.
I can hear it in your voice.
You need a break.
Goodbye, Michael.
Jan and I understand each other.
The romance thing is sort of
on hold for the time being.
But we've remained good friends.
Good friends with privileges.
Not now. Someday.
Okay, everybody. Tonight's event is
to benefit the Boy Scouts of America.
- Again. We do that every year.
- Well, they need our money.
They don't have cookies
like the Girl Scouts.
It'd be nice to do something for
people who are actually suffering.
Well, Oscar, if you don't like it,
then you should concentrate
on winning.
Because the person at the end of the
evening with the highest chip count
will receive $500 to donate
to the charity of their choice.
And, they will get a mini fridge
compliments of Vance Refrigeration.
So, get your charities into Pam.
I, for example, am playing
for Comic Relief.
That doesn't exist anymore.
Comedy's very much alive,
as are homeless people.
No, they stopped making that show.
Well, then they need our money
more than ever.
You have to pick an approved,
nonprofit organization.
There's a great soup kitchen
in downtown Scranton.
Delicious pea soup on Thursdays.
I'll probably give the money to them.
Something with animals.
Or people.
Kobe Bryant has a foundation
and he is so hot.
And he gave his wife
the biggest diamond ring.
I know he didn't do it.
Maybe he did it.
We are giving money
that has been gambled.
Why don't we just deal drugs
or prostitute ourselves
and donate that money to charity ?
Oh, and another fun thing.
We, at the end of the night,
are going to give the check
to an actual group of Boy Scouts.
Right, Toby ? We're gonna...
Actually, I didn't think it was
appropriate to invite children
since it's, you know.
There's gambling and alcohol.
And it's in our dangerous warehouse.
And it's a school night.
And, you know, Hooters is catering.
You know. Is that enough ?
Should I keep going ?
Why are you the way that you are ?
Honestly, every time I try to do
something fun or exciting,
you make it not, that way.
I hate, so much about the things
that you choose to be.
Okay, you know what ? I will not
donate my winnings to Comic Relief.
Since, apparently, it doesn't exist.
I am going to donate to
Afghanistanis with AIDS.
Who ? I think you mean
the Aid to Afghanistan.
No, I mean Afghanistanis with AIDS.
- Afghani.
- What ?
- That's a dog.
- No, that's afghan.
- That's a shawl.
- Wait, canine AIDS ?
- No, humans with AIDS.
- Who has AIDS ?
- Guys, the Afghanistanannis.
Okay, you know what ? No, no.
AIDS is not funny.
Believe me, I have tried.
There are certain topics
that are off-limits to comedians.
JFK. AIDS. The Holocaust.
The Lincoln assassination
just recently became funny.
"I need to see this play like
I need a hole in the head."
And I hope to someday
live in a world
where a person could tell
a hilarious AIDS joke.
It's one of my dreams.
- What are you doing ?
- Oh, nothing.
"Till Death Do Us Rock."
They're wedding bands.
Roy was supposed to pick the band,
but he's concentrating more
on the bachelor party now.
Wait, wait, where are you going ?
I mean,
even if you don't hire a band,
you still have to watch the bands.
Pam, these are people who have
never given up on their dreams.
I have great respect for that.
And yes, they're all
probably very bad.
And that'll make me feel better
about not having dreams.
- There's a KISS cover band in here.
- Let's do it.
I'm pretty happy these days.
I'm getting married soon, and I'm
getting along with everybody at work.
Why did I talk to Jan
about transferring ?
Well, you know...
I have no future here.
I have already put down the deposit.
Do you understand how
a deposit works ?
Mike, I am not having fire eaters
in a paper warehouse.
It's Casino Night. Like Las Vegas.
There are fire eaters
all over the place.
- Except my warehouse.
- Well, actually, it's my warehouse.
Actually, it's owned
by Beekman Properties
and Dunder Mifflin is four years
into a seven-year lease.
Why are you here ?
When Darryl was coming, you said
you wanted me here for protection.
I said, not that.
We just have a lot of stuff down
there that could be stolen.
- That's ironic.
- What ?
That you are afraid.
Why ? 'Cause I'm from the hood ?
Dinkin' flicka.
I taught Mike some phrases to help
with his interracial conversations.
You know, stuff like "fleece it out,"
"going mach five," "dinkin flicka."
You know, things us Negroes say.
Gimme some.
Oh, yeah. I taught him
a handshake too.
I don't know how you're gonna decide.
They are all extremely good.
I think I should hire them all.
Do like Lollapalooza.
Have three stages. Yeah.
Your mom would love that.
She would.
Now this band is called
Scrantonicity.
Let's take a look.
- Nice.
- Oh, wait! That's Kevin.
- On the drums.
- What ?
- On the drums! On the drums!
- Oh, my God! That's Kevin.
Great song, Kev.
Oh, my God.
He's the drummer and the singer.
We really don't do
a lot of weddings.
We actually don't play
in public very often.
We're all really hoping that
Pam's wedding works out.
This could be a turning point
for the band.
- Oh my...
- You haven't seen that since 1983.
That is amazing.
Okay, we have to sign him.
I'm gonna call the label...
No, no, no! Come back.
You're gonna lose him
to another wedding. Kev!
Jim is great.
Being with him just takes away
all the stress of planning my wedding.
Michael, Carol Stills for you.
- Who ?
- Carol Stills.
- Do I know a Carol Stills ?
- Your realtor.
Oh, yeah. Put her through.
Hey, Carol, how goes the real
estate biz ? Is it real good ?
Still me.
Sometimes I don't put Michael through
until he's already said something.
I look at it as a practice run
for him.
He usually does better
on the second attempt.
Carol, you're on with Michael.
- Hello, Michael.
- Hi, Carol. How you doing ?
I'm great, I just needed one last
signature for your mortgage insurance.
Oh, hey. No problemo.
Incidentally, I love the place.
Oh, great.
Great, had a little bit
of a weird smell. It's okay.
At Christmas, the tree helped.
Oh, good. I'm glad.
Can I drop it over later ?
Actually, I'm sort of hosting
this charity thing in our warehouse.
Casino night.
- Oh, great.
- Yeah. It'll be good.
You know what ?
Why don't you come by ?
Bring the papers. I'll sign 'em.
And then you can stay
and have a drink...
- To the casino thing ?
- Yeah, it'll be fun.
- What do you...
- Um, what ?
Oh, I'm sorry. Can you hold on ?
Michael. Jan's on line two.
Okay, put her through.
Jan Levinson, I presume ?
It's still me.
Jan, here's Michael.
- Michael ?
- Hey, Jan. How you doing ?
You know, I...
I thought about it,
and you are right.
- I am ?
- I could use a little fun.
So I am going to drive up
for your Casino Night.
Incidentally, what is the charity ?
AIDS.
Okay then. I will...
I'll see you tonight.
Okay, sounds great.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Hello, Carol ?
Sorry about that. I just...
No, problemo.
Right.
- I...
- To answer your question...
- What ?
- I'd love to go.
I have to get a sitter,
but that shouldn't be a problem.
Problem, good.
-And I'll bring the papers too.
- Good. All right.
- Sounds great.
- Well, I'll see you tonight.
- Bye.
Two queens on Casino Night.
I am going to drop
a deuce on everybody.
Oh, my God!
That's great.
- Hey, Carol.
- Hi!
- You look great.
- Thanks.
Thank you for inviting me.
It looks so great in here.
Well. Just...
That's how we do it in the paper biz.
It's European.
- Michael.
- And... yes ?
Ah, Dwight!
Codename ReMax is here.
No sign of Lan Jevinson.
I'm Michael's wingman.
I've got his back.
Two dates.
He's got two dates tonight.
My job is to keep Jan
away from Carol.
And vice versa. Michael said,
"We must deceive them,
so as not to hurt them,"
"and in that way, we honor them."
Can I get you a drink ?
The food is from Hooters.
- A drink would be good.
- Okay.
Oh, I steal things all the time.
It's just something I do.
I stopped caring a long time ago.
You should see how many supplies
I've taken from this place.
Honestly... I love stealing things.
I'm going to get a drink.
Do you need anything ?
I'm fine. Thanks, sweetheart.
Billy, your nurse is hot.
That's my girlfriend.
Your nurse became
your girlfriend ? Sweet.
She was never my nurse.
I met her at Chili's.
She was my waitress.
Chili's is great.
Willkommen. Bienvenue.
And welcome to Monte Carlo.
Dwight!
I am no longer your boss.
Lady Fortune is your boss.
- Will Lady Fortune give me a raise ?
-Shut it, shut it, shut it.
Will Lady Fortune be your mistress ?
Only time will tell my friends.
Leave all your preconceived
notions about casinos at the door.
Old friends. New lovers.
And the disabled. Welcome all!
Great, okay. Shuffle up and deal.
Let's get it started.
Black-eyed crows.
Okay, the game is no-limit
Texas Hold 'Em.
Good luck, everybody.
That's at least four red chips
to you, sir.
All in.
Bluffing is a key part of poker.
Which is too bad because
I am not very good at bluffing.
Did you believe me ?
I'll call.
What are...
- That's insane.
- I have good cards.
Well, Toby, I went all in
on the first hand.
So doesn't that tell you that
I might have good cards too ?
So, don't be stupid.
Just take it back.
I'm sorry. He can't, sir.
He's gone all in.
All right, whatever.
Flip 'em.
You really scr...
you really screwed that up.
Way to go Toby.
I don't really play cards...
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
It felt really good to take
money from Michael.
Gonna chase that feeling.
That's the normal question.
I expect to do very well tonight.
I have an acute ability
to read people.
Jim, for instance, has a huge tell.
When he gets a good hand,
he coughs.
I will raise.
Thanks.
It's the weirdest thing.
Every time I cough, he folds.
- Wow, bad luck.
- Ah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, you know what ?
If luck weren't involved,
I would always be winning.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Michael ?
- Jan.
- Hi.
- Look, okay.
I think we're all adults here.
And it has always been
my understanding
that we have an open relationship.
What are... wait.
What are you talking about ?
What does that mean ?
After you said you weren't coming,
I invited Carol to come.
And I don't think that
I did anything wrong.
No, no you didn't.
- Hi, I'm Jan. I'm Michael's boss.
- Hi.
- Does anyone want a drink ?
- No, I'm good.
- What ?
- Jan's here.
- Give me the dice.
- Come on, Dwight.
- Let's go.
- It's on you, baby.
Good evening, Dwight.
What is this ?
Evening, Angela. This is craps.
I need to roll an eight.
If I do, everyone wins.
Then roll an eight.
- Thank you Angela.
- Good luck, Dwight.
That's good stuff.
Dwight, let's keep it going.
Let's keep it going.
- Let it ride. Let it all ride.
- Gimme the dice.
- Yeah, right.
- "Yeah, right," what ?
What was this ?
- I have good cards.
- Really ?
And I'm going to take you all in.
I think you're bluffing.
Yeah, I think she's full of it.
Sorry. Straight.
Three nines.
Jim Halpert, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much. It was fun.
Cosmopolitan, please.
Can I get a red wine ?
So two hours. That's a long drive.
Well, it's part of the job. You know,
keep an eye on things. So...
why not ?
So, how long have you
and Michael been, um...
Well, actually, I guess this would be
our first date, I guess.
Casino night in the warehouse.
Good sport.
Well, I'm having a nice time.
Oh, me too. Me too.
One beer, and one 7 and 7
with eight maraschino cherries,
sugar on the rim,
blended if you can.
So, that's still going on ?
You and Kelly ?
- All right!
- Point is four!
Shooter roll a four.
- Come on shooter! Come on shooter!
- Blow! Blow for luck.
Also you. Not playing favorites.
All right, here we go.
- Five.
- So close, so close.
Come on.
So, where are you staying, Radisson ?
- What ?
- Super 8 ?
- No, I...
- Motel 6 ?
- Best Western ?
- I..., I didn't, I don't...
Holiday Inn ?
The Hyatt in Wilkes-Barre ?
- Are you staying with Michael ?
- All right!
I won the 2002, $2,500...
No-Limit Deuce
to Seven Draw Tournament
at the World Series
of Poker in Vegas.
So, yeah. I'm pretty good at poker.
All in.
Okay, let's do it.
Good luck, honey.
Oh, thank you Bobby, but it doesn't
matter. It's just fun to play.
- Three queens.
- Nice. Very nice.
- I have an Ace.
- No, that's a flush.
Oh man!
- I have a flush!
- Yes!
Look, I won.
Look, I have all the clovers.
You want to play again ?
I suck.
She took you down, huh ?
I do not want to talk about it.
Hey, I saw your tape.
Your band, Scrantonicity.
You guys rock.
Yeah, you guys want
to play our wedding ?
Awesome. Did Pam say it was okay ?
Whatever.
I'm in charge of the music.
Dude, you will not be sorry.
Sweet. All right.
Smoke ?
No, thanks.
You, having fun ?
Fabulous time.
I drove two and a half hours
to get here.
- Yeah, we all really...
- Left work early, drove down here.
And I am completely underdressed.
I think you look great.
Why did I hook up with Michael ?
Yeah, why did you ?
It was very late, Jim. Very...
very late and...
Have you given any more
thought to the transfer ?
- Oh, yeah.
- Good.
Have you told anyone ?
- No.
- Well, you should.
Excuse me. Big moment.
The, evening's chip leader
and winner
of this beautiful mini refrigerator
courtesy of Vance Refrigeration.
Creed Bratton, Dunder-Mifflin.
Thanks, I never owned a refrigerator.
Sorry babe, I am just beat.
It's okay. I'll see you at home.
Okay. Hey, don't try to lose
too much money, all right ?
- Okay.
- In case you still want a honeymoon.
Hey, Halpert!
Keep an eye on her, all right ?
Okay, will do.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Hey.
- Hey, how's it going ?
Good. Especially after I took
all your money in poker.
Can I talk to you about something ?
About when you wanna give me
more of your money ?
Did you wanna do that now ?
We can go inside.
I'm feeling kinda good tonight.
I was just, um...
I'm in love with you.
What ?
I'm really sorry if that's weird
for you to hear. But you needed to...
hear it.
Probably not good timing.
I know that, I just...
What are you doing ?
What do you expect me
to say to that ?
I just needed you to know.
Once.
Well, I... I...
I can't ?
- You have no idea...
- Don't do that.
- what your friendship means to me.
- Come on.
I don't wanna do that.
I wanna be more than that.
I can't.
I'm really sorry
if you misinterpreted things.
It's probably my fault.
Not your fault.
I'm sorry if I misinterpreted
that... our friendship.
- I'm leaving.
- Hey! Okay.
So, I just wanted to congratulate
you on a fantastic evening.
- Did the company proud.
- Thank you.
And thanks for inviting me.
You were right, I needed it.
- So thanks.
- Okay. Thanks for coming.
Nice to meet you.
And you guys have a,
- have a good time together.
- Okay, talk to you Monday.
- Buh-bye.
- Goodnight.
- She's a good boss.
- She seems really nice.
Oh, she's great.
Love triangle drama.
All worked out in the end though.
The hero got the girl.
Who saw that coming ?
I did. And Jan is really
happy for me.
So actually the hero got two girls.
He got the girl that he works with,
and he got the girl
that he buys real estate from.
So, I've got my New York girl
and my local flavor.
Life is good.
About ten minutes ago.
No, I didn't know what to say.
Yes, I know.
I don't know, Mom.
He's my best friend.
Yeah, he's great.
Yeah, I think I am.
I have to go. I will.
Listen, Jim...
www.tvsubtitles.net