The building's custodian is
on vacation for the month,
and Dwight is too chip to
hire a replacement.
So, instead,
we're living in filth,
but, not for long...
because I have created
the chore wheel.
Oh, yeah.
Can I spin first?
Well, it doesn't spin.
We'll just move the wheel
one notch each morning,
and you see what chore
you get that day.
A wheel is supposed to spin.
Yeah, you know,
like "guh-guh-guh-guh-guh-guh
guh-guh-guh-guh-h-guh--"
- No, I'm familiar
with spinning.
It's just that wouldn't work
with the chore wheel
because people might get
the same chore--
- Yuck. Boring.
All she talks about is chores.
A wheel wants to spin, Pam.
Spinning would be more fun.
Okay.
Okay, that's what
I'm talkin' about.
- Woo!
- Wow!
- Spinning!
- Big money, big money.
Yeah!
Mug duty?
Yes, you clean all the mugs
in the sink.
This sucks.
Yeah, seriously,
it's like everything
on there's work.
I don't think you guys
understand why we're doing this.
- It's--
- Yeah, and I don't think
that you understand wheels.
I've been through several rounds
of development
with the team,
and here's where we stand
with the chore wheel.
We've got prizes!
Ten bucks, candy bar,
manager for an hour.
But there are also penalties,
like no internet,
Stanley gets your lunch.
The one thing
that is not on the chore wheel
is chores, but they were right.
It's more fun this way.
Oh!
Ahh! Whoo!
- Tiny wheel!
- Tiny wheel! Tiny wheel!
- There it is!
The tiny wheel
actually does have chores.
It's so cute,
no one seems to mind.
- Toilets!
- Aww.
- Tiny wheel.
- Lucky!
- Good choice.
- Woo!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Pam, we gotta go!
Cece, go back inside.
Grandma's got breakfast, okay?
We are going to Roy's wedding.
Yep, Roy.
I think the only weird thing
about going
to your wife's
ex-fiancee's wedding
on a weekday at 8 AM
is that it's
your wife's ex-fiancee.
Thanks, mom!
- Banana?
- Yeah.
I'm afraid
he's only gonna have hot dogs.
Oh, come on, not even Roy
will have hot dogs
at his wedding.
I planned a wedding with him.
He wanted hot dogs.
Just-- it's so weird.
Oh, Pete, you've got mail.
Really?
I got somethin'?
Well, it's addressed
to customer service,
so it's your mail.
Well, you know,
I'm also customer service.
Yeah, I'm alternating.
Yay.
Another person yellin' at me.
Well, it could be
a nice letter.
I write nice letters
to companies all the time.
That's really nice.
Wow, Newsweek, huh?
This election thing
is crazy, right?
It's open.
Oh, yeah.
I accidentally read it.
It's not a nice letter.
Okay.
Get excited.
The special projects fairy
has arrived.
I know you don't really exist.
Today, I launch
my big charity initiative,
"Operation Give Back."
Andy has shot down all of
my special projects thus far,
but this one is about charity
so I'd like to see him
piss on that one.
Darryl!
Ho-o-o! What's happenin'?
Congratulations, baby.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
- Is this his house?
- Think so.
Mimosa?
- I'm okay.
- Thank you.
Would you like me
to take your peel?
Yes, thank you.
Okay.
Who's that?
- Uh, my ex-fiancee.
- Ha-ha.
I started a new business
with my college friend,
but Pam doesn't know.
Um, actually I--
I did tell Pam,
and we decided no,
but then I decided
"yes, anyway,"
so I'm thinking there's another
conversation coming,
and it's hard to know
when that will be.
With "Operation Give Back,"
you pick the charities
Dunder Mifflin supports.
Aw, boy.
What's happening?
There's $4,000 to give away,
so who has filled out
their forms?
- Stanley?
- American Diabetes Association.
Um, you have diabetes, Stanley.
I'm sorry, is the assignment
to pick a selfish charity?
I, uh, I would love
to give--
Heifers International.
Listen to this.
They give a poor person
like a goat or something.
It's a great prank.
I wanna work
with, uh, Jimmy Carter
and Help Build Gnomes.
Dwight, what about you?
I will not be participating,
as there is no evidence
that charity works.
Uh, correction--
I give to a foundation
that teaches homeless children
nautical flag signaling--
Changes Lives.
- Thank you, Andy.
- I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it
for the preservation
of nautical flag signaling.
Dwight, you will
be participating.
- No, thank you.
- Participation is mandatory,
Dwight, but you can choose
whatever cause you like.
Fine, I choose
the Global Relief Foundation...
- Great, thank you--
- ...which was recently discovered
to be a front for the Taliban!
- Oh, for goodness' sake.
- Oh, yeah.
The Taliban
in Af-a-ghanistan.
The Taliban is the worst.
Great heroin, though.
Dwight, I cannot have
the Taliban on the roster
of "Operation Give Back."
Well, then, it looks
like there won't be
any "Operation Give Back."
The nanny state is over,
ladies and gentlemen.
You're welcome.
There he is.
Is it almost time
to cut the pancake, or what?
Aw, yeah.
We appreciate everyone
coming so early.
Everyone's just been so nice.
Thanks for inviting us,
by the way.
- That was-- that was a surprise.
- Are you kidding me?
Come on, if it wasn't for you,
I never would've met Laura.
But seriously, could've dodged
a bullet on that one.
- Just kidding.
- You're welcome.
Thanks.
Ohh.
By the way, man,
this place is beautiful.
I started a gravel company.
I mean, who knew
it would take off?
- Gravel company.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
- What are you doing?
Not gravel, obviously.
Nah, things are good.
Things are good.
Got some stuff in the works,
so...
- Oh, cool.
- Yeah, you never know.
Hey, bro, stop wasting time
with this haircut.
He's got a $50,000 sports car.
- Cheers.
- Okay, Kenny.
Duncan, listen,
I would love to help you out,
but where am I gonna
find somebody
that's pretty, smart
and well-informed, huh?
Hold on-- hold on!
Erin, do you know anybody
that might--
Oh, my gosh.
You love the news, right?
Well, it depends.
I mean, sometimes I find out
things that are really sad.
Well, I got a buddy
that's a big time
local news producer,
and I can't tell you his name,
but it'd blow your mind.
Uh, is it Duncan?
He's looking
for on-air talent,
and he'd kill me
if I didn't get you on tape.
You mean put me on the news?
You'll just come over,
put on a little lipstick,
loosen up
with a glass of red wine,
and then we'll just run
through a few stories.
You know, a couple
different ways
with a couple different outfits.
It'd be really tasteful,
and it'd really help me out
with Duncan--
with my friend.
What'd you say?
Ehh--
No, maybe, okay?
Let me think about it.
Okay.
- Woo.
- Think it over.
No, Clark's not my friend.
He is the douche that sits
next to me at the office.
My friends
are Scott, Glenn and Rob,
but you don't know them.
I never really thought much
about being more
than a receptionist, but why?
Because I happened
to answer a "help wanted" ad
to be a receptionist?
I mean, what if the ad
had been for a CEO
or for a brain surgeon?
So, uh, it was a year ago today
that I met Laura.
I thought she was my waitress,
and, uh, took her three weeks
to tell me that she actually
owned the place.
You are full of surprises.
You are
my beautiful mystery girl,
and today,
I have a surprise for you.
He plays piano?
No.
Roy? No.
You know how I said
I was taking boxing lessons?
Actually, I was doing this,
um, so, I hope
that you like it.
You got this, Roy.
♪ She's got a wa-a-ay
about her ♪
♪ don't know what it is ♪
♪ but I know that I can't live
without her ♪
♪ she's got a way-- ♪
We still surprise each other.
Definitely.
You know, I never did it,
but for your 30th birthday,
I really wanted
to surprise you.
Courtside seats.
Sixers.
Yes, but what I didn't tell you
is that I actually bought
the tickets.
We only didn't go
because it was--
It was an away game.
In Phoenix.
They should really tell you
that more specifically.
I mean, every game
is an away game
for one of the teams.
Do we know everything
about each other?
No.
Tell me one thing
about you I don't know.
Um, okay.
Oh, there's one.
Did I ever tell you
about the time
that my brothers videotaped
the lottery announcement
and bought the winning numbers
the next day,
and then, played the tape for me
the next week--
And you thought
you guys were millionaires.
You heard that one.
Yes, but there's-- Wait.
Oh!
There's a funny ending
to that story.
I can't remember.
That I thought
we were millionaires.
That you thought
you were millionaires.
- Yep.
- That's funny.
- Shoot, I knew that one!
- That's all right.
The senator and I
still have mystery.
I'm always waiting to see
what he's gonna surprise me
with next.
You all right?
You support the Taliban abroad,
so I assume you're willing
to live by their rules here.
Anything else
would be inconsistent.
Will you join me then
in a pledge
to live by Taliban law
in this office?
Absolutely, I will.
I feared Nelly
had some sort of a plan,
but she used a ridiculous font.
You don't have a plan!
When you use a ridiculous font,
no one thinks you have a plan.
Looking for this?
What the--
Oh, this is a lovely pen,
and it's mine now,
because I stole it.
- Gimme that.
- Didn't you sign a contract
to live under Taliban law?
And now, there's been a theft.
That means you're not serious,
or someone's getting
their hand cut off.
- You're insane.
- I know,
so it's better
that you pick another charity.
Oh, and let your precious
"Operation Power Grab"
proceed unchecked?
No, thank you.
In that case, you...
will have to chop off my hand.
This cleaver
appears to need sharpening.
I suggest you spend
some quality time together,
just you and your hand,
tie a shoe, toss a salad.
Do any of the two-hand
activities
that you'll miss the most.
I tell you what.
I need to make three calls.
And then after that,
you can become a person
who chops off people's hands.
Sounds like a plan.
Clark wants to film you
in different outfits
- inside his apartment?
- Yeah.
Clark, you and I
need to have a little chat.
What clothes does Erin need
for this news audition?
Uh, a couple
of button-downs,
a camisole, a blazer,
a pencil skirt,
stilettos, maybe a--
no, no, not maybe,
definitely open-toed.
Uh, something low-cut,
because the camera
makes everything
seem higher-cut.
- Really?
- Yeah, industry secret.
You're gonna want
some of those pantyhose
with the seam up the back.
Seems unnecessary
for an audition.
And then, you know,
maybe just a robe
to wear in between takes,
but I probably got one
that she could borrow
at my place, so--
Thank God someone here knows
what they're talkin' about.
I want you
to take this credit card.
Take Erin to the mall,
and get that stuff.
I absolutely will do that.
Awesome.
Plop.
Guess I'll just head over
to the mall then,
buy Erin
some sexy, fun outfits.
That Clark, huh?
Next question for our oldyweds.
What is the craziest place
you ever made whoopee?
Language.
Who was
Pam's first celebrity crush?
- Oh, this is good, okay.
- Pam's first celebrity crush.
John Stamos.
- Ready?
- Uh-huh.
- John Stamos.
- Oh, yes!
John Stamos was temporary.
I quickly moved on to Johnny--
Johnny Depp.
Uh, um, I was having
a separate conversation
with Kevin?
Uh, Johnny Depp.
Totally. George Clooney.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'll have one.
I have one.
Where is the craziest place
you ever made whoopee?
Kevin, stop it
with that question.
Right?
And did you show them
the market-- yeah.
And what'd they say?
That's awesome.
That-- aw, my God.
Wow.
It's not even real yet,
and I'm not gonna tell her
until it's real.
I think maybe
they're actually is something
I don't know about Jim.
Everyone, we have
a voluntary meeting
in the conference room
to discuss Erin's confidence.
Her body.
We're gonna talk about her body.
Good. Great job.
Andy made me his consigliere,
which means
assistant regional manager.
I guess he thought I'd be
into The Godfather
because I'm black.
Wrong!
I'm into The Godfather
'cause I'm a cinephile.
I like Scarface
'cause I'm black.
Erin has an audition
to be a newscaster.
- Wow!
- Woo!
- Uh-huh.
- Congratulations!
And I want her
to feel very comfortable
in her very sexy skin,
so everybody say
something that you like
about her body, all right?
- Darryl.
- Okay.
Um, I like Erin's hair.
Those are very pretty colors.
- Yeah, right?
- I'm sorry.
- This is for a news audition?
- Yeah.
Then why are we talking
about her looks?
Why not her credibility
or her reliability?
News flash, everyone--
the human race
finds attractive people
more trustworthy.
So sorry, Andy,
but for 20 years,
the most trusted man in America...
Walter Cronkite.
Cronkite was hot.
If I could go back in time,
I'd take that moustache ride.
Does Erin have any experience?
Has she taken
any journalism classes, maybe?
Has she done
the pageant circuit?
- No, I watch the news--
- She's gonna be amazing.
Look at her.
She's gonna light up the screen.
This is a first for me,
and I don't get a lot
of chances,
so I have to take them
really seriously.
I will do whatever it takes
to get the job.
- Whatever it takes.
- Yeah, I know, I heard.
This is it.
- Any questions?
- Is it gonna be numb?
No, it's gonna be
over before you know it.
Mm-hmm.
Afghan president Hamid Karzai
declared a new policy
of dollar days
throughout the country,
promising low, low prices
on all 2012 Kia Sentras
and Sonatas.
"Aren't you glad you waited?"
Karzai commented.
Um, where did you get
that story?
A little bit here,
a little bit there.
I bet you didn't think
I knew current events.
I love it.
It's fantastic.
Now, tag it with your name.
For Channel 11 News,
I'm Erin Hannon.
Pause after news.
For Channel 11 News,
- I'm Erin Hannon.
- No, pause longer.
- That was a good one.
- Pause-- pause-- pause longer.
Okay, build suspense.
Don't be shy.
Got it.
For Channel 11 News...
What, it's--
- I'm Erin Hannon.
Okay, all right.
Great.
Some great stuff in there.
I can feel you looking at me.
Okay, well here's something
you don't know.
- A couple of weeks ago...
- Mm-hmm.
I ran into this guy
from my high school
who has just gotten divorced,
and he hit on me in the mall.
And I didn't tell you
because-- I don't know,
I felt embarrassed,
and I didn't know
if you'd be mad or worried,
but anyway,
I thought you'd wanna know.
That didn't happen.
You would've told me
right away.
Yeah, I would've.
What about you?
Come on, there's
gotta be something.
Between your birth
and the last two days,
something you just haven't had
the chance to tell me.
Uh...
Just tell me.
God, give it up, Beesly.
You know me too well.
- Hey.
- Hmm.
Um, I knew
something bothered me,
and I finally figured it out.
What news producers
are gonna wanna see
is how Erin relates
to the other people
- on the news team.
- Oh.
The weird thing is Erin
is doing the audition alone.
Oh, God.
Now, I'd say Clark
could be your co-host.
He's already doing camera.
Somebody who's already
got rapport with Erin, maybe.
I don't know.
Hey, this is
for real this time.
It's gettin' late.
Thought you guys
could use a little inspiration.
Oh, a movie.
- What is this?
- 127 Hours.
- It's about this guy who--
- No, no, no, no,
- no spoilers. Please.
- My bad, my bad--
- No--
- You're right, okay.
Good night.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Everybody.
- Yeah.
- Come in.
- All right.
- Come on in.
- Wow!
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
Sorry, man.
Andy thought Erin
need a co-anchor.
I'm his makeup guy.
My hands are tied.
The victim was released
from the hospital
with second-degree burns.
Oh, wow.
You know what they say, Erin?
If you can't take the heat,
get out of the kitchen.
Well, he tried to,
but the fire door was blocked.
- He sure did.
- All right.
We got that.
That's a rap everybody.
It's just-- you sure, Clark?
Yep, she's done.
No, I just--
I don't mean Erin.
I mean for me.
I didn't feel good about that.
Oh, no, we got it.
We got it.
Great! Let's get some food.
I'm starving.
I don't think we did get it.
I could do a couple more takes.
We could do it in close-up.
That might even be better
for editing.
Okay, I don't.
All right.
I'm hungry.
Uh, Pete, you wanna take Erin
to get a burger or something?
- Yeah, whatever you say, boss.
- Okay.
- I'll call you later.
- Great job.
So this is a single.
Hey, even this doesn't
work out for me,
I'm just glad I had
the guts to do it,
and maybe it'll work out
for Andy.
Oh, that is
absolutely revolting!
- Yeah.
- He is so good, though...
Yes.
The way he just
cuts off his arm.
If you like James Franco,
we really should watch
Rise Of The Planet Of The Apes.
Well, he's a genius, you know?
He was in graduate programs
at Yale, Columbia and NYU
- all at the same time.
- Whoop-de-doo.
That doesn't make you a genius.
Well, it doesn't
make you stupid.
Oh, yeah, it does.
Actually, it makes you
- real stupid.
- Oh, stupid like you.
- No, like you.
- Like you.
- You're the stupid one.
- You, you, you, you, you--
www.tvsubtitles.net