(BOTH GREETING IN SPANISH)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello, Dunder Mifflin.
No, no, no. No.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I believe that every man,
woman, and child in this country
should learn how
to speak Spanish.
They are our neighbors to the south,
and this would be a healing thing
for all of North America.
And I am going on vacation
next week to Cancún.
(GREETING IN SPANISH)
(CHATTERING IN SPANISH)
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
(GREETING IN SPANISH)
(GREETING IN GERMAN)
I don't understand why Michael
is wasting his time with Spanish.
I have it on very good
authority that within 20 years,
everyone will be
speaking German.
Or a Chinese-German hybrid.
(SPEAKING SPANISH INCORRECTLY)
(CORRECTING IN SPANISH)
Michael's having a hard time
with the gender part of Spanish.
So, I told him
to mark everything
with the international
symbol for gender.
And...
I should have been
more specific.
Your office is full
of genitalia.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
"That's what he says"?
Damn it.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Ah, Angelo!
Angela.
Michael.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SCOFFS)
All right, so I'll finish up on bulk pricing
and then you go into delivery guarantees.
You know, maybe there's an
opportunity for a joke there, like...
Like, "I just
delivered a baby.
"They didn't offer
me a guarantee."
Yeah. Maybe we don't
even need that.
Can you smell the power?
Halperts, power couple.
You know what? I should be
getting this client, Michael.
My numbers are better
than either of theirs.
I went with the people I thought
would put the best face on the company.
If you want people to put
the best face on something,
why would you
get two people
who probably have never cut the
face off of anything in their lives?
It's a good point.
This is our first
joint sales pitch.
I think we're gonna work
really well together.
Yeah. I think we have
complementary strengths.
We understand
each other.
We have good
give and take.
I give, he takes!
I don't even know
who you are anymore.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hi. Donna Newton.
Here to see Michael Scott.
Hey, Miss Newton. Hi.
I'm Jim. How are you?
Did somebody order
a hooker over here?
Stop that. Hi.
Hi. How are you?
There's this woman
I met a few weeks ago.
Her name is Donna. Manager
of a Sid and Dexter's.
And right now, we're in the
midst of a passionate love affair.
No, but she is coming by today,
maybe to buy some printers, so...
Right here, we have the wonder
twins, Jim and Pam Halpert.
They will be
assisting you today.
You look exactly alike.
No, we're
actually married.
We're not
brother and sister.
I have a sense about
these things. All right.
You have some ancestors
in common somewhere back.
I knew it. You should see their baby.
So, yes, laser printers are more
expensive, but they cost less to operate,
so it's a trade-off.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
Little time sensitive. Do
you, Donna, by any chance
shop at Victoria's Secret?
What?
Because I keep getting
these magazines sent to me
via the address of the woman who
used to live in my condo before me.
None of this
is time sensitive.
Yes, the sale's on
now through May.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Okay. I have more of them.
You would have weekly conference
calls with executives in corporate,
a two week training program at
the Yale School of Management.
Obviously you would be high on the
list for advancement opportunities.
Sounds all right.
What is this?
This is Print
In All Colors,
Sabre's minority
executive training program.
(SCOFFS) It doesn't just sound
"aite," it sounds amazing.
I didn't say "aite."
How do I apply?
You have to be a minority.
Glasses wearers,
cholera survivors,
geniuses, non-organic family
farmers. The list goes on and on.
You want me to keep going?
Those don't really count.
We're thinking more ethnic
and racial minorities.
Come here. Come here.
Ten seconds ago this guy
was driving a forklift, okay?
Now, all of a sudden, he's Cinderella of
the office? What are you guys thinking?
I like the sound of this.
Maybe one day I'll be
sitting in Michael's chair.
Wouldn't that be something?
DWIGHT: One minority from this branch
is going to get into this program.
Who would I prefer? Hmm.
The competent hardworking one
who does things his own way,
or the malleable simpleton who can
be bought for a few fashion magazines?
This is the second time that
you've sent me the wrong size.
I mean, I know what
a four should feel like.
I've been a four
my whole life.
You know what? You can go to hell,
all right? Thanks for nothing.
Oh, man.
White people, right?
I don't know
if she was white.
Well, you can kind of
tell from their voice.
Yeah.
I bet you get pulled over by the
cops a lot just because of your race.
Well, they say it's because of
texting, but maybe you're right.
I think you should consider applying for
the executive minority training program.
I never thought of myself
as an executive before.
I know, 'cause you
have no role models.
How many Indian CEOs
can you think of?
I can't think of
any CEOs, any race.
You could be
the Indian Bill Gates.
the Indian Ted Turner.
I could be
the Indian Julia Roberts.
That's not... She's...
Okay. Yes.
I took the liberty to scan a few things
earlier, and I want to show you...
There we go! Look at those
vivid colors. Look at my eyes.
Those are
Shrek-green eyes.
That is me again. I think this
displays the crisp, dazzling white.
And that would
be a display
of the crisp,
gorgeous black.
DONNA: Yeah.
It's subtle.
It's how it works.
I show her an image
that turns her on,
and then she looks at me,
then she looks at the image,
then back at me,
then back at the image.
Soon she doesn't know what
is me, what is the image,
she just knows
that she's turned on.
This is a place that I like to
go to be alone with my thoughts.
I've never taken
anybody there before.
Who took the photo?
Ryan.
Oh.
And that's it.
That's me.
That's who I am.
Not bad.
Oh, thanks.
You're not bad, either.
Thank you.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Oh, my God.
Jim, could you come
in here for a sec?
What was that printer
we were looking at?
You didn't see it, Pam.
She was giving me all sorts of signals
that she wanted me to make a move.
Shortbread?
No.
I'll have one.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
try to kiss people at work.
Oh, really, Jim?
What about Pam?
And you did a heck
of a lot more than kiss.
Maybe this could
be my Pam.
Okay, well,
all that is irrelevant...
Maybe Michael
has a point.
I mean, if she was really that
upset, she wouldn't still be here.
Was it professional? No.
But I work in the nightlife
industry. I get hit on all the time.
In my 20s,
it would've been annoying.
In my late 20s,
I find it really flattering.
Look, I know that
I screwed up in there.
I know that I probably
messed up your sale.
I just want to go
in and fix it.
What if I back out and you
finish the pitch with Jim?
What?
What was that?
Just let him flirt with her.
People meet each
other all sorts of ways.
Pam, you know he's not gonna get
anywhere and he's gonna blow our sale.
Who cares?
It's not that huge a sale.
Hey, the Schwab guy told us to treat
every sale like it was a huge sale.
Don't act like you understood
anything that guy said.
Good luck, wingman.
How has being
a minority affected you?
Well, there's a lot of
pressure from my parents
to settle down
and marry an Indian guy.
Oh, good. And you
resent this because...
Indian guys always wear their cell
phones outside their pants. It's so dorky.
No, no, no. That's not dorky. Look,
it's easily accessible. Boom. Like this.
911, hello. Scranton
Strangler's in the house.
Inside the house!
Just put it
in your pocket.
(CHATTERING)
Look at that. She's
totally flirting with him.
You don't know that. Some people
can't help oozing sexuality.
You ever notice you can
only ooze two things?
Sexuality and pus.
Man, I tell you.
She just crossed her
arms together. That's bad.
Maybe she's just pushing her breasts
together to make them look bigger.
Like that?
Is this the best
you can do right now?
For that printer, yes.
Unfortunately we don't
have a lot of flexibility.
Oh. Well, I guess I'm just used
to the restaurant business where,
if you're in charge then
you can always get discounts
for the people
that you like.
JIM: Yeah.
Maybe we can find
a little wiggle room, right?
What's that?
Maybe we can find some
wiggle room. (SIGHING)
I don't...
I don't think so.
I think we could.
I don't see how we could possibly sell
these for that little without losing money.
Delivery alone will cost...
Okay, well, sometimes,
sometimes it makes financial sense to
lose money, right? Like, for tax purposes.
Actually, I ran the numbers
on this, and in this case,
it makes more financial
sense to gain money.
Why don't you
run them again?
What if she's just flirting
with you to get a better price?
If she is,
it's working.
Yeah, Michael, here's a trick.
Ask her if she wants a mint.
If she says no, then
she is not interested.
She does not like him.
You can flirt with someone to get what
you want and also be attracted to them.
How do you think
we got together?
'Cause I stopped by your
desk, like, 15 times a day.
I was after your money.
Well, the joke was on you.
Yes, it was.
Can you stop
micromanaging?
I know how to do this.
You're yelling... Okay. Okay.
What are you guys doing?
This girl was really rude
to me at the mall,
so I created a fake IM account
from a hot guy at her high school,
and now I'm trying
to make her anorexic.
Tell her everyone in
homeroom thinks she's fat.
KELLY: That is so good.
You know, we really should keep
practicing for this interview.
Oh, that's okay.
Ryan coached me.
Ryan? What does he know?
It's easy. You just turn
every question around on them.
Do you think you're treated
differently because of your race?
Would you ask that same
question if I was white?
We're so in.
We?
When I become executive,
I'm gonna make Ryan manager.
And then the two of us
are cleaning house.
DWIGHT: Kelly will be
even worse than Darryl.
If you'd have told
me this morning
that today I'd be creating a monster
capable of my own destruction,
I'd have thought you were referring to the
bull Mose and I are trying to reanimate.
"So, corporate approval of this contract
is contingent upon buyer and seller
"obtaining..."
Blah-de-blah-de-blah.
"Boilerplate, pound
of fish." Just kidding.
Do you like mints?
Yes.
I carry mints
with me sometimes.
Oh, I haven't
tried those.
Ever tried those?
No.
They're good.
You want one?
Sure.
It's like...
"Cool... Certified cool." I
like how they say "certified."
Like there's some
consortium of...
Michael!
I'm sorry.
I can't stop myself
from kissing her.
Yeah. Now you know how I feel
sitting next to those M&M's all day.
Well, why don't you
just move the M&M's?
Why don't you shut up?
Okay. Guys, guys, guys, just tell me it's
not totally insane to try one more time.
It is totally insane.
Michael, he's right. You
are turning into a stalker.
(SIGHING) Okay.
What do you think?
I think it's over, man.
Andy?
(GROANING)
Okay, some for,
some against.
Nobody's for.
Pam.
Hmm?
What do you think?
I think it's really,
really unlikely.
Okay.
Really unlikely.
But I can't say
that it's impossible.
What?
I'm not saying
she's in love with him,
but she could have
left a while ago.
Most printer sales are done
over the phone, Miss Boob Shirt.
I'm going
with Pam's group.
Wait. Michael.
Okay.
Michael. Michael.
No. Guys, guys, guys, guys,
just thank you for talking.
Wish me luck.
JIM: No.
What sort of movie would Rudy
have been if he had just stopped
and given up
after two rejections?
Would have been a lot shorter,
probably been a lot funnier,
but it would have ultimately
been a disappointment.
I still would have seen it,
but that's not the point.
Kelly is disqualified.
What?
You said the program
is not open to Caucasians.
Well, anthropologically,
she is Indian.
Indians migrated from the
Caucasus region of Europe.
Therefore, technically, she is
Caucasian. You're welcome, America.
Yeah, but she's
not white, though.
Well, obviously
she's brownish,
but come on. I mean,
Darryl is far more ethnic.
Darryl withdrew
his application.
The dates of the Yale program interfered
with his softball league, so he's gone.
I got my whole life
to be a minority executive.
I only have about a year
left in these knees, though.
So Kelly is
the only applicant.
Yeah, unless somebody
else applies today.
(GREETING IN HINDl)
Oh, dear God. Okay.
Don't make any decisions just
yet. Okay? I'll be right back.
Hello.
That's very nice. I
never noticed that before.
Sometimes my bangs cover it.
Yeah. I don't want to be offensive,
but may I ask you what that means?
I do find that offensive,
actually.
We should have your
contract done by Thursday.
Oh, great! Great. I will
look out for that stuff, then.
Okay.
And...
You know, I just wanted to say it was
really, really nice to do business with you.
Yeah. It was nice to do
business with you, too.
Thank you.
Did I get everything?
I don't know.
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
Okay.
So... Oh! Donna?
DONNA: Yeah.
Do you need validation?
We don't validate.
No. It's just
in the lot, so...
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Mmm.
Bye.
(CLEARING THROAT)
So, if you have...
If there's any other
questions that you have...
I don't have any
other questions.
I'm just gonna make
my way down to...
MICHAEL: Okay.
All right. Bye.
DONNA: Bye-bye.
Have a good elevator ride.
DONNA: Okay.
What's that out there?
Michael,
how did it go?
How would one of you feel if I told
you I could put you on a fast track
to an executive position
at this company?
Holy cow.
I'd be so happy.
I wasn't talking to you,
pale face.
I know. I meant
I'd be happy for them.
What I'm offering is a ticket on a bullet
train straight to middle management.
Dwight, I know
these programs.
Every color is important, because
together we make a rainbow.
Yes.
I'll slap you in the
face with a rainbow.
Mmm.
Speaking of rainbows, Oscar, you
are kind of a double minority.
Gay.
So, we at Sabre could really
benefit from your perspective.
Dwight, we know
Kelly applied.
We're not going to cross her, no
matter how good the program is.
I can protect
you from Kelly.
(SCOFFS)
Will you get out
of here? Seriously.
For hobbies, yoga,
belly dancing,
snake-charming, beds of
nails, I like lying...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is Hidetosha Hacigawa.
He would like to apply for the Sabre
Minority Executive Training Program,
Print In All
Colors initiative.
Dwight, what
are you doing?
Helping heal America in a dramatic
fashion in the eleventh hour.
God, I hate you so much.
Caucasians.
Am I right?
Have a seat.
I'll translate.
Why? I don't
need translator...
You don't know
what you need, just...
Why don't you tell me
a little about yourself, Hide.
(SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(SIGHING)
Hey, Michael,
how you doing?
I don't know.
Can't really trust
my feelings anymore.
You know what, Michael? For what
it's worth, I was wrong, too.
I thought she was
interested in you.
She suckered you, too?
Was it the cleavage?
Yeah, and the shoulder cutouts. Yep.
Michael, you know,
it's easy to get fooled.
Bob's warehouse guys flirt with me
all the time. It's mostly harmless.
Usually I don't
let it go too far.
You know, when I tore
my scrote, I was...
I was seeing this really hot urologist
about it and thought she was into me,
but now I think she was just doing
a bunch of stuff to bill my HMO.
You know, she's touching
around down there.
It's easy to
get confused.
Michael, I think
Donna left this here.
Should I put it in the lost and found
for 14 days and then I can take it home?
God.
She left this here? Okay.
Maybe she wants me to return
this to her at her work.
What? No.
No.
KEVIN: No.
Yeah. This could
be a signal.
People don't just
take barrettes off.
It's not a signal.
It's just a coincidence.
No, it's not even
a coincidence.
It's just something
that happened.
Michael.
Well...
She doesn't want you to return the
barrette. She's not interested in you.
I know. I know. I know.
I'm sorry.
I know. You're right. Thank
you. Thanks, everybody.
(CLEARING THROAT)
No.
Michael!
(SIGHING)
Oh, you're still here.
I have your baguette.
Everyone, it is my
pleasure to announce
our newest member of the Sabre
Minority Executive Training Program,
Kelly Rajanigandha Kapoor.
They're going to be pretty
pleased in Tallahassee
that I snagged
an Indian for the program.
She'll be the first.
The program's mostly black.
It's almost too black.
That didn't sound right.
And the best part is, is
that I get a business stipend
to buy all new clothes.
KEVIN: Awesome.
So you can totally buy
any of my old clothes
that I'm not gonna
need anymore.
Oh, my God,
thank you so much.
I love that denim jumpsuit
you have. How much?
Actually, I was thinking about clothes that
I was just going to give to Goodwill anyway.
Great.
Hey, kiddo.
Congratulations are in order.
You deserve it.
Thank you, Dwight.
Oh.
I'll never forget everything
that you've done for me.
Gosh. (LAUGHS)
Because I never
forget anything.
Just once I would like to be a puppet
master and have nothing go wrong.
Is that too much to ask?
You know what? Everybody told me that
you weren't interested. Everybody.
And I didn't believe them.
And they were right.
So, here's your barrette.
No, you were right.
Who?
You were right.
About what?
I'm sorry.
No. No. No.
I'm...
Nope.
What happened?
Kelly got into the
minority training program.
Really? Oh, that's great.
That's such good news. I did it.
I kissed. We kissed.
Oh, Michael...
No, I'm serious.
The... This happened.
I went down to the parking lot and
I was... I returned her barrette.
We...
We did. Okay.
We did. We did.
You know what?
It doesn't matter,
because I know what happened,
and that is all that counts.
I did do it!
www.tvsubtitles.net