I have left Dunder-Mifflin
after many record breaking years.
And I'm officially
on the job market.
And it's very exciting.
For your convenience,
I've broken it down
into three parts:
professional resume,
athletic and special skills resume,
and Dwight Schrute trivia.
I am ready to face
any challenges
that might be
foolish enough to face me.
How would I describe myself?
Three words:
hardworking,
alpha male,
jackhammer.
Merciless.
Insatiable.
There's nothing on my horizon
except everything.
Everything is on my horizon.
I got this job to make some money
while I continue
my employment search.
And- uh-
that's fine for time being.
Ooops. Break's over.
Big turkey.
(Rockin' Robin - Bobby Day)
He rocks in the tree-top all a day long
Hoppin' and a-boppin'
and a-singin' the song
All the little birds on J-Bird St.
Is that you singing?
All four parts.
Recorded it on my computer.
Took me forever.
Nice job.
Thank you muchly.
Oh rockin' robin
Well you really gonna rock tonight
Every little swallow
You gonna answer it?
I called it myself.
Just thought you'd get
a kick out of the new ring.
Yikes.
Side note:
I'd just like to say
I'm thrilled to be working
directly beneath you.
I feel I have a lot to learn from you,
even though you are younger
and have less experience.
So... here's to the future.
Andy and the Tuna.
Andy and the Tuna...
I miss Dwight.
Congratulations, universe.
You win.
Script & Syncronization:
EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
µð¾¾ÀÎ»çÀÌµå ¹Ìµå°¶
The Office 3x14 "The Return"
Original Air Date: Jan 18, 2007 (NBC)
Yes, Dwight Shrute
has left the company.
More personal turnover.
Cost of doin' business.
Yeah, well-
it is a big loss.
Dwight was the top salesman.
Was- the top salesman.
I said, "was".
Addition by subtraction.
What does that even mean?
That is impossible.
Yeah, you're right.
But, there is some good news.
Oscar is back.
Addition by addition.
So, we are going to
have a big party today
to welcome him back and...
And, hopefully
that'll lift everyone's spirit.
Hi, everyone.
Oh, hello Oscar.
How was your gay-cation?
That's very funny.
Yeah, I thought of that
like two seconds after you left.
Hi, Angela?
Oscar.
Hey, boss.
Hey, what's up?
Nooothin'.
TGI Wednesday.
Am I right?
Yeap.
Gonna go home, get my beer on,
get my Lost on.
What're you doing later?
You wanna hang out?
Ah- I don't know. Maybe.
I'll take that as a "Maybe"
Where're you going?
Bathroom
Oh, I'm about to go to kitchen.
I'll walk with you.
Things are going pretty good.
Getting a lot of
face time with the boss.
Oscar.
I have a question.
Would you like to join
the party planning committee?
The committee
with all the women?
Yeah
Because I'm gay.
No- no-
Certain events
have transpired,
and I've thought about
certain things.
And I'm sorry for the way
those certain events transpired.
And I would just like to make
some changes about certain things,
- and certain situations,
- Okay, Okay
- and certain accountants...
- Alright, Alright
I'll join.
I'd love to.
That's... thank you.
Thank you
Can I join too?
Never
You sold those two printers
this morning.
Nice work.
Child's play.
Give me something
hard to sell.
Wow, what is wrong
with this thing?
Looks terrible!
Do you want me to ask
the night cleaning crew
if they stop watering it?
Yeah. Oh- you know what?
Ask them about
the toys on my desk, too.
They always used to
arrange the toys on my desk
in a very pleasing way.
Used to brighten my morning.
Oh, that wasn't the night crew.
That was Dwight.
Really?
It was very nice of him.
We need more attitude like that
around this office.
Feel ya, dawg.
Yeah, do you?
Absolutely.
What did I say?
You said...
Which is like...
"right on!"
Pam is like...
You are like...
Nailed it.
Love that Andy, right?
Solid fellow.
Seems smart enough.
Likes me a lot.
A lot.
Too much.
Like a crazy person, a little.
Not super crazy, just...
There's something about him
that creeps me out.
I can't really explain it.
He's always up in my bid-ness,
which is Ebonics for
"being in my face and annoying
the bejesus out of me."
I don't understand
how someone could have
so little self-awareness.
I really have no preference.
We don't even
have to have a party.
No, hey- hey-
Don't be ridiculous.
Of course
we are going to have a party.
A celebration of Oscar.
Oscar night.
And I want it to be
Oscar-specific?
- Michael, I...
- No, no. I mean, not...
not because you are gay.
Your gayness
does not define you.
Your Mexicanness is
what defines you, to me,
and I think we should celebrate
Oscar's Mexicanity.
So, Phyllis?
I want you to go find
firecrackers and a chihuahua.
Pam, in the frozen food section,
Swanson makes
a delightul chimichanga
Why don't you have me
riding in on a donkey,
into the office, like Pepe?
Ah, a burro, of course.
If Oscar wants a donkey,
let's get him one.
Need any help?
Oh, no thank you.
- I'm just looking.
- Great.
I will literally be standing
right here
if you need anything at all.
Okay
I think I could go for
some tuna fish right about now.
Got my rod here.
Hey
So, Andy is in rare form today?
Yeah, you should not
encourage him.
Encourage him?
I'm the victim, okay?
He's fishing for me.
We gotta do something.
Look, I got like 15 new clients
that I've inherited from Dwight.
And, each file
is password-protected
with a different
mythical creature, so...
Sorry, I can't.
Fine.
Party pooper.
Who's that sportscaster
that bit that lady?
Marv something?
Andy is like Marv something.
Great sportscaster,
Big weirdo creep.
180 pounder. check it out.
- Hey Ryan
- What?
Do you want to
pull a prank on Andy?
Not right now.
But ask me again
ten years ago.
I liked you better as the temp.
Me too.
Hey guys.
How's the workload.
All of Dwight's old accounts.
Handling that okay?
Sorta
He had a lot of clients.
Yes, he did.
Have any of you
talked Dwight?
Oh sure. We talk all the time.
- Really?
- No
Don't- Don't do that.
That's not nice.
What about you Phyllis?
You and Dwight were close?
No.
Sorry.
Dwight had a big personality
and I have a big personality,
and a lot of times,
when two people like that get together,
it can be explosive.
Really comin' down out there.
The commute going to be hell.
I have snow tires and chains.
Plus exceptional
hand-eye coordination.
So- uh- where were you
working before this?
Dunder-Mifflin.
What kinda company is that?
Paper company.
They're only one of
Staples' top competitors in the area.
I never heard of them.
Oh, really.
Have you heard of paper?
It's gonna be like that, huh?
I don't like him,
his giant head,
or his beady little eyes.
That's all I got to say
on the matter.
(Cranberries - Zombie)
In your head!
Zombie! zombie! zombie!
Would you like to pull
a prank on Andy?
I'm kind of in the middle of ...
yes, please.
Okay, good.
Stay right here.
- Sorry about that.
- Yo- tuna.
- Are there any messages?
- No
- So weird.
- Thanks
Nice to have Oscar back.
Yeah
Large Tuna, have you seen
my cell phone device?
No.
'Cause someone is
calling right now.
There is a call.
Angela.
Is everything okay?
No.
What's going on?
What're you talking about?
Where is my freaking phone?
You know what?
Maybe it's in the ceiling.
Maybe you're in the ceiling!
Okay.
I don't trust you, Phyllis.
I just wanted to
tell you that
Dwight was
late that morning
because he had to
drive to New York
to drop off
the quarterly tax forms
that I forgot to send.
Though to be fair,
Kevin never reminded me.
Dwight loves this company.
Do you think that anyone else
out there would've driven to
corporate for you?
None of them.
Especially, not Andy.
Pam.
I have a mission to accomplish.
Make sure this party gets rolling
And I will be back shortly.
Where're you going?
Do you want me to come with you?
Just listen. I forgot to tell you
the plan for this Saturday.
you, me, bar, beers, buzzed.
Wings, shots, drunk.
Waitresses, hot.
Football, Cornell/Hofstra,
slaughter.
Then quick nap at my place,
and we hit the tiz-own.
No. I don't want to do any of that.
Duh. Which is why
I was joking about doing it.
Just stop, stop.
Just stop doing it.
You're going to drive me crazy.
Fine. I will just go
and sit my desk, and be quiet.
Sorry I annoyed you
with my friendship.
Excuse me.
And I'm also sorry
that a lot of people here
for some reason think it's funny
to steal someone's personal property
and hide it from him.
Here's a little newsflash.
It's not funny.
In fact, it's pretty freakin' unfunny.
That was an overreaction.
Gonna hit the break room.
Did anybody want anything?
Pam, you good?
- Yeah
- Sure? Okay.
That question is meaningless.
Just go with the copy paper.
It's your funeral.
See how that works out for you.
Hey
What's up?
Same old
It takes a big man
to admit his mistake.
And I am that big man.
Angela from accounting told me
what you did.
Oh my god. She told you?
Yes, she did.
And, Dwight, if you are willing to
do something like that
With some of the random co-worker,
then, clearly, I've misjudged you
from the beginning.
And, I apologize.
Accepted.
How's this place treating you?
The boss isn't funny.
Oh, well...
I don't get to wear my ties.
No, I'm sure.
So...
So maybe you should come back.
You should come back.
Please.
I don't want to do
your laundry anymore.
We can talk about that.
Oh my god.
That's half-inch drywall.
I think we broke his brain.
It's not freaking funny.
Are you enjoying this fiesta?
Actually, yeah.
I didn't think I would...
... but it turned out great.
Ladies and gentlemen.
May I present Mr. Dwight Shurut!
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Okay, Dwight,
you can let go of her hand.
You're going to break it.
Not bad, huh?
You did this for me?
Guilty
Hey
Do you still have feelings for her?
Yes.
And now, ladies and gentlemen.
The big finale!
Sir, would you do the honor.
Oh, man.
No, no, no, no-
I don't need it.
It takes a big man
to admit his mistake,
and that's what I did.
The important thing is,
I learned something.
I don't want somebody
sucking up to me
because they think
I am going to help their career.
I want them
sucking up to me
because they
genuinely love me.
Script & Syncronization : EasyL (easylong@yahoo.com)
Date: Feb. 11, 2007
drama forum in South Korea : http://kr.dcinside13.imagesearch.yahoo.com/zb40/zboard.php?id=f_drama
www.tvsubtitles.net