W.B. Jones is renovating their offices
and their cruise are taking up some of
the parking spaces we used to get.
So we had to park
at a satellite parking lot over there.
Which just means we get to see more
of our lovely street.
Tell them what we saw today, Jim.
Oh, today we saw a junkyard dog
attacking the bones
of a rotisserie chicken.
Nature.
I've been here 9 years, and suddenly
I'm supposed to park half a mile away.
I lost a penny out of my loafers, Oscar.
I will quit.
As God is my witness, I will quit...
if this is not fixed.
Some of us like the walk
more than others.
It hurts like hell.
Transcript: SwSub
Sync: DarKsh
Episode 4x10
"CHAIR MODEL" (1.00)
Did you pick a new chair?
It's been a while.
Pam,
when I first opened this catalog,
I thought I was just going
to be picking out a chair.
But instead you found something to
distract you from picking out a chair.
Michael started the process of selecting
a new chair about three weeks ago.
And normally I wouldn't care
but he promised me his old one.
It's way better.
It's one of these:
I really want it.
- Have you ever seen this woman?
- Her?
The one in the really great mesh,
black, hi-back swivel chair?
Look at her smile.
It's the eyes. Look at her eyes.
She's got...
I don't know what it is exactly.
She dresses like a professional,
and yet you know
there is a side of her
that could just curl up on a couch.
Or in a great chair.
Yeah, maybe, but...
Remember after my dinner party when
I said that I was swearing off women?
I definitely remember your dinner party.
I think what I meant was that I am
completely swearing off one woman:
Jan.
I think that fate
put this catalog in my hands.
Actually, I put the catalog in your hand
'cause you have to pick out a new chair.
What is it like being single?
I... like it.
I like...
starting each day
with a sense of possibility.
And I'm optimistic,
because every day
I get a little more desperate
and desperate situations
yield the quickest results.
Ladies and gentlemen, would you please
open your supply catalogs
and kindly turn to page 85?
- Yo, is this his new chair?
- No, he hasn't picked one yet.
When Pam gets Michael's old chair,
I get Pam's old chair.
Then I'll have two chairs.
Only one to go.
I am ready to start dating again.
Getting back on the market.
So...
FYI, for those of you
who're thinking about fixing me up,
with any of your friends,
use the woman on page 85
as a template.
That will be all.
I left my cell phone in my car.
Call us when you get there
so we know you're okay.
Listen, man...
I am completely over Jan.
So...
would you set me up?
If I had somebody
to set you up with, Michael,
then I'd take her for myself.
- I thought you were engaged.
- Nope.
Stacy broke up with me.
What?
God, that's terrible, man.
She's crazy.
Um, are you still on good terms
with any of her friends?
Not anymore.
It's a bitter situation.
Yeah...
She's...
You don't deserve her.
All right.
Hello, Oscar Meyer weiner lover.
I bet that you have
a bunch of very liberal
girl-type friends
who trust you implicitly
because they know you'd never touch 'em
'cause of your condition.
- Michael?
- What?
I have a friend who's single.
Sandy.
She's gorgeous
and she's got a feisty personality too.
Feisty...
So she's not jolly or sassy?
Not like a jolly, sassy opera singer?
No,
she's a professional softball player.
- Catcher or in field?
- I don't know, Michael.
Is she a dress-wearer
or a pants-wearer?
Could we share a rowboat?
Could a rowboat support her?
What are you asking?
I think I'm being very clear
what I'm asking.
Would an average-sized rowboat
support her without capsizing?
It bothers me that you're
not answering the question.
No, all right?
She can't fit in a rowboat.
Damn it! I knew it!
I knew it, Phyllis!
What is wrong with these people?
I would do anything for them,
and they're just
hanging me out to dry.
Dating shouldn't be hard
for somebody like me
but it is, and you know why?
Because nobody here
is willing to help me.
Nothing would ever get done
in this office without
a formal request, would it?
Well fine, here goes.
- I don't think that...
- Now okay,
I know that this
is probably not appropriate.
But I need help.
Because I want to play ball
with my kids
before I get too old.
And before that happens,
I need to get laid.
I need to be in love.
And I don't wanna hear,
"I don't know, I can't help, na na na."
No, no, I am a catch,
and I am not going
to be the one who got away.
So this is what we're going to do.
Dwight is going to hand out index cards,
and I want you all
to write down the name
of an eligible woman for me to date
by the end of the day.
No, by the end of the hour,
or you are fired.
Write legibly, people.
Because of the construction
at W.B. Jones,
half of us have to park
in the satellite lot.
- It's, like, a 10 minute walk.
- No, 30.
Look, I have an assigned
parking place in front, so...
All right, all right.
Let me try to think about
what it would be like to not have one.
Okay, yes, that would be bad.
- That would be bad.
- Okay, so...
- help us out.
- Wish I could, but I can't.
Well can, but won't.
Should, maybe, but...
shorn't.
Michael, please...
What part of shorn't
don't you understand, Kevin?
Look, I could
probably handle it, yes, but...
I think it would be a good exercise
for you to do it yourselves.
- We won't let you down.
- You can't because I don't care.
Don't forget
to fill out those cards.
My love cards.
There's nobody I hate enough
to write her name on this card.
Well, I'm setting Michael up
with my fat friend anyway.
He can just deal with it.
- Who are you putting down?
- Oh, you don't know her.
- Who is it?
- Your mom.
Yeah, whatever.
Give that to me!
Give that to...
Okay, "Wendy"...
Hot and juicy redhead.
Let's give this a try.
Wendy's.
Hello, Wendy.
This is Kevin's friend Michael.
This isn't Wendy.
Sorry.
Could you put her on, please?
Dude, this is a Wendy's restaurant.
Damnit, Kevin.
Okay...
Could I just have a frosty
and a baked potato, please?
You've to come here to order food.
I'll send somebody to pick it up,
just have it ready.
It's ready now.
Well, put it aside.
- I've collected the rest of the ladies.
- Good, good.
Because this batch was awful.
- This one says "chair model."
- I wrote that.
Michael,
you shouldn't have to settle.
This is my pledge to you.
I will find her,
and I will bring her to you.
And as God is my witness,
she shall bear your fruit.
That sounds good.
Go get her.
Wait!
First go to Wendy's, get my food,
come back, and then go.
That is fantastic.
Thank you, thank you very much.
This is just what I needed.
The furniture company gave me
the name of the advertising agency.
They gave me the name
of the photographer.
The photographer, a spaniard,
used a Wilkes-Barre modeling agency.
The agency gave me
the following information:
Debrah Shoshlefski,
142 South Windsor Lane.
Dead, car accident.
Case closed.
She's dead?
She's so young.
She was so young
and now, she's dead.
As dead as every dead animal
who has ever died.
God.
Why don't you sit down, Michael?
Come on.
There we go.
Michael, you didn't even know her.
Try not to be so hurtful, Jim.
- Jim, how dare you?
- Not at time like this.
Okay, Michael, you know what?
I might have someone for you.
Oh, really? What's her name?
Burgerking?
No, I mean it.
She's really nice and sweet and...
you guys might actually get along.
I don't think I'm ready...
Is she hot?
I'm setting Michael up
with my landlady.
She's really sweet and...
Whatever, I just can't
take Michael like this.
No question about it,
I am ready to get hurt again.
We need to assemble
the five families.
- No, not the five families.
- We have to!
The five families are the five companies
of Scranton business park.
The bosses rarely meet.
There's Michael Scott,
regional manager, Dunder Mifflin.
Bob Vance, Vance Refrigeration.
Paul Faust
of Disaster Kits Limited.
They call him "Cool Guy Paul".
W.B. Jones
of W.B. Jones heating and air.
Grade a badass.
And Bill Cress
of Cress Tool and Die.
Bill Cress is super old
and really mean.
Kevin, I don't have
time for this right now.
I'm trying to get a date
with Pam's hot friend.
And she needs to meet me right now.
I'm calling the meeting anyway.
Thank you very much.
Our suspect
has straight brown hair.
She is wearing blue jeans
and a black top.
So...
behold our bachelorette.
Give her a 10 for her looks and
a 3 for her ability to describe herself.
Hello, my lady.
Are you Michael Scott?
Is who a Michael what?
I'm sorry. I'm supposed to be meeting
someone named Michael.
That's not...
Yeah, I'm not...
Michael?
Large hot chocolate with caramel
and a shot of peppermint.
So you...
get the rent checks
every month and...
What happens next?
What...
You're asking me what I...
do with the checks
that people write to me?
Just making conversation.
Why is it so hard to meet people?
I... You know, it's...
All I want
is somebody nice,
and sweet,
and someone I can talk to
and share an experience with,
you know?
Why is it so hard
for people like us?
I don't know.
You wanna see what I walked out on?
This is going to blow your mind.
Look at that!
- She's beautiful.
- Yeah.
And you can't see her whole body,
down here, she has a boob job.
Just...
She was just crazy smart
and really manipulative and...
I don't know.
Michael?
Hello...
Well, I'm gonna head out.
Well...
I enjoyed this conversation.
It was very nice.
It was like talking to...
the sweet, old lady on the bus.
That's incredibly rude.
Now you ruined it.
Where's Scott?
Michael Scott could not make it today
due to an unforeseen prior engagement.
- Let's just meet back in an hour.
- Gentlemen, please.
We called this meeting.
Andrew Bernard...
is the name of me, and this is
my associate, Mr. Kevin Malone.
I have things.
All right, what do you want?
Well, first of all, I'd just like to say
what an honor it is to be sitting here
- with you...
- You've 10 seconds.
We want our parking spaces back.
- Whose parking spaces?
- W.B. Jones's construction guys
park in our parking spaces
every morning,
and some people
have to park really far away
and walk all the way to the office.
And some people...
sweat too much for comfort and...
My God.
I don't have time for this, guys.
Just give 'em back their spaces.
- Okay.
- We good? Okay.
Could've done this over email.
After Stacy left, things...
did not go well for a while.
And it was hard to see...
It's just nice to win one.
Margaret the landlady? Really, Pam?
Is that what you think of me?
She's sweet and... cute.
I thought you would get along.
Oh, okay. Well,
I'm looking for a passionate affair,
not companionship.
I'm a man of intensity.
Of... of cool, and youth,
and...
and passionately.
God...
- Margaret?
- I know...
You just got yourself
kicked out of your apartment.
Oh, I don't care. I don't really like
that place that much anyway.
- I'll just move.
- Oh, really?
Who's gonna take you in?
You're messy.
You're a klutz,
you spill everything.
And you leave the volume on the TV
way too loud.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll move in with my boyfriend
'cause he's kind of a slob too.
Okay. Sure.
Let's do it.
No, I...
Well, I'm not gonna... I'm...
I'm not gonna move in
with anyone unless I'm engaged.
Have I not proposed you yet?
I don't... No.
Well, that's comin'.
Oh, right now?
No. I'm not gonna do it right here.
That would be rather lame.
Okay, so then when?
I'm not gonna tell you. I hate to break
it to you, but that's not how it works.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Wait, I'm serious.
- It's happening.
- Okay.
And when it happens,
it's going to kick your ass, Beesly.
So...
Stay sharp.
I've been warned.
I am not kidding.
Got it a week after we started dating.
I don't know, man.
I was with Jan for so long...
I was excited
about meeting somebody new.
Put my heart out there.
You know what you need?
Closure.
You're right.
What do you mean though?
There was a woman in your life
who affected you very deeply,
and she left
before you could say good-bye.
I think you need to say good-bye.
Come on.
I'll drive.
- We did it!
- I did it.
We got our spaces back.
Nice job.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
There it is.
You're welcome.
Did I do this for me?
No.
I did this for the little guy.
For Joe six-pack,
the guy who wakes up every morning
in his $400 a month appartment,
wonders how he's gonna pay
his mortgage this month.
Wonders how he's gonna fill
his car up with oil.
Wonders how am I going to pay
my kids' orphanage bills?
That guy...
shouldn't have to wonder
where he's gonna park.
How did she die?
I guess you could say
she died of...
blunt force trauma and blood loss.
She got in a car accident and ploughed
into the sight of an airplane hangar.
- God...
- Yeah.
She was so innocent.
She was stoned apparently.
You know, I used to think that...
I had this perfect person
out there waiting for me.
But now I know that that's just silly.
Because she's dead.
What do you do?
You wait till next year's
chair catalogue comes out
and find someone who's still alive.
- You move on.
- Yeah.
Where do you wanna go for dinner?
I don't know. I kinda hate
all our regular places right now.
You know what?
That one...
Hey, Pam.
Will you wait for me one second
while I tie my shoe?
- I hate you.
- What?
My shoe is untied.
What is your problem?
Oh, my god!
You thought I...
- No, no, no.
- How could I have thought that?
Bye, bye, miss chairmodel lady
I dreamt that we were married
and you treated me nice
We had lots of kids
Drinking whiskey and rye
Why d'you have to go off and die?
You believe in rock'n roll?
Can music save your mortal soul?
And then, can you have to dance
real slow?
Well, I know
that you're in love with him
'Cause I saw you dancin' in the gym
- Kicked off both her shoes
- Turned off her shoes
- No more rhythm and blues!
- No verdict was returned!
Rhythm and blues.
This will be the day that I die
www.tvsubtitles.net