- Hey.
- Hello.
- Jim !
- What's up buddy ?
This is not funny.
Why is my stuff in here ?
Wow, that's weird.
Ooh, dollar for a stapler,
that's pretty good.
Yeah, well, I'm not paying
for my own stuff, okay ?
I know you did this 'cause you're
friends with the vending machine guy.
- Who, Steve ?
- Yeah, Steve.
What do I want ?
It's a pencil cup.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's my pencil cup.
Um, I don't think so,
I just bought it.
Uh, I think so, and you're
going to hand it over to me.
I love these.
Okay, fine.
My wallet ?
Um, oh, there it is. J1.
I don't have any...
Here you know what,
you can have some nickels.
5, 10.
15, 20, 25...
Saison 2 - Episode 11
Booze Cruise
Transcripts : Nikki (twiztv.com)
Synchronisation : El Uploador
Hello everyone.
Morning Michael.
Where are we going
this afternoon ?
Last week, Michael sent out
this mysterious memo.
"It's time for our first quarter
camaraderie event."
"So pack a swimsuit, a toothbrush."
"Rubber-soled shoes..."
"...and a ski mask."
A ski mask and a swimsuit ?
So that he can have us rob a bank,
and then escape through the sewers.
And brush our teeth.
Yeah ?
- Michael...
- Stanley...bo banley.
- I need to know-
-  Banana fana fo fanley.
- What we're doing.
- Me mi mo manley.
- You said bring a toothbrush.
- Stanley.
Is this an overnight ?
Maybe. The suspense is just
so exciting, isn't it ?
Should my wife tell her boss
she's not coming in tomorrow ?
- Maybe, I don't know.
- Not maybe, yes or no.
Well, no, but...
okay, don't spoil it for everybody.
All right ? But, we...
are going on a booze cruise
on Lake Wallenpaupack.
In January ?
It's cheaper.
This is not just another party.
This is a leadership
training exercise.
Right ?
I'm going to combine
elements of fun
and motivation and education
into a single,
mind-blowing experience.
It is now time to unveil the
destination of this year's retreat.
We are going on a harbor cruise
of Lake Wallenpaupack.
- It's a booze cruise !
- All right !
I have a test for business school
tomorrow night.
Is it okay if I skip the cruise
and study for that ?
No, this is mandatory.
But don't worry, you know what ?
You're going to learn plenty.
This is going to turn your
life around, Ryan.
I'm already in business school.
- Wait, Michael.
- Yeah?
Why did you tell us to bring
a bathing suit ?
To throw you off the scent.
Yeah, but I bought a bathing suit.
Well, just keep the tags on
and you can return it.
I took the tags off already.
Well, that's not my fault, okay ?
Just-we're not going to pay
for a bathing suit.
Okay. I know what
you're all thinking.
Who is this smart little cookie ?
Her name is Brenda...
...something,
and she is from corporate.
And she is here, like you,
to learn from what I have to say.
I am a great motivational speaker.
I attended a Tony Robbins
event by the airport last year,
and...
It wasn't the actual course.
You have to pay for the actual course.
But, it talked about
the actual course.
And I've incorporated a lot
of his ideas into my own course.
Leader...ship.
The word ship is hidden inside
the word leadership.
As its derivation.
So, if this office is
in fact a ship,
as it's leader...
I am the captain.
But...We're all in the same boat.
Teamwork.
Last  year, Michael's theme was
"bowl over the competition."
So, guess where we went ?
Now, on this ship
that is the office,
what is the sales department ?
Anyone ?
How about, the sales department
is the sails ?
Yes, Darryl, the sales department
makes sales. Good.
Let me just explain. I see the sales
department as the furnace.
- A furnace ?
- Yeesh, how old is this ship ?
How about the anchor ?
What does the furnace do ?
All right, let's not get hung up
on the furnace.
This just...
It's the sales. I see the sales
department are down there,
they're in the engine room and they
are shoveling coal into the furnace,
right ?
I mean who saw
the movie "Titanic" ?
They were very important
in the movie "Titanic".
Who saw it ?
Show of hands ?
Not really sure what movie
you're talking about.
- You sure you got the title right ?
-  "Titanic" ?
I think you're thinking of
"The Hunt for Red October".
No, I'm...
Leo DiCaprio, come on !
Michael stands in the front
of the boat
and says he's king of the world
within the first hour,
or I give you my next paycheck.
Michael,  everyone in the
engine room drowned.
No, thank you, spoiler alert.
You saw the movie,
those of you who did.
They're happy down there
in the furnace room.
And they're dirty and
grimy and sweaty.
And they're singing
their ethnic songs. And...
Actually, that might be warehouse.
- What ?
- The, no, no.
No I didn't...
okay, well, the...
Okay, in a nutshell what
I'm saying is leadership.
We'll get, we'll talk more
about that on the boat. Ship.
Aye, aye, Captain.
A three hour tour.
Pam, you are Mary Ann.
We have...
The Professor and Ginger.
Welcome aboard.
Angela, you are Mrs. Howell. Lovey.
Uh, the native.
Sometimes they come
from neighboring...
Oh, uh, we have, uh...
one of the Globetrotters.
I am the Skipper,
and Dwight, you will be Gilligan.
- Cool.
- Actually, I'm the Skipper.
- But you can be Gilligan.
- Oh, I'd rather die.
Hi, I am Michael Scott.
I am the Captain of this party.
I'm Captain Jack.
I'm Captain of the ship.
I'm also captain of anyone
who sets foot on this ship.
Hi, welcome aboard.
Okay.
In an office, when you are
ranking people,
manager is higher than captain.
Oh a boat, who knows ?
It's nebul-ose.
Hey look.
I'm king of the world !
Okay, all right.
Welcome aboard.
I am your captain, Captain Jack.
And I am Regional Manager of
Dunder Mifflin, Michael Scott.
Welcome, welcome.
- Okay, so, um...
- Okay, so.
Please. The, uh, life preservers.
They are located underneath the seats
all along the perimeter of the boat.
But don't worry,
you are not going to be needing
life preservers tonight.
Well, we might just be, okay ?
Please let me finish, okay ?
Thank you.
So, the Coast Guard requires that
I tell you where the safety exits are.
Now, on this ship, it's very easy.
Anywhere over the sides.
Not only am I your ship's captain,
I am also your party captain !
Woo, we're going to get it
going here in just a few minutes...
And I'm your party captain too !
And you are going to put on
your dancing shoes later on.
- Hey, Mike, Mike.
- So we are gonna...
- Uh, if you don't mind.
- Rock it !
- What ?
- Please, okay ?
If the boat's a-rocking,
don't come knocking.
- Michael.
- Yup.
Uh, your company employees
are not the only people
on the boat tonight, okay ?
We're all going to have
a good time tonight.
Why don't you let me and
my crew do our job ?
You just sit back and
have a good time ?
- Okay, yup.
- All right ?
You guys, it's like we're in high
school and we're at the cool table.
- Right ?
- Yeah.
Pam, were you a cheerleader ?
No, she was total little Miss
Artsy Fartsy in high school.
She wore the turtleneck
and everything.
That's hilarious.
It's not hilarious, but...
- Where'd you go to school ?
- Bishop O'Hara.
Piss slop who cares-a ?
We played you.
You, you really look familiar.
Did you, uh, you cheered
for them, didn't you ?
Mmm, no.
Yes, I did.
A-W-E... S-O-M-E,
awesome, awesome is what we are
we're the football superstars.
-  A-W-E
- I remember that !
- S-O-M-E
- We crushed you like 42 to 10.
-  Having fun ?
- Yeah.
Everybody's really nice.
Good, well, that is what
Scranton is all about.
Not like you "New Yawkers."
When are you going to
start the, uh, presentation ?
Well, I already sort of started it
back at the office.
And on the dock
with the Gilligan thing.
So, right now, I was thinking.
Yes. Okay !
Listen up, all you,
Dunder Mifflinites.
I would like to talk to you
all about life preservers.
Now,  one important life preserver
in business is IT Support.
Not now, Mike, we're
doing the limbo !
Ha, ha, that's right, partiers.
It's time to limbo, limbo, limbo !
- So, okay.
- All right !
I need a volunteer to come up here
and hold my stick.
- Huh, who's it going to be ?
-  Me.
- Okay.
- Me, me, me.
Me, me, me.
Usually it's a woman.
- I'm stronger.
- Hey, I got an idea.
How would you like to steer
the ship, Dwight ?
Keep us on a steady course.
Keep a sharp eye out,
I'm counting on you.
I was the youngest pilot
in Pan Am history.
When I was four,
the pilot let me ride
in the cockpit,
and fly the plane with him.
And I was four and I was great !
And I would have landed it,
but my dad wanted us
to go back to our seats.
All right, all right.
That was great,
now it's time for
the dance contest !
Why don't we do that after
I do my presentation and...
Nope ! Dance contest !
All right, we'll have a motivational
dance contest. Hit it !
Yeah, okay. Dancing.
It is a primal art form used
in ancient times
to express yourself with the body.
And communicate.
Sometimes you have
to take a break
from being the kind of boss
that's always trying
to teach people things.
Sometimes you just have to
be the boss of dancing.
What do you do with
a drunken sailor
Ear-ly in the morn-ing
Hey, come inside and talk to me.
I can't. Do you want us
to run aground woman ?
Snorkel shot, snorkel shot !
Snorkel shot !
Who's next ?
Come on, Pammy, come on, come on !
- I'm not doing that.
- Come on !
Tequila !
That's what I'm talking about.
Hey, why don't we find like,
a quieter place to hang out ?
You know what, I've just gotta
wait for Darryl to do his shot.
Just a minute.
Come on, Darryl, Darryl !
It's getting kind of rowdy
down there.
Yeah.
"Darryl, Darryl, Darryl."
Sometimes, I just don't get Roy.
Well.
I mean, I don't know.
So.
What's it like dating
a cheerleader ?
I'm cold.
So, what's this presentation
all about ?
Ah, see, this is of
general interest.
It is about...priorities.
And making decisions,
using the boat as an analogy.
What is important to you ?
If the boat is sinking,
what do you save ?
- Women and children.
- No, no.
Salesmen and profit centers.
That's a stupid analogy.
O-kay, well obviously you don't
know anything about leadership.
Well, I was the captain of a
PC-1 Cyclone Coastal Patrol Boat
during Desert Storm.
Wow, you should be the
motivational speaker.
Him ?
O-kay.
Yeah, he gives me real
responsibility, Michael.
Captain Jack delegates.
He's let me steer the ship
for the last hour.
I'd like to be engaged.
How did you manage
to pull that off ?
Uh, I've been engaged for
three years,
and there's no end in sight.
So, you don't want to ask
my advice.
Suppose your office
building's on fire.
Jim, who would you save ?
Let's see...
the customer.
Cause the customer is king.
Not what I was looking for,
but a good thought.
He's just sucking up.
When you were in the Navy,
did you, um, ever almost die ?
Oh yeah, oh yeah. And I wasn't
thinking about some customer.
I was thinking about my first wife.
The day I got back on
shore, I married her.
You know what,
I would save the receptionist.
I just wanted to clear that up.
Hey, everybody, uh, could I have
your attention for just a second ?
Would you listen to me
for a second ?
We were up at the front
and we were talking about
what's really important and...
Pam, um,
I think enough is enough.
I think we should set a date
for our wedding.
How about June 10th ?
Come on, let's do it.
Come on baby !
Oh, my God, congratulations !
Congratulations.
Yes !
Oh, my God !
I love you baby, come on !
Congratulations !
Come on, I don't want
to take credit for this,
but Roy and I were just having
a conversation about
making commitments and making
choices, right ?
Did I motivate you ?
No, it was, it was Captain Jack.
- Well....
- Captain Jack !
Could have been either one of us
because, pretty much, we were
saying the same thing.
Congratulations, that is great.
We gotta celebrate !
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
I got an idea, I got an idea.
I can marry you right now
as captain of the ship, huh ?
I can marry you as Regional
Manager of Dunder Mifflin !
No, no, no, no, I want my mom
and dad to be there.
Then, I'll give you away !
No, thank you.
Do you think that'll ever be us ?
No.
What is wrong with you ?
Why did you even bring me
here tonight ?
I don't know.
Let's break up.
Wh-what ! ?
This is where old Captain Jack
drives the boat.
Seasick ?
Captain Jack says you
should look at the moon.
Captain Jack's a fart face.
I'm on medication.
Really ? What ?
Vomicillin.
Okay, all right,
it's time to be boss.
Time to motivate,
let's blow some minds here.
Okay guys, guys, guys, cool it.
Everybody. Dunder Mifflin
and Scranton employees.
Brenda. I have some very, very,
urgent news I need to tell everybody.
Right now, listen up.
The ship, is sinking.
Okay ?
We're going down, right now.
Just wrap your heads
around the reality of that.
Shh, please, everybody, it's my
turn now, okay ?
Captain Jack is gone.
In five minutes, this ship is going
to be at the bottom of the lake.
And there aren't enough
spaces on the lifeboats.
Who are we going to save ?
Do we save sales ?
Do we save customer service ?
Do we save accounting ?
This is a business scenario, right ?
It's a scary...
- What the hell's going on here ?
- It's a predicament.
And it's something that each and
everyone of us have to think about.
I'm in the brig, see ?
Boat's not as corporate
friendly as advertised.
What is the deal with the guy
jumping overboard ?
What was...
If he had just waited and
heard what I had to say,
he would be motivated right now
and not all wet.
Somebody there ?
What happened to you ?
Captain Jack has a problem
with authority.
Oh, right, 'cause you announced
that his ship was sinking ?
Yeah, he just totally lost it.
If you ask me, he caused the panic.
What a night.
Well, it's nice for you.
Your friend got engaged.
She was always engaged.
Roy  said the first one
didn't count.
That's...great.
You know, to tell you
the truth, I...
used to have a big
thing for Pam.
So...
Really ?
You're kidding me.
You and Pam ?
I would have never...
put you two together.
You really hid it well, God !
I usually have a radar
for stuff like that.
You know, I made out with Jan.
- Yeah, I know.
- Yeah ? Yep.
Well, Pam is cute.
Yeah.
She's really funny and...
She's warm and she's just...
Anyway.
Well, if you like her so much, uh,
don't give up.
She's engaged.
B.F.D. Engaged ain't married.
Never, ever, ever give up.
Don't worry, Michael.
I'm taking us to shore.
It's a fake wheel, dummy.
www.tvsubtitles.net