(PHONE RINGING)
OPERATOR: Vancouver Court
Hotel, how may I help you?
Hello, Vancouver,
this is Michael Scott
calling from
the United States of America.
I have a reservation
in your fair city
from February 12th
to the 19th.
First week of the Olympics.
Well, we're looking forward
to having you,
so let me just pull up
your information here.
Oki-doke.
Uh, I don't seem
to have it, sir.
What?
I'm not seeing anything
under confirmation...
No. No. Could it be under "affirmation?"
'Cause you have
thousands of those.
We're just trying to
look it up right now.
You did get the
e-vite to my barbeque.
Come on, Dwight.
Michael.
OPERATOR: Sir, a lot of people are
trying to get last-minute reservations
at hotels here
for the Olympics,
but we've been
fully booked for months.
Well, I have been booked for three
years, so you should have that.
I have always heard that British
Columbia is a very nice place,
but I'm not getting that
from this conversation.
Wait, I got it! Confirmation
code, X-V-2-R-D-M.
Oh.
Here it is. Yeah.
OPERATOR: Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Seven nights in our
street-view economy single.
That's it.
Yeah.
We changed systems a
while back. I do apologize.
Okay.
(STAMMERS) How may I
help you, Mr. Scott?
All right. I would like to
cancel my reservation, please.
There is a cancellation fee
for this, sir.
Okay, put it on my card.
MICHAEL: Today, Jo Bennett,
the CEO from Sabre
is coming to see us
here for the first time.
She bought us sight unseen,
like a mail-order bride,
(CHUCKLES) so she's gotta be kind
of nervous. I mean, are we ugly?
Are we smart? Are we cool?
Are we too cool? (BARKING)
Do we speak English?
(JO LAUGHING)
Why, hello!
GABE: This is
Michael Scott,
co-regional manager
of this branch.
Pleasure to meet you,
Miss Bennett.
Uh, that's Mrs. Bennett,
sweetheart.
My husband and I are divorced
but I kept the "missus"
just to piss off the new wife. Oh.
(ALL LAUGHING) Well, let's
take a gander around this place.
These sure are
pretty dogs.
JO: (CHUCKLING)
They love a good crotch.
They sure do.
You should take that
as a compliment.
Oh, I do.
JO: Hello.
Hello.
Do you always stay seated
when a lady enters the room?
I am treating you
the same as a man,
for whom I would
also not stand.
Unless it was the
president, or Judge Judy.
I like that.
GABE: This is Accounting.
JO: Uh-huh.
Hi.
Good-looking group.
Over here is Meredith
Palmer, Creed Bratton.
JO: Another couple
of heartbreakers.
Who's this tall
drink of sun tea?
That is Jim Halpert. He is the
co-regional manager of this office.
I thought this guy
was the manager.
Oh, he is. He's the co-manager.
That's the other co-manager.
Two guys doing one job?
We gotta do something
about that. (CHUCKLING)
I've got some
Valentine's cards
for my co-workers
and my bro-workers.
No. No.
What? No candy?
ANDY: Valentine's Day.
Right around the corner.
Erin and I have been
on zero dates.
So I got her a
Valentine's Day card,
but I didn't want
to seem too eager,
so I got cards for
everyone in the whole office
to kind of dilute
it a little bit.
Look alive.
(EXCLAIMS)
Jeez, you gave me
a paper cut on my throat.
Yeah, I have this thing
about men cutting
or threatening
to cut my throat.
Don't try to
cut my throat.
Jo, I don't know how things work in
Florida, which from your description
sounds like a colorful,
lawless swamp,
but here it takes
two men to do one job,
where in Florida,
it might take
one very strong
woman to do such a job.
Whoa. Whoa.
I'll take over. Um,
what we're doing here,
Michael handles more of
the big picture stuff,
and I handle more of
the day-to-day stuff.
Yeah.
JIM: So, together...
I think I understand.
All right.
Each of you is
doing half a job.
No. (CHUCKLES) And sometimes
I can hardly handle that.
(JO CHUCKLING)
Now this is knucklehead talk. I'm
not going to abide it, you know.
You can't give me gravy and tell me
it's jelly, 'cause gravy ain't sweet.
Is it, Jim? (SOFTLY) I don't think so.
Michael?
Forget the question.
I think one of you
should return to Sales,
and the other one
will be a manager.
I humbly accept
the management position.
Why would you just
automatically get it?
Because, well, Jim, where I'm
from, there are two types of folk,
those who ain't and those who
are knee-high on a grasshopper.
Which type ain't you ain't?
Y'all come back now.
Do you even know what that means? Yes.
Well, I'm gonna let this
marinate. So you can go.
Um...
You can go on.
Yeah.
(SHOOING)
I'm Jolene Bennett, Jo for short.
I'm a breast cancer survivor,
close personal friends
with Nancy Pelosi,
and Truman Capote and I slept
with three of the same guys.
When I was a little girl,
I was terrified to fly,
and now I have my
own pilot's license.
I am CEO of
Sabre International
and I sell the best damn printers and
all-in-one machines Korea can make.
Pleased to meet you.
(EXCLAIMS) Traffic jam.
Uh-oh. Traffic jam
on route three.
(BOTH IMITATING
HORN HONKING)
Twenty people
dead in a pileup.
There's blood everywhere.
Um, I got you
a Valentine's card.
You did?
Yeah.
(EXCLAIMS) A bird and a dog!
Yeah, well, it's Snoopy and Woodstock.
You named them?
Uh, Charles Schulz did.
I thought it was relevant
'cause I got you all those
birds for Christmas, remember?
Yeah, I do remember.
Oh, they love each other.
Oh, look at that. They
sure do. I hadn't noticed.
Oh, it smells
really good, too.
Yeah, it's
Roger Federer for Men.
I sprayed
some in there.
Andy, whoa!
Thank you very much.
It's got pheromones
in it. (CHUCKLES)
JO: Hey.
KEVIN: Hi.
Just choosing seats, not getting
married. Chop, chop, little onion.
Jo, there's books
in my chair.
That's right, darling.
Now you're the proud new
owner of a Sabre handbook,
and my autobiography.
Now, you all must be in a tizzy.
I can see it on your faces.
I mean, what's going on now? I
mean, who owns Dunder Mifflin?
Right? I mean, Sabre?
What's that?
Some company we never heard
of from down in Tallahassee?
I mean, where is that?
Near Mars?
No, we know. Texas.
Now, Dunder Mifflin
has an arm's reach
into all these small businesses
all over the northeast,
and now we're gonna
take that arm
and we're going to
start selling printers.
I could manage my
way around that.
They're the easiest-to-use
printers in the market.
I will try to
manage my excitement.
I have been saying
the word "manager" a lot,
so whenever Jo thinks
manager, she thinks of me.
Camel cigarettes did the
same thing with Joe Camel
by making him
look like a penis.
I can't even go
near a cigarette now
without thinking of
a penis, and vice versa.
I think that's it.
So we're all good.
Okay.
Thanks, y'all.
Oh, my God.
I guess Andy likes me. I never
thought of him in that way.
But I guess in most
romantic comedies,
the guy you're supposed
to be with is the one
that you never
thought of in that way.
You might have even thought he was
annoying or possibly homosexual.
So check this out.
According to the handbook,
you could make more money
as a salesman
than as a manager.
They have all these
incentive programs.
I ran your numbers
from last year.
This is way more
than I make now.
I don't think I'm gonna
miss being manager.
You know how some people say
they're not in it for the money?
Well, with all due
respect to this job,
I think I'm definitely
in it for the money.
And, quite honestly,
the women.
Hey. Got a second?
Sure.
All right.
You here to tell me that you
think I would be a better manager,
and that you are sorry
for being such a jerk?
Actually, yeah.
What?
Exactly that.
I think that you absolutely deserve
the manager position more than I do.
What? Really?
Yeah.
(LAUGHING) Wow! Wow!
(VOCALIZING)
Hello, Oscar.
Michael, reading.
What are you reading?
The Atlantic.
Oh, that is my favorite
ocean. I love it.
I'm so happy right now. No, I
can't keep it a secret any longer.
Jim's stepping
down to salesman.
I am going to be the
sole manager once again.
(SIGHS) I should step
into Sales myself.
Why? Is there an
untapped gay market?
Sabre has no caps
on commissions.
He can make a lot
more money in Sales.
(SIGHING)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Where did you get
that information?
Manual.
Manuel who?
Mmm-hmm. Well, according to the manual,
there is no cap
on commissions.
I have been hustled.
(SOFTLY) Son of a bitch.
JIM: This is...
Pardon me.
Speak of the devil. We
were just talking about you.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Now, Jim here is thinking
about taking himself
out of the running
for being manager. Yep.
Oh, really? (EXCLAIMS)
That is so sweet of you!
But I cannot accept, because
I have been thinking about it,
and I think I want
to go back to Sales.
Really?
JIM: Really?
Yeah, you can take the man
out of the salesman,
but you can't take
the sales out of salesman.
Well, I think you're both
being a little too modest.
No, I really, really think
Michael is better at being manager
for so many reasons.
Mmm-mmm.
No. I think I would be bad.
I would sleep in my office...
JO: Okay. ...and I would
sexually harass people.
Why would you do that? I'm
turning myself in right now.
You know, Michael, you have more
experience in sales and management,
so I'm going to defer
to your judgment.
Thank you.
I think you will
become the salesman,
and congratulations,
you're gonna be the new
manager of this branch.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Have fun signing my
commission checks, boss.
(EXCLAIMS)
Michael marked his heights.
He's grown.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Bobcat, this is Dragon. Listen,
he's been promoted to sole manager.
We have got to step this up. Meet
me behind the dumpster in 90 seconds.
Eighty-nine, 88...
You're 20 minutes late.
Um, I was
at another dumpster.
Just admit you lost
track of time. (SIGHS)
DWIGHT: Ryan and I have been meeting up
to work on our diabolical plot against Jim.
Ryan is always late
for our meetings.
I wish I had a lair.
Did you see Saw?
Of course I seesaw. Mose
and I seesaw all the time.
No, the movie. Did
you see the movie Saw?
Oh. Yeah. Great film. Almost
as fun as going on a seesaw.
Okay. The reason these movies
are so popular... Mmm-hmm.
...is the element of
psychological torment.
I like where you're
going with this. Continue.
Could we lure him into an
old warehouse or something?
I have an old barn.
It's kind of smelly. Yes.
But that might be a
plus. And then what? Okay.
We do what they
did in Saw.
I mean, we don't
kill him, obviously.
I have a mask.
Okay, that's your idea?
Exactly like in the movie?
That is the most idiotic thing
I have ever heard in my life.
Well, suggest something
else then. Don't just...
Are you supposed
to cut his leg off?
Don't just criticize my idea! Think!
You think of
something then.
Michael, I'm worried that not all your
toys are gonna fit on your new desk.
How is that possible?
Well, in your old office, there were
all those ledges and extra space.
No excuses, Erin, come on.
Make it happen.
You know, I actually think
that I should get back to work.
Jim asked me to do some
stuff, and he's manager.
Oh, yeah, fine, fine.
Leave it here.
Okay. All right.
MICHAEL: I have to make
some sales anyway.
Who should I call with
my magic sales fingers?
(PHONE RINGING)
Michael Scott,
Head of Sales.
You gotta do something, man.
You can't just sit there.
The new IT guy. Nick.
Nick.
I think he's the key. He's very
trusting. He's looking for friends.
He's been given an
awesome amount of power,
and does not know
how to wield it.
Like Frodo.
Why don't you just let me handle the
Tolkien references, okay, dumb jock?
Well, I think he can be
corrupted. Like Gollum.
Smeagol was corrupted
and became Gollum.
I might start a diabolical
plot against him after this one.
Who's hungry?
What is that?
It's ants on a log. Michael would
always have me bring them in at 2:30
and say, "Who's hungry?"
(CHUCKLES) Oh. I'm fine.
Thank you, though.
Do you want me to spin you in
your chair and make you dizzy?
Why would I
want to do that?
It's a thinking technique.
All the top executives do it.
It keeps the brain moving, and a
spinning brain's a working brain.
For now I'm just gonna
go back to work here.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, thank you.
Well...
It will be a pleasure doing
business with you. Thanks. Bye, bye.
I just got a new account. The
gentlemen's club in Carbondale.
It is called Curves. I
went by there the other day,
saw some of the women walking
in. Not really my cup of tea.
Actually, Kevin,
you might like it.
Nice.
You know, we really don't announce
out loud our sales that much.
Why not? It's part of
the sales experience.
It's not really
1992 anymore.
(ALL LAUGHING)
MICHAEL: Okay.
"You brighten my day with
the sound of your voice.
"You bring so much laughter and
love. You're everything to me,
"and I was so blessed when
God sent you here to me."
(CHUCKLES) Jeez Louise.
I know.
Obsessed with me much?
Well, everyone got one.
What did yours say?
"Friends are worth sharing
a dog house with."
It's no wonder that Andy gave
Kelly such a romantic card.
I can't
compete with her.
That girl can sing and dance and
gets all of her clothes at the mall.
And I feel like such a fool for thinking
that Andy was only going after one girl,
because Andy Bernard is a
playboy. And why shouldn't he be?
He's got it all.
(EXCLAIMS)
There he is.
The IT guy.
I see you discovered
the break room.
Yep.
I imagine one of the best
things about being an IT guy is,
you get to know everyone's
computer passwords.
No, I actually don't.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Listen, I know you
have to say that,
but we got
a little problem here.
There is an employee
named Jim Halpert,
and he's doing some
terrible things. Okay?
He's molesting people via the
Internet, and we need to stop him.
I think that you
should call the cops.
No, the cops called us.
So I'm gonna need you to give me the
password to Jim Halpert's computer.
I don't know what to
tell you, man. I'm sorry.
I just can't give out
his password like that.
Nick, we can make things
very difficult for you.
Are you threatening me?
Threatening you?
No.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
What is that smell?
Do you smell that?
What is that? Like a
sulfur deposit under here?
Michael, stop.
No, I'm serious.
We don't have to put up...
(SOFTLY) Is it the dogs?
Michael.
You know what? We don't
have to deal with this.
I am going to
google sulfur maps.
Michael, it's Phyllis.
No, this is geological.
I sent an email out to
everyone in this area
that this might be
a side effect
to my new allergy
medication I'm on.
Are you kidding me?
No.
And you guys are
okay with this?
She sent an email.
PHYLLIS: I did.
It's not 'cause
of the smell.
I'm just expecting
a nose bleed.
Oh, my God.
(LAUGHS)
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
I thought you saw me.
I didn't see you. And
you were there all along.
Well, warmed it up for you,
so it should be good to go.
Cool. Thanks.
Bye, Andy.
That was weird.
No, it ain't. We all saw
the valentine you gave her.
I don't even know
what that card said.
Believe me,
if I got that card,
we'd be in the bathroom
doing it right now.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hey.
You know, it's funny. I used to stand
in here and wish I was out there.
Now I'm out there,
and I wish I was in here.
Well, the grass
is always greener.
Yeah, except there's
no grass out there.
It's just a farty dirt-patch.
Well, it's what
you wanted.
I really need my job back. We
made a terrible mistake here.
For the record, I
fought this. All right?
And now, I'm not
really sure what we do.
We make a poster that says,
"Happy Opposite Day"
and she sees it on the
way out. That's stupid.
Oh, I wish we had one of those
amnesia flashlights from Men In Black.
Hey. What was that movie where
their boss was within earshot
and they could have just
gone and talked to her?
Lethal Weapon?
That's it.
I think we should do it
the Lethal Weapon way.
You two are grown-assed men.
What do I have to do?
Fire you and get
two people in here
who don't need so
much management?
Ah!
(COUGHS) What I... Michael's
saying that he's better
at being a manager,
and I agree.
I'm just... He's a better
people person, weirdly.
And weirdly, I'm a good
dog person, right, guys?
Come on. See?
They love me.
Fine. I don't care which
one of you does which job,
just stop meeting with me
to talk about it.
(DOGS PANTING)
All right.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh.
I gotta take this. Yeah.
Finish walking my dogs for me.
And don't ride them. A lot
of people try to ride them.
Excuse me, everyone,
please check your emails.
I just sent you
the following message,
"Coworkers, you may have
received a valentine from me.
"Please understand this does not
mean that I like you in any way."
You don't even
like us as friends?
Phyllis, you guys are,
like, my closest friends.
I just mean I don't
like-like you.
What are we, five?
"Please don't read
into this card.
"Yours in professionalism,
Nard Dog."
Um, why did I just receive
a mass email from you
that said that
you don't like me?
Do you realize how hard
that makes me like you, Andy?
It's not... That wasn't...
I like someone else.
Who?
(STUTTERS)
It's not...
Whether or not...
(MUMBLING)
Who? What?
Yeah, I guess Andy
never liked Kelly.
How about that?
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
It smells good in here.
It sure does. Okay, we have your
space heater, your humidifier,
your dehumidifier, your fan, your
foot fan and your food dehydrator.
Erin, what about
my keyboard?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON KEYBOARD)
Ah.
So good to be home.
How about a little
Bossa Nova?
(EXCLAIMS)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
He looks happy.
Yep.
Well, well, well.
Hmm. Boss for...
What was it? Oh.
Four-and-a-half hours.
New record. Low.
Previous record,
Henry Rostin.
Boss for nine years,
four months.
And he only left because he
had family matters to attend to,
and he... What?
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
DWIGHT: Michael!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
I can't help but think that
something we did made this possible.
Jim dug his own grave, but
maybe we provided the shovel.
(EXCLAIMS) Temp, I like that. I'm
gonna engrave that into a piece of wood.
Care to celebrate
with a drink?
I would love to.
(CHUCKLING)
Why not?
Because martini bars
are pretentious.
No, thank you. I'm
sorry that I don't want
farm-boy swill
like you do, you know?
It is not farm-boy swill.
I will show you.
It is beet vodka
and it is delicious.
I'm not interested in
anything I have to make myself.
www.tvsubtitles.net