Everybody, everybody, listen up.
I need your ideas now.
Ideas, please, right now. Go, go!
- Come on!
- What you're talking about?
Wet cement outside, it's drying fast.
Come on, this is a lifelong dream.
What do I write?
Michael, you could put
your initials in it.
M.G.S., no.
Some idiot named Mark Greg Sputnik
will claim credit for it. I don't...
Once in a lifetime opportunity, people.
- Come on!
- Well...
Here we go!
Phyllis, yes?
- When I was a little girl...
- Okay.
Okay, do it!
Come on, great, let's hear it!
- We found some wet cement...
- It's drying, it's drying.
All right, Phyllis, come on!
- Come on, Phyl!
- What did we write?
Aah! Come on!
- Draw a picture.
- No!
- 'Cause that says so more than words.
- No, no!
Come on, give me something good!
I was watching E!, and I saw Will Smith
outside the chinese theater,
- and, oh, my god, he looked so good.
- Pam, translate.
She's talking about the handprints
that celebrities make in cement.
- I love it!
- A real star would put his face in it.
- I love it more!
- Michael, that doesn't seem safe...
I love it!
Come on, let's go!
We are here today
not to immortalize a man,
but an idea.
Maybe the idea of a man.
Hurry, please.
Greatness is only skin-deep
some people say.
Well, that's not true.
Other people believe
it's deeper inside
and in this case,
that's also not true.
Go!
Force it in as deep as you can.
That's what she said.
Today's a very special day for me.
And it's really not about me.
It's about my grandkids.
It's about my great-grandkids.
I can come back here when I'm 100,
and I can find that piece
of cement and say,
"That's me. Look, kids.
Your daddy left that facehole."
I don't know.
It's a good feeling.
Transcript: SwSub
Sync: DarKsh
Episode 4x12
"DID I STUTTER" (1.00)
Okay...
Adjective.
Tall.
No, no, uh, nice.
Good one.
Okay...
You ready?
"The tall man
entered the nice building,
"to visit a very nice man.
"Sit down, Mr. Smith.
"Can I interest you
in any good cat food?"
It's a man eating cat food!
What about a cat eating man food?
Andy and Angela seem very happy.
I hope nothing horrible
ever happens to them.
Yeah, I slept over at a...
friend's house, and...
I forgot my contact solution, so...
I had to wear my back-up glasses.
Shut up.
All right, everybody.
Oh, my god.
Pam...
Those make you look so ugly.
Pam, in order to get hotter,
you take the glasses off.
You're moving in the wrong direction.
- I don't have my contact...
- Blah blah!
I can't even hear you.
It's just noise coming out
of an ugly scientist.
We're gonna have
a little brainstorming session
in the conference room.
Energize.
You know what would energize me?
If you, Pamela Morgan Beesly...
Don't, don't.
If you propose to me during
the Michael meeting, I will say no.
Well, it's too late,
'cause I'm proposing...
that you get me a cup of coffee,
which would energize me greatly
and make me the happiest
man in the world.
Everybody, so how are we going
to energize our office?
I mean, I haven't done
anything since Christmas.
Pam clearly has just given up trying.
So what we need to do
is we need to get things going.
We need to get percolating a little bit.
Anybody have any ideas what we could do?
Any suggestions?
Yes, Andy?
What if we changed
our outgoing answering machine message
so it just had a little more zing
and a little more pep?
Zing and pep. Those are the kind
of words we're looking for. Yes, Jim.
What about if we did
an even newer voicemail message
that had even more zing and pep?
Now we're cooking, I like this.
Maybe a whole theme.
- Like a rap... a rap rhyme.
- An urban thing.
An urban... Yeah, Stanley,
you wanna help us out with that?
- Stanley! Earth to Stanley.
- Not me.
Yes, you. Come on, Stanley,
put your little game down
- and join the group.
- No.
- Stanley, we're having...
- Leave me alone, damn it.
We're having a brainstorm session...
Did I stutter?
Good. This is good.
I'm going to grab a glass of water.
Can I talk to you a second?
What?
I really think that you need to address
what happened with Stanley this morning.
What are you blabbering about?
Nothing happened.
Well, you know, Stanley
was openly insubordinate.
- That, in the conference room?
- Yeah.
We were joshing around,
the two of us.
And he said, "Did I stutter?"
And I said, "wh-wh-wh-what, dog?"
It was joking, Toby, all right?
He didn't seem like he was joking.
Well, you don't get it,
because Stanley is a beautiful,
sassy, powerful black man,
and you're you.
If you had any friends,
you would understand.
Friends joke with one another.
"Hey, um, you're poor."
"Well, hey, your mama's dead."
That's what friends do.
It's...
You're so white.
All right.
Well...
If you really believe
that Stanley was joking...
- Why don't we go ask him that?
- Okay, I will.
I'm not feeling very well
right now, though.
My stomach hurts,
so I may be going home early today.
You know, Michael,
sometimes my daughter's stomach hurts
when there's a mean girl at school.
Well, sometimes my stomach hurts
when you come into my office.
So it's probably psychological.
You meet a lot of ladies
driving an Xterra,
because you pull up to a stop light
and look over
and there's an Xterra next to you,
they're always driven by chicks.
So there's your ice breaker.
Scratch!
That's a racing stripe.
- Bumper's sagging.
- Hmm, I doubt that very much.
This car is crap.
I will buy it for next to nothing.
- How next to?
- Well, here are your options.
You can sell it for parts.
Drive it off a cliff.
You can donate it to a person
that you'd like to see
die in a car crash, or...
you can sell it to me and I'll use it
as I would a wagon on my farm.
It will be towed by a donkey.
- I have to pick one of those?
- Yes.
- Can you go over those options again?
- You know what?
You knock $1,500 off the price right now
and I will take it off your hands.
It's gonna be now.
- I have the blue book value...
- Seal the deal.
Let's do this thing.
Three, two, one.
- Can I think about it?
- Five, four, three, two, now.
- Let me think about it.
- Say it. Do it now.
Do it now!
Do it. Shake my hand.
You will sell me this car.
Shake my hand.
Yeah, all right!
What?
I see that you gave me that form
that I asked you to give me,
Stanley the manly.
So thank you for that.
I guess we are back to normal.
What are you talking about?
Well, you know,
the thing that you said earlier that...
you didn't mean.
And that I forgive you for.
The whole thing's silly, isn't it?
Friends don't need to apologize
to friends as far as I'm concerned.
So we are cool.
I am not going to apologize to you.
It's like I used to tell my wife.
"I do not apologize
unless I think I'm wrong
"and if you don't like it,
you can leave."
And I say the same thing
to my current wife,
and I'll say it to my next one too.
Jim is in charge of Stanley
only in sales-related matters.
Hence the green line.
Green for money.
Sales, get it?
There's this yellow zigzag
that does give Ryan
the authority to discipline Stanley.
- Great.
- However, in so doing,
it zigs past your name,
hence zagging you
and making you appear weak. Thus
the yellow color. Yellow for cowardly.
What's the pink?
Menstrual cycles.
Okay.
Is there anybody up here, anybody at all
that can deal with this
- other than me...
- You.
Well, there is the emergency
disaster mode
for the org chart.
This gives me
full authority
over every single person in the office.
- I never said you could do that.
- All you have to do is say it.
- Okay, I'll think about it.
- Say it. Just do it.
Don't think, say it. Do it.
Five, four, three, two...
Do it.
Give me control.
Michael...
I promise to give authority
back to you when this crisis is over.
Do it, Michael.
Do it. Hey.
This office needs a strong man.
Say it.
- No.
- So...
All right, well then, you're gonna have
to deal with this yourself.
Hey, Pam.
I really like your glasses.
Thanks.
All the girlfriends that I've ever had
have worn glasses.
Okay.
Yeah, it's kind of a turn-on
for me actually.
- I should probably get back to...
- Like librarians.
- entering the...
- Could you just say,
"These are due back thursday."
No.
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Okay, go ahead.
A lot of jazz cats are blind,
but they can play the piano
like nobody's business.
I'd like to put
the piano in front of Pam
without her glasses
and see what happens.
I'd also like to see her topless.
- Mike.
- Hey.
- I'm very busy here, man.
- Darryl...
Have you ever been in a gang?
Why?
It's an advice question, and...
if you don't want to talk about it,
I completely understand. It's...
- No, no.
- I know it's very personal.
No...
- I have.
- I knew it.
Okay.
Who are we talking about here?
- Crips, bloods?
- Both.
- God.
- Yeah, them and the latin kings.
- The warriors, Newsies.
- Okay.
Okay, so dig this.
You're on the street
and one of your gang disses you.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Yeah, right.
What do you do
to get him to make it right?
Well, see...
in the gang world,
we use something called fluffy fingers.
What is that?
That's where if somebody
really gets in your face,
you know, just start tickling them.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And he starts tickling you.
You know, pretty soon
you're laughing and hugging.
Before you know it,
you've forgotten the whole thing.
Y'all can just go to church together
and get an ice cream cone.
I would have never thought that...
gangs would be tickling each other.
Well, it's effective.
I think it's self-explanatory.
Hey, Jim!
Come here for a second.
Can you answer me something
as a true Eagles fan?
Oh, boy.
How do you live
with a franchise this bad?
- On a wing and a prayer mostly.
- All right, whatever you say.
Listen, while I have you here with Toby,
I need to give you a formal warning
about your job performance.
A formal warning?
It's actually not a joke.
I know how you spend your time here.
I know how little
you care about your job.
And honestly, if you spent
as much time selling
as you do goofing around with Dwight
and hanging out at reception,
we wouldn't be having this conversation.
I'm sorry, is this because
I talked to Wallace about your website?
Because I really didn't mean
to go over your head.
This is nothing to do
with that, all right?
I always appreciate
constructive criticism
about my job performance.
I thrive on it.
Then do you mind
explaining it a little better?
- 'Cause I'm not sure...
- Don't get all defensive, okay?
It's just a warning.
If you want details, Toby can provide
them. You take it easy, all right?
I'd say all the goofing around
at Pam's desk
and hanging out with Pam
has finally caught up to him.
P... with Pam.
Hey, what happened?
What did Ryan want?
Oh, we were just...
talking about bureaucratic stuff.
Because you're very important.
Yeah.
Oh, what's Dwight up to?
Oh, probably nothing.
What the hell is this all about?
You're flipping my car for profit.
It's my car now.
I gave you a deal
based on what you said to me.
Yeah, well...
seller beware.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got to monitor a three-way
bidding war for my car on ebay.
I've got a mad lib for you.
"A stupid idiotic numbskull
"named Andy Bernard sold his Xterra
"to a smart and capable man
named Dwight.
"This is shaping up to be
an awesome day for Dwight."
Okay, everybody, shh!
Listen up.
Earlier today, Stanley sassed me.
And Toby gave me some suggestions
on how to discipline him.
They didn't work, obviously,
because they were stupid.
So I am now going to fake fire him.
- What does that mean?
- It's like a mock execution.
- That's not a good idea.
- Yes, it is a good idea.
It's the only possible
solution I have left.
- Well, you can actually fire him.
- No...
- I've had enough of you.
- Why are you telling us this?
Because I want you to behave as if
I'm actually firing him, Oscar, okay?
Michael, if you hadn't told us this,
then we would've thought
that you were actually firing him.
I'm not firing him!
I will need you to act
like I am firing him.
Just... what I'm going to do
is I'm going to pretend
that I'm firing him.
And I need you to act
like I am firing him. Do you get that?
Do you get it?
I'm teaching him a lesson.
He needs to learn humility, all right?
That's all I'm...
Okay, here he comes.
Let's just play act.
Stanley,
may I talk to you for a second?
Stanley Hudson,
you are fired.
Are you serious?
I am serious.
We are all serious.
You are fired like a heart attack.
You're firing me over three words?
- Yes.
- Have you lost your mind?
Do you think I'm gonna
let you do this to me?
I've watched you screw up
this office for ten years,
and I'm filing a lawsuit, and I'm gonna
tell them about every stupid thing
- you've ever done up in this office.
- All right, okay.
You know what?
Now you know how I feel.
This was a fake firing.
Lesson learned.
Good work, everybody. Very nice.
So I'm not fired.
That's it.
And...
do you have anything to say to me?
Yes, I do.
You are out of your damn
little pea-sized mind.
What is wrong with you?
Do you have any sense at all?
Do you have any idea
how to run an office?
Every day you do something stupider
than you did the day before.
And I think, "There's no possible way
he can top that."
But you do you do?
You find a way, damn it, to top it.
You are a professional idiot...
Hey, stop it!
Okay, everybody out.
- Who?
- Yeah, everybody except Stanley.
Let's go.
- I can't find my glasses.
- You know what? Take my hand,
and leave 'em
and let's get out of here.
Okay, okay.
It's Michael versus Stanley,
and it is the clash of the titans.
In one corner, you have Michael,
and he is mad.
And then in the other corner,
you have Stanley,
and he's mad.
So that's about it.
I don't understand
why you keep picking on me.
- Oh, for the love of god.
- You just...
do, and I don't know why, so...
please help me understand.
Fine. Here it is.
You are a person I do not respect.
The things you say, your actions,
your methods and style.
Everything you would do,
I would do it the opposite way.
Well, Stanley,
maybe you are feeling
that you don't respect me
because you don't know me very well.
Michael, I've know you a very long time.
And the more I've gotten to know you,
the less I've come to respect you.
Any other theories?
All right, you don't respect me.
I accept that.
But listen to me.
You can't talk to me that way
in this office, you just can't.
I am your boss.
Can't allow it.
Fair enough.
I am a good person,
and sometimes...
good people don't get no respect.
Rodney Dangerfield.
Hey, I don't get no respect.
No respect at all.
When I was in the sandbox
as a kid, I got no respect.
My wife likes to talk after sex.
So she called me from a hotel room,
said, "I don't respect you."
Thoughtless.
You know what don't get no respect?
Airplane food.
Why don't they just make the plane
out of the airline food?
My wife don't get no respect.
Some... take her, please, for example.
If you don't get no respect,
you might be a redneck.
Respect is nice.
Borat.
What's the deal with grape nuts?
No grapes, no nuts.
I don't get no respect.
So I'm thinking as a reward
for our loyal clients
that we contact their assistants
and we find out where they live.
And then, we go to their houses
in the middle of summer
and go caroling.
It is a summer Christmas celebration
and we'll call it,
"A summer sales a lot."
Feedback, anybody?
Stanley?
Has the potential
to be the best idea yet...
That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
Damn it. All right,
everybody out except Phyllis.
www.tvsubtitles.net