We can get Deangelo flowers.
No, you can't get flowers
for someone who's in a coma.
They'll wilt
before he wakes up.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Good point.
All in favor
of the baskets
full of chocolates,
Teddy bears, and balloons.
Wait, wait.
All in favor
of the knapsack
filled with canned goods,
chainsaw, gasoline,
and emergency radio
in case he wakes up
post-apocalypse...
Nope.
Baskets have it.
So as it turns out,
unless you're a young child
or a prison inmate,
you don't need anyone
supervising you.
People just come in
and do their work
on their schedule.
Imagine that-- People like us
allowed to sell paper.
Unsupervised.
And yet, somehow it works.
It must be because
the stakes are so high.
Well, I really
appreciate the offer,
but I'm just happy
the way things are.
Okay. Thank you.
That was Jo asking me
if I wanted to take over
as acting manager
while they find a replacement.
I told her...
I don't want to mess
this up, right?
There's a consensus.
People are happy.
Dwight Schrute.
Yes, I would.
Thank you.
Jordan.
Gather my things from my desk.
Wait...
What have you done?
Mose...
You'll never guess
where I am right now.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Can't stay there all day.
I'm coming.
Do I at least get to
go with you in this fantasy?
You'd slow me down.
Dwight has been acting manager
for...Three months now.
No. A week.
Just feels like three months.
Let's see...
We all have to punch into
a time clock
which is very old, very strong,
and has a slot
about the size of a finger.
We were all given
new business cards
big enough to set us apart
from the competition.
Which is how I learned
that our titles
are all now junior employee.
Our lunch breaks are staggered
to prevent wasting time.
Mine's at 10:30.
And I find that the first
hour of the day goes by
a lot quicker
than the second seven hours.
Stop stalling.
Come on.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the Republic
for which it stands,
one nation, under God,
indivisible,
with liberty and justice
for all.
- Amen.
- Excellent.
Morning announcements.
There's been a problem with some
people sharing copier codes.
Your copier code
is a distinct 21-digit number
that is unique to you
and you only, okay?
Don't share it.
Jo Bennett, our ceo,
will be here today
for a high-level meeting
involving Gabe and myself.
Ooh. About what?
That's on
a need-to-know basis.
I thought I needed to know
for your calendar.
General meet and greet.
So I expect you to be
on your best behavior,
which means none of you
will be insubordinate
nor will you
foment insurrection.
Question. If we've already
fomented insurrection,
may we be grandfathered in?
- Define foment.
- You define foment.
Please take note of the new
color-coding system.
Aha!
Oh, my God!
What is wrong with you?
Gotcha! Why are you late?
It's none of your business,
actually.
It's very medical and personal.
All right.
You stop me when I reach
the diseased area.
In fairness, Darryl
did tell me that joke, so...
Oh! Darryl's funny.
- I know, right.
- Hey, Andy?
- Yeah.
- Can I talk to you a second
about these client memos?
Sure.
What's going on?
Are you still
in love with Erin?
What?
Because I am.
I need to get her back.
I can't be alone anymore.
Andy, do you like being
alone with me right now?
No. This is horrifying.
No. I don't like being
alone with me either, okay?
I have to get her back.
Are you still gonna date her?
We're just friends, okay?
Do you promise that?
Yeah, fine, I promise.
We'll never date again.
Can we go outside now?
No. Just give me a second.
I don't want anyone to know
I've been crying.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What do you think you're doing?
What's this?
What's the fist?
Oh, it's just a social club.
You know,
like the French revolution
or the black panthers
or communism.
It's just a club.
Guys talkin'. You know.
You expect me to believe that
you're starting a rebellion?
Nope. Social club.
God, I hate when everybody
calls us a rebellion.
Okay, you know what?
I would love to join the fist.
And we would love
to have you-- But not today.
Unfortunately, it's a bad day,
what with operation overthrow
and everything.
But I have noted it.
One...
Pam, I have to show you
this video.
You're gonna love it.
It's Beyonce falling...
With a fart mixed in.
I will never be happier
than I am right now.
I will also be
never less happy.
I will be at my current
maximum happiness
for the rest of my life,
because I am manager
of the Scranton branch
of Dunder-Mifflin.
Acting manager.
No food now!
Someone has to do something
about Dwight.
He put some snacks
in the freezer for us.
You mean the frozen mice
for the piranha?
No. The blueberry
slurpee pouch.
Hmm. He means
the ice pack.
2:00 should probably
be okay.
I can either take
your number or--
I'm sorry.
This can't wait.
He's just gonna call back.
Erin. I am in love
with you.
I don't believe in much, okay?
I don't believe in horoscopes.
I don't believe in Christmas.
Uh, uh, I sure as hell
don't believe in God.
What?
Or maybe there's a God.
I don't know.
I mean, it's just not a guy
with a long white beard.
Or it could be.
I mean, it's possible
that that is exactly
what-- What God is.
But for all of the disbelief...
I believe in us.
I believe in love.
You have made me believe
that for all of the hokum...
Out...There...
Uh, do we not have voice mail?
Dwight doesn't trust robots
to give us our messages.
Well...
It's just...
It messes up my rhythm.
But...
I'm taking a break from dating.
Gabe was a great guy with
so many wonderful qualities,
but it was a challenge
being touched by him.
Wow. You've really embraced
the whole bond villain
aesthetic.
Ah, Jim, Jim, Jim.
The gun is a beaumont-Adams.
Jo collects them.
I thought we could have
some nice small talk about it.
And the piranha's a rescue.
And the desk.
The desk is a replica
of Uday Hussein's desk.
I saw a picture in newsweek.
Listen, I'm a very busy man.
Let's get right down
to business.
- Okay.
- Jo is coming later today.
I cannot have a subordinate
trying to make me look stupid.
Okay?
I need you to promise me
that you'll be
on your best behavior.
I promis...ed
other people
that I'd be
on my worst behavior.
And I gave them my word, so...
Don't make me fire you.
You can't fire me.
You're acting manager.
Not office manager.
So you have no firing powers.
- Don't make me pre-fire you.
You wouldn't dare.
- Watch this.
You're pre-fired.
And when I'm promoted,
you'll be full fired.
If you get promoted,
and if you haven't fallen
in love with me by then.
What?
If I had thought
that there was a real chance
that Dwight would be
permanent manager,
I would have pre-quit.
And you might be saying
to yourself,
"well, that's pretty
premature to think,"
but I always say it's better
to be pre-pre-preprepared.
- How you doing, Jordan?
- I'm good.
Everyone here thinks
that you're a joke.
They think that you were hired
because of your good looks,
which won't last long anyway.
As your pale skin
and severe bone structure imply,
you'll age swiftly and poorly.
Why are you telling me this?
Now I want you to find out
what people are saying about me,
things they don't want me
to know abou--
It's a holster.
Yep. Yep, yep, yep.
Lookin' good.
Oh, what a day.
What a day.
Dwight, are you carrying a gun?
The holster was a gift
from my great-uncle honk.
Um, I don't know.
I guess he's saying
that he's proud of me.
Dwight, guns make me
really uncomfortable.
The gun is just an accessory
to the holster, okay?
I can't walk around
wearing an empty holster.
Why do you need to wear
the holster at all?
Why do you need to keep
wearing those booby shirts
all the time?
Thank you.
You could put your
cell phone in it instead.
Uh...Hello!
You could put a banana in it.
Why would I put a banana
in my holster?
In case you weren't hungry now
but you got hungry later.
Dwight, no gun, okay?
Don't make us call Jo.
Okay, all right, fine.
Everyone calm down.
Someone get me a banana.
- Sorry I freaked you guys out--
- Aah!
Andy!
Aah! God!
It's so loud!
Oh my God.
There is a hardwood floor
underneath this carpeting.
Why would they do that?
Eeeeeee...
There's like this
crazy ringing going on.
I can't--
Eeeeeeee....
* Eeee *
I can't find perfect c.
Okay, everyone make a list of
what's lost for the insurance.
I lost a necklace, a ring,
painting--
Hey, what happened?
Dwight went on
a shooting spree,
and then he shot Andy
in the head.
No, no, no.
All we know is that a gun fired.
That's all we know!
No. That's not true.
Actually,
we heard a loud noise.
Later, a hole was seen.
No one saw the bullet
leave the gun.
Something's definitely wrong.
I'll look on WebMD.
What are your symptoms?
Oh, everybody.
Oscar found a reason
to look on WebMD.
Firewall.
I can't reach Jo-- She must
already be on the plane.
Why are you calling Jo?
I think I should
go to the hospital.
- I'll go with you.
- No!
We really shouldn't be
without a receptionist.
Now more than ever.
I'll take him.
Thank you, Darryl.
What's wrong with you?
- It's my ear.
- Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Oh. I should get
the accident report binder.
I've never used
the gun violence forms before.
I'm gonna keep trying Jo.
Okay, everyone--
Conference room.
Right now!
Howdy, partners.
It's me,
gun-safety Dwight.
And I'm the rootin'est--
I can't do this.
Um, look.
Obviously,
a gun went off under my watch,
and I'm launching
a full investigation.
We all saw you do it.
Really? You did?
What hand was I holding
the gun in?
What did Andy's tie look like?
Navy blue.
Little red anchors.
I have no way of knowing
if that's true.
I am supposed to collect
eyewitness accounts.
Who saw Dwight do this?
Okay, really?
Would you consider this
a terrorist incident?
- I felt terrorized.
- Come on.
Oh, there's a whole nother
terrorism booklet for that.
I just really, really think
that we should handle this
internally.
Dwight, why is it on us
to protect you?
Because you guys
are my best friends,
and I mean that.
Managing you for this last week
has been the greatest honor
of my life.
And if you ruin this,
I will burn this office
to the ground.
And I mean that figuratively.
Not literally.
Because you guys are so...
So important to me.
I love you guys.
But don't cross me.
But you're the best.
Hey.
- We're back.
- There he is!
Our hero!
You look fantastic.
How you doing? Here.
Tell us your war stories.
Well, I burst my eardrum.
Doctor said it could take
weeks to heal.
Did they say what caused it?
'Cause I know you like
putting q-tips
deep into your ear canal.
Yeah.
How's your hearing?
Temporary deafness in one ear.
It was both ears.
I couldn't hear a thing
Darryl was saying
when we were
in the waiting room.
I don't feel good about it,
but he just kept calling himself
a gunshot victim,
and it got to me.
Dwight, I would like
tomorrow off
so that I can go on
my American idol audition.
American idol?
What? No.
Okay. I guess I can
just not go.
Do you guys wanna hear my solo?
No.
* Why did my temporary boss *
* go on a shooting spree? *
Okay. Fine. You can go
on your singing audition.
Okay, well, then I want
an extra vacation day.
Pet day.
I want pet day back-- No dogs.
Put back everything
in the vending machine
except the fruit.
I put everything back
in the vending machine.
Put everything back
in the vending machine
except...The fruit.
You have to get rid
of all your weapons.
All of them.
Including killer fish.
Okay.
Oh, it's my turn?
Ooh, I'm on the spot.
I don't know. Um...
You know what?
I think I'm good.
- Thank God.
- Nope. When Jo's here,
can you work in
"shagadelic, baby,"
at least three times
in a conversation?
Oh, and when I cough,
can you do jazz hands?
What's jazz hands?
Fine.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, my...
Hey, all!
Cornelius, Bobo, have at it.
Nobody let my dogs
hump each other.
They don't seem to know
they're brothers.
Hello, Jo.
Welcome.
Well, shall we begin?
Slow yourself down there.
Just like a man.
Wants to jump right into it
while I still got my socks on.
Jim Halpert-- The only man
that ever turned me down.
Well, I don't know about that.
Just wasn't for me.
But let me assure you,
Dwight is firing
on all cylinders.
Right?
Well, some pretty big shoes
to fill.
I was sorry to hear
about Deangelo.
He was a good man.
Tragic.
Well, what can you do?
Life.
- We have to clean this up now!
- She had so much--
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
No!
Hey, Andy, did you tell Erin
about our conversation earlier
when you said you would never
want to date her again?
I just thought that
it was so interesting
that you promised that.
Did I say that earlier?
Yes, I did.
Because you, Gabe,
were crying...
- No, I was not.
- And sobbing uncontrollably.
Yes. Uh-huh.
You were in hysterics.
And my maternal instincts
kicked in.
Is it actually how I feel?
Yes.
Or no.
That is...
Between me and my diary.
Oscar, can you print out
last year's sale statements?
- Sure.
- Hey, Dwight.
Gimme a back massage.
No, Kevin, come on.
My back is sore, Dwight.
Massage it.
Kevin, not now.
- Hey, Jo...
- Okay, okay.
No. Under the jacket.
You're kidding me.
God, what am I touching?
It's moist.
- I don't feel anything.
- Oh, it's so wet.
- Push harder, Dwight.
- I can't.
I can't push harder!
- Go a little higher.
- I--
There.
There you go.
Nope. Higher.
I c--
Higher.
- Oh, my God!
- There we go.
Okay. How's that?
Knead it.
Knead it like a pizza.
- I'm kneading it!
- But don't eat it.
Okay...
Dwight.
Walk me out.
Oop.
Let's talk soon.
And stay on top of
these people.
You gotta admit it--
It's nice to have
a little power, eh?
How's it feel?
Jo...
I accidentally fired a gun
in the office today.
- What?
- I am telling you this
because I care too much
about this job
to be blackmailed
into doing it poorly.
All I've ever wanted
is to be manager here.
And if you feel like
you cannot promote me
over this one accident,
I understand.
But if you think
that extortion is worse--
Shooting is worse!
Are you kiddin' me?
It's not even in the same--
You shot a gun?
What is wrong with you?
It was a Beaumont-Adams,
if that helps.
Beaumont-Adams
is a girl's gun.
That just makes it
plain stupid.
I take full responsibility.
Who else would be responsible?
Pam made me put
a banana in my holster.
You shot a gun off--
Okay. Did I make a mistake?
Yes.
Do I regret the decision
that I made? Yes.
Stop asking yourself
easy questions
so you can look like a genius.
- Got it.
- I love you, Dwight.
But you don't fit this job.
Jo, please...
- No.
- I will--
No, child.
No.
It's over.
Now I gotta find a replacement
for my replacement.
You three
are my search committee.
You're in charge of finding me
my next manager.
All righty?
- Yep.
Till then, we need
a new actin' manager.
Now, who's got the most
experience in this office?
Uh, well, we probably don't
wanna go just on seniority.
Who is it?
Hey, Dwight.
What's up?
Shut up.
Okay. Well...
You do know that Jo was right
to take the job away
from you, right?
There's no debating that.
But I will say...
In your one week,
every single one of the orders
went out on time,
And I think
that is shagadelic, baby.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Four.
One.
Seven.
Another one?
- Yes!
Seven.
- Two, six,
- Could you turn down the beeping?
nine, shut up Oscar, eight...
Nine first, put the nine.
- Nine, eight, five,
- Thank you.
Three, zero, zero...
- Again, zero.
- Okay.
- Four, six...
- Nice.
- Two, one.
- I hit three, I head three instead of...
God!
www.tvsubtitles.net