(CLICKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(CLICK!)
(GROANS)
I don't like it.
What's not to like?
The ceiling's too low, fridge is
too small, and there's no bath.
You haven't even checked the bath.
You can sense a bath.
10 bucks?
Yeah.
(GROANS)
Grab us a beer, will you, Dean?
I'll get you a beer 'cause I'm getting one.
Knock yourself out.
(FRIDGE OPENS AND CLOSES)
DEAN: Six months. Long time.
Cheers.
Eh, Sammy?
I guess.
DEAN: It's not natural, is it?
I'm gonna wash up.
Yeah, you're right, Harry.
There's no bath.
It's a gift.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Think he's OK?
(SHOWER RUNS)
Who knows?
He seems fine.
Think he's fine?
Who knows?
Well, should we talk to him
about it or something?
Who fucking knows, Dean?
Well, Sam's out of his hands now.
Hear Glenn got transferred?
Yeah.
HMAS 'Dignity'.
Yep.
Someone snitched on him.
Thank Christ.
Firstly, Glenn Carter
is executive officer.
Secondly, Glenn Carter was just...
Glenn Carter is a walking fucking
power trip and you know it, Dean.
Glenn can be a prick.
Glenn is a prick.
He was well within his rights.
You defend that motherfucker once...
We all went through it.
We didn't go through that.
Alright.
What am I talking to you for?
It was probably your idea.
Watch it.
Or what?
I mean it, Harry.
You've got a taste for it now?
Shut the fuck up!
Hey.
I was following orders.
Thank you, Dr Goebbels.
Glenn was just doing exactly what...
Glenn, please, no.
Stop calling him Glenn around me.
You would have done exactly the
same thing if you'd been made XO.
Maybe you would, Dean.
Sam needed shaping up.
You even said that yourself.
Not like that!
Glenn probably thinks
that's how you treat a screw-up.
Then he's a fucking sadist.
Oh!
Watch the hat.
What are you doing?
Letting my fingers...
...do...
Bingo!
Tell me you're not.
I'm ordering it for later.
'It'?
Christ, Harry!
Oh, what, you got some kind
of moral stance now, have you?
It'll do him good.
Do him good?
He's a bloody handsome guy.
He doesn't need...
Hi.
Who am I speaking to, please?
Debbie. Hey, Debbie.
Guessing that's not your real name,
but let's roll with it anyway. Hey.
Um, just want to inquire
about your service.
That sounds exactly like
what I'm after.
Um... How much?
OK.
Yep. Uh, Novotel, Darling Harbour.
Room 522.
Sam Fisher.
Do you need the... No?
OK.
Yep.
Yep. No worries. OK. 'Bye.
She's gonna call me back.
You shouldn't have used his name.
You are so paranoid!
So why didn't you use your own name?
What's in a name?
(PHONE RINGS)
Don't.
Debbie?
Hey.
Um...
Oh, OK.
250 for the hour?
(SNORTS)
Well, that's very reasonable.
Well, how much is the taxi?
What, so that could be up to 300?
No, no, let's not haggle.
We're having such a nice time.
Um... OK.
(MOUTHS WORDS)
No, they all sound lovely.
Yep.
No, this is for a, uh...
This is for a very special guy, Debs.
Um...
She needs to be...
Yeah, she needs to be,
you know, lovely, but nice.
Simple.
Not like retarded simple, just...
He's not into mentals
or anything. Just...
Well, uncomplicated.
Sweet and gentle.
That sounds perfect.
Lock her in. That's great.
Um...
Oh, bugger it.
Let's get one for me as well.
You've talked me into it, Debs.
(MOUTHS WORDS)
So two girls? Yeah, just two girls.
That'd be great.
So that's, like, 600?
Oh, look... (SIGHS, FLAPS LIPS)
Just... oh...
Throw me something skanky.
You know? Just...
something off the rack.
(SNORTS)
Mileage on the clock.
You know.
Little older.
Nothing I have to impress.
You know what I mean? Yep.
OK.
Uh... No, what time is it now?
Alright, let's go... OK, midnight.
Let's go midnight. Yep.
OK. Deb.
Yeah.
I have to interrupt you there,
OK? Yep, Deb.
I've got to... Cool. Midnight.
Thank you very much.
OK. Adios.
(WHISTLES) That is a load off.
Well, Sally definitely
can't come here now.
Well, that's a side benefit.
You're an arsehole!
Who called?
Uh, Glenn Carter - he wanted to
make sure you cleaned the dunny
before you got ahead of yourself.
DEAN: See, he's fine.
You're fine, aren't you?
You're great.
You're through
the worst of it now, mate.
(UNZIPS AND ZIPS BAG)
Just...
Look, can we just have
some fun now, or what?
Hey, Deano, you're welcome
to bring Sally here if you want.
Me and Harry, we could just
go to the bar, whatever.
Thanks, Sammy.
You done in there, Sam?
I'm about to bust
that fucking porcelain.
(DOOR CLOSES)
HARRY: Oh! It's Royal Doulton.
Turn on the television
and open the window, lads.
This is gonna be big.
(FIGHTING AND GUNFIRE ON TV)
Been on the town.
Go on, Sammy.
Come on.
Go on! Go on!
Alright.
(HARRY LAUGHS)
SAM: I can't do moves.
I can't do moves.
Fuck!
What'd you do?
Look at you. Look at you. Ooh!
(LAUGHS)
You're beautiful. Beautiful.
Thanks.
You are. I mean...
Can't go wrong.
DEAN: Oh, you almost picked up there.
What a dog.
HARRY: I'll give you a head start.
Oh, and he takes it!
Hi.
How are you?
HARRY: I'm good. How are you?
What are you up to?
Oh, you know.
Looking for somewhere to drink.
I was drinking over there.
I'm now heading back to my hotel.
Your hotel? Where are you staying?
The dirty, stinking one up the road.
Oh, really?
What room number?
Can't remember.
Oh, you can!
(LAUGHS)
SAM: Dean!
HARRY: You can. What room number?
No, it's not... No. It's not
glamorous. It's not glamorous.
Yeah, well, what room number?
Um, 3... 1... 4.
That is so... I'm gonna be knocking
on the wrong door.
No.
I'm gonna be...
What's your name?
Sue.
Harry. Lovely to meet you.
Hi, Harry.
You're gorgeous. You're beautiful.
See ya. 314, yeah?
OK.
Room 314.
Mum.
Mum, it's me.
Turn down the Cilla Black.
Hey.
Yeah, and I love you too.
Oh, Mum, come on.
Mum, don't cry. Come on.
Shh.
I got promoted.
Yeah. Yeah, no, I'm an officer now.
(LAUGHS)
Not a gentleman. Very funny.
Nothing. I miss you too.
How's Pop?
Really?
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Mum, I... Can you stop crying
for a sec? Mum?
Mum, they're sending us over there.
In the morning, first thing.
I don't... I really don't know, Mum.
They don't...
They don't tell us that stuff
until we're actual...
No, Mum, you can't tell...
Mum, you can't tell anyone.
I'm not even supposed...
For Christ... goodness sake,
don't tell Pop. OK?
Mum, just...
Mum, I need you to listen
just for one sec.
I'm not going.
I'm not going back.
No, you... you don't understand, Mum.
They almost killed me out there.
No. No, I've decided.
I guess not.
Alright, well, you know what?
I'm... I'm sorry I'm such a fucking
embarrassment. (ENDS CALL)
You should absolutely talk to her.
He talked to her already.
When he ordered, he talked to her.
She's out of his league, man.
Talk to her properly.
Sorry, Sammy, but look at her.
Exactly. Look her in the eye.
Don't do it.
And tell the truth.
Sammy! Sam.
He's trying to embarrass you.
Shouldn't you be
in the honeymoon suite?
Isn't that why we evacuated
the fucking room?
They just texted, by the way.
They're stuck in traffic.
They're probably avoiding you.
'They'?
I told you, her parents are coming.
You're bringing your girlfriend's
parents to our hotel?
Fiancée's. No, we're
all going out to dinner.
With her fucking parents.
Fiancée's.
I can't guarantee
what state I'm gonna be in.
Come on, guys.
I want her to meet you.
Jeez, how are we gonna eat more food?
We have to go to dinner with
his girlfriend's fucking parents.
Fiancée's.
You know, her old man.
Some people like
their parents, Harry.
Don't do it, Sammy.
HARRY: Let rip, Sammy. Let rip.
Excuse... excuse me, ma'am.
WOMAN: Yes?
Could, um...
Could we have some water, please?
Sure.
(HARRY SIGHS)
DEAN: Wise move, mate.
Go fire a fucking cannon
or something, Dean.
Look, mate, I don't want to do this.
No, you do want to do this.
You want to do this.
Believe me, you want to do this.
You're never gonna
see this girl again.
You're never gonna see her again.
Here she comes.
SAM: Thank you.
Beautiful meal.
Ta.
Anything else?
Yeah.
I, um... I just... I just wanted
to tell you something.
Sure.
You are the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen.
Truly, truly. The way you move,
the poise, the whole, um...
I... I was... You know, I was
gonna say aura, but I don't even...
OK. You know. OK.
Hey, look, this...
this isn't a pick-up.
Look, I'm actually gonna pay the bill
and I'm gonna go.
MAN: Emma, what are you doing?
EMMA: Uh...
Wiping tables.
Look after everybody else.
Leave the boys alone. Stop flirting.
We've got customers.
I couldn't leave without telling you
that you absolutely devastated me
the second I saw you.
And... you've made my night.
Thanks.
What in blue Jesus was that?
No, that was good.
'Devastated' was an odd call.
You just made a fool out of her.
He didn't.
She thought he was pulling the piss.
No, she didn't.
I wasn't.
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
EMMA: Hey, Shakespeare.
Yeah.
My cousin has a friendly poker game
round the back
if you guys want to play.
DEAN: Ah...
SAM: Oh...
Some of my friends
are coming down too, so...
A... bonus. That sounds like a winner.
I'm Sam.
Emma.
This is Harry and this is Dean.
We can't actually stay, ma'am.
We're running late.
Ignore him. Call your friends.
We're staying.
EMMA: Sure. Well, the game's
straight through the kitchen, boys.
HARRY: Awesome.
Alright.
Sit the fuck down. Sit the fuck down.
McCabe.
Come on. Leiberman, move.
DEAN: We're not staying long.
HARRY: Oh, we're staying long.
Hi.
Hi. I'm Harry.
Straight through the back, boys.
Thanks. This is my friend Dean.
Straight through the back.
DEAN: How you doing, pal?
Ooh!
SAM: Great rooftop.
Yeah, you get over it after a while.
Have you worked here long?
If I gave you three questions,
is that what you'd ask me?
Uh... (LAUGHS)
Yep.
OK, since I was 12.
I live with
the Italian boys downstairs
that your friends
are playing poker with.
They're very protective,
so you'd better play your cards right.
Yeah, no, I'm kind of hoping
that my friends
are playing their cards right.
(BALL BOUNCES)
Ooh.
Ah!
Pretty good.
That was my boob.
Was it?
Yep.
OK, second question.
Where are your parents?
They live in England.
My dad's a pilot.
Why didn't you go with 'em?
Fuck living in England.
I've never been.
Mmm.
OK, I'll give you another question,
'cause the first one...
It's kind of like backyard cricket.
You got out for a golden duck.
Alright.
So how long have you been
on the ship for?
For six months.
No sex for six months?
(LAUGHS)
That's a bit of
a personal question, isn't it?
I'm an open kind of person
to questions like that.
Six months. No, um...
No sex.
What's your favourite position?
On top, 'cause there's more con...
I like to be in control.
Yeah, right.
You?
Um...
Behind for sailors, wouldn't it be?
Oh, come on.
No, I like to definitely
be on the bottom.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What's the most unusual place
you've ever had sex?
Um...
Hopefully, not on the ship.
That means you'd swing both sides.
Probably...
In my mum's bed, I would say.
Not with my mum, though.
Yeah. I hope not.
Yeah.
OK, my first question. That wasn't
counted. That was a warm-up.
Um...
Well, how long, um...
When do you ship out?
Tomorrow morning.
But I'm... I'm... I'm not.
So you're stationed here?
Nah, I'm just, um...
I'm not going.
You were meant to say,
"At first light."
And then I say,
"Well, let's not waste time."
I'm not a... I'm not a coward.
Who said you were a coward?
No, I know.
I'm just saying that I'm...
I'm saying I'm not...
OK, well, my third question.
If you're not such a coward,
why haven't you made a move?
Alright, uh...
I'm gonna take my third question.
You don't have another question.
I do. I had the cricket duck thing.
Do you want me to make a move?
Um, what are four things
you don't like in life?
Heights. I don't like...
No, no, fuck off. Don't do...
Don't do that. Don't do that.
Sorry. Sorry.
Um... Sharks.
But you're on a boat.
Yeah, I know. I'm on the boat.
I'm not in the water with...
Don't you go fishing?
You ever caught a shark?
No, I've never caught a sh...
Uh... spiders and...
This... this question, to be honest,
I really don't know what to say.
OK.
What about you?
Uh, chocolate cake. Overrated.
You don't like chocolate...
No. Not at all.
Everyone likes chocolate cake.
Yeah, no, not me.
Um, flowers. They're already dead
when someone gives them to you.
Just a boring present. Like,
I'd rather get something than flowers.
Um...
Olives.
Alright.
Acquired taste.
Alright. Well, I won't get you...
I won't get you, what, chocolate cake,
flowers and, um, olives.
And...
...weddings.
(LAUGHS) And I'll never
propose to you. There you go.
Don't fucking do that.
Don't. Seriously.
Sorry.
It's alright.
So you definitely won't propose now.
No, I'm not.
So, what's this?
What?
This.
Like... like, what?
Like, that. What,
do you take all guys up here?
What do you think I do,
bring guys here and...
...sit on top of them or something?
(LAUGHS) On top of them?
Is that what?
Have you taken me up here to?
Fat chance.
Alright.
Oh, that's a shame.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, game over.
The food was great, by the way.
It was awesome.
That final truffle was just like...
when you think...
It's about layers. Should see
the food we eat on the fucking ship.
It was delicious food.
We call it scran.
"Shit cooked by
the Royal Australian Navy."
(MAN LAUGHS)
Come on, Lady Luck.
Yeah.
HARRY: OK.
It's alright. I'll lick it up.
Four for me, thanks, John.
Ahh!
JOHN: Here you go.
(HARRY COUGHS)
I'm fine.
JOHN: You want no cards?
You want to keep going?
Put 50 on this hand.
Yeah.
Oh! You put this in?
OK.
Hang on.
I've got two fives.
What have you got?
You can't. You've got to go in.
Let's see what you've got.
Oh, OK.
Motherfucker.
Fucking...
Does that mean that's all mine?
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks.
First time I saw Harry do this,
I was like, "It's full-on."
DEAN: Mate, all we do out there
is play cards.
Is that right?
Yeah.
'Cause your mate looks like
he doesn't know what he's doing.
HARRY: I just watch.
I'm like the mascot.
Pour myself one first.
Oh, no, dickhead.
No, you pour everyone else first,
then you pour yourself.
Shut up, dickhead.
When you deal cards it's the same thing.
You deal everyone else
and then you deal yourself last.
You pour everyone...
Go and deal your mum one, alright?
HARRY: I'm not touching this one.
I'm growing a beard. Um...
Um... You have to ask for permission
to grow a beard.
And, um...
MAN: Yep?
Yeah, you go to the CO -
the commanding officer -
and you say, "Can I grow a beard?"
And they give you two weeks.
You stop shaving.
And then two weeks later,
you go to the CO and, uh...
They say, "Can you shave that
scraggly shit off your face, mate?"
Absolutely. Yeah. So...
Yeah, well, I actually just
asked permission two days ago
just so I could have the shadow
for the chicks.
I'm gonna shave tomorrow.
I want a break.
Top call.
I'm happy to push on through.
I'm not. Drink up.
(SLURRED) Are you trying
to get me drunk?
Occifer, I didn't mean it.
HARRY: Oh! Ah!
Who's dealing?
You can handle another one?
MAN: We're having a break, dickhead.
You shut up, dickhead.
HARRY: No, no, no, that's fine.
You can talk to me, alright?
MAN: Pathetic.
HARRY: Ooh, burns the lips.
MAN: Oh, beautiful.
It's good stuff - the best.
That went down pretty easy?
Can I pinch one of them?
When you're done?
Sure.
Here you go, mate.
What about your other mate?
He doesn't like poker?
DEAN: Sam? Nah, hates it.
No, he can't stand it.
His mum's a gambling addict,
actually.
Not cards. Yeah, like...
betting on the football, whatever.
Yeah?
It's tragic.
Do not talk about gambling around Sam.
MAN: Fair enough.
DEAN: Someone say there were
some girls coming or something...
Not that I'm...
I'm engaged, actually.
Not that that stops anyone.
But... Yeah, I'm not being...
Why are you so jumpy, mate?
HARRY: He's late.
He's late for
a very important date.
Ship's comedian, this one.
Grab some coffee, Dean.
WOMAN: Hello, boys.
Hey!
Ladies!
How are you?
JOHN: Esther and Kristy,
this is Dean and Harry.
Kristy? Esther?
Kristy.
WOMAN: Esther.
Esther! Hello, Esther.
Aren't you meant to stand up for us?
Sorry. You're right. We are.
Pleased to meet you, boys.
Do you want to sit down?
It's alright. I'll sit on your lap.
JOHN: So where's Emma?
Is that your hat?
You're not...
Where's Emma?
...attached to any of these...
KRISTY: Esther, where's Emma?
Illegal.
No, they're just the boys.
MAN: Oh, just the boys.
Just the boys, the boys.
KRISTY: Esther,
stop being such a hussy.
Where's Emma?
She's with the other one.
Where the fuck is she?
MAN: It's cool.
What do you mean, where is she?
MAN 2: Oi. Oi.
Don't fucking "oi" me.
I've been playing cards
here with you.
Oh, stop being such a hussy.
MAN: She's in the restaurant, John.
Look at you.
When he's looking at ya,
that's when he's interested
in what you're saying.
Was he looking at you?
Was I talking to you? No.
No. No. No.
No. Fucking dickhead.
Exactly. I don't know where Emma is.
Girls, want to find Emma, bring her
back in here, for just a minute?
Would you? Go find Emma,
bring her back in.
Dickhead.
JOHN: Thanks.
WOMAN: See you, boys.
Thanks.
HARRY: Ah!
DEAN: They'll be back, mate.
DEAN: Sam's a totally
respectable guy, John,
if that's, you know, what's...
He's completely honourable. Yep.
He might be a virgin, for all I know.
So are you guys
going to the Gulf or what?
Par 40.
Pass by it. Yeah.
MAN: You see some action?
Yeah, a bit.
Yep?
MAN 2: What sort?
Skirmishes, mainly. Pirates.
We saw a fucking fishing boat, Dean.
He was so excited. This is
his most exciting day on the ship.
...to talk about it.
We saw a boat.
That he thought was a pirate boat.
He ordered the side-arms out.
Basically, things
that the militia can't handle...
...falls to us.
HARRY: Like fishing boats.
MAN: No pirates, huh?
They're out there.
And it's part of our job
to keep our eyes peeled for 'em.
Yeah, yeah, Captain Bluebeard,
Yellowbeard, Blackbeard...
Yeah, I could have
gone over there too, yeah.
ASIO, they wanted me.
Where? ASIO doesn't go to war.
How do you know
ASIO wanted you exactly?
Because they came to our school.
Came to your school?
High school, yeah.
ASIO came to your high school?
When was that?
'92.
'92, was it?
Well, it was right after
Gulf the prequel, yeah.
(MEN LAUGH)
Episode one.
Exactly.
So, you know, they were
talking about spies in Australia
and what to look out for and whatnot,
and this ASIO dude told me
that I had the right kind of profile
to be a political assassin.
Dickhead. Dickhead.
ASIO don't have assassins.
Who you calling dickhead, dickhead?
You.
ASIO don't have assassins?
That's what they
want you to believe.
I was fucking in every fucking class
you were in, Tony.
I never saw any ASIO dudes. Bullshit.
Bullshit, bullshit.
He told me if I channelled myself
into some kind of focus,
I could have been
one of the best ever, in the world.
That's pretty good.
Thank you.
There was no fucking ASIO dude,
dickhead!
Fucking drop it!
Told me that if I channelled...
Settle the fuck down,
will you, please, for fuck's sake!
Maybe Tony wanted to play
with the ASIO dude's Glock.
(MEN LAUGH)
I didn't... (MUMBLES)
It's fucking true.
HARRY: Yeah. I'm...
Not that part.
No, no, no. I was more...
Nothing.
So did you guys ever kill anybody?
It's not something we talk about.
What's the matter? You get like?
Bad flashbacks or...
Shut the fuck up, Tony.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's a legit question.
MAN: Sorry, bad question.
Bad question.
HARRY: It's cool, man.
No, no, 'cause my grandfather
was in the Italian army.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Like 50 million years ago. But...
I won't go into the boring details.
(COUGHS) Bullshit. (SNIFFS)
Shut the fuck up, Tony.
Oh.
No, no, but, you know.
50 medals later, he did alright.
Did really well.
(TONY COUGHS) Bullshit.
But he never wanted to talk about it.
Can we just play cards?
Do you mind, mate?
It didn't fucking happen.
It fucking happened, mate.
You just need to shut the fuck up!
Will you shut the fuck up?!
(SILENCE)
What have you got?
My 50's in.
Can I borrow another 50?
OK. It's in the ledger.
Thanks.
So are you sober enough
for this, Tony, or what?
JOHN: Want two?
Don't need to be, playing you, V.
Hey. At least I've got some left.
Yeah? Dickhead.
Four for me, John.
How many do you want?
Uh, no.
MAN: I'll get off your mum later.
You're fine?
I'm right.
I betcha.
You what?
How many do you want?
Fuck it! Three.
That's a wicked poker face he's got.
Mate, I'm jinxed. I'm telling you.
You're on.
Not yet. Gotta wait for Tony
to bet, check or fold.
What are you gonna do?
Come on, dickhead. Good game.
Quick game.
Tony folds. I fold.
HARRY: I'm going to raise...
Bet.
Bet?
I'm gonna bet the three.
JOHN: 300?
Mm-hm.
You got a streak on, do you?
Is that alright?
Are you kidding me?
What about you, sunshine?
Fucking out.
Owe you 50, owe you 250.
Do you need to borrow it?
I'm right, mate.
I'll win it back in a sec.
OK.
Let's see ya.
Let's see, mate.
Fuck me.
I'm getting sick of this shit.
I'm getting really pissed off.
How the fuck did you do that?
Is that good?
That'll be a flush.
That is fucking bullshit.
OK.
Hey, Johnny. I can't find her.
I'll just be back in a sec.
I'll come with you.
No, it's alright. You stay here.
I wasn't asking permission, mate.
I hope you and I
can stay friends, Harry.
With that in mind,
I think I'll pick up my winnings.
TONY: You can't just call it quits.
No, no, bullshit.
Mate, you're fucking ahead.
Bad sportsmanship. You know it.
Wait, you're leaving the table?
Are you going to the toilet?
If you are, you can leave the table.
If not, then you can't if no-one...
Is that right? You making
the fucking rules, are you, sunshine?
Harry, for Christ's sake.
Leave the money. Let's go find Sam.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't want
any trouble, but... You understand?
Yeah, no, fair enough.
OK. He's got a point.
No, it's alright. It's alright.
You can take the fucking money.
You won it fair and square.
I just want to know how you did it.
You weren't cheating.
I can tell that.
What were you doing?
You were counting them?
Magician never tells.
Well, you can tell me.
Some people just win at cards.
I don't think you understand.
See, I'm seriously asking you
to tell me.
It's fine. You won the money.
You can walk out of here,
both of you, no problem, no trouble.
Just tell me how you did it,
that's all. What is it?
Luck.
I found her. Fucking the other sailor
up on the roof.
You fucking arsehole!
Where's my other 100?
(BOTH ARGUE)
Whoa! Hey, yo!
Here we go.
Oi!
Arggh!
Jesus!
Shit!
Sammy!
Sam! Fuck!
Shit!
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ow!
Arsehole!
Shithead.
Hey!
(SHOUTS)
Ow!
(YELLS)
Go! Go!
Fuck!
Shit!
Go, go, go!
JOHN: Hey, come here...
Taxi! Taxi!
Shit!
Emma!
Hey! Emma!
Get in! Get in! Get in!
Give him the money!
Come here! Come here!
Fuck!
HARRY: Dean the ma-fucking-chine.
I did not think
we were gonna make it, man.
HARRY: Cheers, brother.
DEAN: No sweat.
HARRY: You should have seen him,
Sammy. Fists of steel.
So was the little waitress
worth all that, Sam?
EMMA: Oh, well, you'd hope so,
wouldn't you?
What the fuck's she doing here?
Hi. Sorry, ma'am.
Hi.
What the fuck's she doing here?
Poor Johnny's such a wannabe.
Can my jaw disagree with you?
DEAN: What is she doing here?
SAM: Have a small adventure
until we ship out in the morning.
A small adventure?
Fisher!
I shouldn't have told you guys.
Jake-O told me 'cause he was pissed
and you guys took it seriously.
Stole over a grand off 'em.
Stole over a grand off your cousin.
Just keep it on the hush-hush.
I'll make it worth your while.
I knew I shouldn't
have told you guys.
You should ignore him, by the way.
Well, am I in the way?
No, hardly, ma chérie!
And don't trust this one at all.
No, I don't think I should.
DEAN: We're supposed to meet them
at a Japanese restaurant.
HARRY: The gang, are they?
DEAN: Sally, Fred and Kathy.
Can you drop us
in the city somewhere?
Can you fuck them off for a while?
My fiancée.
HARRY: For Sammy. For an hour.
Guy fun, Dean.
HARRY: No, OK, for me, then.
Please don't leave me with Prince
and the fucking showgirl back here.
Oh! I got a better idea, Harry.
Why don't you go with Dean?
And Sam and I can go back
to his hotel room.
I think that's a terrible idea.
That is a great idea.
Sounds like the plan, Stan.
Your vote doesn't count, sweetheart.
Says who?
DEAN: Sammy, I want you to meet her.
Oh, for fuck's sake, Dean!
Why would it be necessary
for me to meet your fiancée
and her fucking parents?
Why would I need to do that?
How about this?
How about we all get out in the city,
Dean goes and has
the Partridge Family wet dream
and you, me and the delectable Emma
all go have really fancy
motherfucking cocktails.
HARRY: How does that sound?
SAM: Cocktails it is.
Cocktails it fucking is.
Friend of mine got beaten up
in Hyde Park, by 15 guys.
A friend of mine did.
Yeah, right.
1515-year-olds.
They asked for his wallet.
He gave them his wallet.
Then they beat the shit out of him.
Doesn't matter if they're 15.
If there's 15 of them, you're rooted.
You don't get that in Perth.
How was Sam in the taxi?
Never seen him like that before.
Yeah, it's good.
Something's up, I reckon.
Yeah, his dick.
Speaking of which, do I have you
as my wingman later this evening,
or are you being all dedicated?
I'm always dedicated.
What was Tokyo?
Shut the fuck up about Tokyo.
It was fun.
Be nice to have one last hurrah.
Yeah, it would,
with my fucking girlfriend.
Fiancée.
Shut up.
Harry.
EMMA: Come on! Catch up to me!
Heh-hey! Are you OK
running in those shoes?
Yeah, they're flat but hard.
If I had flat shoes on
like you, though...
Well, I'm not carrying you.
How much fitness
do you have to do in the...
Well, it obviously hasn't paid off.
What the fuck am I doing?
Let's go faster.
Did you see a navy guy come down
here, an officer? Brown hair?
Yeah, running.
With a blonde girl?
Where? This way?
Excuse me.
Have you seen, like,
another officer anywhere?
About this tall, with a blonde girl?
No.
No?
OK. Thanks anyway.
MAN: We'd see a uniform, though.
Yeah, good point.
Fucking arsehole.
Sammy!
Emma!
Who's Emma?
Who's... The fucking waitress. Emma!
What part of Scotland are you from?
Glasgow.
OK. Cool. I'm not
walking with you at all. You...
Have a good night. See ya.
Not at all? OK. Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
If you see him, his name's Sam.
Have you seen
another navy officer around?
Tell him he's in big trouble.
Thank you very much.
Sort of Italian-Iooking.
No.
Alright. Cheers.
I'd do her, but...
What, the Scottish one?
No.
I mean even the kind of
50s blonde bob one.
You're nuts.
He's off fucking someone.
What we should be doing.
Sammy!
Are you off fucking someone?
Dean.
He's scarpered. He's bolted.
You keep saying that
like it's a new idea.
Bad-bad or just bad?
Um...
Oh, alright.
I cried in f...
I cried in front of the whole crew.
Well, everyone.
Oh, that's bad.
Yeah, I know.
I cried like a little girl.
Baby.
Like a baby girl,
in front of the whole crew.
That's not funny. That's sad.
Where do you, um...
where do you sleep on the ship?
Bottom or top bunk?
What's it to you?
I reckon you'd go bottom bunk.
Am I top or bottom?
Yeah, you'd be bottom bunk.
What about you?
What are you doing here? Huh?
What, lying in the middle of the park
with a sailor?
Yeah.
I don't know. Pretty cute.
Alright.
But I've never lied in a park
with a sailor before.
Well, that's good.
That's good to know.
Yeah.
Neither have I.
I can live with that.
The uniform's
actually quite nice. Yeah.
So you'll just go wherever...
Yeah.
Anywhere?
No.
Not Ukraine.
Yeah?
Uruguay.
Um... Yugoslavia.
OK.
Just all the 'U' countries.
Yeah, right.
Both of those.
What could you possibly
have against...
Nothing. I just don't... Yeah.
That's none of my business.
And also Rotorua, New Zealand.
I went there on a soccer tour,
and it...
It's, like, got egg gases.
Smells like fart.
(LAUGHS)
What about you?
Do you speak any other languages?
No.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
No?
Can you do that again?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
What are you saying?
"What would you like me to say?"
Oh.
I was hoping... Yeah, OK.
Some dirty French?
Mmm.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Uh, that is really sexy.
Really?
Yeah. It's really sexy.
Well, I actually said...
No, I won't tell you.
What?
Ask me something
and I'll tell you how to say it.
And then you've got to say it
with a French accent.
Um...
"Will you..." (LAUGHS)
"Will you kiss me?"
Did you think I was gonna say that?
Yeah.
Est-ce...
No, um... Oh.
Uh... Well, 'je t'embrasse'
is to kiss.
Like, "I kiss you." So...
So... you'd say, "C'est possible,"
"It's possible,"
or... (SPEAKS FRENCH)
Dunno.
Did I make you up?
I mean... Am I... am I insane?
Two separate questions.
Probably... Yeah. No. Yes.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Sorry. That was really stupid.
Just 'cause I'm speaking French
that you can kiss me?
Oh, yeah. I wanted to
before that. But...
Really? When?
I think... like, a good...
...the kind of the second I, um...
Shut up. Shut up.
Mmm.
Awkward.
(LAUGHS)
What if it's more like a...
No, OK. That's it.
Two strikes.
That won't... That won't...
Well, I'm gonna save the last one
for the...
Yeah. So we'II... That batter
just didn't go up to bat.
OK.
Just went home.
So I got... one more go.
So two strikes.
Yeah.
OK.
You could bunt, though.
I could bunt?
Yeah.
I would really like...
You could do a Sax,
like running squeeze or push bunt.
I would love to bunt you.
Would you?
Anyway, I don't have any money.
I've only got, like, $40. So...
Maybe we might have to go down
to, like, Wollongong or something.
But I do have a car.
There...
There's something I have to do first.
About this tall. Brown hair.
With a blonde girl.
Looks a bit Italian-ish.
This kind of uniform.
No?
Could I wear your hat?
HARRY: No. Sorry,
that's against regulations.
Do you want a photo?
With you.
With me? You want a photo? OK.
Sure. We got time for a photo?
I'll definitely sign you.
BOTH: Me too?
Rose between two thorns?
Anywhere? On the fun stuff?
It's been six months.
OK.
You can't spell your name, Harry?
You've got to press it.
Oh, I was talking. Let's do it again.
What about kissing each cheek?
Dean! Hello, Dean.
DEAN: Yeah, goodo.
You like a, um, s... sail man.
Hey. He's been on the ship
for six months. So...
Good work, guys. Keep on sailing.
Would you give him a kiss?
HARRY: You happy?
GIRL: Yep.
OK. You haven't seen our friend?
The navy guy?
GIRLS: No.
No. OK.
You're very pretty, by the way.
Thank you!
You really are. You're very pretty.
You're very handsome too.
Fucking hell. Did you see that?
Did you see that?
I took a photo of it.
(LAUGHS)
That was fun.
They were pretty cute.
They're 12.
Old enough to bleed,
old enough to butcher.
Grass on the wicket,
right to play cricket.
(SNORTS) You've got it in you. See?
You have got it in you.
Sorry to interrupt.
Sorry to... interrupt.
Excuse me. Have you seen
a, uh... a navy officer?
Brown hair.
With a blonde girl.
Not RAN?
Can you tell him
he's in big trouble?
So, what, you just sit down?
When you get dumped on
every single day, Dean,
you get real good
at making yourself invisible.
Where are we meeting your fiancée?
Um, Juju's.
Great.
No idea where it is.
Awesome.
SONG: # Don't hold back
# Is there anybody out there
# Feeling something?
# Don't hold back
# Is there anybody out there
# Feeling something? #
(TURNS MUSIC DOWN)
What are you doing?
It's the best song.
Turn it back up.
(TURNS MUSIC UP)
# 'Cause I want to watch you
taking off your... #
(TURNS MUSIC OFF)
Well, go on, then.
Go on, what?
Tell me a story
if there's gonna be no music.
Um... Alright, uh...
Alright, um, can you slow down
just a tiny bit, do you mind? Cheers.
I worked with my grandad
until I signed up.
He's 84 and he still...
he still runs the local leagues club.
Uh, I managed...
Just a bit. Slow... Sorry. Sorry.
I managed... I managed
the bar there for a bit until, um...
...until I was fired
by my own grandad.
And... that's...
Dad. No, Dad fucked off
when I was two.
So it was just me, Mum and Pop.
That... that's kind of it. I'm sorry.
It's not very exciting.
Yeah, I think you should get out.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
OK, very funny. Come on.
Can we go, please?
No.
Come on.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, come on, it wasn't that hard.
No, it's...
It's just one of, um...
one of Glenn's favourite spots.
Well, that's fucked.
I didn't know that.
(LAUGHS)
Oh! What was that?
Oh! Oh, OK, stop! Stop!
Alright, alright, alright. You win,
you win, you win. Stop, please!
Oh!
OK, I'll show you something.
Oh, come on. We've got to go.
I'm not doing that. Don't worry.
Oh, please.
Watch.
An audition for
'Hey Hey It's Saturday'.
Do you want me to
play you a tune up my nose?
(PLAYS TUNE)
Alright, that is disgusting.
Can we please go?
Emma, please.
Come on. OK, OK. I'm very impressed.
But, please, can we just go
and stay within the, um...
...within the, uh, speed limit?
Yeah.
Would be good.
(PLAYS NOTE)
No.
Do you have any other
tricks with this?
No, not for now.
Really?
Right.
(PLAYS NOTE)
(COINS CLINK)
(PRESSES BUTTONS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, Mrs Fisher. Hi.
It's Harry McCabe here.
I met you last Christmas.
I'm a friend of Sam's.
Yeah. Have you, um...
have you heard from Sam tonight?
Right. Did he say
where he was going?
No. Yeah. No, no, that's...
that's... That's kind of...
Yeah, no, that...
That's kind of why I'm calling.
We've just worked that out.
He's not... I'm gonna find him
before they get to him.
I will find him.
I love him too.
Mrs Fisher, crying's
not gonna get us anywhere.
It...
Mrs Fisher.
Did he say to you where he was going?
Any friends or family?
Mate, you got any coins?
Mrs Fisher...
Mate, come on.
Mrs F... Fuck off.
Mrs Fisher. Fuck off.
OK. Mrs Fisher, seriously...
OK. I'm sorry. I'm gonna have to...
Harry McCabe. We met last Christmas.
I had the...
I threw up... That's...
That's the one.
Yeah, with the funny moustache.
Mrs...
I'm gonna have to go.
I gotta find him. OK?
Mrs Fisher?
Please stop...
Mrs Fisher!
Mrs...
(COINS CLINK)
So everyone's looking at me,
and I'm like, "It's not Jake's fault.
"He's never been in Bangkok before."
(MAN AND WOMAN LAUGH)
Well, money's like that, you know.
You couldn't trust your own brother
when it comes to money.
I mean...
Well, think about Cain and Abel.
KATHY: Oh, Cain and Abel
wasn't about money, Fred.
FRED: Yeah, well, I mean...
KATHY: That was love.
FRED: It's the same thing
in the world today.
Hey.
Ooh! Hello.
Ah, there we are. We've been chatting
up some chicky babe, have we?
Squash in here.
Bet you were, Harry. I bet he was.
Took your time.
Ah, you've got to take your time
with the ladies, Dean.
He wasn't talking to a girl, Fred.
You're so negative.
Oh, have some more food.
No, you have some more food.
Anyway, Harry, so Dad's company
just bought some cargo ships.
And he needs two guys
to be in charge.
And he said you and Dean
can take over when you get back.
Wow! That...
Yeah.
Catch me up on all that, Fred.
No, no.
HARRY: Terrific.
Absolutely.
There's jobs for the boys. Um...
You don't have to worry about that.
Yes, because I'm sure
the first thing they want to do
is get straight back on a ship.
Yeah, well, they may have a taste
for it. They've found their sea legs.
Oh, you do whatever you want, Dean.
No pressure, love.
I'm actually thinking about
studying something like that.
(LAUGHS LOUDLY)
Sorry.
Sally, don't be like that.
Sorry!
No, just thinking about it.
Like, what would you study?
I was thinking law or something.
(LAUGHS)
Sally!
Sorry.
It's not fair.
Mum, he... Come on,
you hated university.
I mean, what, did you turn up
for, like, two weeks
and they never saw you again?
So who's talked you into this?
No-one.
Don't you listen
to the peanut gallery, Dean.
She won't mind spending
a lawyer's pay cheque, rest assured.
Oh, sweetie.
He can be homeless as long
as he kisses me like that.
Show-off.
So, what do you do
for a crust, Sally?
Oh, I'm a social worker.
Of course you are.
Yeah. Kids...
Sorry? Pardon?
Oh, no, I, uh...
Just the whole package. It's...
Smart, sexy, funny
and you help the underprivileged.
It's exactly what I pictured
Dean having.
Right, and, um, clearly
you're the smart-arse friend
who always gets him into trouble
and then takes the credit
for getting him out of it again.
I like you.
Oh, and he doesn't have me.
Oh, you're good. She's good.
And what do you do
on the ship, Harry?
Um, communications.
Oh.
Oh. What about for a crust?
See? You're feisty.
She's feisty. I really...
I, um... I was a schoolteacher.
I signed up after 9/11.
Really? What did you teach?
Mathematics.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(GASPS) Oh!
Look at you.
Hey, Mum.
Oh, Sam!
Yeah.
What are you trying to do, kill me?
I had your friend calling at all hours.
I haven't slept a wink.
You're not coming in.
I am coming in.
No, you're not. He's not well, Sam.
No, Mum, I want to see him.
He's not well enough.
Well, we came to see you guys.
Oh.
I brought him up
to have no manners.
I'm Sam's mum.
Hey, Ms Fisher.
Bernie, Bernie.
Not Bernie Bernie, just Bernie.
Sense of humour from his late father.
Dad's not dead.
Is that right?
Mum, this is Emma.
Hey, Bernie.
Come in.
Can't have a lovely young girl
like you
standing out there like
you're flogging insurance.
Ooh!
(LAUGHS)
Close the door, Sam.
See what he does to me?
I haven't even got any face on.
Oh. Hope I look as good as you
after I've had a brat like Sam.
(SOFTLY) Let's keep our voices down.
How old do you think I am, Emma?
Oh...
Don't answer that.
I'll just imagine the answer.
Do you prefer Em or Emma?
Either/or. My friends call me Em,
so you can call me Em.
You hungry?
No, I've actually worked in a kitchen
all night, so I'm kind of over food.
Tea or coffee? Something stronger?
MAN: What's all this bloody hoo-ha?
Oh, God.
No bloody sleep as it is,
and when I finally bloody drift off,
it's disturbed by bloody strangers.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, Pop.
Oh! How are you? Good to see you.
You too. You look great.
Cover yourself up, Dad!
Oh, hello!
Bob Fisher, Sam's feeble old
grandfather. Pleased to meet you.
Pop, this is Emma.
Sorry it's so late.
This isn't late.
You've come to a party house!
BERNIE: Yeah, rage a minute.
(BOB LAUGHS)
Come on.
(LAUGHS)
Come on, Emma.
Help me with the drinks.
It's a new millennium, Bern.
Why don't you ladies
go and put your feet up
while the men go hunt and gather?
He's just trying
to impress you, Emma.
Don't you burn down
my kitchen again, Dad.
You what?
(SPEAKS CANTONESE)
No, no, no, look.
What I'm saying is, my name is
down there, and I'm ready to do it.
I don't want to have
an argument with you. OK?
No, no, no...
No, no...
Do you think I need
to come and step in?
Oh, my God.
I'm happy to.
HARRY: Dean.
If you guys...
HARRY: Yeah. I mean...
He is so embarrassing.
I know.
He's just so uncultural.
Yeah, no, no. Speak English, OK?
(SPEAKS CANTONESE)
Look. You...
Watch it, now. Watch it.
I'm sorry, but I think this is
getting a little bit out of control.
I'm next on here, and I'm pissed off.
Hey! Hey! Come over here.
HARRY: Come. Come, come.
Come over here. Look. Look at this.
I spoke to... Come here.
How you doing?
SALLY: You know what?
HARRY: Can they squeeze in here?
Oh, well, just...
Sorry. Sorry, no.
KATHY: I'm sorry, girls.
HARRY: What is your name?
Hang on. It's OK. What's your name?
KATHY: I'm sorry, girls.
Anna.
He's taking no notice.
His name's down there.
And my name is next. OK?
Excuse me. I'm quite
uncomfortable about this.
With the contact?
She's got her hand on your leg.
Anna! You...
What, are you trying
to break up some...
This is a beautiful relationship.
KATHY: I'm just having a hot flush.
I love it, Anna. I love it.
Yeah. You tell him to
go and sit down for a minute.
Sorry? What language
are you speaking now?
Can you show Dean...
show Dean your butterfly?
Can you show your butterfly?
What butterfly?
You know what butterfly.
You know exactly what butterfly
I'm talking about.
Show him the butterfly.
Dean. Check the butterfly out.
KATHY: Oh!
DEAN: Oh!
Do you know what?
It's quite beautiful.
DEAN: Inappropriate.
Do you have any butterflies, Anna?
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
Yeah. Yeah, right. Yeah.
Well, I don't think
we'll be coming here again.
Sally! Come on, don't play that role.
That's not a fun... That's not fun.
That's not fun at the dinner table.
KATHY: That's lovely.
That's very attractive.
HARRY: I'll tell you what.
I'll tell you what.
What if we got a little, like...
Dean! Check this out.
See what I'm saying?
OK.
See how it feels?
Yeah, it's terrible.
HARRY: It's all a little party.
You're not studying? What do you do?
You just go over there,
sit down and wait,
and I'll be a few minutes, right?
OK, yep. See you. OK.
Yep. Piss off. Piss off.
Oh.
I've been wanting a good burger
for six months, Pop.
Uh-huh.
How's the club?
Mum said you might be expanding.
(SNORTS)
You still cleaning up after Simon?
Simon's a good man.
Yeah, I know.
Hard worker.
Yeah, but...
You know, you always say that he's...
I know what I always say.
I always say it.
But it's not for you to say, though.
I'm probably gonna
be made petty officer, Pop.
What's that?
I'm... I'm gonna be made
petty officer.
Probably.
You're joking, mate.
Nope.
I was petty officer.
I know. Why do you think
I requested the position?
(LAUGHS) Hey, that's terrific.
My boy the petty officer.
Oh, they'll love that,
Simon and the lads.
(LAUGHS) Really stick it to 'em.
Don't... don't tell Mum
until it's all definite, though.
You're a good kid.
You've got a great smile.
What are you talking about?
(LAUGHS)
Get your hand off it
and pass me the bloody onions.
So, what's this problem
with you, Fred?
FRED: Just argumentative, you know.
I mean, he can speak
perfectly good English,
but it's that thing, he just wanted
to, um, make me think that, um,
I couldn't understand him.
I knew perfectly well that he was
trying to jump the queue there.
SALLY: Dad! You're horrible!
FRED: Was I?
Deano.
Eye on the time, Harry.
I think we should...
What's going on with you two?
You got some...
Couple of hot dates or something?
Gotta go meet Monica and Anna.
(HARRY AND SALLY LAUGH)
DEAN: No, it's just, um...
HARRY: It's just... our friend.
Yeah.
What?
HARRY: Uh, he's with a girl.
Oh, who's with a girl?
That's who I was talking to on the
phone before. He's gone somewhere.
We've got to go
get him now, actually.
DEAN: Going through a bit of a rough
time and they're strict on rollcall.
He's a really great bloke, actually.
Wish you guys could have met him.
But he's...
Excuse the salty language.
He's a bit of a fucking drop kick.
DEAN: He's had a rough time.
Look, the XO took a... (COUGHS)
...dislike to him, and, um...
Can leave it at that.
Yeah, well.
FRED: What, a little man
with a big dollop of power?
That's it, Fred.
Had one in the academy.
The academy?
Fred wasn't a bang-bang copper.
I was in records, actually.
Uh! I didn't say that.
(LAUGHS)
Because of his hip.
Filing, mostly.
It was his hip.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I have a wonky hip.
Thank you, Kath.
No, there was this guy.
He was named Trevor Sinclair.
Oh, God, Trevor Sinclair!
Yeah, well, he was
the drill instructor.
Can't remember anything about
the ugly-Iooking prick's face
apart from the fact
that he had this great big vein
that ran right down
the middle of his forehead, right,
and it would pulsate
every time he screamed at me.
You're being quite random, Fred.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
OK. So, uh, yeah. Anyway.
What's happened? Has your friend
gone AWOL or something?
If you say that, he gets arrested.
I don't think anyone can hear me.
Is he in trouble or something?
What goes on at sea stays at sea.
Oh, and other shite, Dean.
You know, I think you should tell us.
Oh, come on. We want to hear it.
Come on.
They want to hear it.
Shut up, Harry.
Come on. They want to hear it.
We want to hear it.
Yeah, you should tell them, actually.
KATHY: Who are we gonna tell?
HARRY: Yeah, who are they gonna tell?
You tell us, then, Harry.
Alright, fine, I will tell you.
I don't think you'll tell anything.
Actually, I don't know what...
I just don't think
it's dinner conversation.
Oh, we've finished dinner,
so it doesn't matter. So just tell us.
He's protecting me.
He's so predictable.
We'll clear the table.
We're family, you know.
You're related, almost.
Tell you one of the tamer ones.
Uh... One of the ones I know, anyway.
KATHY: Good.
DEAN: It was Easter Sunday.
Sam was on laundry duty that week.
And he hadn't put the uniforms
in the dryer overnight.
So when he did 'em...
WOMAN: Some more sake, sir?
Yeah, bring it on.
Oh, great.
Thank you.
I might grab that.
Anyone? Anything?
DEAN: So when he did the uniforms
in the morning,
they all had that rotting damp smell.
KATHY: Mmm. Oh, God,
I hate that smell.
Right, and it's, like,
the officers' uniforms,
so they were off-the-charts angry.
And... Like, you have to ration,
you know, washing, showers, out there.
So they're walking around
in these uniforms all week
stinking like dead birds.
So two of us were ordered
to take Sam into the bathroom...
You?
HARRY: Deano? Mate.
And we ordered him to strip,
which he did, quickly.
And we cuffed him to the sink.
And we were given steel wool
and deck brushes,
which we used to scrub him down with
until he was bloody and raw.
They were the exact orders.
He didn't make a sound
the whole time.
And when it was done,
Glenn, the executive officer, and I,
urinated on the wounds.
Then we hosed him off,
put his uniform back on him,
took him back to his post.
So...
There. You happy now?
That's torture.
You're given an order and you take it,
otherwise you're next.
Dean did what any of us...
I mean, that's disgusting.
That's torture.
SALLY: Mum! Lay off him.
That's disgusting.
Lay off him! He just
told us something full-on.
He told us something disgusting.
That's absolutely disgusting.
Yeah, OK, and he gets an order
and he takes it.
That's an excuse. I'm sorry,
that is absolutely an excuse.
SALLY: Mum! Shut up!
FRED: It's the navy.
The navy, exactly.
It's the Royal... the Royal Navy!
Yeah, well, she's a monarchist.
Now, just settle down, Kath.
It happens everywhere.
It's a bit like Janine, you know...
Janine?
...when she was harassing you
at the pharmacy...
Oh, for heaven's sake,
it's nothing like that.
On a... you know,
on a different scale.
It's nothing like that.
On a different scale.
How can, um, we help, Deano?
KATHY: You know what you do? You...
You report him to the authorities
and you get him booted out quick smart.
FRED: No, no, you don't do that.
That is what you do!
That is what you do. Why not?
No, you don't.
Because the navy's like the force.
The force?!
Oh, God, give it a rest!
You don't go dobbing somebody in.
Shut up about the force!
Well, no wonder he's gone AWOL.
Don't fucking say AWOL.
Sorry, Kath.
HARRY: He's with a girl.
He's just... That's... the size of it.
He's with a girl.
Let's shoot from the hip.
KATHY: Oh, what, your wonky hip?
Your mate's a deserter.
Go look up the word 'torture', Fred.
Look, I'm just saying, that's the way
he will be treated if he's convicted.
Shit a brick, woman!
FRED: Ju... Look.
If he's gonna do the disappearing act,
he has to do it right, right?
That's all I'm saying to them.
Right? Not just the state.
He has to get out of
the whole bloody country.
I mightn't know much,
but I know that much.
Listen to Carl Bernstein over here.
Yeah, well, I would prefer to
refer to myself as Bob Woodward.
Thank you very much.
Well, you can't be Woodward,
'cause he's dishy.
KATHY: You get yourself
a top-shelf lawyer.
Just do that. You deny everything
and you just hope for the best.
That's what you do.
I'm sorry, I'm just a little bit...
I'm sorry, Dean, love, it's not
your fault. It's just that this...
I'll say a prayer for your friend.
Look.
I might be able to help him
get out of the country.
You and your wonky hip are gonna help,
are you, Fred? Oh, my God.
KATHY: Can we have the check?
HARRY: Let's get the check.
KATHY: Get the check.
Check!
The house is just getting
too big for us.
Losing the garden's
gonna kill me, naturally.
Are... are you gonna tell your mother?
Tell me what?
Oh. No, I don't really
want to show off, Pop.
He's been made petty officer.
Is that right?
It's not official yet.
Isn't that amazing?
Amazing's the word.
Hey, guess what. Did Sam tell you
when he caught a tiger shark?
Emma!
What's this?
Sam. Anyway, I'll tell the story,
'cause, you know, he's too modest.
So the boys have the day off
and so they're on the boat fishing.
And then after, like, an hour,
he notices something
on the end of the fishing rod,
like, pulling really hard.
And so as he goes to wind it in,
everyone starts to look around,
and it's a tiger shark.
And then naturally,
all the guys gather around
and try to, like, help him
and take the credit.
And Sam, like, shrugs them off
and says - my favourite part -
"No, boys, this is between
me and the sea."
(LAUGHS) That's my boy.
But I think they were kidding
when they said the captain
had it mounted in his cabin.
Emma!
You bloody dark horse!
So...
Tell me about you two.
SAM: Mum.
Where did you meet?
Mum.
A mother's entitled to know
about her son's love-life.
And a father's entitled
to know about his daughter's.
I like your hair.
Wouldn't have been regulation
in my day.
BERNIE: Better than the dreadlocks.
EMMA: Dreadlocks?
(GROANS)
She's very pretty.
Her name is Emma.
She's sitting
next to you, Mum.
Sam's pretty. Ha!
Hey, guys can be pretty too.
Sam's got pretty eyes. Like Bob's.
(LAUGHS) You can bring her again.
BERNIE: Oh, please!
What about some Scotch to celebrate?
Girls?
A little dabble?
EMMA: Sure.
Don't... don't go to any trouble.
No.
What's this game
you're playing, Sam?
Do you want to give him
another heart attack, do you?
Trying to make life
difficult for me?
Get back at me for something?
Come on, tell me!
I just wanted to see him happy.
For how long?
And I wanted you to be happy
'cause he was happy.
Happy for how long, Sam?
What happens when he...
You're a fool!
And now you're a fugitive. Lovely.
Bernie, you don't understand.
I don't like you.
Let's get that clear from the outset,
Miss Tiger Shark.
But, Bernie...
My name's Mrs Fisher.
Mrs Fisher, they tortured him.
He needs a bit of discipline.
Structure.
This... this wasn't structure, Mum.
When are you ever gonna finish
anything you start, Sam?
(SIGHS)
I'm not heartless.
Some people even think
I'm quite nice.
Well, that's not true,
but I can act nice.
It's just that whatever
Sam's involved in is an ordeal.
BOB: I've got the single malt.
EMMA: Wow!
So we can have a taste test.
No sex.
Going to parties by myself.
One email a month.
You've got no idea what it's like.
Yeah, it must be hard.
I feel terrible for you.
Hey! You signed up, not me.
Yep.
Just promise me
you'll be careful, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Hey.
Just... promise me
you'll remember me and...
...you'll remember you have
this great life waiting for you.
Life that's gonna be wonderful and...
...lucky and... full of love.
Mmm.
Just promise me.
Baby, I promise you.
Mmm.
I promise.
Yeah.
It's a different world out there.
It's like when you're at school,
you know -
like, the whole universe crumbles
if you haven't done
your French homework, you know?
'Cause that's all you know.
It's the same out there.
And when it's good...
baby, when they smile on ya,
life is roses.
Mmm.
(MAN SHOUTS)
(LAUGHS)
Alright. OK, kids. Alright, kids.
We alright? OK.
Uh! Uh! OK. Come on.
How about you, Harry?
You got a girlfriend?
No, thanks.
Mmm?
No, thank you.
What... what is it?
You've been heartbroken?
Is that what it is?
Mate, you're not. Are you gay?
No, thank you.
(LAUGHS) Oh, come on, tell us.
Me and Kath, we're good.
Very good.
Yeah, well, we're the leading lights
at our group therapy sessions.
Oh, Fred, he doesn't know.
What?
It's called couples rehabilitation.
(LAUGHS)
It's for people who've...
...had emotional and sexual trauma
in their relationships.
Yeah, OK. Look.
We started about six months ago.
And you wouldn't believe what a world
of difference, Harry, it's made.
Believe you me.
Good!
So, what is it, darling?
Once bitten, twice shy.
Is that it?
A handsome man like you
should be, um...
Kath!
...getting as much as you can.
OK, OK, OK.
Let's keep going. Keep going.
It's alright, it's alright.
No, no. It's OK. It's OK.
How far are we walking?
Just look at the fountain.
Hey! That's a great fountain.
Isn't that beautiful?
Those things that I did...
I don't care about what you did.
Just... It doesn't matter
to me, alright?
Yeah, babe...
Look...
Just... go find your friend.
OK?
Really?
Yeah.
I'II, um...
I'll just... I'll meet you
at the docks in, like, five hours.
Alright?
That'll give us 45 minutes
for you and me
plus, you know, 15 minutes travel time
to get you back for rollcall.
I've kind of got it all worked out.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, there's this,
like, long, dark street
two blocks over from
Harry's Cafe de Wheels.
Hello!
And I am bringing the station wagon.
I love you.
Well...
I just can't wait to see you
out of this uniform.
Oh, oh, oh!
OK, OK, OK.
Just a sec. I've got to throw up.
Yep. No, don't. No, no, no.
Let's keep walking.
You'll be fine. You'll be fine.
Oh, I feel great.
Absolutely fine.
We can have a shower in the fountain.
That'd be cool.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah.
Cool. (LAUGHS)
OK, OK. Alright.
Do you want to shower with me?
Uh, no.
Would you like to lather me? (LAUGHS)
Um, Deano, I think it's cab time
for these two.
Yeah, but I heard
what you were saying.
No.
What? I wasn't flirting!
That's my arm, Fred, not hers.
I said there was chemistry.
I didn't say we should
do anything about it.
Oh!
God! Oh!
KATHY: Whoa!
FRED: Jesus!
(LAUGHS)
Really sorry.
You right? You right?
Fuck. Yep.
HARRY: Fucking hell.
FRED: I thought it was funny.
Oh, Jesus!
You right?
DEAN: What have you done, McCabe?
HARRY: He's broken my fucking nose!
FRED: Oh, you're alright.
Have you hurt yourself?
(KATHY LAUGHS)
SALLY: Mum!
Come on, Kath. Get up. Shut up, Kath.
DEAN: You OK?
He's broken my fucking nose, man.
What'd you do?
He's broken my nose.
DEAN: Alright, Kath,
have you hurt anything?
Harry, Harry, Harry.
Did you look up my dress?
FRED: You right?
Here we go.
Hey, can you get a cab?
Yeah, sure.
KATHY: Leave me alone!
Mum!
Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
SALLY: Mum!
Do you mind getting
a cab or something?
SALLY: Fuck it.
It's alright. Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
I think... Jesus! Can we just not?
Dad. Dad. Can you just
control Mum, please?
SALLY: Dad!
DEAN: That's my mother-in-law.
HARRY: Yeah, I'd love one.
SALLY: Mum, go home with Dad.
You are embarrassing
the fuck out of me right now.
KATHY: Where is he?
You OK?
Can you just take Mum home?
You're not on medication
or anything like that, are you?
I have never been better.
I have never, ever...
(HARRY LAUGHS)
See, this is what it's done for us.
Watch this, now. You ready?
You watching?
You ready?
SALLY: Just leave them.
(LAUGHS)
Are you watching? Hey, hey, hey.
Yep.
FRED: This is how you do it.
Alright?
Awesome to meet you. Thanks, Sally,
for tonight. It's been great.
(GAGS AND RETCHES)
Is my nose crooked?
Please tell me
my fucking nose isn't crooked.
Let's go to the hotel.
Dean, this is the fucking end of
the monologue. Let's go to the hotel.
OK, this might sound about...
a bit, you know.
What if we go to shore patrol?
Yeah, it sounds ludicrous.
Jake's a mate.
Is anyone not your mate?
He might do us a favour
and keep it quiet.
Well, how is the weather
in Fools Paradise, Dean?
We could explain it to them.
Oh, we'd explain it to them? Great!
What would we say?
What's the first thing you'd say?
It's a thought.
Next thought, please.
Mm-hm.
No, here we go.
OK, we can't dillydally.
Dillydally?
What's wrong with dillydally?
(LAUGHS)
Mmm. (MUMBLES)
(ENGLISH ACCENT) Hi.
Hey.
Goodnight.
Got the time, mate?
Uh... yeah, it's, uh...
...2:27, on the dot.
So it's not midnight?
No. Nope.
Yeah, my watch must be...
Hang on, you're saying it's...
You're saying it's exactly two hours
and 27 minutes after midnight?
Yeah. (UNLOCKS DOOR)
Have a good one.
Yeah, I'll try.
Sam Fisher, yes?
Yeah.
We can do this out in the hallway
if you want, Sam.
I run a legitimate business.
I'm not ashamed.
No, mate. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Let me explain.
Come on.
See, one of the girls
is taking it personally,
like it's a rejection or something.
Girls? What... what girls, mate?
I mean, it's... That's just rude.
OK, look, you know what?
I reckon there's been some sort
of misunderstanding here. We're...
We're not the people you're after.
There's been some sort
of misunderstanding.
There's a cab as well. I mean,
you were supposed to pay for that.
OK.
I get here, meter's up to 70 bucks.
He's kept it running the whole time.
Can't blame him for that.
Totally understand.
Where's it coming from?
I reckon you've got
the wrong room.
Well, we do a callback as soon as
the order's made, chummy, so...
OK, look, you're out a lot of money.
I understand.
This has to be some sort of mistake.
EMMA: Just go back.
Emma, shut the fuck up, please,
please. You're not helping.
There's...
Yeah, there's been a mistake, Sammy.
(OPENS FRIDGE)
About 600 bucks' worth.
Oh, just help yourself for a drink.
Hey, it's all good.
You're not... You're not...
600 bucks - I'll let you off for 50,
seeing as I'll give the girls a lift home.
They won't need a cab. How's that?
Can't say fairer than that.
Yep. It's Harry. It's my friend.
It's my stupid fucking friend.
That's it. It's not me.
Oh, well, your stupid fucking friend
isn't here now, is he, Sammy?
Why don't you just go back?
Emma, it's all good.
Just shut the fuck up.
Just shut the fuck up, Emma.
Do yourself a favour.
Go back to fucking England,
you wanker.
I'll tell you what, you know,
for your information -
future reference and all -
uh, that pussy I was gonna get you
is far better than this.
Ooh! You've got balls,
have you, Popeye?
I'll tell you what,
you give me my 650
and we'll get 'em out,
we can all see.
Eh?
Look, just go home, seriously. Whoa!
I hope that wasn't your big guns.
(GASPS)
Hey.
Be a pal. Let me back in.
Back off, Sam. It's no good.
No, it's still there. Hey, mate!
(SLAPS)
No, Sam, go get a pillow.
Hey.
Hey, mate. Are you OK?
Tell me what to do.
Where do I put it?
Just underneath. Here. Hold on.
Mate, you OK?
Mmm.
Can you move your neck?
Yeah.
OK.
Sam, just calm down.
You OK, mate?
MAN: Yep.
Hey, do you know where you are?
Hote...
Yep.
No.
Hotel.
SAM: Yeah.
Yep.
What... what's your name?
It starts with a 'W'.
MAN: Warren.
Great. Fantastic, Warren.
EMMA: First go.
I'm one of the Wombles.
WARREN: Warren the Womble.
SAM: You're not
one of the Wombles, mate.
Who's your favourite Womble?
What year is it?
Mmm... Tomsk.
He's a big one.
SAM: What year is it, mate?
EMMA: What year? Hey.
Warren, concentrate.
Mmm... Orinoco?
SAM: No, what year... what year is it?
Orinoco?
Tobermory was clever
with his hands, wasn't he?
He was the clever one.
Alright. We'd better get him up.
EMMA: Let's see if you can sit up.
Hey, Warren.
Yep.
SAM: We're gonna get you up.
Alright, mate?
OK.
Come on, Warren.
(GROANS)
Oh, fuck!
Hey, it's OK, Warren. It's all good.
Someone hit me.
Yeah, I had to hit you.
Yeah, he's sorry. He didn't mean to.
SAM: OK, come on.
Come on, let's get you
up into the bed.
Sam, his neck.
I know. He's fucking heavy.
Come on, Warren.
(MOANS)
Hey, it's all good. Just over here.
Put him on the bed.
Where am I?
SAM: You alright, mate?
Yep. (GROANS)
Hey.
Hey, Warren.
Yeah?
Look here.
(SINGS INDISTINCTLY)
Look over here. Warren. Warren.
Warren.
(MOANS)
Hey.
You're gonna be OK.
I'm OK.
Yeah.
Where's my dog?
SAM: You didn't bring a dog.
Do you remember
why you came here, mate?
Yep. Came with a...
With t...
The Wombles.
Two girls.
SAM: The girls.
You made the Wombles cry.
I didn't make... I didn't make the
Wombles cry. I made the girls cry.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
(MOANS)
Hey.
I think we should get him...
Warren, I think we're gonna
get you to a hospital, OK?
I'm sweet. I'm sweet.
SAM: You sure?
Mmm.
Someone hit me.
Just gonna take your shoes off
and do a check on your toes,
if that's alright.
Got my football socks on. Pull.
You've got your football socks on?
Got my football socks on.
You're a football fan, are you?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Comment?
C'est Slippery Nipple.
C'est sambuca.
Avec Baileys.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
It's rude to speak
in another language.
I like to be
a bit international, Candy.
Not with that accent.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
How are you doing there, Candy?
Oh, best I've ever been.
How long have, um...
Fucking people for money?
About 10 years professionally.
I used to get taken out for dinner.
And then I'd be taken home
in the Maserati.
And, um... Yeah.
Yeah, I used to get
all the good stuff then.
(SIGHS)
I prefer it now.
Why?
Now I know what I am.
(WARREN GROANS)
This is Mr Bowen.
WARREN: Warren Bowen - that's me!
He's hit his head,
so he's got a concussion.
Oh, Warren.
And his hearing's slightly impaired.
So that's why he's shouting, OK?
Alright!
Are you alright?
No alcohol for 48 hours, OK?
Put your jacket back on.
No, it's fine.
I don't need it.
You'll get cold. Put your jacket on.
Warren, I'll get you
the money, mate, I swear.
Stop being stubborn. Put it on.
I'll get you the money, I swear.
Terrible thing to owe money, Popeye.
Yeah.
Just forget about it, eh?
Thanks.
You're supposed to offer again,
aren't you?
Taking advantage, eh, isn't he?
Yeah.
No, Dr Paulie says
that I'm gonna come out of this
looking well scary, so...
...it's sweet, eh?
Yep. Leave me alone now, girls.
We're gonna hold you up.
You can't.
You can't. You can't stand up.
Fucking leave it!
Got me good, Popeye.
SAM: Won't happen again.
Won't happen again.
No free hit next time, eh?
(SAM LAUGHS)
It was a big mistake, that.
Here, I've got you.
Mmm.
Come on.
Hold him.
Au revoir.
See you. 'Bye.
SAM: See ya.
Let's go and have a beer.
No beer.
(GROANS)
We can have a beer.
Listen.
Hey.
I've guessed.
And it's OK.
It's cool. (LAUGHS)
Cool?
Yep.
No.
Look at you in your... nice
scruffed shoes and your slick hair.
Tight belt.
Hang on.
Do you want me to take your bag?
Yep.
Alright. Final...
You walk like a girl anyway.
...humiliation.
(SPORT COMMENTARY
PLAYS ON TV)
Hey, champ. Scotch, double. No ice.
(LIQUID POURS)
Glenn.
Harry McCabe.
How are ya, mate?
Look at us.
How are ya?
Sit down.
Thanks.
How are you faring?
Getting there.
Oh, do you...
Do you still partake?
Yeah, the wife doesn't like it.
(LAUGHS)
I don't see her.
She's upstairs. She smells 'em.
Can't get away with anything.
They're good like that.
No.
So, uh, how's my boy doing?
He's good.
You looking out for him?
Yeah.
Course I am. He'll be fine.
Have you met Deano's little lady yet?
(SIGHS) I...
Uh, yeah, yeah. She's, um...
She all that?
Oh, she's not my...
She's giggly. You know?
I like it when they giggle.
Oh! Oh! HMAS 'Dignity'.
It's a good boat.
How the fuck did you know that?
(GLASSES CLINK)
Deano's got a big mouth.
Is that right?
Mmm.
Deano. Have you heard about
the guy who's replacing me?
Makes me look like
the fucking Wiggles.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Oh...
Yeah.
It was me, Glenn.
I told 'em what you did to Sam.
Sorry?
I snitched on you.
Pardon?
I... think you heard me.
Oh, Harry.
You've got no idea what
the next six months of your life
are gonna be like.
Do you realise how much pain
once I tell the boys? Jesus.
I mean, strap yourself in, Harry.
No, you can't touch me.
I'm sublieutenant.
Let's see.
Let's just see.
(SIGHS)
You're weak, Harry.
You're what's wrong with us.
You are.
Not Sam. You see, I like Sam.
He's done his time in the shit box now.
He can face anything.
But you...
You know, the brain
is man's worst enemy?
You are never gonna understand
toughness, are you, mate,
'cause you just worm your way
out of everything.
But that's the world.
Sam will thank me one day
for what I did for him.
And so will you.
I would very much like it
if you would fuck off now.
And get a fucking haircut.
Because you're not fooling anybody
with that.
Fuck off, please. Go on.
Jesus.
Think I shat my inner child.
Sam...
I thought...
I thought you'd done yourself in.
Surely I'd still be in if I had.
What the fuck happened, then?
Harry hired some hookers, apparently.
I tried to stop him.
Just like you tried to stop Glenn?
Where's...
Emma. She's gone home.
Where the fuck's McCabe?
He's mad at me.
(BOTTLE HISSES)
What else is new?
No, mate. He's... really mad.
You're right, Sam.
About what, Dean?
I'm not going back either.
(JAUNTY KNOCK AT DOOR)
Waitress was a virgin, was she?
We'll serve eight months max.
I'll get out. I can marry Sally.
What do you think?
Hand ourselves in together?
So sorry, Sam.
I... I just tried to believe
that that wasn't me doing that.
(SNIFFS)
I'll tell 'em. I'll report Glenn.
I'll tell 'em what I know.
Ohh.
And what I did.
Oh...
I... I don't want you to do that.
I have to.
I'm going back, Dean.
No...
No-one forced me into this.
And no-one's gonna force me out.
How can you go back?
It's a terrible thing
to owe somebody.
It'll happen again.
And I'll serve my time.
What if they make you do it?
Fuck 'em.
(TOILET FLUSHES, DOOR OPENS)
(FRIDGE OPENS AND CLOSES)
Drink quickly.
We've got to make a move.
Where you off to?
Rollcall. Slack-arse.
I knew it. I knew it.
You knew shit.
Crawling back.
SAM: We've got to go.
Can I ask you something?
Can you hand me in?
Yep.
You'll be having breakfast with Sally
before we're even
out on the harbour, mate.
I'll meet you in the foyer.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Christ, I hope
he makes a run for it.
I'm fucked.
I'm gonna apply to be
petty officer.
Congrats.
Should we do a runner on the carpet
trauma and just leave a massive tip?
Sure.
Yes?
Yep.
Is my nose crooked?
I don't think so.
Hey, thanks for those hookers,
by the way.
Oh. I forgot. Was that helpful?
Not in the slightest.
Hm.
SONG: # Please
# Throw a rope to my aid
# Down here digging my own grave
# You don't have to be a hero
# And rescue, to save
# And please
# Throw a rope to my aid
# I'm about to turn to dust and fade
# Never gonna give up
till I turn grey
# And I can hear them calling in the
# Deep valley
# Echo of the desperate,
pleading heroes
# But I have no strength
to return those calls
# Hope their path
stumbles down my way
# Stumble down my way
# And please throw a rope to my aid
# Pull me from this hungry shade
# Always gonna be starved for praise
# And please throw a rope to my aid
# Pull me from this hungry shade
# Always gonna be starved for praise
# And please
# Throw a rope to my aid
# Pull me from this hungry shade
# Always gonna be starved for praise
# And please
# Throw a rope to my aid
# Life is no longer today
# It don't take too long
for a man to fray
# And I have no strength
to return those calls
# Hope their path
stumbles down my way
# Stumble down my way
# And the sunlight is my enemy, water
# I know that you won't fight me again
# The sunlight is my enemy, water
# I know that you won't fight me
# So please
# Throw a rope to my aid
# This dust is where I once lay
# You don't have to be a hero
# And rescue and save
# A hero and rescue, to save. #