-Hey, Adelson!
-My man, Tino!
-Give me the usual.
-Thanks.
-Hey guvnor!
-Hi Tino.
-Let's eat?Let's eat?
-Honey, I'm home!
-You're here early, Tino!
-Yeah, well. I..
My only client cancelled
his workout.
But he paid, right!
Saved our light bill and dinner.
Yummy.
Hi baby, my little princess. Hi.
Want some more, huh?
Honey, I think she's got a little
surprise for you in her diapers.
Tino, it's not her, it's you.
Jeez, sure is.
My little princess
is smelling sweet,
ready to give her mommy some luck,
huh, Teté?
-Aww, the lottery again, honey?
-One hundred million reais.
Aww honey, it's accumulated.
One hundred million.
Doesn't cost anything
to dream, you know.
Look, they're beginning.
Number thirty-seven.
Honey, I got the first one.
Fifty-eight.
Honey, two!
Great baby, you've set
a new record!
And the third number is nine.
Three, love!
Four!
Four?
Four, honey!
Four!
Four! Four! Four!
Four! Four! Four! Four!
Fifty-four.
The fifth! The fifth!
One more! One more!
What's your number honey?
Thirteen!
Go Thirteen! Come on Thirteen!
...worth one hundred million reais.
Thirteen! Thirteen! Thirteen!
And, the number is: thirteen!
UNTIL LUCK DO US PART
Whatever happens,
we're always going
to trust one another.
And not let this money
change us, OK?
You promise?
We'll always be our same selves.
I promise, Tino.
15 years later
CALL ME! GUILHERME
Good morning, Dona Matilde.
Good morning, senhor Tino.
Hi honey.
A nice breakfast...
So, you'll change mine?
I'll change yours, honey.
Dad, I want that one.
Son, you remember that
car in the video game?
And this one's just
fantastic! How do I look?
Polish it man.
Hey handsome!
All down the drain!
Beer all around!
Tino! Tino! Tino!
That's right, here at home,
Christmas is all year round,
Just help me get this stuff inside.
Here, take these two, there.
The video game is mine, not yours.
It's just for a minute, stingy.
Dad, tell him.
Hold it just a sec...
Listen, you guys have got to
learn to share your things,
Just what I said, tell him dad.
Son, Juninho.
Take daddy's card,
and go buy one for yourself
and left this for your sister.
Wow, alright.
But dad, that's not
learning how to share!
I just can't get any rest.
It sure is learning how to share.
The card is mine and I share
it with whoever I want.
No way.
Oh, look, it's ringing...
ALARM AMAURY
I've got things to do, honey,
excuse me, daddy's got to go.
Hello.
Hey, neighbor!
How's it going, man?
What's up, Faustino.
I was just thinking,
wouldn't you like
to come over for a barbecue, huh?
Barbecue, pool, drinks,
take a little break.
Tino, thank you for your
invitation, but I've got to work.
Again? Bad news man,
days like these are good
for lazing around.
Sloth is a sin,
did you know that?
Yeah, and envy too, right?
Honey!
What kind of soap opera is this?
Who would treat their
mother like that?
It's because
she was poor and got rich,
and now
she's ashamed of her mother.
They make it look like whoever
gets rich mistreats their family.
Dona Jane? Your mother,
from Miami.
Aww, let it ring, Jesus.
Not like poor folks, honey,
because poverty educates you.
I know what I'm talking about,
I'm not just saying this, no way,
I know what I'm saying,
it's true, I know,
I was poor once myself,
and no big deal,
I could be poor again,
and I wouldn't have any
problem with it at all.
I'm not like those other
futile broads you see, like...
Hi friend!
Hi! Debinha!
Hi honey.
Why, what happened there?
Something's not right there!
A medical error,
two hundred milliliters,
Aren't you going
to get that fixed?
Of course I am, it's just that my
lawyer told me to wait, you know?
Because he said I'm going to
make a fortune off of this.
And, speaking of fortunes,
how is Faustino?
Working like crazy, honey.
Way to go kid!
Hey!
Nice!
Great.
You got the idea.
Now you're pumping.
Tino, no way man.
What? You wanted a piece?
No, Tino.
Tino, you shouldn't even be here.
What are you doing here anyway?
Listen, Nelsinho,
I own this place too, right?
We need a partner who is like
this, look, like us, you get me?
But, I am like you guys.
I'm old Tino from...
Sure miss those days!
I'm the same old Tino,
and besides,
I bet I can still lift more
weight than you two.
When getting out of bed?
Exactly. When I get out... hey!
I used to knock you out on the
treadmill, and I still can,
you wanta bet?
Your part of the gym.
I don't have
to prove nothing to nobody.
Ahh, chickening out, fatso?
Nobody calls me fatso.
Tino, are you sure you
want to do this, man?
Listen bro, let's do it,
I'm not even going to
put on sneakers,
it'd make it too easy.
Listen man,
I know what I'm doing.
Let's go!
What?
What is it?
What was my time?
Three minutes on the treadmill.
Yeah?
Yeah, and twenty on the floor.
Tino, it doesn't have
to be like this, right?
Let me tell you something,
this gym here is going
to miss me more
than I'm going to miss it, right?
This here, for me, is crumbs.
How much does this place
make a month?
Fifty, sixty grand?
Six hundred.
Lot's of crumbs, I'd say,
but, I could care less,
screw it!
I don't need this place for nothing.
And besides, I have to go.
Hey, honey!
No way, you don't have
to pay the bill, go on.
This is stupid, stop it.
Hold it, Nelsinho, you crazy?
He's going to pay,
he eats too much.
Nelsinho, I'm talking to Nelsinho,
I'm talking to Nelsinho.
Nelsinho, I insist on paying.
Here honey, OK, OK?
What's wrong?
Your card was cancelled.
What? My card, refused?
Are you crazy? My card...
I've never had a card
refused in my life, honey.
But this one was.
Forget it, Tino, forget it,
you're not paying.
Nelson! Nelson, formally now,
we're here, signing a contract.
Nelson, I insist,
I'm not leaving till
I pay every cent.
Use this card then, please.
What is it now, huh?
No credit.
Smiling, are you, huh?
Well then honey,
take your pick here,
let's try another card.
If there's one thing I have,
it's credit cards.
I've got them in black,
gold, silver, purple...
I've got a whole rainbow
of cards here, OK?
Rainbow! You know
what a rainbow is?
Refused.
Refused, and, refused.
Just a minute.
CALL ME! GUILHERME.
Guilherme, what's going on here?
I tried to use my credit cards
and they're all maxed out.
Dona Lúcia that's fine
for now, please.
Excuse me,
I have to hang up.
How are you,
senhor Faustino?
I'm just fine, just fine.
Please, sit down,
we have to talk.
No, we have to settle this, right,
Guilherme, settle this.
What's going on?
Listen, I had a credit card
refused once.
One, but fourteen?
Is this some kind of joke?
A lack of respect.
Let me tell you,
I even felt like I was poor.
Faustino,
your account is in the red.
You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not.
I could have done a couple
extravagant things, OK,
spent more than I should
have, once or twice,
small excesses, right?
But, spend it all?
Let me tell you
something my friend:
Nobody is able to spend
one hundred million reais, no way!
Well, you did.
HOW?
You really want to know?
Five trips per year,
spending an average of 2 hundred
thousand dollars each one.
But, trips are culture,
right, Guilherme.
Yeah, all of them to Disney.
Yeah, I like Mickey, I really do.
Two million for a sailboat
to go round the world.
The Schijrmann family does it.
You sunk the boat
in half an hour.
Because of some big rock,
And, no insurance.
Nobody had told me about
the insurance,
how we needed it,
it wasn't in the manual, I...
You bought out
all of Rock in Rio
for your 30th birthday.
Thirty years old, man,
that's historical,
a couple friends,
what's wrong with that?
Only you invited Hulk and
lvete Sangalo to liven up the place.
They let me pay in installments.
Your cotton wedding anniversary
at the Chantilly Castle, in France,
for three hundred guests.
Ronaldinho Fenómeno
did the same thing
and nobody said anything.
Three hundred thousand
dollars per year
on zero gravity flights.
But, that was a dream of mine,
Guilherme,
can you imagine,
to fly, it's amazing.
Faustino, lottery winners
lose fortunes,
everyday, around the world.
It's not unusual.
But, unhappily,
the bank isn't going
to be able to do anything for you.
Great...
Faustino, don't worry.
I called in a big friend of mine,
who works with
an investment company,
to help you.
He should be getting
here any moment now,
Amauri?
Amauri!
Guilherme.
-You?
You know each other?
That's great!
No way.
This guy is my neighbor.
I know,
I wanted somebody close by.
But, that's not all,
there's something much worse,
something above and beyond that.
What?
The guy's a jerk.
Hey, I'm still here!
I know.
Faustino, please.
You got any cookies?
To go with the coffee?
Amauri, I need your help,
the board is on my back.
You let the guy hang himself
and then you go looking
for somebody to get rid of the body,
I know how that works, Guilherme.
No way.
I would never
deny doing you a favor,
you've always helped me,
but I just can't help you here.
I'm not going to help this guy.
You won't or you
just don't know how?
I didn't find any cookies.
Listen, Tino, I'm not happy
with this situation at all.
Yeah, and I'm jumping for joy,
really.
Yeah, but for your own good,
we're going to have to get
along with each other.
Listen, Amauri,
I ain't no kid, OK?
I know how to take care
of myself,
without anybody having to
tell me what I have to do.
You come by car?
Can I get a lift?
Faustino, I'm going
to need your financial
records for the
last three years.
Forget it.
Tino, you're going
to have to collaborate.
There are five steps
to get rich:
I could give a shit.
Organization, planning,
equilibrium, security, investment.
It's all here.
Amauri, what you got a
doll in your car for, huh?
To keep robbers away.
Really? The doll works for
SWAT or something?
No.
Surveys indicate that 62%
of car thieves
avoid cars with kids
in the backseat.
I'd rather have my
car stolen, really.
That doll is horrible.
It looks like the son of Chuck.
Numbers don't lie, Tino.
And besides, from the outside,
it look like a real kid.
Yeah, but up close he
looks just like Chuck.
I get this feeling it's
going to jump me at any
moment with a knife
in his hand and...
He's not Chuck.
But he looks alike like him,
must be related.
Yeah, but he's not Chuck.
That doll is evil, for sure.
No, it isn't Chuck.
No way, let me tell you.
Got you nervous, huh?
OK. First step:
you're going inside and
tell your family the truth.
The truth?
Yeah. You're going to tell
them you were negligent,
how you squandered your money,
were irresponsible,
that you are bankrupt,
you failed them and
that you are all going to
have to tighten your belts.
That's all?
Yeah. Why?
You can't do that?
Good night, Amauri.
Amauri, what were those five
steps again in the book, huh?
Organization, planning,
equilibrium, investment,
what was the fifth one again, huh?
Tino, grow up.
You're broke.
Squanderer my ass.
No way.
Surprise!
What's this?
What is going on...
What is this all about?
Take it easy, honey,
it's just a little get-together.
You now, like, on the spot.
But... a little get-together, Jane?
Just a minute honey,
turn on the music everybody,
for God's sake.
No, don't turn on the music,
hold it!
Turn it up.
What's the party for?
-To celebrate what?
-Celebrate what?
The day we met my love.
Ohh, the day we...
How long ago?
Sixteen years.
Six years, sixteen years.
Sixteen years ago,
I love you.
Sixteen years, me too.
I love you too, love,
I love you.
I love you too.
But, honey,
are you sure you
didn't exaggerate a bit, huh?
Tino, honestly,
you're not acting
like my old Tino.
Why?
Because you,
for much less,
threw a mega party just because
your team won the championship.
I'm Botafogo,
it doesn't happen everyday, right?
It's very rare.
Lobster.
I'm going to go fill up.
Right, go fill up honey.
I love you.
I love you too, only just take
it easy because... Jane...
Hi, Faustino, hi, Faustino,
congratulations!
Oh, thanks.
What? I'm sorry.
What happened there?
This here?
Yeah.
It was, an error.
An error, a medical error.
A big error for sure.
Jane invited both of them,
I guess, huh?
Bye Bia, see you tomorrow.
Bye!
Nasdaq!
Down!
Let go, let go!
You bad dog!
Do something!
Look what he's doing!
He's going to tear it.
Let go, Nasdaq!
I'm sorry,
this is all I could save.
Hey, Juninho, 3D for everybody,
is that it?
How much did all this cost, huh?
Aww dad, I don't know.
My God,
I'm creating a congressman.
Amauri, another party
at the neighbor's.
The last royal ball.
Oh yeah? Why's that?
Forget it.
And us? Let's have our
own little party?
Oh no, I just found out that
I have to correct a statement...
What was that for, Laura?
You don't fool me, Amauri.
Fool you?
You're the one who's doing
everything you can to get pregnant.
Aww, Amauri,
you're being unfair...
your favorite brand.
Come here.
Don't blame me if
it's a lousy brand.
Forget it, Laura.
Aww, Amauri...
Amauri, our son is
already 15 years old,
there's still time for
me to have another one.
Laura, we haven't even
paid for the house yet,
Bruno will be going to
college in three years,
we don't have any money
set aside for a rainy day.
No.
No Amauri, don't start on
that again, no way.
OK then, I'll just give
you one number.
Seventy.
Seventy what?
Seventy percent of all couples get a
divorce after their second child.
Think about that.
Right. So I'll give you another
number: thirty-seven.
Thirty-seven what?
Years old!
I'm thirty-seven, Amauri!
I don't have
a whole lifetime to wait.
My inner clock is ticking away,
and it isn't stopping.
Think about that.
Attention everyone,
let me see what is
happening here, with
this microphone...
well, I would like
to thank you all for
coming here
to my and Tina's party.
Thank you.
Today, me and Tino, we...
we've been married
now for 16 years.
And this party is to celebrate
this special moment.
This wonderful moment.
And I'd like to say that...
that I love you so much, honey,
and that you're the
best husband in the world.
The best husband, the best father,
the best friend,
the man who has always
been standing by my side.
It's true, really.
All these years.
In which we've always
had everything we ever needed,
affection most of all.
Oh, I'm so nervous!
You are the man I love,
the love of my life, Tino.
Thank you so much.
Long live us.
Viva!
Good evening.
How's it going, Tino?
Here, take this.
That's all I've got.
How'd your family react?
They didn't, funny isn't it?
You know
why they didn't react?
Because I didn't tell them.
I didn't tell them.
You have to tell them, Tino.
Look, Amauri,
let me tell you something,
I don't want to argue.
Right this moment, at home,
there's a party going on.
Interesting, huh?
People,
because the other half didn't come.
So, it just wasn't the right moment
to say anything tonight.
But, I promise you:
first thing tomorrow.
Poor?
What do you mean, poor?
Poor, like with no money.
Broke.
Let me get this straight,
you're telling me that you
spent all of our money?
The money
I won in the lottery?
We spent, Jane, we...
But, no big deal, honey,
no problem, no sweat,
you always told me
you weren't afraid
of being poor
again one day, right?
Of course, because I never
thought we'd be poor again,
I don't want to be poor,
you understand?
I've forgotten what
it's like being poor.
No way! Nobody ever forgets
what it's like being poor.
Being poor is like
riding a bicycle.
Of course, because bicycles
are for poor people.
Listen here, do you have
life insurance?
Yeah.
With me and the kids
as beneficiaries?
We both do, why?
Does it cover murder?
Hold it Jane, for God's sake,
I'm your husband.
So? I'll get another one.
I'm still pretty sexy.
God bless silicone!
But, I'm your lovey-dovey.
So start running,
lovey-dovey.
Faustino, Faustino,
you want
to scare me to death?
You want to kill me,
you want to kill me!
For God's sake, Faustino,
why would I want
to kill you for?
Why? Oh, nothing, nothing,
nothing, forget it.
Delete it, just delete it.
Let's get some rest, huh?
Sorry, let's get some rest.
Try to calm down, honey,
get some rest,
Yeah, great.
Auction?
ART AUCTION
Dad, give me money
for ice-cream?
How much is it, huh?
Huh? What kind of question
is that dad?
What's wrong,
can't I ask how much it cost?
You act like I never asked for
the price of anything before.
No, you haven't.
You're acting weird dad.
I don't even feel like
ice-cream anymore.
Not me, I want one,
give me the money.
Bring me a coconut Popsicle.
Amauri.
Hi, Amauri, what's up.
Tino, where are you?
I'm at an... auction.
You're where? An auction?
Tino, you can't
spend one more cent,
do you understand?
I know Amauri,
but my wife doesn't know.
So, I think you'd better
tell her quick,
because your situation is
a lot worse than you think.
You're not only down to zero,
you owe money.
And lots of it.
You're probably going to have
to sell lots of your things.
But, in the meantime,
do me a favor:
Don't spend
any more money.
Not one cent,
you get me?
Our next item is a very
delicate piece,
a rare collector's item.
An Imperial Persian Kahr rug from
the early twentieth century,
made by master rug
maker Abu Zahid...
I have to tell you something,
very important.
Not now, baby,
just look at that
scandalous rug!
I could care less
about the rug,
I don't even want to know
how much it costs.
Only ninety thousand.
Ninety thousand?
Ninety thousand for a rug, why?
Is it a flying rug by any chance?
The gentleman bids ninety-five.
What you talking about, buddy?
This some joke?
Oh honey,
I don't think this rug is
all that special,
no need to bid.
But, I didn't.
One hundred thousand
for the gentleman.
Listen buddy,
you don't understand,
when I do like this...
One hundred and five
for the gentleman.
For God's sake,
somebody make a bid,
Look at the rug from Yemen,
all the way from Yemen.
I'll give one hundred and six.
One hundred and six, great.
I'll give one hundred and fifty!
Why? Why bid that?
You didn't like the rug,
why bid more?
I didn't like
the rug all that much,
but I didn't like the looks
of that old hag even more.
I'll give one hundred fifty-one.
Way to go, old hag!
I'll give two hundred.
Two hundred, but why,
two hundred thousand
for a rug, guys?
Honey, what is wrong with you?
You're acting very weird.
Honey, I've got to talk
to you right now!
I can't right now.
Yes you can.
What is the gentleman's offer?
I'll offer you a smack in the face.
Two hundred thousand for a rug,
you gotta be out of your mind.
Are you crazy?
They're still going to
auction the vase I want.
Jane, honey, I have to tell
you something right now.
Just a moment.
I feel kinda dizzy,
I don't know what it is.
I stood up too quick inside.
My pressure must have dropped.
Wait, let me talk first,
then you can feel bad, OK, Jane?
Our family,
constituted with so much love, isn't...
Water.
Water? You want water?
OK, but in a plastic cup.
What can I do?
OK, I'll get you it.
My.
Honey, you are a warrior,
a woman full of spirit,
a woman that won't let
any old thing knock her down?
So, honey...
Jane?
Senhor Faustino.
Please come with me.
Mom!
Hi, kids.
Hi, honey...
And so? You feel alright?
Yes honey, I'm alright, just fine.
Thank God, honey,
you gave us a fright.
It was nothing.
Nothing, no.
She has news.
What news?
I'm pregnant.
What?!
What is it, honey?
It's happiness.
Mommy is pregnant.
Mommy is...
Mommy is... mommy is...
And I'll set up my lipo
at the same time,
because when I get pregnant
I usually put on a couple pounds,
right honey?
What do you think?
What do I think?
You happy?
So HAPPY-
Look at me, look.
I'm, I'm...
Perfect timing...
fits like a glove.
-A glove, like...
-I knew it!
...in the middle of my head.
I'm going outside,
I'm a little...
I need some air,
I'll be outside,
to celebrate.
OK, give me a kiss, honey.
A kiss here.
A kiss honey.
It's like normal,
he is very effusive.
Oh, my God.
My wife is pregnant,
dear God.
My wife is pregnant.
Why? Why?
Senhor Faustino,
could I have a word with you?
Right.
I talked to your wife,
she and the baby are alright.
Thank God.
But, she's sort of exaggerated
with her plastic surgeries.
Twenty-eight, twenty-eight.
Right, senhor Faustino,
Tino, just call me Tino.
Tino, I can't hide my concern,
I don't know just what this
has done to her body,
I mean, this could be
a difficult pregnancy,
so I think it would be better
if you avoided any kind of trauma.
Trauma? What trauma?
There is no trauma at all.
Do you see any trauma?
Calm down, no, of course not.
Did anyone say anything
about a trauma to you?
Of course not,
I just mean, like,
bad news, arguments, or...
financial problems...
She needs peace.
For hers and the baby's good.
The baby's?
The baby's most of all.
Me, when I attend to a client,
the first thing I do
is try to set them at ease,
make them feel safe..
Amauri, I'm screwed!
I'm screwed good this time,
Amauri, totally screwed, Amauri.
Oxygen.
This is not one of our clients.
Yes I am!
No you're not.
Yes I am.
OK. Tino,
the only thing I can say is:
Cut down on expenses.
How, Amauri?
Jane like drains away money.
Look, if Jane were
married to Eike Batista,
he'd be selling coconuts
on the beach in no time.
I can't tell her anything, nothing,
do you get what I mean?
Don't you have any relatives,
who you could ask for help?
No, her mother lives in Miami,
I'm the one who sent her there.
And then there's Uncle Olavinho,
but that guy, let me tell you...
Who is this Olavinho?
Forget him. He's an uncle of
hers who has some money,
but I'm not getting
anywhere near the guy,
you understand, no way.
OK, then. Tino, I can't
believe I'm going to say this,
What?
Yeah, you just tell her
change.
I'll call the bank,
and ask them to not
cancel her cards just yet.
But only her cards.
You're going to control yourself,
not spend any money,
you'll probably have to
sell some of your things.
She'll understand
later that it was
The most important thing now
is to tell your kids.
But, do you think
they'll understand?
No harm in trying.
Son, don't scream like that,
you'll wake up your mother,
he sure likes to make a scene, huh?
I knew this was going to
happen one day. I knew it.
Honey, it isn't
the end of the world.
Just almost.
The important thing right now,
is to not let your
mother know anything.
But, dad, she'll notice.
Teté, you're the smartest
one in this house,
if you can't do it,
nobody can.
The smartest?
Father you live me criticizing.
Honey, I'm just saying that you
didn't come out anything like me.
And, believe me, honey,
that's a compliment.
So cancel ballet,
france, only ingles.
OK.
Hi.
Hi, Bruno.
I just wanted to apologize
for the other day.
I bought you this.
Thanks, but you shouldn't have.
Come on, I'm just
trying to be nice.
You going to get all upset just over
a small bear worth three reais?
Man, the day I was born,
my father was so broke he
had to walk to the hospital
to not pay the three
reais for the bus fare,
which he used
to buy that bear.
My mom said it
was my lucky bear.
Can you buy that back?
No, but, look at the good side,
you guys were real lucky.
You're kidding me, right?
I can't believe that
you don't know.
Know what?
Dad, why didn't you tell me?
I made a fool of myself
at school today.
Professional secrecy, son, and,
please, don't go spreading
it around, OK?
Yeah, well thanks for the help.
Son, listen, what your
father is saying is
that their life is theirs
and ours is ours.
We don't have to know about
what happens to them.
Oh yeah, mom? Did you know
that Dona Jane is pregnant?
Laura, Laura, Laura!
Laura, don't have a fit, Laura!
You said yourself that they don't
have anything to do with us.
I'm not talking
about them Amauri,
I'm talking about us! Us!
OK, you want to talk about us?
OK then, let's talk about us.
What do you want
to say about us?
She's younger than me!
That's not talking about us.
Amauri, I know that you think you're
the most rational man around,
the most intelligent,
but let me tell you,
I envy that family.
They're vulgar, crass,
give the worst parties
in the world, but they live.
They have friends at their house,
laugh, have fun.
Their life has nothing
to do with ours,
except for the way in
which they rub it into
our face and show us
how unhappy we are.
Speak for you.
Way to go Tino, nice shot!
Right on man, nice!
Listen, how 'bout paying
a round of drinks for us,
just one, no big deal.
Don't get me wrong...
but stop bumming drinks all the time.
Just one drink, man.
No, let me tell you something,
Things aren't easy,
and I'm kinda broke,
you know?
But, then I thought, right?
Like: "Shit, who can help me?
My friends, of course".
What? Where is every...?
Things aren't looking
very good, man.
Couldn't you lend me
some money, huh?
A little cash?
Sure, how much you need, Tino?
I don't know,
two, three hundred grand.
Come on Tino, seriously, Tino.
Who do you think I am?
Some millionaire
or something?
You always successful
in whatever you did,
ever since your hot-dog stand,
a big success.
If you knew just how much I miss
those days with my hot-dog stand...
If you miss them,
Why'd you quit then?
Because you gave me the
money to buy this bar here.
And I accepted because
I thought it would be good for me,
but, really, I still haven't
found myself here yet, Tino.
Adelson, no joking man,
you're the only real friend
that I have, you know that?
So then I feel like it's
my duty to give
you some advice,
some friendly advice.
Sure man, tell me.
Tino, why don't you start
working again, huh?
And so guys? I was always
a good coach, huh?
And like they say, once a king,
you never lose your majesty.
Nor your belly.
Listen man, what did I
ever do to you, huh?
Tino, let us talk here a minute,
let me talk to him.
Nelsinho, I can't believe you're
going to give in to this guy.
He left us here doing
all the hard work for years.
But if it weren't for him
we'd still be doing all
the hard work in that flea-ridden
joint over in Vila Isabel.
Do you really think you
don't owe him anything?
This isn't going to be easy.
OK, girls, let's get started...
Today a new coach
will be helping you all.
Coach Tino.
Alright!
I don't want to see any
lazybones around here!
This is about health.
I want to see fit bodies.
I don't want to see any
bellies bouncing around.
What about yours honey?
I see!
We have a difficult group here!
No problem, big Tino knows how
to deal with people like you,
I'll lay it on nice and heavy.
Everybody up on the trampoline!
Richard, this one is broken, look.
It wasn't before.
Right. So everybody
off the trampoline,
get off the trampolines.
You want to play with Tino?
I'll show you what a high impact
aerobic exercise is all about.
Again a again!
Oh, God.
Nelsinho! Hi, Richard!
What happened?
Where am I, guys?
What happened here?
Beat it!
Tino.
Tino wait.
Nelsinho.
Here. Your payment.
Payment? Five thousand
for 15 minutes of class?
It's the best I can do right now.
And the least too.
Don't tell Rick
anything about his, OK?
Don't worry, thanks, buddy.
Who is the woman who wouldn't
love a pair of earrings like these?
The time is now.
Pick up the phone and call.
Right, I want the earrings...
Merely four thousand
nine hundred and ninety...
Right, I confirm the purchase.
No!
Tino, what are you doing?
What did you do that for?
It's just... the earrings
are horrible.
They'll make your face look fat.
That's it.
Faustino, I don't care,
they're diamonds!
And I love jewelry.
I love jewelry.
You know that.
I have loads of jewelry.
Yeah“.
Come on Tino,
stop saying that,
I don't do
nothing like that, man.
Everybody knows what you do.
Everybody here knows
you're an in-and-out man,
that you like to lift
things once in a while.
Everybody knows that here.
And you want to
spread it all around?
And I'm on parole,
you know I can't go doing
no kind of scam man.
This ain't no scam, you jerk,
I'm not talking about a scam.
Stop fussing with that,
that's a real nasty
habit you have.
Then you go round
touching other people.
I'm not talking about no scam,
this is the deal,
I just want you to go
and get all the jewels
I have at home,
so Jane won't know.
I'll settle things
with her later.
For God's sake, give me a hand here,
I'm desperate.
Shit, you put me down in
front of everyone, Tino!
I was just talking, sorry,
I didn't mean anything, really.
No, now you're alright,
I'll do this to help you out.
I'm real sorry if I was too...
you do this for me then, right?
No problem, no problem.
So, this is what
we're going to do...
But I liked the movie,
I just didn't get that
part about the arm,
Go get some shuteye, go on.
No, no shuteye before whoopie.
Vander, and so,
you get the jewels?
Tino, I haven't finished yet, man,
I can't read
the numbers you wrote, Tino.
What do you mean,
you're not through?
No, Tino.
Man, beat it right now!
Why?
Tino!
Hi, Jane.
There's a burglar in our room.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes there is!
I think you're judging
people before you
No, I'm not judging anyone.
There's a man.
A burglar inside our room
standing in front of the safe
with a crowbar in his hand!
Yeah, well that is a very
revealing, for sure.
That's really hard to doubt,
but for God's sake,
you can't get stressed out.
My father was a cop, did you
forget about that, honey?
Ohh, I had forgotten about that.
And I just love it when the
adrenalin starts pumping,
And I am raring to teach
this guy a lesson.
No, you're not going to
teach anyone a lesson,
the kids are downstairs and you
have another one here. Please.
Yeah, that's true.
Please, calm down,
take care of your offspring,
Wow, go on, alpha male.
Shit, what was that, Tino?
Tino my ass,
stop saying my name,
are you stupid
or something, huh.
Listen,
pretend we're fighting, go on,
and I'll open the safe.
How am I supposed
to do that, Tino?
I don't know,
make believe man.
Are you crazy?
I told you to pretend.
Well your wife
wasn't pretending, shit.
I've opened it,
get the stuff, go on.
Honey, you want me
to call the police?
No.
My God...
What happened here?
Jane!
Honey, what happened?
Oh my love, it's you!
How glad I am to see a friendly
face at a time like this.
This place was a battlefield.
It was pure chaos,
let me tell you,
all hell broke out,
with fingers in the eyes,
fisticuffs, half-nelsons,
whole nelsons, blood,
it was just gushing,
listen, it was terrible,
and then, suddenly,
he hit me over the head
and I thought:
"Man, my family,
my family, my family".
And he got away.
But, how did that happen honey,
if I knocked him out cold.
I don't know, but he got a way,
terrible, he got away.
What is it?
He didn't get away!
He's just plain stupid!
No, that is worse than stupid,
he deserves to be
committed for that!
But, honey, leave this
to me, go on outside
Hate in my eyes,
I'm going to destroy him.
Leave him to me, no problem,
'cause now I'm going to be attack,
like a mad dog.
Yeah, a mad dog.
Yeah, and a crowbar.
A crowbar, get the crowbar.
Don't you think that's
a bit too lethal?
Follow me, come on.
I'm coming,
behind the crowbar.
I like it when they don't move.
You want my jewels?
You dirty crook!
Could you lend me a hand, Faustino?
Or you'll get some you too!
But, he's had enough now, honey, Could you lend
me a hand, Faustino? Or you'll get some you too!
But, he's had enough now, honey,
that's enough now.
You got him good.
Go and call the cops then, honey,
that's it.
I'll call the cops,
and you keep hitting him.
Call the cops, leave him to me now,
I'm hitting him,
call an ambulance.
Vander, let me help you here.
You OK?
No way...
That wife of yours is worse
than the devil, huh?
It sometimes depends
on the time of the month,
right, but Vander, you'd better go,
because, really,
the cops will be here
any moment now...
try avoiding any
sudden movements, OK?
And if you can,
put a splint on at home...
This isn't going to be cheap, no way.
Caribbean here I come!
Caribbean, no way, huh?
I'm Brazilian, I never give up.
Tino. I'm gone.
Don't go running off with them...
Vander, hey Vander...
I can't believe this!
You don't have any more
credit cards, no more checks,
you're broke.
Nobody... will give you
any more credit,
yes, you're going to
have to sell everything.
No, Tino,
I don't want to buy your Ferrari.
Tino, sell it all.
Let's go shopping?
I need to buy a whole
bunch of things...
You have to sell everything,
and that means everything.
How long can I stay
in the house?
Three months, Amauri?
But Jane is going to have
her baby before that.
I know Tino, it's just
that the house belongs to...
I'm sorry.
Laura, my dear neighbor.
Jane!
How are you dear?
What are you doing here?
Don't waste your breath,
I know already!
You've got something baking
here in your oven too.
No, no, it's not that.
I'm just looking for
a present for my niece...
for my niece.
Well, as long as
you're here, maybe.
If you had to pick,
for your niece,
between these two,
which one would you choose?
You're going to have a girl?
I never thought a mall
could be so boring!
If you can't buy anything,
what'd you expect?
Come here, you two
going to sit around talking?
I brought you here to help
me find your mother, OK?
So, get moving.
If it had been up to Tino,
this one is beautiful.
Poor Juninho,
if it hadn't been for me,
And you guys?
Don't you ever another one?
Us...
Yeah.
Well, I do, sometimes,
you know? But...
Ohh, no way, it's like my
grandmother used to say,
you can't give the guy time to think,
you get me,
you have to just
go up and, bang!
Bang?
That's it. Why do you
think animals don't have.
Because they just
go up and, bang,
grab them and bang.
Bang.
Where could she be?
And I'll take...
Hold it, don't move,
give me this.
Tino, what are you doing here?
It's just that I want to...
participate in this moment
picking out the furniture
of my daughter's room.
How nice.
Oh no, that is impossible,
you don't even know
the color of Tete's room
and now you're saying
that you want to
help pick out
the baby's furniture.
I've changed.
I've changed and I want
I'm not going to let
you buy our daughter's.
This is an award-winning store.
Yeah?
Just a minute dear,
I think you're acting so strange,
really.
No, I'm not...
Because I have to tell you,
I really want
to give this baby here,
the room that Teté didn't
have when she was born,
for sure, and the only place
better than this store here
would be to hire some
designer, right, someone...
A designer! A designer!
A designer.
Yes.
I know one who we can hire...
You want me to do what?
Adelson,
let me explain it to you.
You're the only one
who can help me.
I'm not asking for any money,
I just need you to do this,
for my wife,
to pretend you're a designer.
A what?
A designer.
What's that?
A designer is a guy who...
somebody who...
works with design,
you understand?
Listen, let me tell you something.
My wife doesn't know you,
it'll work.
No, no, no, no and no way.
You look great.
Look, if you start bugging me,
I'm leaving,
I'll leave, you get me?
Did you read the magazines?
Yeah, looks like everything
today is vintage, vintage is in.
Vintage.
Right, and what else, what else?
I'm going to have to ask
you to play the fruitcake.
Now, wait a minute,
you didn't say anything about that!
You have to be gay.
Look Tino, not every
designer is gay man,
that's just prejudice on your part.
And you know
anything about design?
The first thing about design?
No, you don't.
You have to be gay,
hold your hand back.
Tino I'm not going to hold my
hand back, I won't do it, no way.
I'm asking you, help me!
I'm not going to do it.
For God's sake!
You have to be gay.
I'm never going to do
anything like that.
You have to make
Jane believe that you are a designer,
if not it's all over.
Tino, is he here, is that him?
And who's got
that lovely belly?
The designer.
And so, Jaques?
This room is fabulous!
Simply fabulous. F-A-B.
Fabulous.
But, it's still empty.
Yes, but I can see it all in
my head, something very simple,
used furniture.
Right, but I'm not going to buy
used furniture for my daughter.
Listen, Jane, I think, really...
No, you shut up.
Jane, darling,
that's exactly why it is chic.
It's vintage.
Vintage.
True vintage.
Listen to me Jane,
people spend fortunes
Old. Repeat please.
Old.
Yeah, old.
But, only those who are truly chic,
like you, right?
Use furniture that is truly old,
used, you get me?
No, but...
Tell me something,
I have a question, a question,
tell me something,
for you, for you,
who is, like, the chicest
person in the world
Oh, you know that actress?
I have a couple...
The one from the plane, the jet?
No, she's second rate.
Kate, Kate Middleton.
Kate?
Who is that?
The English Princess!
Jane, darling, where does
Kate Middleton live?
The princess...
does she live around here honey?
I can't remember right now...
No, she lives...
Excuse me.
She lives
in the Palace of Buckingham.
Oh my God!
The Buckingham Palace.
Really? My...
And... what do you think?
That in the Buckingham Palace
the furniture only looks old?
No!
Hey, hey.
The furniture there is truly old.
It just isn't older
than the queen mother.
I simply loved you, Jaques!
No, really,
you have style, right,
not everybody has that,
no way.
So everything today
is vintage then?
Right, vintage, a must.
Listen, I have to recommend
you to my friends.
Of course, of course I do.
Of course!
No, but, I mean,
I don't know if I can,
I don't have my card,
and with all my clients, no time...
Imagine.
I'll get your number later with Tino,
he'll give it to me,
no problem,
you have to meet my friends,
right honey?
For sure, you have to.
OK then.
Before you leave, wouldn't
you like a cup of jasmine tea?
Jasmine is a m-a-s-t.
For sure, m-a-s-t, a must!
Jasmine is a must, m-a-s-t.
A must.
That lipstick suits you, Tino.
What? Want a kiss?
Listen Tino,
you know I always carry a gun,
Show some respect.
Laura?
Meow.
Laura, I'm home.
The kitten wants milk.
Great.
Amauri, Amauri,
if you're checking out
my fertile days
on the phone...
Meow.
And this is the first order?
No.
What's wrong with you,
why you walking like that, huh?
I sprained a muscle...
Tino, I know you don't
like to talk about this,
but your situation
is getting worse...
and you said
that Jane had an uncle...
I'm not going to talk to...
Sorry.
I'm not going to talk
to Uncle Olavinho, OK?
No way.
You're just going to have
to swallow your pride.
Sometimes, it's better
asking a relative...
What does this uncle...
Olavinho.
What does he do?
What's his line of business?
He's got this store,
a chain of stores I think.
A chain of stores?
Yeah.
Really
What's his name?
Olavo Mendes.
Your wife is niece of Olavo Mendes
and you don't tell me?
Tino, forget the doll.
I can't, it gives me the creeps.
Tino, focus.
Olavo Mendes has stores
everywhere in the world.
He makes more money
than Uruguay's GDP.
Why not talk to him?
Because he's a skinflint.
A cheapskate,
who doesn't help anyone.
And when I got rich
I told him to eat shit.
That's wonderful.
But he was the one who began it, OK?
He called me an imbecile.
A man of vision.
Yeah“.
Oops
Thank you.
Tino, Olavo is 104 years old,
he doesn't have kids,
Jane is his only niece,
I know how rich folks think,
he'll help you,
but, he's going to want
something in exchange.
He's going to play with you.
This is just a waste of time,
he won't even see me.
It's up to you now.
Good luck.
Well, Uncle...
Can I talk now?
Yeah, Gesundheit.
So, Uncle Olavinho...
are you going
to be able to help me, sir?
You, no. Janine yes.
Did you forget that you
offended me here,
inside my own house?
I, really, I...
it's been so long I can't
even remember what I said.
You told me to eat shit,
which I'm doing still today.
Good memory you have.
Good memory.
For God's sake, forgive me,
forgive me,
I'm desperate, Uncle Olavinho,
I'll do anything I have to do,
Uncle Olavinho,
anything.
You used to play tennis,
didn't you?
Me, yeah... I was an athlete,
right, I played all sports,
I was good in any sport, right?
How about a game
of tennis worth...
Worth one hundred
thousand reais, a set.
Me and you?
Yeah.
One hundred thousand, playing.
Right.
Me against you.
Help me up here, Sabaré,
give me a hand.
Uncle Olavo, of course,
of course I will,
one hundred thousand,
me and you, in a game?
Uncle Olavinho, it's your idea,
I'll take the bet!
But don't be
too hard on me, OK.
Uncle Olavinho,
are you sure you want to do this?
Don't forget,
you're 104 years old,
wouldn't you rather we play bridge,
dominos, checkers?
Listen here boy,
I do orthomolecular therapy.
An active mind,
an active body.
So, don't be too hard
on me then, OK.
Keep on dreaming boy,
dream on.
Well, OK then, Uncle Olavo,
let's do it then,
let's start the game then,
try to get the ball over
the net at least, OK?
And hit this here, OK?
One hundred grand, in the till.
You caught me off guard.
Another hundred thousand in the till.
So now it's my turn.
Never seen such a lousy player...
Have a drink boy.
Have a drink, relax a bit.
No thanks,
I want to spare my liver,
I'll probably have
to sell it soon.
I'm not going to hold you
to the bet, don't worry.
What, so what was this
all about then?
You just want
to humiliate me?
Yeah, to humiliate you,
because money isn't everything
in the world, no way.
Listen, why don't you eat s...
Again, huh?
Listen, Uncle Olavinho,
it's easy for you to say that,
you hear me?
You're filthy rich,
a billionaire,
living in this mansion.
But not me,
I'm 38 years old, two kids,
a pregnant wife, unemployed,
without a cent to my name.
Want to trade?
Boy, I'd give up all this,
everything, to be poor,
just to be 38 again.
I'd give every cent I had just
to have a young wife,
pretty, and kids that loved me.
I'd trade my life with yours,
like this.
It's not me, nor Jane, who puts
money before everything else, no,
it's you, you Tino.
And you'd better tell Jane soon,
you hear me,
because a woman can forgive
a man without money,
but a liar no,
you understand.
That's right, send the taxi to 415,
El Salvador St.
Jane, I...
Stefani and Junior,
you both go on outside and,
as soon as the cab gets
here you tell me, OK?
Why did you do this?
The doctor, he told me
you couldn't get upset,
What trauma?
Of being poor again.
Tino, look at me.
Here, look into my eyes.
Do you really think that being
poor again is a trauma for me?
Look, honey...
I can even forgive you for
having made the kids lie to me,
for you having
made us all poor again,
I can even forgive you for
thinking I'm some futile.
Please, Jane.
I can forgive you all that,
but, the only thing
I can't forgive you is
for not knowing who I am,
after being
married to me
for 16 years, Tino.
Not that,
that I can't forgive you.
Jane.
Let's go guys.
Get in honey, get in.
Jane, just a minute, honey...
Where are you going?
To the place I never
should have left, Tino.
Things have gotten
pretty heavy next door.
Son, look and learn,
that's what.
Better not talk too fast dad.
Son, I'll be by to
get you tomorrow, OK?
I'll be staying at this
address here.
Give me a call
if you need anything.
Laura, let's talk.
No, Amauri.
Why not?
Because you know how to talk,
you're good the logica
and Mister of the reason.
I always lose any
conversation with you,
I just don't need to lose
my life with your talking.
Laura! Laura!
Laura, I...
Hi.
Hard day, huh?
Very.
Wanta go have a drink?
You paying?
Four years looking
for the perfect girl.
Four years?
Shit, you were one finicky guy, huh?
I even had
this chart at college,
where I'd take note of all
the girls I had slept with.
And then Laura showed up
and I threw the chart away.
I planned everything just
for her to in the end
come up and tell me that
I plan things out too much.
And you and Jane,
how'd you meet her?
We met at school,
began dating, the condom leaked,
and we got married.
That's real nice.
Beautiful.
Thanks.
Bye, Wonder Woman!
Fabulous!
Bye Adelson honey!
See you Friday!
Until Friday, kisses!
Adelson, you still playing the part,
huh?
I sure am.
And it's all your fault, right?
My fault?
Yeah.
Why?
Because I never made so
much money in my life man,
and I even came out in
a magazine, look.
Let me see.
Well look at this,
the man himself!
VINTAGE HOUSE
Look at the guy,
looking good, huh?
I don't know how, but it seems
I was born for this kind of work, man.
Really
You're the...
Designer.
Designer of this...
Yeah, my bar,
Vintage.
Say it: vintage.
That's it!
Man, I can't believe it, huh?
Whose apartment is this mom?
It's grandma's.
Mom, are we going to be
staying here for long?
Amauri
What is it man?
I think it's much easier
for you to get back with Jane
than for me to get Laura back.
Of course, no doubt about it,
you're such a jerk man.
Yeah, well thanks
for your kind words.
No, no, really.
Thanks.
Amauri, when was the last time
you told Laura you loved her?
The last time I told her...
that I loved her?
Yeah. Declared your love,
I love you.
Jeez, when I met her,
I told her I loved her.
Are you crazy man?
Why?
You can't do that.
You have to tell
her everyday
that she's special.
Every day, Amauri.
But why?
Why, for God's sake, why?
Because they're special,
Amauri,
they are very special,
Amauri.
Right. Right.
I'm going to go get a pillow...
Tino?
Honey, may I suggest something?
Why don't you come here
with the kids?
Live in Miami?
The apartment here
is too big just for me.
My store is doing great,
and we have the best
hospital in the world.
Aww, I don't now mom,
I don't know.
I'll think about it.
Honey, what have
you got to lose?
Naughty dog, very naughty.
Sometimes it's the dog food,
you know?
Jeez!
Dad, how long is senhor Tino
going to be staying here?
Not too long I hope.
You're using this?
Yeah.
A teddy bear keychain,
worth three reais,
It's worth a lot to me.
And my dad,
how's he doing?
Alright.
And you guys?
Alright too.
I mean, my mom is
kinda flipping out,
can you believe she is thinking
to move to Miami together.
She's going where, Amauri?
Bruno told me now,
during lunch,
and I thought
you should know.
You'd better give her a call.
But, I call and
she doesn't answer.
Tino, after all you've done,
to leaving now.
If she doesn't answer your calls,
go after her.
You think so?
Of course. Fatso.
Jane! Jane!
Open the door, Jane.
Jane, I have to talk to you,
honey,
open the door,
Teté, Juninho!
Senhor Tino!
Senhor Severino,
help me out here.
Where's Jane, huh?
She's not here,
senhor Tino.
What do you mean?
Not here?
Where'd she go?
I think I heard her talking on the
phone that was going to the airport.
The airport?
-Yeah.
-That can't be.
Senhor Severino,
do you still your car?
Old faithful?
Sure do.
I can't believe this, no way.
For God's sake, why?
Hold it, hold it right there,
I need you bike.
Sorry about this bro,
sorry man.
Come back here, man!
Not now, not now!
Oh God.
Jane!
Lady, lady, I need a ticket,
fast, to any place,
as long as I get into
the boarding area,
because I have to
save my family, lady.
I have to save my family,
I spent all my money,
spent it all!
The only thing
I have left are
was the clothes with me
and a bicycle, worth around $250
that it is outside,
that I stole from its owner.
Please, you have to help me!
Don't you have mileage?
Yeah, mileage, those I have.
I didn't have to expose
my life with a stranger.
Jane'. Jane'.!
Don't close yet, mister,
mister, don't close the door,
look here, I have my ticket here.
Jane, Jane'.!
Open the door!
BOARDING CONCLUDED
Tino?
Jane?
Tino, what are you doing here?
Well, Janinha, it's because...
I came to tell you, if you decide
to go to Miami, I support.
I guess you're right, you're
and I just came
to say goodbye,
and tell you
all that I love you...
Dad.
What?
We're not going to travel.
Flo?
Of course not, Tino.
I just brought the kids here
to knowing our store.
Our store?
Uncle Olavo gave us this store,
is that it?
No, there's no "us" here,
no more,
there's no more "us".
And, in reality,
I like to open a store for me.
But Uncle Olavinho said they
don't make any money.
I love you.
I love you too, Tino.
Jane, I know we both said,
long ago,
Yeah.
But, we do change, don't we?
A lot.
Time and money makes
us change even more.
Listen,
I would do anything, even,
eat hot dog at lunch
and dinner every day.
But I just can't
live without you.
I can't go on
living without you, honey.
Let me fill in a form?
You're getting
in the way here,
-Why?
-you know that?
Why?
Because you think
that all you have.
No.
It's not that easy.
But, I'm good working
with people.
That's not the only thing, Tino,
there's a lot of things.
-I'm always well groomed.
-It's too small here!
It's too small here!
I'll sleep on the premises...
I just said that
they're too small.
I know, look...
And then, you won't fit...
You won't even
fit into a uniform.
We only have small and medium.
You won't fit.
Give me a chance?
I'll go get...
I'll get a form.
Don't worry ma'am,
I've already bought the stocks.
Look guys, Amauri.
Someone turn it up please.
No need for that guys.
Well, Roberto, I usully say that
inteligent couple rich together.
I can't believe you guys
are going to make me listen to this.
And what do you base
yourself on when you say that?
Based on my own experience.
On my marriage.
I have... I had an incredible wife,
who helped me a lot.
Laura.
Laura, I know you're watching
right now and a friend tell me
that we have to say the
feelings for our wife always.
But, I'm not very good
at that, really,
so I'm going to soy it the
only way I know how.
I always talk about the
five steps to getting rich,
today I'm going to talk
about the five things
more important without her
getting to not rich.
Love,
respect,
affection,
trust and,
most of all,
forgiveness.
7. MONTHS LATER
Hey kid, where's Jane?
Where's the baby?
Take it easy senhor Tino,
Jane is in her room with the baby.
So come with me then,
come on.
She keeps on gurgling...
Mommy's little darling,
look at your brother and sister, honey.
Honey, I'm sorry.
Hi honey,
look at how beautiful she is!
Beautiful.
Sorry I was late,
it's just that the store is so far...
No problem,
isn't she wonderful?
Wonderful.
No problem honey.
But, at least you brought...
Yeah... it's... ahh... right...
Did you bring it or not?
Yeah, sure.
Well?
It's right here,
a little surprise.
Tino, it's wonderful,
and I can't believe it,
That's the same that you broght
for Teteia when she born.
-What a beautiful thing.
-Really? Yeah, I remembered.
Honey, we're going to have to take
very good care of ourselves too,
We will, honey.
I'm serious, Tino.
And you are way over weight,
No way,
a heart attack, imagine.
THE END
You lose all you have.
Just joking!
Congratulations, triplets!
Triplets.
Three.
Doctor, three of them.
No way guys, lilac?
Lilac, you want lilac? No way!
She knows that
you're not gay.
She does?
Yeah.
And you didn't tell me?
But lilac?
Lilac will look horrible.
Lilac my ass,
that's what I say.
A-ha, a-hu,
I'm going to eat Uncle Olavo's cake!
Come on guys, no?
Blow out the candles,
Uncle Olavo.
I'm going
to eat your cake...
I don't think he's enjoying this,
but no problem.
Wealth is living a well-balanced
and happy life.
If it comes accompanied
by lots of money, better still.