www.sous-titres.eu
You got nothing on me.
All right, you can call my lawyer,
Saul Goodman.
Talk to my lawyer, all right?
You hear me. I got nothing to say.
I told you. You can call my...
You had my cell phone number!
You had my wife's name!
How'd you do it?
Talk!
Who you working with?
If you're ready to talk,
they want to get a statement.
Your side of what happened here.
Or we can hold him off
till another time.
Maybe you'll want to talk
to a lawyer.
There it is.
Yo, Adrian.
Rocky called.
He wants his face back.
Come on.
I got to cheer you up.
You see that?
That's your Get Out of Jail Free card.
You understand Get Out of Jail card?
Just blink once if you're following.
The D.A.'s worst nightmare
is that face out in public.
They're going to have to steer
a wide berth of young Master Pinkman
for fear of the P.R. poop storm
that will rain down on them
if this story ever gets out.
I mean, this beating?
Best thing for you.
You're home free.
Good, right?
Right.
You're now officially
the cute one of the group.
Paul, meet Ringo.
Ringo, Paul.
I am so sorry for this.
This should not have happened.
But it did.
No thanks to you.
But the plan did work.
We would have been locked up
right now if we didn't lure him away.
This, I just...
I never saw this coming.
What happens now?
I'll tell you what happens now.
Your scumbag brother-in-law
is finished,
done.
You understand?
I will own him when this is over.
Every cent he earns,
every cent his wife earns,
is mine.
Anyplace he goes,
anywhere he turns,
I'm going to be there,
grabbing my share.
He'll be scrubbing toilets
in Tijuana for pennies,
and I'll be standing over him
to get my cut.
He'll see me when he wakes up
in the morning
and when he crawls to sleep
in whatever rat hole's left for him
after I shred his house down,
I will haunt his crusty ass
forever
until the day
he sticks a gun up his mouth
and pulls the trigger
just to get me out of his head.
That's...
what happens next.
My advice...
that's probably not a good strategy.
They're scared of you right now.
They want nothing to do with you.
But if you hit them,
they're forced to hit back hard.
They will turn over every rock
hither, thither, and yon
until someone spills
the beans on you
and anyone associated with you,
present company included.
Yes, I think what Saul is saying
makes a lot of sense.
Move on with your life.
Leave it behind, all of it.
Nothing changes.
Once I walk out of here,
I get myself a new RV
and go start cooking again.
How exactly do you think
you're going to get away with that?
They will catch you.
So what?
I have a Get Out of Jail Free card.
I may have overstated the...
the power of your face.
Not this.
If the cops catch me...
I give them what they want the most.
You.
They nab me,
I make a deal
to give up the great Heisenberg
and his million-dollar drug ring.
You're my free pass,
bitch.
You're so sure.
Look, if he didn't give up my name
while Hank was beating him senseless,
he's never going to talk.
What do you think that was
in there, a bluff?
He wants your brother-in-law.
And there's going to be a many lawyers
creaming their underoos for this case.
I'd take it myself if it wouldn't
cause so much collateral damage.
And him cooking again.
When, not if, he gets caught,
and he's facing 20 years,
what'll he do then?
Believe me,
there's no honor among thieves.
Except for us, of course.
No, he'll...
He'll come around.
And if he doesn't,
there may come a time
to talk options.
Options?
I'm convinced that Mr. Pinkman
was involved in the manufacture
and distribution
of phenyl-2 methamphetamine,
specifically what we're calling
the blue meth.
I tracked him to a scrap yard
where he stored
an early '80s camper,
an RV.
While waiting for a warrant
to search this vehicle,
which I believed to be
a rolling meth lab,
I received a telephone call
telling me my wife Marie
had been injured in an accident.
Upon hearing the news,
I left Mr. Pinkman and his vehicle
to tend to my wife.
After arriving at the hospital,
I learned the emergency call was a hoax.
My wife, fortunately, was unharmed.
So I immediately went back
to the salvage yard,
but the RV was gone.
Most likely destroyed on site.
And it was at this point that you drove
to the home of Jesse Pinkman?
I think we're done here.
Agent Schrader needs to get home,
get some rest.
That's fine.
But just to confirm,
- you're taking the Fifth here?
- Yeah. That's correct.
We just want
to give you all a heads up.
Mr. Pinkman is pressing charges
in this matter.
He's given a detailed version
of events as he sees them.
- The word of a meth head.
- We know all about his history.
We're well aware,
but toxicology on Pinkman...
his blood is clean, he's not using.
The kid is even refusing
his doctor-ordered pain meds,
as far as we can tell.
Where do we go from here?
A couple of gentlemen
from OPR will come down,
probably tomorrow morning.
Janice will give us
an exact time on that.
And you men will be
continuing your investigation.
- Thanks for your time.
- Right.
We just need one more thing.
Photo of Agent Schrader's hands,
for the record.
Yes, of course.
Bandage off, if you would.
On the table is fine.
Flat on the table is fine.
It's all going to work out.
You've been too good to them
for too many years.
I hope it goes without saying
that we're not
talking to anybody about this, okay?
Marie, who?
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
I guess crime does pay.
I don't suppose you just came by
to insult me.
We need to talk.
You heard about Hank?
About what happened
with this Jesse Pinkman?
Yes, I know.
Whatever Hank was investigating,
him trying to find an RV,
is there any danger
that could lead back to you?
Why would it?
Is this why you're here?
I'm here to talk about Hank.
You know what's going to happen to him
if this Pinkman presses charges?
Hank could lose everything.
I thought maybe...
There's a way you could help him.
How?
Contact Pinkman.
Get him to drop the charges.
Look, I don't know
what kind of relationship
you picture me having
with this person.
I'm not asking.
He's not my friend.
I mean,
it's not as if we were even close.
I'm not asking.
But there must be something
you could say.
Isn't it even worth a try?
Hank is your family.
Not currently.
I said not currently.
I'm late. I have to go.
I was starting to get worried.
Car trouble.
That's a bummer.
You should call me next time.
I'll pick you up.
No sandals today?
I just thought...
a bit more professional.
Everything is on track.
We got our distillate.
Just waiting to...
Let's get our trays ready.
Clean, no moisture.
Done.
Is our...
Our solvent filtered?
I thought you might ask that.
Done.
That's good.
Hand in glove.
That's what we strive for.
You know,
this might be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
So, you the gentlemen?
Lucky you. I got a load to pick up.
I'm taking the 40 through to Memphis.
I could hammer it out in about 15,
but there's a girl down there.
Lainie or Lolly or something.
Maybe Fran.
She's got one of these fetish things.
Wants to get peed on.
I was hoping to see her tonight,
but she wants to sleep before 10.
So I want to wrap it up here ASAP
because traffic can be a wild card,
rubbernecking and such.
The surprising thing is
women who like to get peed on always
tend to be from the warmer climates.
You'd think the ones in the colder
zones would be more inclined.
Maybe it's a shock to the system
if the body's not properly acclimated,
but, you know, I leave that
for smarter minds than me.
Science is a mystery.
Take a gander.
Prices are negotiable.
A bulk gets you a discount.
I'm running a special
on these little honeys.
JHPs. Hollow-point bullets,
known by the natives as Black Death.
Check it out. You like that?
So sweet, you want to lick it.
Nickel-plated brass casing,
Lubalox coat for panache.
Sucker has six razor claws
that expand upon impact.
Shred your mama's head
like a cabbage.
Keep it. On the house?
I've been windjamming long enough.
Tell me what you're looking for?
What do you need?
What can I do you for?
Vests.
Vests?
Hell, yeah, we got vests.
Right here.
Sleek, comfortable,
thermally bonded
non-interwoven Kevlar fiber.
Stop a bullet like a soft wank
against a Quaker girl.
Just ain't getting through.
And lightweight?
Damn, so lightweight,
you'll forget you're wearing it.
They work?
Sure as shit, they do.
I don't leave home without it.
What the hell?
You broke my freakin' rib,
you maniac son of a bitch.
You're welcome!
What temperature did you set here?
There?
Station Five... 75 C.
I said 85.
8-5.
I wrote it down.
You said 75.
- I wrote it.
- Then you wrote it wrong.
That's not what I said.
I said 85.
It's always been 85...
not 75, not 95.
85.
This is chemistry.
Degrees matter.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Great. You're sorry.
Meanwhile, you've just brewed
50 gallons of useless sludge.
Congratulations.
Just dump it. Dump it all.
This batch is ruined.
You look nice.
I look like a TV weatherman.
You want a coffee?
Nah.
I squeezed some orange juice.
You want a glass of orange juice?
I'm all right.
What are you going to tell them?
Here's what you're
going to tell them.
He attacked you.
He attacked me?
He swung at you with something.
Attacked you with a pipe.
With a pipe?
It happened fast.
He resisted arrest,
and muscle memory kicked in,
and you had to disarm him.
Muscle memory.
Yes.
It happens all the time.
Years of training, and your body
acted faster than your brain.
You had no choice but to hit him.
You had to fight back...
I'm not going to go in there
and lie.
It's some lowlife degenerate
versus you...
Doing the job you're supposed to.
Why should you be the one who pays
for doing the right thing?
Oh, baby, it wasn't the right thing.
It's not what the job is.
I'm supposed to be better than that.
And you made one mistake.
No, it wasn't one mistake.
I've been...
unraveling, you know?
I don't sleep at night anymore.
I freeze.
I freeze up.
My chest gets all tight.
I can't breathe.
I panic.
Ever since that Salamanca thing.
Tuco Salamanca.
If ever a scumbag deserved
a bullet between the eyes.
It changed me.
And I can't seem to control it.
I tried to fight it.
But then El Paso.
And it's just gotten worse.
What I did to Pinkman...
that's not who I'm supposed to be.
That's not me.
All this...
everything that's happened,
I swear to God, Marie,
I think the universe
is trying to tell me something,
and I'm finally...
ready to listen.
I'm just not the man
I thought I was.
I think I'm done as a cop.
Now, this is not an easy decision,
but it is one that I have to make.
I'm sorry.
This whole...
Gale situation...
He's just not working out.
Yes. Now.
It may sound unorthodox,
but I think
our first best option...
Is Jesse Pinkman.
No, look. There's...
There's a shorthand
that exists between us...
experience together
at a level that, quite frankly,
I'm just never going to reach
with Gale.
Look, Mr. Fring,
when I accepted your offer,
I was told the lab is mine.
And I know best how to run it.
Thank you.
Yes, I will. I will.
Good-bye.
Listen, something's come up.
I think it's a good opportunity.
There's been a job opening.
I need a new lab assistant.
I already did my time.
Why don't you just go
get yourself a monkey?
I don't want a monkey.
I want you.
Oh, gee, thanks.
Well, not interested.
I got my own thing
going on.
Nice try
saving your ass head brother-in-law.
That's not why I'm here, Jesse.
There's more.
It's more than an assistant.
Partners.
We'll be partners again.
Split everything 50-50,
just like before.
$1.5 million each.
- I don't think you heard...
- I've heard...
you fine.
I said no.
Let me understand this.
You're turning down $1.5 million.
I am not turning down the money.
I am turning down you.
You get it?
I want nothing to do with you.
Ever since I met you,
everything I have ever cared about
is gone...
Ruined, turned to shit,
dead, ever since I hooked up
with the great Heisenberg.
I have never been more alone.
I have nothing!
No one!
All right?
It's all gone!
Get it?
Why...
Why would you get it?
What do you even care
as long as you...
get what you want?
Right?
You don't give a shit about me.
You said I was no good.
I'm nothing!
Why would you want me?
You said my meth is inferior,
right?
Right?
You said my cook was garbage!
Screw you, man!
Your meth is good, Jesse.
As good as mine.
50-50.
Yes. 50-50.
Partners.
Good.
This is the statement
you want to give?
Yes, sir.
Hank, you don't have to do this.
I do.
I'm good.
So we understand if we write it up
like that, you'll sign it.
That's the way it happened.
I accept the consequences.
In the light of these facts...
As of this moment,
you're suspended without pay.
I have to ask you to hand over
your badge and your gun.
Yes, sir.
Hold up.
Yes, sir?
I just want to tell you something.
And to be clear,
you didn't hear it from me.
I don't want you
to get your hopes up,
but the word in the pipeline is
Pinkman isn't pressing charges.
Why not?
Who the hell knows?
Maybe you have a guardian angel.
It went fine.
Well, fine means what it means.
Yeah.
I'll tell you all about it
when I get home, okay?
I don't know, baby.
I just think...
I think we may be okay.
Okay. I love you, too.
I need you to listen very carefully.
Two men are coming to kill you.
Come again?
They're approaching your car.
You have one minute.
I don't get the gag, jerk off.
Who is this?
They're coming.
Gomie, I don't know
what that call's supposed to be,
but it's dumb
even by your standards,
so call me when you get this.