So cigarettes and gas is...
$79.70 cents.
Crap.
There's an ATM right outside.
I don't have a card.
You can write
a personal check with I.D.
Kind of in between banks right now.
You think I could just
come back later?
I'm totally good for it.
I'd come back. I swear.
If it were me, I'd be,
"Totally, you know, no problem."
But my dad is this ginormous
hard ass.
He was in Fallujah for a year,
and he always checks the receipts.
I mean, like... always.
I've got to call him.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Hold on a second.
Maybe if we could,
trade.
Ever try it?
I smoke pot a lot sometimes.
I party.
But...
But that stuff's really addictive,
right?
Not really. It's just a media thing.
You know?
What's it like?
It's awesome.
Everything's
maximum interesting.
You get these
really cold
and sharp-like
action dagger feelings.
It's awesome.
Come on.
What do you say?
Have a nice day.
Subtitles:
Breys, Michvanilly
www.sous-titres.eu
How does it feel?
Does it hurt?
It's tight.
But is it painful?
It's hard to breathe.
You need your breathing.
Although let's not
lose sight of the fact
that you were the victim
of a terrible accident, Antonio,
so some discomfort
is to be expected.
Let's go with that one.
And spread the word.
I'm building a class-action, flight 515.
Victims' families would be great,
but I'll take anyone
on he ground who suffered emotionally...
anxiety, sleeplessness,
you get the picture.
Trouble?
Ted Beneke?
You cannot be serious.
That guys is a joke.
I called...
What does that even mean?
You dared me to tell the police,
and I couldn't do it, so you win.
If you want to stay in this house,
fine, but we are not married anymore.
I told you that I was done
cooking meth, Skyler.
I promised you that.
At least I didn't run off to go...
Everything that I did
I did for this family.
You just keep telling that.
And what is that supposed to mean?
You don't like it?
Then leave
- and take your drug money with you.
- That's what you want.
Jesus.
Garbage disposal.
You think this will get me
to move out?
You can screw Ted.
You can screw the butcher,
the mailman, whoever you want.
Screw them all.
I'm not going anywhere.
Suit yourself.
Is this a good or bad thing?
You want me to suit myself?
I'll suit myself to his face!
It's a bad thing.
Walter White to see Ted Beneke.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Beneke's on a conference call.
I will wait.
It could be a while.
I have all the time in the world.
Here we go.
Excuse me.
Mr. Beneke's not available.
- Come on.
- Sir.
Excuse me.
I can see you.
I can see you
standing right there in your office.
Now, come on.
Open the door.
Come on,
let's talk.
I just want to talk. That's all.
Come on, let's be men about this.
How about that?
I'm kind of in the middle
of something right now.
Yes, you are.
So open the door.
You're damn right you are.
You're right in the middle.
Just open the door,
and let's talk about it, okay?
Open the door, Ted, right now.
You don't want
to be a man about it? Okay.
Plan B. How do you like that?
Plan B.
What are you doing?
I'm talking with Ted.
Next time,
you'll open...
the door.
Damn it.
Can I just talk?
I just want to talk to him.
Calm down.
All right, I'm calm.
What do you want?
Come on.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You act like you're the first guy
this ever happened to.
I caught my second wife
screwing my stepdad, okay?
It's a cruel world, Walt.
Grow up.
I just wanted to talk to him.
Yeah, well, now I'm talking to you.
Consider this an intervention.
You could have been arrested back there.
You understand.
Speaking as your lawyer,
I'm always looking for billable hours,
but speaking
as your business associate,
I'm strongly advising
that you get your shit together.
Just cool it with this Beneke guy,
at least for now.
Let's talk shop
because I think
this is a great opportunity
to channel some of that negative energy
into something positive.
How did you know?
Sorry?
About Skyler.
About where to find me just now.
How did you know?
That's just my meticulousness.
Don't bog down in detail.
- The lesson here...
- Did you bug my house?
I didn't know it was your house, did I?
You had moved out.
- Besides, you basically told me to.
- I told you to?
You strongly hinted that I should.
You were worried
about your wife, remember?
You were concerned she might say
something to the police.
What? That's not true.
When the hell did I say that?
Let's not get lost in the who,
what, and whens.
The point
is we did our due diligence,
and she didn't talk.
She kept quiet.
She stood by you, which,
if you ask me,
is the ironical silver ling here.
On the one hand, sure,
she snuck off the reservation
to get some dirty, damp, and deep.
On the other hand...
You're fired!
- You're done!
- Good.
I won't cook meth anymore.
You're a crybaby.
Who needs you?
I'm unplugging the website,
so no more money laundering.
- How do you like that?
- I want you to remove those bugs today.
I want them out now!
You just bought a $300 suit, psycho!
Great,
drilled right into the stucco.
A little bit of putty,
you'll be fine.
Just make sure
you get all of those things.
A,
these things cost $800 a piece.
B, you're not that interesting.
So yeah, I'll get all of them.
Great line of work, by the way.
Real upstanding field.
I enjoy it.
You're free to leave now.
Anytime.
You know,
sometimes it doesn't hurt to have
someone watching your back.
What's up?
I can't begin to understand
what you're going through,
with all of your health concerns and
the stresses you've been under.
Still, as educators,
there are certain responsibilities
we need to be meeting here
to the school
and to the students themselves.
Of course.
Is this a Wheaten terrier?
Norfolk.
That's surprising.
Could you come back over
here and have a seat, please?
Sure.
You've been absent a lot recently,
and when you are here at school,
there have been
some behavioral questions,
and frankly I'm concerned.
Thank you.
Are you feeling okay?
And do you think
maybe I should call Skyler?
Let's just...
keep this...
What's wrong with you?
You're the one
who was talking about D.C.
This is how you get there.
You answer the bell.
You pay your dues.
Besides,
it's... you know, it's a big deal
to get picked for this.
El Paso's like
the Super Bowl.
I could get killed
crossing the street, okay?
Whatever.
I want to go.
What about last time?
Blue?
Thing is,
Thing is I'm supposed
to be getting on a plane right now.
The stuff this guy had was blue.
You sure about that?
I want to talk to him.
Taxi.
I'm sorry.
I need to talk to you,
but you weren't at your apartment.
I moved back home.
That's good, right?
Did you just get fired?
More like a sabbatical.
Indefinite.
So
what's up?
Should we go somewhere?
No. This is fine.
So,
I want an intro to your guy.
What guy?
Your guy.
Your distribution guy.
- The guy Saul hooked you up with.
- Come on, Jesse.
I thought about it,
and I want to.
It's the one thing I'm good at.
No, that is just not true.
You're good at a lot of things, son.
Like what?
What about your sobriety?
I told you. I'm not using.
Ever.
I just want
back into the business.
I don't.
I'm sorry.
I know, and that's cool.
I'm not asking you to cook.
What's this?
In the end, I just went with
two reflux condensers. I didn't
want to lose track of my Ph levels,
but I did everything else
just like you taught me.
Super careful in my amounts
and watched the numbers
every step of the way.
So what do you think?
It's good, right?
What
in the hell
is this?
What?
What? This. This.
This is my product.
This is my formula.
This is mine.
It's our product,
- but yeah, I was going to cut you in.
- You were going to cut me in?
I cut you in.
What the hell is your problem?
All I'm asking is for you to set a meet.
Absolutely not.
Why?
Because I am not going to lend
my name to an inferior product.
Look at the diameters here.
What did you use for reduction?
Don't tell me.
Platinum dioxide, right?
Mercury-aluminum amalgam.
The dioxide's too hard to keep wet.
You must've done it wrong, then.
Your color is all cloudy, so you were
struggling with distillation, too.
Now, this is very shoddy work,
Pinkman.
I'm actually embarrassed for you.
What?
No way. I gave out samples,
and everyone said it was the bomb.
They said it was the bomb.
And who are they? I wonder.
A bunch of meth heads?
They should know, right?
Sorry.
I can't help you.
Fine, ass wad.
You know what?
I'll contact the guy myself.
Good luck with that
because my guy is a pro,
and he doesn't deal with junkies.
- You know what? Eat me.
- Anytime, loser.
I can't believe it's only 4:00.
This day is dragging.
I wish I could stay.
So stay.
What's stopping you?
What?
Like everything, you mean?
How about my lunatic husband
refusing to leave the house?
So move in here.
And then my son
hating me even more.
It'll pass.
I went through that with the girls.
They adapt.
And now everyone at work
thinks I'm an evil,
ladder-climbing whore.
They're all fired
effective immediately.
What else?
Aren't you the answer man.
Where did it...
Where did it go wrong, exactly...
you and Walt?
I mean,
I always saw him as kind of...
mild-mannered.
Something, I don't know,
changed when he got sick, or...?
I don't know what changed, Ted,
and I just don't feel really comfortable
talking about it.
Sorry.
Just asking out of self-interest.
Got to make sure
I don't make the same mistake.
I would be amazed.
Just let me see
if I'm following you here, Russell.
You got this stuff
from some guy at Gasparza's
who was wearing tan pants
and who you're 80% sure
had a mustache.
That's it, right?
That's your brain
working at maximum capacity?
Russell.
Everything all right in there?
Mel.
The dude's name was Mel.
Well, there you go. See?
You served
an actual earthly function.
I can't believe I remembered that.
Mel who?
Does he have a last name?
Mel.
Wait.
Was it Mel?
Mark.
It was definitely an "M" name.
Man, I'm losing it.
Wait, wait.
Yeah.
It's gone.
It was an "M" name, though.
I remember the "muh" sound.
We'll go with the "muh" sound.
- Thanks a lot.
- Yeah.
He definitely had tan pants.
Remind me to get a vasectomy.
It's after 9,
so this bar that Girl George is at,
probably wall-to-wall
dirtbags by now.
Let's go have a little looky-loo,
see if we can't find
this M-named clown.
What?
It's a lead.
Lead to what?
To Heisenberg.
I told you it was only a matter of time
before this guy booted up again.
Here we go, my friend.
Don't hate me
because I'm beautiful, Gomie.
Just apologize and buy me a beer.
Man, you're reaching.
This stuff could be a knockoff
or left over from an older cook.
How do you know
Heisenberg's gearing up again?
How do I know?
Because I know.
I don't get it.
This is the reason
why you're blowing off the task force?
Chase down teeners?
I'm getting tired
of all the second guessing.
If you're not sufficiently stimulated
by this investigation,
do us both a favor
and ask for a transfer.
What is up with you lately?
Starting bar fights?
Turning down El Paso?
And now this bullshit?
Do you need to talk to someone
or what?
Talk to someone?
Talk to who?
I'm not trying
to step on your toes, bro.
I'm just worried about you.
- That's all.
- Appreciate that...
bro.
Now take your hand off my shoulder.
Yeah, the one that was on TV.
Did any little piece
fall on your property?
I'm not looking
for an entire wing here, Mr. Linkas.
It could be a nut or a bolt.
It could be a bag of peanuts,
just so long as it caused you pain
and suffering.
Closed.
Calling you back.
You had your chance.
I told you to get him cooking again,
and you blew it off, now it's too late.
The guy's gone mass maniac on us!
All I wanted was to show you two
your potential, and what do I get
in return? A bone contusion.
You want to see the scar?
I wish you two had...
Hi, there.
- How in the hell did you get Walt to...
- I made it.
You know the guy
who knows the guy, right?
Good news is, for a stage three cancer,
the guy's doing well physically.
Mentally, the guy's a disaster.
He's gone off the rails
over this thing with his wife.
My opinion, he's not coming back,
not on his own.
Your friends were at his place again,
by the way.
They drew something
on the street outside his house.
The scythe.
Animals.
- Does the lawyer know?
- Should he?
If you want this guy to produce again,
why not just tell him?
You're the only thing that stands
between him and an ax in the head.
I don't believe fear
to be an effective motivator.
I want investment.
For now,
I'm simply interested in time frame.
He will live
for the foreseeable future, yes?
Foreseeable, couple years at least,
barring acts of God
and men with axes.
From the lawyer,
I'm supposed to let you know
the Pinkman kid is looking to sell.
I don't work with junkies.
That's what I thought you'd say.
Probably for the best.
What I hear,
he and Walter are splitsville.
Really?
That's what Goodman says.
Cats and dogs.
Do the deal.
You have one unheard message.
Agent Schrader,
you need to be calling me back ASAP.
I've got Texas breathing down my neck,
and I'm not about...
Yeah, I haven't seen Matt
since my dad fired him,
like, a while ago.
Where can I find him?
- No idea. I haven't seen him...
- I know. You said that a few times.
Because I haven't seen him.
I don't know what else to say.
What's your name, darling?
Cara.
Where did this come from, Cara?
I... I don't know.
What is it?
Drugs?
I'm just going to come right out
and say it.
You're a bad liar, Cara.
Don't get me wrong.
Not the worst I've ever seen.
Once had a guy try to explain
the dope balloon up his butt
on bad Thai food.
Still,
you're not a very good liar.
I honestly don't know.
Stop.
You look like a good kid.
I'm not here to get you in trouble,
but tell me where this came from now!
I never do stuff like this.
I swear to God.
I tried it, and I hated it, so I...
- just gave it to Matt.
- And who gave it to you?
Some guy,
he came in a couple days ago
- and wanted to trade it for gas.
- Some guy? What's his name?
What did he look like?
I don't know.
He looked pretty normal.
You know? White...
I think his hair was lightish brown.
He had really blue eyes.
They were really, really blue.
Yeah, he's dreamy.
What else?
Piercings,
jewelry,
distinctive articles of clothing?
Come on.
Listen to me.
It's real important that I find
the person that had these drugs,
so if you can remember
anything else...
Come on.
Think.
He drove an RV.
Okay, good, good.
What can you remember?
What kind of RV? What color?
Did you spot a license plate?
I don't know the kinds,
and I didn't see the license,
but the color was, I think,
white, brownish color.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not helping you, but...
Please don't tell my dad.
Please tell me
that that camera works.
Dammit.
Bingo.
These eggs are good, Mom.
Thanks.
You know what's weird?
Dad's website.
It's been three days
since the last donation.
Yeah, well...
people lose interest.
So how long are you off for?
A few weeks.
We'll play it by ear.
I probably...
pushed it, you know,
going back to work so soon.
Think I can get a ride today?
Louis has a doctor's appointment.
So Dad can babysit now.
Right?
You won't have to take Holly to work
every day.
Sometime, maybe.
We'll see.
What's up?
I think you'll seriously enjoy, yo.
Wait.
No. Wait.
- What the hell? This is only half.
- That's right.
It's your half.
Where's the other half, bitch?
I mean, it was...
The whole thing was crazy, man.
Poor bastard. I felt sorry for him.
He actually thought we were
the cable guys, you know?
Anyway...
sorry about those miscalls, Chief.
I'm changing providers.
It won't happen again.
Are you going to El Paso, Hank?
Hell, yes!
With pointed boots and bells on.
Just I got this break
in the Heisenberg case.
The blue meth, you mean?
The teenth?
That teenth got things rolling.
I traced it to a gas station in Cibola.
That's where I got these.
The station's... closed circuit,
was down... surprise, surprise...
but I was able
to pull some of these snapshots
off an ATM security camera.
Now, I always thought these guys
might be camper cooking, right?
First off,
your typical Class C
motor home is gonna
grunt at least 5,000 pounds
of interior fixtures.
We're talking appliances, furniture,
built-ins. 5,000 pounds at least, okay?
See how high
that suspension's riding?
No way, no how, this thing's
carrying that kind of weight.
I mean,
this thing has been cleared out
and stripped down
to its tight and curlies.
For what?
Blood bank?
Maybe a bookmobile?
There's no clear view of the plates.
Yeah, well,
you can only get so lucky, right?
But the fact
that there's no front plate
tells me its likely
New Mexico registration.
I checked with DMV.
There are only 29 of these early '80s
Bounders registered in the state.
Only 29?
So I got to go, you know,
knock on some doors.
They need you in El Paso, Hank.
You bet. I...
I'm just going to wrap up
this Heisenberg thing first.
- So you're refusing the assignment.
- No, I'm not. I'll go. It's just...
- I need some more time.
- You're not hearing me, Agent Schrader.
You're out of time.
Are you going to El Paso now?
Tonight?
Just a simple yes or no.
I can't.
But that's only because
I'm really close
to something big here.
Better get to it, then.
This is KECA 480,
Albuquerque news radio.
KECA news time 10:13.
Our top story this hour...
Donald Margolis,
the air traffic controller criticized
for his role in the recent air disaster
in which 167 persons died,
was rushed to an area hospital
early this morning,
apparently the victim
of a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Police won't say whether or not...
Your half.