In the litlle village
where I was born,
life moved at a slower pace...
yet felt all the richer for it.
There, my two uncles were known
far and wide
for their delicious cooking.
They seasoned their zesty chicken
using only the freshest herbs
and spices.
People called them
"Los Pollos Hermanos",
the Chicken Brothers.
Today, we carry on their tradition
in a manner that would make
my uncles proud.
The finest ingredients
are brought together with loving care...
then slow-cooked to perfection.
Yes, the old ways are still best
at Los Pollos Hermanos.
But don't take my word for it.
One taste and you'll know.
Subtitles:
Breys, Michvanilly
www.sous-titres.eu
201.6.
Jesus, seriously.
Better over than under.
Over by a pound and a half.
I thought you were all,
like, precise.
Whatever. We'll just save
it out till next week.
No. We ship it as-is.
What are we, running a charity?
Come on, man,
we're gonna take it out.
Leave it.
One batch, one ship.
Stop complicating things.
Why are you purposely
giving him free meth?
These bitches are bleeding
us enough already.
You are paid extraordinarily well.
Why can't you just appreciate that?
I been crunching numbers, all right?
- You've been crunching numbers?
- I've been crunching numbers,
and I don't gotta be a
mathematician to figure out
that this deal you made is bullshit.
- We both earn...
- I know...
a million and a half each.
Whoop-de-doo.
What's he getting?
Say he's wholesaling
at 40 large a pound.
That's probably high.
High. What, for our stuff?
That's what I was getting.
Look, say he's getting 40 a pound.
All right? 200 pounds a
week for three months.
And, like, what happens at
the end of the three months?
Look, what... whatever.
200 pounds a week for three months.
That's 2400 pounds.
2400 times 40,000 is...
and I swear to God, I double-checked
this, like, 10 times...
96 million dollars.
All right? 96 million.
96 to our three.
That is messed up, yo.
That is so messed up.
Fairness-wise, I can't even...
You are now a millionaire,
and you're complaining?
What world do you live in?
One where the dudes who are
actually doing all the work
ain't getting fisted.
What is going on with you lately?
What's happened to you?
Hang on, can't we just...
We got to hash this out.
What's more important than money?
These things they
laughingly call pillows,
I would not give them
to prison inmates.
You want me to go ask for another?
Just remind me to
bring his from home.
They're not moving his legs enough.
Everybody.
Hi, Marie.
Is it okay if...
if I visit?
His color looks good.
Gomie, is that you?
Buddy. It's me.
That's you, Gomie?
Yeah, Hank. I'm right here.
Come here. Closer.
What is it?
Closer.
Asshole.
Man, he got you good.
I'm glad to see you still have
your twisted sense of humor.
Check this out.
I got something that'll
make you feel better.
I've been keeping an eye
on that blue meth of yours.
Six, seven weeks, nothing.
Then all of a sudden, boom.
It's popping up everywhere.
Look at the new locations.
Texas,
Nevada,
up in Farmington.
Even right here in town.
A teener here and there,
strictly street-level amounts.
Man, it's crazy.
How exactly is that supposed
to make me feel better?
Because you were right.
You're the only one
that saw this coming.
Three cheers for me.
This thing doesn't
do a damned thing.
Hank, it's probably
still on lock-out.
It's been an hour, right?
I'm hurting here.
I could use some meds.
Okay. I'll go find somebody.
No more shop talk.
Sorry.
I didn't see it coming.
What?
Damn right you did.
No, I didn't see shit.
Day late and a dollar short,
as usual.
The only reason I'm...
even breathing...
is I got a warning call.
A warning call? What do you mean?
One minute before they
attacked me,
somebody called my cell
and told me to expect it.
A voice scrambler.
It could have been anybody.
Marie's got my phone somewhere,
if you want to run the incoming.
Not that you're going to
learn anything worth knowing.
I don't get it. Cartel hit?
Who would have called to warn you?
I don't know.
Jesus.
Come on already.
Skyler, I had nothing to do...
Are we safe?
Yes.
Are you safe?
Absolutely.
What about you?
Face looks better.
How's it all going?
Anything you want to tell us about?
What, like my interesting life?
One day pretty much
bleeds into the next.
Been working a lot.
I got a job.
Job is good.
It's in a Laundromat.
- It's totally corporate.
- Corporate Laundromat.
It's, like, rigid.
All kinds of red tape.
My boss is a dick.
The owner? Super dick.
I'm not worthy or whatever to meet him,
but I guess everybody's scared of him.
The place is full of
dead-eyed douche-bags,
the hours suck,
and nobody knows what's going on,
so...
Sounds kind of Kafkaesque.
Totally Kafkaesque.
Majorly.
From the U.S. attorney in Santa Fe.
Very nice.
We've got all these nice
tulips and baby's breath.
This is chrysanthemum.
That looks like chrysanthemum.
Look at these Hank.
Aren't they beautiful?
- Beautiful.
- Look at the size of this basket.
It's got so many goodies in it.
Look, chocolate-covered pretzels
and cheese sticks
and some some fancy designer olives.
You had me at cheese sticks.
You're going to have
to fight me for those, Hank.
"Get well, and best
wishes from Ted Beneke
and all the folks at
Beneke Fabricators."
He gives you all this time off,
and now this?
Get me a job there.
I know. He's great.
Boss hall of fame.
I don't see anything
here from Kleinman.
They're going to have
to get on the stick.
How's everybody doing today?
Good. We're good.
How are you?
I'm very good.
Just going to do a quick
peripheral response, all right?
See where we're at.
Moment of truth?
Yeah. I wouldn't call it that.
All right, let's just
take a look here.
All right.
All right, I want you to
tell me if you can feel this.
All right.
How about this?
Okay.
How about now?
Do that one again, would you?
Right there?
Yeah, yeah, I feel it. A tingle.
Okay, on a scale of one to ten,
ten being your normal level of feeling
and one being no feeling at all.
I don't know.
A four?
Four. Okay.
And how about...
there?
A six.
Okay, good.
And...
here?
Yeah, still there. A little less.
A three. Okay.
All right, good.
Thank you very much, Hank.
Good, good.
So this is good news, right?
Definitely.
It looks like some
nerve function is returning.
Oh, thank God.
All right, so when do we
get him walking again?
It's important that
we manage our expectations.
We're talking about
months of very hard work,
and even then the odds,
they're not great.
But you can't know for sure.
When does he start physical therapy?
We've sent the paperwork
to your insurance.
It's high priority.
We should have pre-authorization
the next few days.
Certainly by early next week.
Next week?
No, that's not going to do it.
I've looked into this.
The sooner physical therapy begins,
the better his chances are.
He needs daily sessions.
Isn't that right?
Actually,
your plan's treatment program
covers four sessions a week.
Actually,
she asked the doctor.
Plan-wise, four sessions
a week is fairly typical.
And the therapists in your
network are mostly fine.
Mostly fine? Okay.
There's a ringing endorsement.
Look, if Hank had
more physical therapy,
with better therapists,
wouldn't it be more
likely he would walk?
It's very hard to say, Marie.
Is the health plan's way
medically justifiable? Sure.
Is it absolutely optimal?
You know, screw it.
I'll make sure he gets what he needs,
and they can reimburse me later.
Mrs. Schrader, I get your
frustration. Really, I do.
But my best advice is
stay in the network.
Don't go out of pocket.
Physical therapy is
just the beginning.
We're talking nursing care,
modifications to your home,
occupational therapy,
medical equipment.
It could run into the hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
So what?
We're just supposed to
compromise on his care?
Well, if you don't follow the
insurance company's procedures,
they may never pay you back.
I've seen patients and
their families go bankrupt,
waiting to be reimbursed.
Who is the best physical
therapist that you know?
I can give you some names.
But they're not likely
to be on your plan.
To hell with the plan.
There he is.
Finally. I went ahead
and started without you.
Ladies, this is Jesse-san.
He's in for the full treatment.
Kick off your shoes.
Lay back.
Exfoliate.
Maybe later.
So, where's the maestro?
Out parking the mini-van?
What do I look like, his shadow?
Who cares where he's at?
What am I doing here?
I was going to
have you two flip a coin,
but since the genius
can't be bothered,
today's your lucky day.
Look around, kiddo. It's all yours.
What?
This?
Yeah. You are now the owner
of this fine establishment.
For free?
Free? Ladies, cover your ears.
Not free.
Look, hey, this is a squeaky-clean,
highly profitable,
at least potentially...
local institution, looked upon with
favor by the Chamber of Commerce.
Better Business Bureau.
At $312,000, it's a steal.
312,000?
Don't you get it?
On the outside,
it's a nail salon, right?
On the inside,
it's the best money
laundry a growing boy could ask for.
Wait.
Ladies, thank you.
Thank you. Good job.
Come back here.
Sit. Come on.
Humor me here for a second.
Now, you know you need to
launder your money, right?
Do you understand the basics of it?
Placement, layering, integration?
I ain't buying no damn nail salon,
so just forget it.
You want to stay out of jail,
don't you?
You want to keep your
money and your freedom.
Because I got three little
letters for you. IRS.
If they can get Capone,
they can get you.
Here's you, right?
Pink, Pinkman. Get it?
Here's your cash.
You're out on the town.
You're partying hearty. You're
knocking boots with the chickie babes.
Who's this?
It's the tax man.
And he's looking at you.
What does he see?
He sees a young fellow with a big,
fancy house,
unlimited cash supply, and no job.
Now what is the conclusion
the tax man makes?
I'm a drug dealer.
Wrong.
Million times worse.
You're a tax cheat.
What do they do?
They take every penny,
and you go in the can
for felony tax evasion.
Ouch. What was your mistake?
You didn't launder your money.
Now, you give me your money.
That's called placement.
Hand me that little thinGod bin.
This is the nail salon, right?
I take your dirty money
and I slip it into the salon's nice,
clean cash flow.
That's called layering.
Final step, integration.
The revenues from the
salon go to the owner.
That's you. Your filthy drug
money has been transformed
into nice, clean, taxable income,
brought to you by a savvy
investment in a thriving business.
So you want me to buy this
place so I can pay taxes.
I'm a criminal.
And if you want to stay a criminal
and not become, say, a convict,
then maybe you should grow
up and listen to your lawyer.
Right, so you can get your 5%.
No, that's 17%.
I heard you say 5.
You said it right in front of me.
That was for your partner.
It's privileges of seniority and all.
But for you, it's the usual.
17%, and that's a bargain.
Hey, what, you... Hey, listen to...
Come on, I'm talking to you
about your future here.
Listen to reason.
How is your brother-in-law?
He'll live.
Good.
I'm glad.
Walter, you seem troubled.
How can I help you?
I asked to see you in order to...
clear the air.
There are some
issues
that could cause a misunderstanding
between us,
and I think it's in our
best interest
to lay the cards on the table.
That's the best way to do business.
My brother-in-law,
moments before he was attacked...
someone called to warn him.
I believe that same
person was protecting me.
Those two men,
the assassins...
I believe I was their prime target,
but that somehow they
were steered away from me
to my brother-in-law.
Because of this intervention,
I am alive.
And yet
I think that this person
was playing a much deeper game.
He made that phone call
because he wanted a shootout,
not a silent assassination.
In one stroke,
he bloodied both sides,
set the American
and Mexican governments
against the cartel,
and cut off the supply
of methamphetamine to the Southwest.
If this man
had his own source of product
on this side of the border...
he would have the market to himself.
The rewards would be...
enormous.
We're both adults.
I can't pretend I don't
know that person is you.
I want there to be no confusion.
I know I owe you my life.
And more than that,
I respect the strategy.
In your position,
I would've done the same.
One issue
which troubles me...
I don't know what happens
when our three-month contract ends.
What would you like to happen?
You know why I do this.
I want security for my family.
Then you have it.
Three million for three months.
That was our agreement.
Extended annually,
twelve million a year.
Call it fifteen.
Open-ended.
Would that be agreeable?
Part of the reason we talk about
what gets us riled up,
in our daily lives
is to help each other put a finger
on what our relapse triggers might be,
head off our disease
before it comes back.
Anyone?
Free license to bitch and moan.
How often do you get that?
Jesse, last time you seemed pretty down
about your job at the Laundromat.
Let me ask you something. If you had
the chance to do anything you wanted,
what would you do?
Make more green, man, a lot more.
Forget about money.
Assume you have all you want.
I don't know.
I guess I would make something.
Like what?
Not that it even matters, but...
work with my hands, I guess.
Building things, like...
carpentry or brick laying
or something?
I took this vo-tech class
in high school,
wood working.
I took a lot of vo-tech classes
because it was just a big jerk-off,
but this one time I had this teacher
name of...
Mr. Pike.
I guess he was, like, a Marine
or something before he got old.
He was hard of hearing.
My project
for his class was to make this
wooden box,
you know, like a small...
just like a... like a box,
you know, to put stuff in.
So I wanted to get the thing done
just as fast as possible.
I figured I could cut classes
for the rest of the semester,
and he couldn't flunk me
as long as I,
you know, made the thing.
So I finished it in a couple days.
It looked pretty lame,
but it worked,
you know,
for putting stuff in or whatnot.
So when I showed it to Mr. Pike
for my grade,
he looked at it and said,
"Is that the best you can do?"
At first I thought to myself,
"Hell, yeah, bitch.
"Now give me a D and shut up
"so I can go blaze one
with my boys."
I don't know.
Maybe it was the way
he said it, but...
it was, like...
He wasn't exactly saying it sucked.
He was just asking me honestly,
"Is that all you got?"
And for some reason
I thought to myself,
"Yeah, man, I can do better",
so I started from scratch.
I made another,
then another,
and by the end of the semester,
by, like, box number five,
I had built this thing.
You should've seen it.
It was insane.
I built it out of Peruvian Walnut
with inlaid Zebrawood.
It was fitted with pegs, no screws.
I sanded it for days
until it was smooth as glass.
Then I rubbed all the wood
with tung oil so it was...
rich and dark.
It even smelled good.
You know, you put your nose in it
and breathed in, it was...
It was perfect.
What happened to the box?
I gave it to my mom.
Nice.
You know what I'm going to say,
don't you?
It's never too late.
They have art co-ops
that offer classes,
adult extension program
at the university.
You know,
I didn't give the box to my mom.
I traded it for an ounce of weed.
He's a hero.
You don't deny coverage to a hero.
They'll say
they're not denying coverage.
No, I'm agreeing with you,
but I went through all this
with Walt.
You'll burn through your savings,
and then what?
You two managed, right?
You said yourself
that Elliot and Gretchen's money
didn't cover everything.
I've got to get back.
What? No.
No, you should rest.
Look, why don't you go in
and take a long bath
I put some fresh sheets on the bed.
I want to be there
in case he wakes up.
With all they're giving him,
he'll sleep till morning.
What are you doing here?
I just thought I'd stop by
to see how you're holding up.
Is this a bad time, or...
Marie, this is Ted, my boss.
Oh, you're Ted.
I've heard so much about you.
Thank you for your gift basket.
That was really thoughtful.
- It was really nice. Thank you.
- Cheese sticks.
You're welcome.
We care about Skyler so much
that naturally
that extends to the whole family.
Are you coming in?
Yeah, you should.
I'm sorry.
Come on in, Ted.
We were just having some wine.
Would you like a glass?
No, thanks.
I'm just on my way home.
- I just thought I'd...
- You know, I...
I am really beat.
I think I'm going to take that bath.
It was nice to meet you, Ted,
and thank you again.
Nice to meet you, too, Marie.
Give my best wishes to your husband.
I will.
Thanks for stopping by,
but it's actually not a...
not the best time for a visit, so...
Can we just talk for a minute?
I know you need to be
with your family, but...
I haven't heard from you in days
- I left messages...
- I'm so sorry.
You gave me all that time off,
and I...
That's not my point.
I care about you. That's all.
It's just this whole thing with Hank
has been one non-stop horror show,
you know, so...
I just want you to know
that I'm here for you.
Thank you.
But I really do need you to...
Skyler, I've got to say
your sister seeing me here...
I mean...
So what?
I'm divorced.
You're divorced. So what?
Let's talk about it later, okay?
Is there some reason for secrecy
I'm not getting? Because...
Not now.
- Just tell me...
- You really want to do this now?
Are you really going
to make me do this right now?
Yeah, you're right.
Bad idea to come here.
I'll see you in a day or two.
Back at the office.
Take as much time as you want.
I can't believe
you had to crush the RV.
Must've been, like...
depressing.
For real. That's a stone loss.
No one misses it more than me.
Free to cook anytime, anywhere.
No quotas, no one to answer to.
What's the point of being an outlaw
when you've got responsibilities?
Darth Vader had responsibilities.
He was responsible
for the Death Star.
True that. Two of them bitches.
Just saying. Devil's advocate.
I've got to pay taxes now?
What the hell?
That's messed up. That's Kafkaesque.
- Church.
- Right.
Let's kick it back into gear.
Let's start slinging again.
Let's do it.
Life's too short. That's what I say.
Hell, yeah. We don't need no RV.
Alls we need is a bicycle,
- some Drano, soda bottles...
- Nah, no shake 'n bake.
Where's your self-respect? Come on.
Maybe it ain't top shelf,
but we could at least move it.
Still kind of dry out there.
It'll sell on the street.
Who says we sell on the street?
Maybe I know a whole new market.
Maybe alls we need is the meth.
What's the yield?
The yield. Come on.
201.8.
I see a couple new faces.
Anybody want to introduce
themselves?
Don't all speak at once.
My name's Brandon.
You want to tell us something
about yourself?
Why I'm here...
it's just one thing.
It's meth.
It's bad.
Thought I had it kicked
a couple times, you know,
but then... Jesus.
This new version of it
hit the streets and...
Not that blue stuff.
Sorry, I didn't raise my hand.
Go ahead.
This is what we do.
Yeah, exactly, the blue stuff.
You had it, too.
Yeah, bro.
I wish I never even heard of it.
It was like lighting
my whole head on fire.
Stuff will burn you down.
Only reason I have a hope in hell
is because it's long gone.
That's the shame of it.
- Don't tell me that.
- I hear it's back in town.
Stay strong, brother. Stay strong.
It's gonna be okay.
I swear to God, I'll do it.
I will go to the press.
I will go to 48 Hours.
I will go to Nightline.
Maybe Nightline doesn't exist anymore.
It doesn't matter.
They will all take it,
and they will run with it
because he is a hero,
and he is not going to be
in a wheelchair at 43.
I know
Skyler's already told you this,
but if there's every
anything that you need,
anything at all...
It's good to have you here.
Both of you.
I just wish there was...
something more that we could do.
We can always pay their bills.
Please,
it's tens of thousands of dollars.
We have the money,
more than enough.
Walt earned it.
I think Marie should know the truth.
Skyler, I really don't think
this is a good idea.
- I think that...
- He earned it gambling.
Walt and I...
We've had our problems lately.
You know that.
And...
what it all came down to
really was...
money.
Pure and simple.
When Walt was diagnosed, it...
It changed him.
Looking back, I don't think
I ever really understood
what it was
that he was going through.
It was more than facing death.
It was knowing
that he was going to leave behind...
nothing.
And so that's how this all started.
For better or worse,
he wanted to provide,
and so...
he paid his medical bills
the only way he knew how.
I thought that Elliot and Gretchen
paid for your treatment.
Yeah, I thought so, too,
but the truth is
he never took their money, not a dime.
He was too proud to take
what he considered to be charity.
Isn't that right?
He put his mind to it and...
You know how Walt is.
He's a problem solver,
and he read books,
and he did a whole
bunch of research,
and he came up with...
this system.
A system?
A system for counting cards
in Blackjack.
What do you mean, like Rain Man?
I don't pretend to understand,
you know, all the details,
but he was convinced
that if you put enough money into it,
he'd have a...
God, what is it?
A statistical edge?
Yes, statistical...
So he...
Every spare minute,
Walt was at some
card table somewhere,
and at first he went to the casinos,
but then he realized that...
But then he realized
that the casinos report
your winnings to the IRS,
and if it gets reported,
your family might find out,
and if you do not want
your family to find out,
then you find another place
to gamble,
like an illegal,
backroom game.
You remember all those long walks
that Walt used to take,
all that time
he used to spend away from home?
I guess for a couple months there
you were...
sort of leading a double life,
weren't you?
Your fugue state,
was that some sort of cover?
He did not fake that, Marie.
The night that Walt disappeared...
he lost $14,000.
It was his pension fund,
our savings,
basically every last dime
we had to our name,
gone.
He couldn't live with it.
He was suicidal.
But you have to understand
that as soon as he got out
of the hospital,
he went right back to gambling.
I mean, that's how deep this went.
How could you
do that to her, Walt?
Anyway, this system of his...
he finally got it to work.
So all this is to say
we have the money.
No more gambling.
But we have the money.
How... much money?
It's in the seven figures.
Holy Mary, Mother of God.
What can I say?
I did very well.
You will take our money.
Use it to take care of Hank.
Please.
Marie, let us help.
- Does Walt, Jr. Know about this?
- Absolutely not,
and I need to keep it that way,
and Hank's got enough
on his mind right now,
so can we just please
keep this between us?
I just... I need to...
We'll talk about it later.
How did you come up with that?
I mean, where did you possibly...
I learned from the best.
Somehow something tells me
that Hank is here because of you.
And I'm not forgetting that.