Is it possible that the water
has already killed them?
- Yes.
- Then what?
If it doesn't work?
Urgh!
Get them in the truck.
Get the hoses in.
Start pumping.
Uh... I'm here to see my husband,
Vasily Ignatenko.
He's a firefighter from
Chernobyl. I have permission.
Chernobyl?
I'm sorry. No visitors.
Well... but Major Burov
told me.
- He said...
- No exceptions.
Please. I've come all the way
from Kievskaya oblast.
Uh... excuse me.
- Uh... excuse me, excuse me.
- Who are you?
- What are you doing here?
- I have a pass.
You can't be here.
It's not safe.
I am here to see my husband.
Vasily Ignatenko.
He's a firefighter
from Chernobyl.
I know who Ignatenko is.
But you can't.
I have permission. I... I've...
You can see him for 30 minutes.
Not a minute more.
And you cannot touch him
in any way.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah.
Room 15.
Thank you.
- You're not pregnant, are you?
- No.
I won't have to
give that to you.
There they are.
Wait, wait.
I haven't finished yet.
No, no, he has it.
Yeah, that's good.
Look who the cat dragged in.
What did I tell you?
There's no hiding from you,
is there? Eh?
Just... easy.
Easy. It's OK. OK.
Yeah. OK.
How? How... How did this happen?
Who gave them the idea?
- Are you suggesting I did?
- Someone did.
Someone decided
that the evacuation zone
should be 30 kilometres,
when we know, here...
Caesium-137
in the Gomel District,
that's 200 kilometres
away!
- It was decided.
- Based on what?
- I don't know!
- Forgive me.
Maybe I... I've just spent
too much time in my lab.
Or maybe I'm just stupid.
Is this really
the way it all works?
An uninformed,
arbitrary decision
that will cost
who knows how many lives,
made by some apparatchik,
some career Party man?
I'm a career Party man.
You should watch your tone,
Comrade Legasov.
Comrades,
we have visual confirmation
that the fire
is nearly extinguished.
There's also been
a reduction in Iodine-131
- and Caesium-137 emissions.
- Good. Yes?
But the temperature is rising.
And uh...
There's a spike in Zirconium-95.
That's from the cladding
on the fuel rods.
Meaning what?
The meltdown has begun.
Get off me!
- Stop moving.
- Get off me!
Get off him!
You're hurting him!
You can't be in here.
- What's happening to him?
- Get out!
- Please!
- You can't be in here.
Yes?
Put him through.
- Well?
- The fire's nearly out.
Bubbler tanks are being drained.
We have successfully eliminated
the risk of a thermal explosion.
And?
The situation inside the core
is deteriorating
faster than anticipated.
The concrete pad will last
for six to eight weeks
but, after that, Legasov
estimates a 50% chance
that the fuel
will breach the pad
and melt down
into the groundwater itself.
Wh... And where does
this groundwater go?
The Pripyat River,
which feeds into the Dnieper...
..the primary water supply for
approximately 50 million people.
Not to mention crops
and livestock would be unusable.
We're recommending we install
a heat exchanger under the pad
to lower the core temperature
and halt the meltdown.
And in order to do that,
I'm told that we will need...
..all of the liquid nitrogen
in the Soviet Union.
Ah.
- Oh. All right.
- Of course, we'll also need...
Whatever you need, you have it.
That should be clear.
- Yes.
- Anything else?
- No. Thank you.
- Yes.
I'd like to address
the 30km exclusion zone.
Wait... Who?
Professor Legasov, is that you?
What exclusion zone?
Minor details,
General Secretary.
Um... Premier Ryzhkov
has determined...
If he determined,
then he determined.
Look, Professor Legasov,
you are there
for one reason only.
Do you understand?
To make this stop.
I don't want questions. I want
to know when this will be over.
If you mean when will
Chernobyl be completely safe,
the half-life of Plutonium-239
is 24,000 years.
So, perhaps we should just say,
"Not within our lifetimes."
I think you and I
should take a walk.
It's late. I'm tired.
We're taking a walk.
What is it you want?
An apology?
Not gonna sit back and...
What will happen to our boys?
Which boys? The divers?
The divers, the firefighters,
the men in the control room.
What does the radiation
do to them, precisely?
Well, at the level
some of them were exposed,
ionising radiation tears
the cellular structure apart.
The skin blisters,
turns red then black.
This is followed by
a latency period.
The immediate effects subside.
The patient
appears to be recovering.
Healthy, even, but they aren't.
This usually only lasts
for a day or two.
Continue.
Then the cellular damage
begins to manifest.
The bone marrow dies.
The immune system fails.
The organs and soft tissue
begin to decompose.
The arteries and veins
spill open like sieves...
..to the point where you can't
even administer morphine
for the pain,
which is... unimaginable.
Within three days
to three weeks, you're dead.
That is what will happen
to those boys.
And what about us?
Well, we've...
We've gotten a steady dose,
but not as much of it.
Not strong enough
to kill the cells,
but consistent enough
to damage our DNA.
So, in time... cancer.
Or aplastic anaemia.
Either way, fatal.
Well...
In a sense, it would seem
we've gotten off easy, then...
..Valery.
I've seen them before.
Now you know why
I wanted to take a walk.
You can presume
the work site is bugged.
And our rooms.
Even our bathrooms.
They've been here
the whole time?
Of course they've been here
the whole time.
But if we're seeing them
out in the open now...
..it's because
they want us to know.
You've seen that?
The fuel is melting
faster than we expected.
I know. I have a plan.
- Heat exchanger, I hope.
- Yes.
There's something
I've wanted to ask you, comrade,
but I see you're already asking
yourself the same question.
Why did it explode?
I've worked the numbers
over and over,
presuming the worst possible
conditions in an RBMK reactor.
And I always get
the same answer.
Which is?
- It's not possible.
- And yet...
You're not gonna
solve this here.
Not on paper.
Everyone who was
in the control room -
Dyatlov, Akimov, Toptunov -
they're all in Moscow.
Hospital number six.
We need to find out exactly
what happened that night.
Moment by moment,
decision by decision.
Go now, while they're
still alive. Talk to them.
Because if we don't find out
how this happened,
it will happen again.
And, Khomyuk...
..be careful.
Well, fuck you.
Here's one. Here's one.
What's as big as a house, burns
20 litres of fuel every hour...
..puts out a shitload
of smoke and noise...
..and cuts an apple
into three pieces?
A Soviet machine made to cut
apples into four pieces!
- Who's in charge here?
- I'm the crew chief.
I'm Shadov,
Minister of Coal Industries.
We know who you are.
How many men do you have?
On this shift, 45 here.
100 in total.
I need all the 100 men
to gather their equipment
and get on the trucks.
Do you? To where?
That's classified.
Come on, then.
Start shooting.
You haven't got enough bullets
for all of us.
Kill as many as you can.
Whoever's left, we'll beat the
living piss out of each of you.
- You can't talk like that!
- Shut the fuck up!
This is Tula.
This is our mine.
We don't leave
unless we know why.
You're going to Chernobyl.
Do you know
what's happened there?
We dig up coal, not bodies.
The reactor fuel
is going to sink into the ground
and poison the water from Kiev
to the Black Sea - all of it.
Forever, they say.
They want you
to stop that from happening.
How are we supposed to do that?
They didn't tell me,
because I don't need to know.
Do you need to know,
or have you heard enough?
Now you look like
the Minister of Coal.
Vasily?
Ah. No, no, no.
They told you, no touching.
It's not safe.
They touch you.
If it's safe for them,
it's safe for me.
You...
Where are the others?
They took them
to a special room.
They won't tell me where.
Can you open the curtains?
- Hm?
- Open the curtains.
Mm.
Please tell me
what you see outside.
Tell me everything.
Um...
I can see the Red Square.
And... the Kremlin.
Spasskaya Tower, Mausoleum.
Do you see St Basil's?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
Yes. It's beautiful.
I told you.
I told you I'd show you Moscow,
didn't I?
- Huh?
- Yeah. Yes.
Thank you.
I'm not eating that,
it's shit.
Give me something else.
I'm not a nurse,
Comrade Dyatlov.
I'm a nuclear physicist.
Well, then,
Comrade Nuclear Physicist...
..unless you happen to have
a butter and caviar sandwich
on you...
..you can get the fuck
out of my room.
What?
I'm not good at this, Boris.
The lying.
Have you ever spent time
with miners?
No.
My advice, tell the truth.
These men work in the dark.
They see everything.
Andrei Glukhov, crew chief.
Do these work?
To an extent.
Of course.
So, what's the job?
We need to install
a liquid nitrogen heat exchanger
underneath this concrete pad.
There's no way to approach
from the interior
of the building,
so you have to get at it
from underground.
And what's above the pad?
The core of the nuclear reactor,
which is... melting down.
What, like...?
Essentially.
Is it gonna fall on top of us?
Not if you're done
within six weeks.
Dimensions?
Break ground here...
dig a tunnel 150 metres to here,
excavate a space 30 by 30 metres
for the heat exchanger.
Because we need to keep
disruption of the ground above
to a minimum,
you can't use
any heavy machinery.
- It has to be done by hand.
- I'm gonna need more men.
400, at least. We'll have
to work round the clock.
How deep do you want this
tunnel? Six metres?
- 12.
- 12? Why?
For your protection.
At that depth,
you'll be shielded
from much of
the radiation.
The entrance to the tunnel
won't be 12 metres below ground.
No.
And we're not
12 metres below ground now.
No. We're not.
We have some
equipment here on site.
More will arrive by midnight.
- You can start in the morning.
- No. We start now.
I don't want my men here
one more second
than they need to be.
If these worked...
you'd be wearing them.
- Are they all like that?
- They're all like that.
- Yes?
- What's it up to?
It's uh... 50 degrees.
Fuck.
Hey!
Hey, you.
- We need fans.
- For what purpose?
What do you mean,
"For what purpose?"
To dig your fucking tunnel,
that's why!
- Who's talking to you?
- Whoa, whoa. Comrades...
It's 50 degrees in there.
We can't breathe without masks,
we can't breathe with the masks.
It's like a fucking oven.
We need ventilation.
Fans will put dust in the air,
the dust will go in your lungs.
I've been breathing dust
in my lungs for 20 years.
Not this dust. I'm sorry.
For your own good, no fans.
My name is Ulana Khomyuk.
I'm a nuclear physicist
with the Chernobyl Commission.
I want you to tell me
everything that happened
on the night of the accident.
Is that all right?
Yes.
I want to tell.
All right.
Your official title was...?
My name is
Leonid Fedorovych Toptunov.
I am the Senior Reactor
Control Chief Engineer
at Chernobyl
Nuclear Power Plant.
Senior engineer?
How old are you?
I'm 25.
Lyusya. Lyusya.
Yes, I'm here. I'm here. I'm...
Have you been here
this whole time?
No-one said I should leave.
I did.
30 minutes, I said.
Where have you been...
when he's in pain?
When the sores
stick to his gown,
when he soils himself
five times a night,
I looked after him.
Where have you been?
In the north and west wing,
where there are dozens
of patients from Chernobyl
exactly like him.
- It isn't safe for you here.
- He's my husband.
Not any more.
He's something else now.
Do you understand?
He's dangerous to you.
He's burned.
Go home.
Please...
I won't take much longer.
I uh...
I don't want him to die, though.
Stay on the other side
of the plastic...
..or I'll have you
removed by security.
- Lyusya.
- Yes, my love.
Is it day?
No, it's night-time now.
I think I had a dream.
And it's just gone.
Vasya...
..we're gonna have a baby.
The fire is out.
It's out, Valery.
The miners are making
incredible progress.
They say the whole job
will be finished in four weeks.
- Four weeks?
- Can you believe that?
I know the job isn't over...
..but it's the beginning
of the end.
I'm sorry to bother you,
Deputy Minister, but...
..it is the miners.
What? You wouldn't give us fans.
It's too hot for clothes.
So we're digging the old way,
the way our fathers mined.
We're still wearing
the fucking hats.
What do you want?
You're not as protected now.
Are you telling me
that'll make a difference?
When this is over...
will they be looked after?
I don't know.
You don't know.
So, the power level jumped
from 200 to 400 megawatts?
Yes. Very fast.
Why didn't you initiate
an emergency shutdown?
Why didn't you press
the AZ-5 button?
We did.
I reported the increase
to Akimov,
and he pressed the button.
Leonid, that's...
that's not possible.
He did. I swear.
I saw him do it.
And that's when it exploded.
What?
Um...
Which room is Akimov?
27.
I pressed it before the explosion.
Before...
Why?
Why would that happen?
I shut it down.
I pressed AZ-5.
Thank you, Comrade Akimov.
I did everything right.
Get out. Get out!
Get out of here.
Let me go. Let me go!
- Stop it. Stop it!
- Get out.
You let her in that room, inside
the plastic, touching him?
- Did you know she's pregnant?
- It's not true.
- What have you done?
- What kind of a place is this?
Where is her protection?
Do you have any idea
what you're dealing with?
- Of course, I do. Please, I...
- No!
- People will hear about this.
- Wait.
People are going to hear.
Understand?
Everyone is going to hear.
What is everyone gonna hear?
I am with the official
Chernobyl Commission.
I've been authorised
by Valery Legasov.
- You can check. My name is...
- We know who you are.
What is everyone gonna hear?
- You have your notes?
- Yes.
Khomyuk was arrested
last night.
What?
- Why?
- I don't know.
Was it...
Of course it was.
- I'm working on it.
- Boris...
I'm working on it.
What more do you want from me?
Fix your tie.
They'll see you now.
After thousands of sorties,
our brave helicopter crews
successfully extinguished
the fire.
The miners are working
heroically to ensure
the fuel does not reach
the groundwater
and, furthermore,
there's no longer a threat
of additional explosion.
The Soviet people
have faced the challenge
and risen to the task, and they
and everyone in this room
are to be commended.
Lastly, Professor Legasov and I
have been vigilant
to protect the security
interests of the state.
Since the unfortunate
release of information
following the accident,
we believe that there has been
no further lapse.
Comrade Charkov...
we hope we have lived up to
the highest standards
of the KGB.
- You have.
- Thank you.
Professor Legasov will now speak
about the work that remains.
Thank you.
Deputy Chairman Shcherbina
has given you the good news,
and it is good.
The immediate danger is over.
Now, I'm afraid,
a long war must begin.
There is an enormous amount
of radioactive debris
and contamination
spread out across a zone
of approximately
2,600 square kilometres.
This entire region must be
completely evacuated.
We must go to every town,
every village, to ensure this.
All animals still surviving
within the zone,
whether domesticated or wild,
must be presumed contaminated
and will have to be destroyed
to prevent the spread
of radiation and disease.
In the immediate area
surrounding Chernobyl,
uh... every rock, every tree,
the very ground itself,
has absorbed a dangerous amount
of radionuclides,
which will be carried
by the wind and the rain
if left exposed, so we will
have to raze entire forests.
We will have to rip up
the top layer of earth
and bury it under itself,
approximately
100 square kilometres.
Um... and finally,
we will need to construct
a containment structure
around the power plant itself,
which will, of course,
still be extremely...
There will be deaths.
What amount of time
and how many men do you require?
We expect this liquidation
effort to take three years
and approximately 750,000 men,
including a number of doctors
and structural engineers.
How many deaths?
Thousands.
Perhaps tens of thousands.
Begin at once.
- Comrade Charkov.
- Valery!
Yes, Professor?
My associate
was arrested last night.
Oh?
I mean no disrespect,
but I was wondering
if you could tell me why.
I don't know
who you're talking about.
She was arrested by the KGB.
You are the First
Deputy Chairman of the KGB.
I am. That's why
I don't have to bother with
arresting people any more.
But you are bothering
with having us followed.
I think the Deputy Chairman
is busy.
No, no.
It's perfectly understandable.
Comrade, I know you've heard
the stories about us.
When I hear them,
even I am shocked.
But we are not what people say.
Yes, people are following you.
People are following
those people.
You see them?
They follow me.
The KGB is a circle
of accountability.
Nothing more.
You know the work
we're doing here.
- You really don't trust us?
- Of course I do.
But you know the old Russian
proverb. "Trust but verify."
And the Americans think that
Ronald Reagan thought that up.
Can you imagine?
It was very nice
speaking with you.
I need her.
So, you will be accountable
for her?
Then it's done.
- Her name...
- I know who she is.
Good day, Professor.
Well, that went
surprisingly well.
You came off like a naive idiot.
Naive idiots are not a threat.
I'll come back
when the paperwork's complete.
- Are you all right?
- They didn't hurt me.
They let a pregnant woman
into a room with a...
Doesn't matter.
They were stupid, I was stupid.
Dyatlov won't talk to me.
Akimov, yes,
Toptunov, yes, but...
Valery, Akimov...
..his face was gone.
You want to stop?
Is that a choice I even have?
Do you think the fuel
will actually melt through
- the concrete pad?
- I don't know.
40% chance, maybe.
I said 50.
Either way, the numbers
mean the same thing. "Maybe."
Maybe the core will melt
through to the groundwater.
Maybe the miners I've told
to dig under the reactor
will save millions of lives.
Maybe I'm killing them
for nothing.
I don't wanna do this any more.
I want to stop...
..but I can't.
I don't think you have a choice
any more than I do.
I think, despite the stupidity,
the lies - even this -
you're compelled.
The problem has been assigned
and you will stop at nothing
until you find an answer,
because that is who you are.
A lunatic, then.
A scientist.
Did you know that they were
running a safety test?
- Yeah.
- There's something else.
Akimov says
they shut the reactor down,
and Toptunov confirms it.
- They pressed the AZ-5.
- Apparently not soon enough.
No...
They say Akimov pressed AZ-5...
and then the reactor exploded.
If it had been just one of them,
I would've put it down
to faulty memory, or...
delusion, even,
but... they both agreed.
They were adamant.
Comrade.
- Do you think it's possible?
- I think it makes no sense.
I think it's what I would say
if I was trying to cover
my own mistakes.
But?
I believe them.
Then you should pursue it.
We have to pursue
every possibility,
no matter how unlikely...
..no matter what
or who is to blame.
I'll go back to the hospital
and re-interview Akimov
and Toptunov...
..if they're still awake.
They're not.
Khomyuk.