Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Show.
Please, pay attention!
I need you to put your cell phones,
beepers, and radios in the container.
Is this necessary, Agent Peña?
- I'm afraid so, Captain.
- Please. I'll take that.
One of my guys
says one of your guys
is working for the cartel.
They have any proof?
Can't say yet.
But this warrant will be hard to execute
if they're one step ahead.
It's just a precaution.
- Gracias.
- Okay.
For the next three hours,
we'll be running silent.
- My colleagues and I will take the lead.
- And the target?
I'll just say that it's everything
you've trained for.
We're advisors.
We work together, same as always.
Credit's all yours.
Gentlemen, you heard!
I need you to be tight and right.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Let's go.
In case you're confused, Capitán,
I wouldn't have come all the way
from Bogotá if it wasn't a big deal.
My men's safety. That's what I care about.
I make the final call
if anything feels off.
You follow?
My kid gave it to me
right before I went out on this buy-bust.
Some Jamaican took a rip at me,
missed by that much, so...
I rub it for luck ever since.
So, what are we doing here?
We're arresting
one of the godfathers of Cali.
Applauded
by the multitude present on 10th street,
president-elect Ernesto Samper Pizano
is welcomed by the people of Colombia...
I don't give
Gilberto Rodríguez credit for much,
but I have to hand it to him...
he was a man in control.
It's too early.
- I rise early. I'm up with the sun.
- Up all right!
He was married to three women.
At the same time.
And he managed them the same way
he ran his business.
Scheduled down to the minute.
Wife number three got him
Monday and Tuesday.
Hi!
How did it go, honey?
Very good! Look, what a beauty.
Number two...
got him Wednesday and Thursday.
And wife number one
got him on Friday and Saturday.
Look at that pass. Goal!
Damn it, what sort of defense is that?
Piece of shit!
I'm paying your fucking salaries!
Sundays were for football.
All the wives were invited
if they wanted to come.
They usually did.
Thank you.
And they all got along.
That was the deal.
And he made it work. He insisted on it.
He made far more friends than enemies.
I can help you expand your businesses...
And he would count on those friends
to protect him.
I could help you make millions.
His retirement was going
to go his way, too.
He wasn't going to die
on some shitty rooftop.
Nobody was stabbing him in the back,
nobody forcing him out.
Like I said, he was a man in control.
The guy who never made
a wrong move in his life.
A guy who built a billion-dollar empire,
brick by brick.
A guy who owned every cop in town.
A guy with a get-out-of-jail-free card
burning a hole in his pocket.
And you want to go after him? Shit.
You'd have to be crazy, stupid, brave,
and lucky all at the same time.
Two units: Calderón's and mine.
Breach one here. Breach two... here.
Feistl, Van Ness: pool.
You come in from the back.
- All right, let's do this already.
- Okay.
If anyone kills the godfather, I kill you.
We can't repeat what happened
with Escobar. I want him alive.
Understood?
Go.
- Nobody lives here, boss.
- That's bullshit.
Intel had Pacho here last night.
What do you think?
What do we do?
I think there could be hideouts here.
- We have to check the house again.
- All right.
We turn this place upside down.
Men, we're going to search
every corner of this house, understood?
It's an elegant house in Palmira, boss.
I don't know whose it is,
but it's not one of ours.
Very good. Get out of there
and make sure no one sees you.
Yes, sir.
- Salcedo.
- Jorge.
Sir.
I need you to do something important.
When you leave your house,
you'll find Navegante.
He knows where you have to go.
Of course, sir, but what should I do
with the operation I'm monitoring?
Córdova. Give it to Córdova.
Jorge...
- be careful.
- Of course, sir.
He's one of my best men.
He'll take care of it.
You're a man of your word.
Juárez.
So close to heaven and so far from God.
Impressive.
I'm so glad you brought me
to see the eighth wonder of the world.
Don't be an asshole, Pacho.
El Paso, Texas,
is what I wanted you to see.
Fucking NAFTA changed everything, Pacho.
It's been around for what?
Two years, more or less?
More than two million trucks
have crossed already, many of them ours.
Filled to the brim.
Do you know how many trucks
the Americans check?
Less than ten percent.
It's insane. They don't have the manpower.
Assholes opened the floodgates
and now they stand there
with a baby's bucket to try and stop it.
This is the right business.
I already know this, man.
No, man. What I'm saying is,
you're getting out of the right business
at the exact wrong time.
And you're going to regret it.
You want some?
Amado, are you suggesting
that I betray my partners?
No. No way. Why betray?
They want to get out.
I'm proposing that we start something new,
you and I.
Just imagine it:
You send it to me, I get it across.
In two years, we'll be flooding
this fucking shitty country.
Think about it, all right? Think about it.
Just don't take too long,
because in six months,
I need to secure a new supply.
Hopefully, it will be with you.
Hey...
Give it another once-over?
Okay.
It should be now.
Thirty seconds.
Hey!
Hey! You can't park there!
Damn truck.
These fucking trucks
are always breaking down.
You can't park here.
Let me just grab the cables
and I'll move it.
Move the fucking truck.
That's the one Lady Di uses.
Gilberto!
Someone's ringing the doorbell!
- Careful.
- Sorry, wait just a moment.
Let me get the door.
Look.
Gilberto?
Police! Back up. Quickly! Move it!
Quickly! Move it!
What's going on?
Sit down, ladies.
Sit down, I won't say it again.
You can't come in here. Get out.
He's fucking running!
Get up! Look at my face!
Let's go.
- Sit down, miss.
- I already told you, Gilberto is not home.
Did he contact anyone?
- No one, Colonel.
- No? All good?
Mrs. Rodríguez, I have a federal warrant
signed and executed by myself,
as representative
of the Colombian National Police.
The question is, will you cooperate?
Are you all right?
Yes.
It's good here.
The only thing left
is to demolish the house.
Yeah. Okay. We're done. I'm calling it.
I'm sorry, I thought we had something.
Welcome to my world.
Well...
Do what you need to wrap up,
have your men report back.
- Okay.
- Feistl, anything else?
- Ride to the airport?
- Sure.
Look, when we get there,
I think it's better if I go in alone.
These people are angry.
What we're asking of them,
it's an insult on top of their grief.
You're different, Jorge Salcedo.
Different? How?
You're crippled. You don't carry a gun.
Most people don't carry guns.
Yeah... but you're not most people.
And that's why it's so weird. Interesting.
That you never carry a gun.
I see. Why do you think that is?
I don't know.
Maybe you're scared.
Fear... of what you could do with it.
That you've been walking around a killer
and never knew it.
Pedrito, go in the house!
Good afternoon, Mrs. Salazar.
Calm down, Mrs. Salazar. Calm down.
My name is Jorge Salcedo.
I'd like to speak with you, if I could.
Go right back to where you came from
and tell that whore
if she wants my grandson,
she can come looking for him.
I just came to talk.
If you don't like what I have to say,
I'll go to Cali
and deliver whatever message you want.
I'm unarmed. I'm here to talk.
Your boss murdered my son...
to take up with his whore wife.
And now you come to take my grandson
far from the only family he has left.
I know this is not what you want to hear.
But she is his mother.
And Miguel Rodríguez is protecting her.
Protecting?
Is that what they call it now?
And he will be protected as well.
And if you let me take him back, I promise
you can see him whenever you'd like.
You promise. How nice of you.
Who told you I would do that?
I have him here and I can see him
whenever I want and protect him.
That bitch made her choice.
Mrs. Salazar... please accept my offer.
The next men who come... won't be asking.
There will be war.
Why don't you ask my sons?
See what they think.
If you don't mind, Capitán,
we need to stop by a friend's house.
Make a right here.
Nice neighborhood.
Your friend's very wealthy.
He's a very fortunate man.
What is this?
My friend likes chickens.
- Colonel Martínez.
- Captain.
You know what's happening here?
Yes, I think I know.
I'm giving you one chance
to do the right thing
and not fuck up this operation.
You think you're clever?
You're in Cali. Cali is my city.
This isn't Bogotá.
You're way out of line here, Hugo.
Perhaps.
He's here. We'll find him.
Watch him.
You got your kid's drawing?
I'm unarmed.
We're going to send your head
back to Miguel in a fucking box.
- Walk, motherfucker.
- Let's go.
Duvan!
Bring out the car.
Pedro. Let's go. I'm taking you
to your mother. Take my hand.
- Very good.
- Shut your fucking mouth or I kill her.
All right, my lady.
Make like a statue or I shoot your ass.
I'm getting in first, you hear?
Real still.
You're taking the boy.
What else do you want?
Relax.
- Stop!
- Mama!
What else, motherfucker?
Fucking asshole!
Fuck!
Drop the weapon.
Don't shoot.
I'm a man of peace.
Let's go.
Hey! Stop!
Colonel! Calderón took off.
- Fuck. We move fast.
- Okay.
- You have a phone in there?
- Yes, in there.
They got Gilberto, they're moving
towards the aerial base.
The whole workforce is on this.
They're not going to leave the city.
Tell all the men to be alert. Understood?
Move it, asshole.
They'll try to take us on the road.
Guns out!
Cleaning, cooking, working.
Hello.
Don Miguel... something's happened.
What happened?
I'm outside Gilberto's house.
They got him. They got your brother.
We've got a visual.
Surround him in the market!
Tail him!
Look! There he goes! Faster!
Let's get him on the next turn!
Hold your fire!
Driver! Put your hands
where I can see them!
Driver!
Out further!
Further!
Get out.
Open the back.
- Okay. Let me get the keys.
- Open it.
Open it.
Okay. All right. Settle.
The American sons of bitches
tricked us. We've got the wrong truck!
They're going to the air field.
We'll get them there.
I took care of security.
Let those sons of bitches
try to touch us again.
Send Salcedo's beeper another message.
Uncle! It's me, Nicolas!
Come in.
- Nicolas.
- Uncle.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
They got him.
Nicolas, why don't you go home
and wait there?
Once something happens, I'll call you.
No, sir, I have to help.
Come.
You know your dad
doesn't want you mixed up in this.
We have to have faith that your dad
won't be taken out of Cali.
And if he is?
Why did we waste all of that money
on my education? I'm a lawyer.
I'm taking the first flight to Bogotá.
I want to help him.
Let's hope that's not necessary.
Fuck.
Wait here.
What's up? Why'd we stop?
There's cops surrounding the plane.
Cops? Good ones?
I don't think so.
Colonel Martínez.
Sir, please don't come any closer.
Your men are impeding the transport
and arrest of a fugitive under warrant.
You know it.
And that means prison.
What you do today...
what you do this moment...
defines you.
For the rest of your lives.
Are you police or not?
That's better.
Home stretch.
Shit!
What's up? It's me.
- About fucking time.
- I was out of range.
They arrested Gilberto.
- What?
- They got him, Jorge.
They got Gilberto.
- You were monitoring the raid.
- But they never mentioned Gilberto's name.
Even so, we checked
all the tapes. It's impossible.
It doesn't make sense!
I just don't understand!
Brother... they got him.
They took him away.
We got beat.
Get back here quick.
Hasta la vista, baby. Ciao.
Take that.
Five seconds to take photos, no more.
Congratulations.
But you know this won't hold up.
You're fucking with things
that are much bigger than you are.
Smile, Gilberto. You're about to be on TV.
This way, Mr. Rodríguez.
Mr. Rodríguez, do you have a response
to the charges against you?
Conspiring to export cocaine
and illegal enrichment?
Enough. Let's go.
Do you have anything to say
to the people of Cali? Mr. Rodríguez.
For those of us
who thought the surrender was bullshit,
Gilberto's arrest proved
that these guys could be caught.
For the people who thought the surrender
was the only way to avoid violence,
it was the beginning of a nightmare.
The first shot in a war
to bring down another cartel.
But whatever side you fell on,
one thing was clear:
Gilberto Rodríguez's arrest
came as a surprise to everybody.
Especially him.
Don Gilberto.
Hey, congrats.
Congratulations. Good work.
No, where you going?
Come on, we want to toast you!
Start without me.
Great work!
- Mr. Ambassador.
- Big day.
- Quite a notch on your belt.
- It was strong intel, sir.
- I acted...
- Know how much work you torched?
People want to see
the godfathers in handcuffs
and that's what they're gonna get.
- Front page of every newspaper tomorrow.
- Colombians may not feel that way.
Let's go find out.
Get changed.
- My love!
- Mommy!
Mommy.
- Are you hungry? No?
- No.
How cute. Looks a lot like his dad.
Come on.
Mom will read you a story in a bit.
Go. I'll be right there.
Thanks for showing up, Jorge.
Sir, we don't know how much the DEA knows.
We need to assume
all your current homes are... unsafe.
I'll stay here for now.
We all need to talk.
What did you expect? A warrant
by definition authorizes the police...
Wait. Let's not lie to ourselves.
This operation was run
by the Drug Enforcement Administration
of the United States.
The takedown, Mr. Attorney General,
was National Police.
The transport was by our police.
The booking was by our police.
So a war started by National Police?
Look, as Attorney General,
my main... concern is achieving
a peaceful settlement with the godfathers.
And the arrest
of Gilberto Rodríguez Orejuela
means we now have new leverage
to negotiate with.
The President of Colombia, Ernesto Samper.
I hate to be late to a good debate.
You know us, might as well
try to smooth rough water with a hammer.
I've been apprised by Minister Botero
about our newly-incarcerated
Cali godfather.
- With all due respect, Mr. President?
- Go ahead, Miguel.
We've worked for months
to negotiate this surrender.
We recommend the immediate release
of Mr. Rodríguez Orejuela.
Colombia is a nation of laws.
Not of concessions.
If I give a pass to the largest criminal
organization in the world...
the trust of the people
will be lost forever.
Mr. Rodríguez is entitled
to the same due process
as any Colombian citizen.
Let's see where due process gets him.
For now...
his arrest stands.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Fuckin' A.
Thank you very much.
We talked about this.
I don't want the stink of this on you.
Relax, Dad.
I'm a lawyer. I'm the only one
in the family who can visit you.
Besides, I thought you could use
a friendly face.
What I could really use
is a tumbler of whiskey about this big.
How's it look?
The warrants are old.
- Invalid?
- Vulnerable.
I have a lunch tomorrow at 1:00 p.m.
with the Colombian Board of Pharmacies.
8:00 a.m., latest, I'm out.
Dad, you're here until our lawyers
get you in front of a judge.
And he'll hold you here in Bogotá
due to the conspiracy charge.
I don't get it.
This is a mistake, a blunder.
A gross overstep
by a rogue American agent!
That's what you want to believe.
But if that was the case,
you'd be out by now.
- Dad, this is real.
- No, money is real.
And what about all I've paid?
Sons of bitches
can't leave me confined here.
How the fuck did they surprise us
like that, gentlemen?
It was Calderón.
Dad, I say we tear him to pieces.
- And his fucking family and his children.
- David, please.
Obviously, there's responsibility
on all sides.
- Córdova...
- Sir, just as we realized...
By the time you realized,
Colonel Martínez had already been
in my brother's house for 30 minutes.
Don Miguel. The failure's mine.
When it comes to the DEA,
Córdova counts on me.
Wait. Córdova, you're my brother's
personal head of security.
Yes, sir.
Then you should've been there.
Your men should've been there.
Your guards were fooled
by a fucking chicken truck.
I want to know what the fuck
is happening here.
Because I'm starting to believe
that none of us are safe.
Not your families...
and not mine.
My family.
Thank you, Attorney General Valdivieso,
Defense Minister Botero.
Today marks an important beginning,
an important victory.
Because of the success
of our Colombian-American operation...
the Cali cartel is on the run.
And with the continued support
of the Colombian National Police...
I promise you...
the other three godfathers will fall.
Questions?
That's as much recognition
as we can hope for, right?
None at all? Smart move.
Keep his face all over this
while we're closing in.
Kiss-ass.
Want some?
No, I'm moving tables.
Oh, boy.
Oh, God.
Can't believe you're eating that shit.
Colonel, please.
Thanks.
Have a drink with me.
Tonight, we celebrate.
Tomorrow, we go back to work.
Well, not for me.
What are you talking about?
You remember those papers
that were seized by your men in Cali?
Yeah, we never saw those.
Apparently, Vargas did.
And there was a list of cops
who've been accepting money from Cali.
One name he was eager to share: mine.
Those son of a bitches
want to discredit Gilberto's arrest.
Exactly. It sends a message to any cop
who wants to try what we did.
I turned in my weapon and my badge.
Good luck.
Colonel...
I'm sorry.
Men like me would give our lives
to arrest a man like him.
You did everything right, Peña.
But now you're all alone.
Take care.
We need to talk about your security.
Let me be in charge.
I'll protect you, Dad.
Now's not the time for a change.
We need to keep things on track
until your uncle is back.
What if he doesn't come back?
Jorge.
- They got Gilberto.
- I don't understand.
I thought Gilberto
had this all under control.
So did I.
And what now?
This could get messy.
Stay where you are.
Right now, we look out for ourselves.
Pacho... be smart.
For now, we wait.
You stay there a while longer.
We have to keep everything running.
The health of the business
has never been more important. Understand?
Yes. Of course.
You listening to me, motherfucker?
Hey, listen, buddy, I don't speak Spanish.
No speak Spanish.
Okay.
Have a nice day.
Hey, boss. Good day today, huh?
The Jurado tapes.
Well, we probably shouldn't call them that
because they're not legal, per se.
I want all of them.