Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Show.
Sir?
The telephone recordings you requested.
From La Picota.
Excuse me.
He killed the DEA rat.
He's beating the shit
out of the North Valley.
What do you want me to say?
- Miguel's surprised us, brother.
- Look, Pacho,
I'm proud too of how my brother's
handled things while I'm gone,
but we all have limitations.
I led our organization for 20 years,
always taking care of all of you.
I know.
But the thing is, I don't think
I'm ready to surrender, Gilberto.
Besides, I still have to find the Salazars
and resolve the situation.
I understand, Pacho.
But you need to keep a cool head.
For now, we need to focus
on the surrender plans.
A fucking fridge?
A message from Miguel Rodríguez Orejuela.
Son of a bitch! What's that smell?
The surveillance team we sent to Cali.
Call me.
It's a fucking leak.
Someone in the Colombian government
is telling them everything.
- Your CI told you this?
- Yeah.
I mean, it adds up.
Our most important witness gets killed
right before I get him to talk.
Sir, Botero knew that Franklin Jurado
was my only play.
The Minister of Defense?
- Your CI said that he was the leak?
- That we had one.
- Then I'd keep that to yourself.
- Sir...
The fact is, Agent Peña, you've got
nothing outside of scorched earth.
A dead witness, a cartel war, and whatever
the fuck that was in the jungle.
We have to turn this over
to Colombian authorities.
I told Botero that he will have
your case files by 5:00 p.m. today.
Sir, what if Botero is the leak?
Then we're handing it over to the guy
who works for the cartel.
Ambassador, our CI, he's done everything
we've asked him to do. He's... He's...
He risked his life.
He's risked his family.
- We'd be hanging him out to dry.
- So get him out now.
I'll authorize the paperwork. I can have
the Marines at his doorstep in 20 minutes.
No. We do that...
Miguel disappears and then we're done.
You're already done.
I thought you said I had until 5:00 p.m.
What's more important, Agent Peña?
Getting Miguel Rodríguez...
or your CI's life?
Crosby's handing it over
to the Colombians today.
Any move we make,
we risk the leak finding out.
Fucking us and Salcedo.
What did Salcedo say
about the new location?
David stepped up security. It would take
a battalion of cops to get Miguel.
He says our best bet's
to wait for Miguel to move.
Which we don't have time for.
So we don't wait.
Sir, maybe we should cut our losses,
get Salcedo out now.
Crosby won't go for it. I asked.
Guy's risked his life for us.
His wife and kids, for fuck's sake.
So it's up to us to help them.
We get Miguel, we get them out.
Call Salcedo again.
We take Miguel today.
General,
Miguel Rodríguez is on the 7th floor.
His son, David,
doubled security after the raid,
and, well, there's no way
to get inside that building
without attracting attention.
We have to get Miguel to move.
- And we capture him while they're moving.
- Exactly.
How?
Leave that to me.
I'll stay here in Bogotá.
You coordinate the operation in Cali.
But it has to be today.
There's no time.
Today.
Agent Peña, after our last operation,
my superior came to see me.
He was very diplomatic, but he made sure
to remind me of all I've achieved.
And that it could all be taken away.
What worries me is the only people
who could do more damage
to the country than the cartel,
are the sons of bitches they've bought.
And I don't want to risk bringing Miguel
Rodríguez to jail through the front door
so they can let him out the back,
you understand?
General...
you put him in jail
and I'll make sure he stays there.
All right.
Let's do it.
Let's hope the bastard
enjoys his last day of freedom.
In law enforcement, your only real power
comes from the strength
of the system that you represent.
You gotta believe it has your back.
But sometimes... sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it's so compromised,
so corrupt, that you can't trust it.
What do you do then,
when it tries to play you?
You look for a way to play it right back.
All right, gentlemen,
Miguel is here in his apartment.
Protected by a small army.
Once I get the signal, I'll organize
a convoy and come down this way.
Carrera 15, until we get here.
There we will turn
and go down 25th Street until Santa Rita.
How many cars?
Four SUVs. I'll be in the first
and Miguel will be in the third.
We set up roadblocks,
close him in.
I think that gives him
an opportunity to escape.
I've got something
far more aggressive in mind.
I don't want to give that son of a bitch
opportunity to end up anywhere
other than the back of my truck.
You flush him out of the apartment,
and I'll take him down.
Sir, please believe me!
I swear it on my family, sir.
No! No, sir! Please wait!
I already told you the truth, sir!
Play it again. From the beginning.
But what for?
All you're going to hear is a man yelling
because he's being tortured, nothing more.
I told you, maybe he said something
that will help us nail the motherfucker.
But didn't we already catch the mole?
I'm going to tell you something.
I hate that motherfucker Salcedo
with all of my heart.
But what's your problem with him?
He may be clean.
The problem I have with him is
that he's a fucking lying son of a bitch.
And I know it.
Now start it from the fucking beginning.
You hear?
For this to work,
I have to leave my family again.
- Okay, we'll get them out. Don't worry.
- They're watching my house.
All right, so we wait,
we stay clear until we have Miguel,
and then we go in for your wife and kids.
Are you gonna keep your word?
We'll keep our word.
Hey, what happened, Jorge?
All right. Hey, listen...
just use this to reach us.
My oldest daughter, she has
her first soccer practice tomorrow.
She's afraid they're gonna
make her play goalie.
I don't know what to tell her.
Hey, we're gonna get him, Jorge.
Put the clothes
you want to take on the bed.
Put any jewelry and valuables
under the clothes.
Anyone comes in,
it will look like you just did the wash.
When it's time,
put everything in the suitcases, okay?
Good. One more thing.
Come with me, please.
Paola, don't freak out.
- Wait, Jorge, wait.
- It's only a precaution, Paola.
Wow.
My love.
Eh...
Take it, Paola.
Like this. Hold on tight.
Here's the safety. Now it's ready...
And now it's not.
That's the only thing you need to do.
If anyone you don't know
comes through that door, use it.
- Okay?
- Yes.
My love, you can do this.
You can do this.
I'll leave it here.
I can do this.
It's my only choice.
As soon as the DEA gets here,
you go with them. You can't wait for me.
What about you?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Don't worry. Everything will be okay.
What I'm about to tell you
is a little delicate.
But it concerns all of our futures.
I've been concerned
about my brother, Gilberto.
The thing is, he's been speaking to some
of our partners without telling me.
Undermining me.
Making it very difficult
to run this business.
So...
I decided to have
my brother's phone tapped.
What the fuck are you saying, Miguel?
We don't tap each other's phones.
I know.
But in this case, it was necessary.
I heard you two talking to him
about the surrender.
You heard something
I wasn't supposed to say?
What is this shit, Miguel?
Now we can't talk to Gilberto?
Of course you can.
You're not going to make
a fucking speech now.
No, I'm not going to make a speech,
but I will tell you one important thing.
The surrender was Gilberto's dream.
It was never ours.
Besides, we all know
how good Gilberto is at promising things
when he wants something from us.
What did he promise you?
New York.
But did he tell you when? How?
You have shit.
Chepe...
here you have a passport,
a new social security number,
and the addresses
to two labs in New York...
so you can rebuild what's ours.
And what did he promise you?
The Salazars?
Here's the location
where the Salazars are hiding.
So you can avenge your brother.
Henao gave it to me.
So the North Valley war is over or what?
That's right. In our favor.
Of course, first I had to send
that motherfucker a little gift.
Look, Miguel...
I think you need to tell us the truth.
No fucking lies.
What the fuck have you done
with the real Miguel Rodríguez Orejuela?
Surrender's for pussies.
Listen up... Mr. Wiretap.
Never ever touch my phone.
Understood?
Don Miguel.
Sir.
- What?
- Excuse me.
I just heard DEA agents are back in Cali.
Any update on the accountant?
Well, we're still looking, but no luck.
Motherfucker.
This has to be the place
Enrique told us about.
Look there.
See if you can find anything
about Salcedo.
Motherfuckers.
I know this isn't the ideal
situation for your team,
but I appreciate
cooperation with the transition.
Of course.
I'll put you in touch with the police
investigative team I've assigned.
I'll give you the phone number.
And they'll stop by for the files
this afternoon.
Thank you.
One more thing, Minister.
It almost slipped my mind.
What's that?
I received some information regarding
Miguel Rodríguez's hideout.
It seems he's in a building in Cali.
It's called Hacienda Buenos Aires.
Well done, Agent. Well done.
I'll get this information
to my men right away.
No, that won't be necessary.
I've already got my men there
preparing for the raid today.
Excuse me?
Well, we can't waste any time.
You want to catch him, don't you?
Of course I do.
This is the best option.
If we do get him, you get the credit.
I promise.
Thank you, sir.
Jorge?
Don Miguel wants to see you right away.
Coming.
Sir.
Just got off the phone
with our friend in Bogotá.
Seems those DEA agents
are here for a reason.
He says they're planning a raid.
We can take you to Santa Rita.
- Do it.
- Of course, sir.
We got some news.
Get the cars ready.
Peña.
Your message
went through. Botero's the leak.
Miguel's on the move.
Good. Keep me posted on stage two.
Copy that.
Good morning.
Hello.
You seem happy.
Defense Minister Fernando Botero...
Mm-hmm.
is working with the Cali cartel.
- What makes you so sure?
- Played a little "telephone."
Something I said to him that only I know
was repeated in Cali.
Normally, I'd say you're crazy, but...
I'm going to show you something.
- Those Curaçao bank files you gave me.
- Yes.
I had a bank source help me
dig through them.
And?
What's interesting is who's listed
alongside Franklin Jurado's name
on this account.
Santiago Medina. Who's he?
He's an art collector.
But rumor is he does some money laundering
for upper class Colombians.
Cleans their cash through fancy charities,
dummy corporations,
campaign contributions.
Guess who Santiago Medina worked with
on the last presidential campaign?
Fernando Botero.
There's nothing.
Have you thought about the possibility
that Salcedo is telling the truth?
Just because you don't like him doesn't
mean everything he says is bullshit.
That's got nothing to do with it.
There's plenty of people I don't like
but still trust. Like you.
Darío. You see that camera?
Maybe it caught something. Huh?
Come on.
I found this one from last week.
Play it.
Fast forward.
Faster.
Hit play.
And stop... stop it there.
See? These motherfuckers
must be the DEA, right?
Mm-hmm.
Keep going.
His transport arrived.
We're in position.
I'll let you know when they come out.
Where are we?
Serrano's in position.
Just waiting for Miguel to come down.
Despite how difficult this week has been,
we're making it out of the storm.
It would seem so, sir.
I've been thinking
about the promise I made to you.
Six months...
until you open your security business.
That's right, sir.
It's even possible
that I'll invest in your business.
What do you think about that?
It would be an honor to have your support.
Can I help you with your bag?
No, this is almost ready.
Take those. I'll see you downstairs.
Of course, sir.
Keep going.
Stop it there.
No, that's Enrique. Keep going.
Open it.
Salcedo is downstairs.
We're waiting for Miguel.
Copy that.
Stop. Go back.
Go back.
More.
There.
- Isn't that Enrique again?
- Can you get this shit to stop shaking?
Man...
Man, you were right.
You were right, man.
I'm going to kill that motherfucker.
Take this.
Careful with this.
Fuck, he's not answering.
Here.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Dad.
It's him.
It's that bastard, Salcedo.
David, again with this bullshit?
When will you stop?
Listen to me.
I found the DEA hideout. The one Enrique
told us Salcedo knew about.
And on the same street, there's a hotel
with a camera pointed towards the street.
We checked the video with Darío,
and we saw the DEA, Enrique,
and that motherfucker Salcedo, Dad.
Are you sure about that?
One hundred percent. I checked the plates.
Dad, think about it.
He's trying to take you out of a safe
place so they can catch you in the open.
It's a trap, Dad.
Dad...
I'll call you back.
Jorge. Don Miguel asked me to tell you
that he needs your help with something
before we leave.
Jorge?
Yes.
Fuck. They just called him back inside.
Shit.
David Rodríguez just showed up
at the Salcedos'.
NO SERVICE
They know.
- Are you sure?
- Has to be.
They called him back inside.
David's at the Salcedos'...
- Just wait, wait.
- We have to go in and get him.
We stick to the plan.
When Miguel moves, we get him.
They're gonna kill him.
Yeah, well, he might already be dead.
All due respect, sir, we have to go in.
All right, go.
Tell Serrano we're going in.
- Let's go.
- Mm-hmm.
General!
We have to go in now! Out!
You need me, Don Miguel?
Take a seat.
All right, but we should be going.
I think we're going to be
a little safer here.
You fucking son of a bitch!
What is this? What's going on, Don Miguel?
Don Miguel!
Look how diligent! Very...
Girls, whatever happens,
you don't leave the room, all right?
- All right.
- Don't come out for any reason.
Cover his mouth.
Don Miguel!
Please!
Ah! Don Miguel!
Go to your room.
Mrs. Salcedo! We're DEA! Open up, please!
Mrs. Salcedo! DEA!
- DEA?
- Yes!
Daniel Van Ness.
There's two men out front.
They're here for you. Stay close.
Let's go through the back.
I believed you over my own son.
You took my money.
I let you protect my family.
You listened to our private conversations,
you son of a bitch.
I gave you all my trust.
And what did it mean to you? Shit.
Nothing.
You're an animal.
You're a little wharf rat.
Not even that.
A rat has more dignity than you.
Do you know what I've just done,
motherfucker?
I told David to go to your house...
and kill your wife and daughters,
you motherfucker!
Mrs. Salcedo.
My kids.
Get to their room. Stay there. Go.
Ma'am, please open up.
Girls, stop folding, please.
Back here. Go back here.
Back! Here.
I want to talk, Mrs. Salcedo. Open up.
Keep shooting!
I know you're in there, Mrs. Salcedo.
Don Miguel! The DEA is in the building.
Get María and the boy into a car.
Sir, you should come as well.
Get the fuck out of here!
Give me that shit. Get out. Motherfucker!
Fucking rat, die!
Go!
Don Miguel, we have to leave right now!
Don Miguel! Don Miguel!
- Don Miguel, we have to go!
- Kill him!
You're okay. You're okay.
Where's Miguel?
Go out the other door.
Hurry up, damn it!
Miguel Rodríguez...
you're under arrest.
- General.
- Agent Peña.
I've got Miguel Rodríguez,
handcuffed, at my side.
And Salcedo?
I got them. They're safe.
Get in.
Let me talk to my wife.
- Jorge.
- Jorge?
Hello, my love. You all right?
Yes, and you? The girls?
Yes. Yes, the girls are all right.
They're scared, but all right.
We did it, Paola.
Yes. Yes, we did it.
I'll be with you soon, my love.
Got a minute?
- We were wrong.
- Wrong?
Yes. I checked
the Samper campaign financials
and I found that in July of last year,
they had serious losses.
They needed money
for travel, ads, etcetera.
And they got $6 million.
Just happens to be the amount
Botero took from the cartel.
So...
- he wasn't laundering the money.
- No.
That money stayed in the campaign.
It was a contribution.
I need a word.
Right away.
- Have a seat.
- No, thank you. I'd rather stand.
- What's going on?
- We got Miguel Rodríguez.
You got him?
He's on a plane back to Bogotá right now.
It'll be all over the news in an hour.
Couldn't let it go, could you?
Sir, there's another piece of this
that you need to know.
These are bank accounts opened in Curaçao
by a guy named Medina.
Yeah, I know him.
Well, good, because he was working
with Fernando Botero.
They received over six million dollars
from the Cali cartel,
which went into
the Samper presidential campaign.
And you know this how?
I did some digging.
Ambassador, I am certain
that the Minister of Defense is corrupt
and that it doesn't stop there.
You ask the president, he's gonna say
he didn't have a fucking clue,
but that money won him the election.
Gilberto, Miguel,
they walk right out of prison
unless these fucking politicians
are in there with them.
The voice you're about to hear
is the voice of the man
you just mentioned, Santiago Medina...
talking to Gilberto Rodríguez.
On the phone.
We've been talking, Mr. Rodríguez.
There's a lot of interest on our part.
If there's interest on your end...
Yes. Of course there is.
We would need to know what
we would be getting for our contribution.
Of course.
As you know, our goal is to reward
our supporters once we take office.
The terms we discussed
are certainly reasonable.
Then you have our support.
- How would we organize the payments?
- We should get together and discuss it.
How long have you known?
It's complicated.
The point, Agent Peña, is you're right.
But in this case...
it doesn't matter.
You're not gonna do anything.
Samper's a good friend to us.
So that's it.
They bought...
the president.
And for now...
they get to keep him.
We never had a chance.
I know it's difficult.
But you get used to being here.
You bastard.
Look, brother...
let's put the past behind us.
I know this isn't
what you wanted to hear...
but, regardless, we are winning.
I don't know
what the fuck we're winning, Gilberto.
By catching you, brother,
they did us a favor.
Now Pacho and Chepe
have to turn themselves in.
That's the only way
we'll be able to negotiate the terms.
Well, you better be right,
because I'm not staying in this shithole.
I heard about Miguel.
I'm going to surrender.
And Chepe too.
But before that,
I have one last thing I have to finish.
Gentlemen.
Mr. Santacruz,
we have to ask you to come with us.
You're under arrest.
There's room at the bar.
Make yourself comfortable.
Please, Mr. Santacruz.
You have to come with us.
Who do you think called the police?
Here's how this is gonna go.
When I'm done...
when I'm fucking ready...
then you can give me a ride to jail.
Take a seat.
Eat this. Come on.
Order whatever you want.
Come on.
Ah!
This your celebration?
Kind of a downer.
I was hoping for some alcohol.
How long have you had them?
The tapes Crosby played for me.
Let me guess. It's, uh...
it's complicated.
How about, uh... I tried to warn you?
Like you've never cut a corner
to get to the front of the line?
Question is...
what you do when you get there.
There's always gonna be
new bad guys to fight, Agent Peña.
We make new ones every day.
But... any way you slice it...
you're the agent that put cuffs
on two Cali godfathers.
No small feat.
Go on.
You earned it.