General Zaragoza!
The French are retreating!
Send the cavalry!
After them! Fire the artillery!
Bring the prisoner forward.
You go that way. I'll go this way.
Stop right there!
Get up and start walking!
- Get up and walk!
- Just a second.
Enough! Walk!
Downstairs!
On your knees.
You're a spy for the enemy.
Say your line.
Long live France!
The hero killed her with one shot!
Will they be angry?
It's Mama's favorite rug.
If they ask questions,
I'll do the talking.
The gentleman will see you now.
I wanted to congratulate you
on your brother's nomination.
He's going to make a fine president.
We're very proud.
It's time for...
a younger generation
in Los Pinos, right?
Exactly.
From what I've read, your
brother seems like a smart man.
He's brilliant.
Whereas I'm simply clever.
Come on, clever usually pays better.
You're in the hotel industry, correct?
Yes, but I have other
businesses as well.
Import, export...
You've done well for yourself.
Can't complain.
I've worked hard.
Yes. Hard work.
Always the cornerstone.
Bet you come across a lot of pretty
girls in the hotel business.
You have tennis courts
at your properties?
Yeah, one or two of them.
Why?
I've always enjoyed the sight
of a woman in a tennis skirt,
with those white shoes they wear.
I'd like to invite you...
to spend some time at my hotel
and be my guest of honor.
What do you think?
We could arrange a tennis
match for you, I'm sure.
I don't care much for Guadalajara.
Prefer the beach.
I have properties all over.
Whatever you'd like.
That's what I wanted to
talk to you about...
all the things I can offer you.
I'd... I'd like the
opportunity to help...
you and your brother, obviously.
You donate to the party?
Of course, every chance I get.
Then you've already helped immeasurably.
My brother's going to do great
things for this country.
I came to propose a relationship.
A more direct one.
I can be an asset...
to you and your brother.
Not only professionally, but...
personally, a friendship.
I'm someone who believes in that.
Who doesn't need a friend, right?
A discrete friend.
And more importantly...
a generous one.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but we're not in need of all that.
I can't be certain what the future
holds for the hotel business...
but I can tell you one thing
about my brother and I.
We value family...
and loyalty.
Juan Nepomuceno Guerra has
been a loyal friend to our family
since my brother and I were boys.
I'm aware of that.
I've heard that story before.
And I'm...
I'm not going to lie.
I've had disagreements with Don Juan.
Well, I hope your issues
can be resolved amicably.
Because if anything were
to happen to Señor Guerra,
my brother and I would be...
very upset.
Juan is quite a character.
What I can tell you is that...
my brother's going to be
everybody's president.
We look forward to your vote.
What kind of fucking politician
doesn't want money?
You're sure he speaks for his brother?
Always.
They're a team, hammer and nail.
- I've heard things. He's a player.
- A player?
A player would take the money.
- Why the fuck doesn't he want my money?
- No idea.
Find out what's going on.
I want every fucking detail.
And Guerra?
Can't touch him.
But the old goat can take another
shot at you any time he likes.
I know.
I'm going to Sinaloa.
Safer than Guadalajara.
Motherfuckers.
Got more on that situation
between Tijuana and Sinaloa.
Now what? They're still at it?
We told them no more bullshit violence.
But I'm not sure the boys
were really listening.
Game over.
After Chapo's thing,
'Mon went after Cochi's
favorite mariachi.
Hey, asshole. Get down.
Please, mister, I'm begging you.
Grab his good hand.
You know Cielito Lindo, man?
No! Don't do it!
And Cochiloco...
he didn't appreciate that.
Hey, hose that shit off.
Call Benjamín and Palma.
It stops now.
Settle on a number for the taxes
they ducked, that ends it.
Let me know as soon as you find
out something on the brothers.
Let's go, Clavel.
You think that shit works?
Couldn't tell you.
I went to bat for you.
Keeping your team down
here, it wasn't easy.
Well, this new angle we got,
it feels promising.
This new informant...
you trust him?
Not exactly.
But he hasn't steered us wrong yet.
The cash keeps Félix on the
right side of the government
and the plaza bosses.
This CI?
He can help put all that into play.
If we can weaken Félix
without having to go
back and cut in State,
then I can live with there being
things I don't know about.
As long as no one else
knows about them either.
So this CI, some kind of trafficker?
Law enforcement.
Félix was in Panama last month.
Meeting with members of the Cali cartel.
What was on the agenda?
Not sure, but it ended
with Félix committing
to move more weight.
Lots more.
Why now?
El Padrino's feeling the pressure.
Does this tie into the reports about
the tension between his plazas?
We think they could be related.
Sure.
There's been talk of major construction
somewhere outside Juárez.
Construction of what?
Runways.
That's the one thing we're
still trying to figure out.
Who the hell's gonna run transpo
between Colombia and Mexico now?
The new Matta-Ballesteros.
Amado Carrillo Fuentes.
Used to be some kind of pilot,
among other things.
Now Félix has him buying
up passenger planes.
Federation's building
their own air fleet.
Running it out of Juárez.
Yeah, if we can pin down
Félix's distribution hub,
then we can unlock his
entire route network.
Track shipments as
they cross the border,
pick them off one by one.
That's right. Bleed the motherfucker.
Starve him of his cash until
the government cuts him off.
You know, hangs him out to dry.
Well...
Amado just bought a one-way
ticket to Belmopan, Belize.
What the fuck for?
That's where Aero Tropical
is based. It's an airline.
Or it used to be. They have
just declared bankruptcy.
They're liquidating their entire
fleet at an auction next week.
I want regular updates.
I got a couple things that
I need your help tracking down.
What the hell is all this?
Just some equipment we
need to work a new lead.
Be sure to use your knees, bro.
Grab my bag.
Hey, boss.
Good to be back home in Sinaloa?
When are you coming home?
I'm not sure. Have some
business I need to handle here.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just need to
figure some things out.
Hang on, I can put the
baby on the phone.
No, no, no. Maybe later.
I'm a little busy right now.
I'll call you later.
I didn't expect to see you again.
But here I am.
And with such lovely company.
Thought it was a good idea for
all of us to meet. We need more.
At least 700 kilos this time.
Business must be good.
We've been saving our
allowances. Right, doll?
Give me two weeks.
I hear things are changing in Mexico.
Changing how?
Cali's going to start moving
product through the Gulf
with Juan Nepomuceno Guerra.
But I don't see why that
should change our arrangement.
Going forward,
maybe we can make this
an exclusive relationship.
Knock ten percent off every
load over 400 kilos,
you're the only supplier
we do business with.
Félix has competition now.
He's weak.
We need to push harder.
It's time to expand.
Every time I sit down with him,
I feel like I need to wash my hands.
WHO WILL YOU PICK IN THIS ELECTION?
ON JULY 6TH JUÁREZ NEEDS YOUR VOTE
Amat, don't forget to vote, huh?
This is it.
- Yeah.
And I thought our last
place was a shithole.
Home sweet home.
Welcome to Juárez.
All right, got it.
Indian motherfucker.
Listen up!
I spoke to Azul.
Says this shit with Tijuana has to stop.
Hey... I mean it, man.
Come on, Chapo.
Damn it, man.
Fuck those pussies.
Félix says it's over. So it's over.
We have to negotiate a price.
Kid's hurt, man. Look at him.
Put his heart and soul
in that fucking tunnel.
Your shit with the
steamroller didn't help.
Ramón fucked with a musician, man.
That's like picking on a child.
Fucking asshole.
Okay, fuck it. I'll talk to them.
At the end of the day,
shit's just money.
Go back and forth a little first.
Just not too hard.
For real, Cochi, don't mess with Ramón.
Fuck him, with his shirts.
I'll just talk with Benjamín
or the other one...
Eduardo?
Javier, the kid?
The other one, with the mopey face.
- Francisco.
- Him, Francisco.
He loves me. I'll talk with him.
Just settle it.
But don't offer too much.
Sounds good. See ya!
Mommy!
Next, we have a 1979 Boeing 727,
registration number N-1779.
Featuring forward and rear galleys.
Currently featuring 12 first-class
seats and 136 coach seats.
And this aircraft is ready,
willing, and able...
We can get in through the
north side of the fence.
Bad sight line for security.
Cut through. Two in,
one outside for lookout.
We need radios. A ladder too.
We can get in through the rear
airstairs, under the fuselage.
You figure it's open? Can you
even lock up a fucking 727?
Either way, I can pop the lock.
Stole a lot of cars
back in the days, huh?
Got me my first promotion.
Comandante was a big Buick guy.
One million. Can I get
one million? One million?
Carrillo Fuentes used
to be a cop, right?
He did two years at the DFS.
I'm sure he served with distinction.
And stole anything that
wasn't nailed down.
Sounds like your kind of cop.
How many of these things
is he fucking buying?
I definitely went astray somewhere...
end up sitting here with you
two broke motherfuckers.
I got an amen to that.
Sold to the man in black!
Son of a bitch.
And up next,
one of my personal favorites
on auction today.
We have a nineteen-seventy...
Hi.
Keep fucking walking, man.
I mean it.
Relax, 'Cisco. Fuck, man.
I hate fucking clowns.
What did the new doctor say?
Wants to do more tests on her.
There's some specialist up in San Diego.
Ruth might take her. We'll see.
Fuck, man.
God's going to protect her, man.
I've been praying every night.
Thanks, 'Mon.
- You want some?
- I left it there on the table.
Hey, Benjamín.
You remember Ivan? He works down
at the nightclub. Security.
Sure.
He's got something you want to hear.
Go on.
Tell my brother what you told me.
Hold up.
Hey, man. Take a walk, okay?
Benjamín. Come on.
He doesn't mind, right?
Or do you?
Nah, man.
It's cool.
What the fuck, man?
David's cool. I know him, man.
I trust him.
Who the fuck is he?
Some fucking American
you met in prison?
Gave you cigarettes?
Doesn't mean I trust him.
Use your fucking brain, man.
What is it?
Sorry.
My cousin's a cop, right?
State police, in Guadalajara.
So we get to talking, tells me about
how last week a call came in.
Gunshots. In this nice
neighborhood. Fancy.
When he shows up,
there's a couple of cars.
One's all shot up.
But whoever was inside... long gone.
The other car was bodyguards.
They tell my cousin it's been handled.
Put some money in his hand.
Fuck off, basically.
But this car that's been all shot up?
My cousin's seen it around town.
He recognizes it.
He knows who the target was.
What did you find out?
Did some digging.
I know why they aren't
interested in your money.
He and his brother are about to
make a bunch of their friends rich.
Oil, steel, and railroads rich.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm talking about his
plans for the economy.
With the 1988 election approaching,
a new generation of leaders
in the PRI had big plans.
And their new candidate was
the perfect man for the job.
Educated in the States,
this guy would be the kind of president
D.C. and Wall Street were looking for.
And he was gonna
shake shit up all right.
Under his leadership,
the PRI would drop its
old ties with labor unions
and gut the subsidies that
kept food prices down.
Communal farms called
ejidos would be chopped up,
sold to corporations.
But the main event of his
economic revolution?
That was known as privatization.
Idea was large-scale nationally-held
industries would be sold off.
Telecoms, steel, railways...
you name it.
And guess who'd profit?
The political insiders who
got to buy these assets
at bargain-basement prices.
In 1987, there was one Mexican
billionaire on the Forbes' list.
By the time the administration
ended, seven years later...
there were 24.
And don't think they weren't
reminded on a regular fucking basis,
by the president and his brother,
who put them there.
So why don't they want your money?
'Cause they don't fucking need it.
The brothers have cut deals
that will make them millions.
Bad news for your
relationship with the party.
What's left of it.
All right, talk to me.
Are we clear?
Okay, hold on.
The guard's still there.
Guard's moving.
He's making his round now.
All clear.
You've got three minutes. Go!
V-3-C-M-R-6.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, a sec.
Hold up, hold up.
V-3-U-B-F-7.
All right, we got one.
Two minutes.
Get a move on it.
Now get that fucking door open.
Fuck!
Head's up.
Security's on the move.
- Oh, shit.
- I'm almost in, almost in.
- Walt.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We see him. We see him.
- Ossie, come on.
- Almost.
- Ossie!
- Walt, you're running out of time.
Come on, Walt, go. Go, go.
The ladder, Walt.
Pull it! Pull it! Pull it! Pull it!
He's going out again. You've
got three minutes. Move!
Hey, guys.
I think we got something.
Tracker's up.
Fuck, what happened?
Shit.
Come on.
Six for six, baby.
He's a goddamn artist.
Nice work.
Thanks, man.
Yes, Benjamín. What is it?
I need to talk to you about
this shit with Sinaloa.
I've already handled it.
- Told them to make it right.
- Yeah, I know.
Cochiloco's on his way up
here to offer us money,
make this all go away.
Then what's the problem?
They're going to make peace.
The problem is
the Arellano Félix family isn't
interested in peace anymore.
We're interested in sending a message.
To everyone.
Benjamín, you're upset.
You need to be an adult about this.
They stole from us.
And now they're going to pay you back.
That's not good enough.
Look, I'll make that decision.
I've already made it, for myself.
Maybe you should start thinking
about what the Guadalajara
Cartel would look like
if Tijuana pulled out.
That will never happen.
Don't even think it.
This fighting between your
plazas makes you look weak.
I know someone took a run at
you last week in Guadalajara.
Shot up your car.
And that makes you look even weaker.
I don't think you want
to answer the questions
that losing my organization would raise.
Keeping my family happy should be
very important to you right now.
Yeah.
What did you have in mind?
Welcome to Juárez, boys.
What the fuck you smiling at?
One of the tracking
units is on the move.
What?
Left Belize about 8:00 a.m. our time.
Stopped over in the state of
Chiapas for a couple hours.
- Refueling.
- Yeah.
Started traveling north
again about four hours ago.
It's heading our way.
You're telling me we already
got a fucking bite?
Sal has got the signal up.
Yes?
- Yeah.
- Yes!
Left here. Left! Turn, turn!
Hold on.
Fuck, man. Try not to kill us, huh?
Well, which is it, man?
What are you doing?
I was going in with you.
Why?
Fuck, no.
Stay with the car.
This is what came in from Badiraguato...
Boss.
Get out, Miguelito.
When'd you get here?
How are you, Güerito?
We need to talk.
Afternoon, Mrs. Palma.
Boss is in there with him.
I'll just drop this for him in the shop.
Please give this to Mr. Palma
when you get a chance.
Thanks.
You can call me Guadalupe.
Very well.
I'm keeping an eye on things out here.
Basically in charge of security.
You're not from Mexico.
Venezuela.
Well, I hope you enjoy Sinaloa.
So far I like what I've seen of it.
Well, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Fuck!
- What?
- I lost the signal.
What are you talking about?
Fuck! Pull over.
Is there a problem?
Lost the signal.
Think we can get it back?
Well, I'm trying. We were
right on top of the thing.
Goddamn it.
Signal's back.
Holy shit.
This gives us everything.
All right.
Find a spot and set up surveillance.
Three-man teams.
Sal, me and Amat work
the first rotation.
This is it, boys.
Fuckin' A.
Look, I know things got
carried away with Tijuana.
But...
we're gonna pay Benjamín.
I promise.
Cochi's on his way right now
to talk to him, make it right.
I know Cochi's been sent to handle it.
Yeah.
But he's not coming back from Tijuana.
What?
Cochi's been in the
game as long as anyone.
They can't just...
Miguel Ángel, please.
This doesn't have to happen.
But it is happening, Güerito.
We were just fucking around.
Trying to make money, you know?
We got caught, so now
we'll just pay the tax.
It was just fucking around.
This is what we do.
We're not fucking accountants, man.
We're not cowboys either.
Things are different now, Güero.
Félix...
Cochi's one of the plaza's top guys.
We...
do not kill each other over bullshit.
Over fucking money?
Cochi's one of us, Félix!
Doesn't that mean something?
How long have you known him?
About 20 years.
Since I was a cop.
Twenty fucking years.
And now...
just because those pussies in Tijuana
get their fucking feelings hurt...
No, Güero!
Because you can't control your plaza.
You can't control your men.
You don't have the balls...
to be the boss.
Because you're weak.
Okay.
You're right.
But please don't do this, Miguel Ángel.
Call Benjamín...
and stop it.
Let's go.
It's done.
I came here...
so you'd hear it from me.
Going back to the house, boss?
Give me the keys.
I'm driving myself.
No, no, no. No snacks before dinner.
But I'm hungry.
After your homework. Go on.
Tell your brother too.
They never stop eating.
Papa.
Want your coffee?
Papa?
- What is it?
- Nothing. It's nothing.
What are you looking at then?
I said yes, now I'm not playing.
Come here! Come here!
Give her back!
Come here, boy!
What the fuck do you think
you're doing out here?
Hello, María.
What are you doing, Miguel?
I'm sorry...
to show up like this.
I've been thinking about you.
I don't care what you've
been thinking about.
Yeah.
Things are fucked up right now.
You don't need me.
Remember?
I haven't forgotten.
And I don't need you.
None of us do.
You're like... You're like a
disease, Miguel, look at you.
I don't want you near me.
Or my children. You hear me?
Understand?
So no more showing up here.
No more following the kids to school.
You aren't wanted.
You're not welcome here.
So get the fuck off my property,
and don't come back.
Hey, let me see those.
Take a look.
How many planes you
say this dude bought?
Six.
Why would you need six fuel trucks?
Unless you're planning on refueling
all six planes at the same time.
Motherfucker.
Félix is planning on bringing
the whole shipment at once.
Why the fuck would he do that?
Take the chance?
Félix Gallardo is over-extended.
Fucker's desperate.
If all that coke comes in
at once, and we hit it?
Burn it to the ground?
We don't have to play hit-and-run
and bleed Félix slow.
He loses that shipment,
Colombians will put a bullet in him.
The fucker doesn't survive the weekend.
Walt, you gonna cut
Heath in on any of this?
Not yet.
I'd say we got Félix lined up.
And that would just complicate things.
History shows us that political errors
are always paid for.
The people and history...
are not forgiving.
Those who have betrayed the people
of Mexico will soon face justice!
They will be called to
account for their sins.
A new day is coming.
Some will be punished,
and others will be rewarded!
Mommy, he's doing it again.
Héctor, stop bothering
your sister and eat.
I'm not doing anything!
Is everything okay?
You haven't touched your dinner.
Héctor, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Leave it alone, babe. Okay?