Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Show.
Careful. You already lost one.
Good.
- Faster, gentlemen, please.
- Yes, sir.
How's it coming?
This is fucking cool.
What did I tell you, motherfucker?
Stop fucking around.
I don't want to be here all night.
Understood?
Yes, it's all good.
Let's go.
Fucking idiot.
My dad had 20 years in this shit.
I only have six months.
Pedal to the metal then, bitch.
How many of these things
do we have to empty?
How much fucking money
do you want to make?
A fucking lot.
In its prime, the Cali cartel
was moving 30 tons of coke
a month into America...
most of it
through their New York operation
and an alliance
with Mexican traffickers out of Juárez
that brought tons of product
across our border.
That means
that in an average six-month period,
they could put 180 tons on the street.
But there was nothing average about this.
These were the last six months
in the life of the Cali cartel.
They were going for it,
making sure there were no loose ends.
Mrs. Salazar?
Mrs. Salazar, housekeeping.
- Come back later, please.
- As you wish.
If you want something done right...
you have to do it yourself.
Just like in life, Don Gilberto.
If you don't play,
you're going to watch others score.
My organization has four partners,
but only one leader.
I wanted to meet with you
to make sure there are
no misunderstandings in the North Valley
regarding the restructuring,
and the necessary house cleaning.
No, we were simply curious
about Claudio Salazar's absence.
I will be honest with you.
Salazar never contributed a thing.
He never gave anyone work.
He made more noise than money.
Better said, too much noise.
We are moving forward with the plan,
and we would like to know
if our friends are in agreement.
Your message about the surrender
was very clear,
and was very well received
by all of us in the North Valley.
Have a safe trip home.
Henao... thank you for your friendship.
Excuse me.
Pacho.
Let's take advantage of this window
to maximize our profits.
I'd like to double
our output through Mexico.
Why don't you go there?
Meet with Carrillo Fuentes. He likes you.
Make one last deal.
We both know that isn't the only reason
you're sending me there.
Pacho.
Look, Pacho...
I think it would be best
if you left Cali for a bit...
while things cool off.
Remember, Pacho, we're going
to walk away from this happy and rich.
Like I said, they were going for it.
While they were building up
their retirement accounts,
what were we doing about it?
Jack shit.
I don't want
to rub your noses in that, gentlemen.
My concern is that your men in Cali
didn't so much as contact
my senior officer there.
We've agreed that we can't have
those kinds of unilateral operations.
Our laws, our rules, will be respected.
Of course, General.
We apologize for the misunderstanding.
Won't happen again.
Well, I'm sorry,
but I will need more than your assurances.
Colonel.
Agent Peña.
How's your son?
Oh, he's fine.
He got transferred to technical services.
Better fit for him.
Maybe I should join him.
Not a lot of police work these days.
Yeah.
What did you expect?
When you sell your soul to the devil,
you're not allowed to ask for it back.
The men who let loose Los Pepes
on Colombia should have been arrested.
Instead, they got promoted.
Excuse me.
There he is.
Javi Peña, el jefe.
Never thought I'd see the day,
but I'm sure as shit glad to see you now.
- Duff, it's been a long time.
- Mm-hmm.
- Lopez.
- Hey.
Can't believe
you two were in the same class.
Miracle this place
is still standing, huh?
Some bullshit, huh, Javi?
Come on. Is this where you go
all Bad Lieutenant on us?
- Like you and Murphy were never made?
- Yeah.
You guys are famous.
Sometimes you get them,
sometimes they get you, huh?
Next time, we get them.
There isn't gonna be a next time.
They're rotating you home.
The Colombians are pulling your visa.
You're outta here tonight.
Come on.
Who's running things here, man?
They are.
Well, thanks for getting our back, sir.
Wouldn't you have liked
to be born in this era? Take a look.
- Just like the Cauca River, right?
- Identical.
Dad, where are we with the government?
They won't let us use the drug stores
as collateral for the Centenario property
until they're cleared through surrender.
I know, but eventually they will be.
And that's all you can tell me?
You know the rule.
You can't be a part of this.
I didn't send you to law school
so you could worry about our surrender.
That's been planned.
I sent you to take advantage
of what happens after it's done,
when our family is a leader
in the business community.
You're reading it again?
You should read it once in a while.
Wise words.
Sir. I'm sorry to interrupt.
You have a call
from our friend in the capital.
Hello?
Four people, including three children,
are dead and thousands more injured
in a mysterious gas leak
in the area of Yumbo in Cali.
Investigators are at the scene
of the incident,
but have not yet discovered
the source of the gas leak.
State officials told residents
there will be a formal investigation.
Silvio.
Can I bum a smoke?
Isn't it dangerous?
No more than it ever was.
If it was a natural gas leak,
I want to know before lighting up.
Unless it's not.
I think you should talk
to the captain, Carolina.
He doesn't have the balls to talk to me.
Silvio, help me out. You have kids.
Off the record.
I don't know, Carolina.
Why don't you talk to him?
He is the district safety inspector.
He'll issue the report.
Why don't you ask him for a comment?
Silvio!
Excuse me.
Careful picking it up.
Lift it up. Careful. Grab the other side.
That's good. A little bit more.
If they connect us to this, our friend
doubts the government will honor our deal.
We'll be seen as no different
than Escobar, killing women and children.
Months of negotiations and money
down the drain.
Just like the poison you monkeys dumped.
There's a reporter asking questions
in Yumbo.
This safety inspector
in charge of the investigation.
I wouldn't worry about the reporter.
We have lots of reporters.
But a government investigator!
If the motherfucker goes...
Dad, let me take care of it.
I said I would handle it.
You've demonstrated very clearly
that you can't handle it.
Take care of it. Discreetly.
Without any violence.
That's the last thing we need.
What? You have another bright idea?
That's why I didn't want our children
in the business.
We made a mistake, Gilberto.
Let go. Turn. Run.
You need to let out some string.
Careful with Grandma.
You see?
Mm-hmm.
- This is the bedroom.
- Uh-huh.
No, sorry, Dad.
- No, this is the living room.
- The living room.
It's big, Jorge.
And the pool will go here.
- And there, the kitchen.
- Mm-hmm.
And look...
Right in front there,
I'm putting in a jacuzzi.
A jacuzzi?
I always thought
your brother would have...
the house on the hill.
You were just always lost
in your engineering ideas.
What was the last one?
Bio-diesel.
Vegetable gas?
Yes, that's right. Well, conversion.
Well...
Very good.
Better late than never.
I'm glad you like it, Dad.
- Thank you.
- Jorge, the girls are calling you.
Yes, I'm coming.
Paola.
You'll be very happy
when you build the house here.
- It's all very nice.
- Affirmative, General.
You impressed him.
I don't care what he thinks.
That's why you haven't told him
who you work for?
It was always temporary.
Temporary?
Right.
You know this lot is bigger than we need.
Yes, but it's the one we want.
It's the one you deserve.
Six more months.
Okay?
I promise.
Go.
I'll go with your parents.
I'm sorry, honey.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Chepe!
- How's everything going, brother?
- All right.
We're about to beat
our profit record, brother.
Good. Keep me posted.
You should be happy, Gilberto.
Chepe, do me a favor.
Keep a low profile. At least for now.
I got a lot of stuff going on up here
at the moment.
I just need more ether
to reach the numbers we talked about.
Why? Is everything all right?
You sound weird.
I'm dealing with a problem
that is stressing me out.
It's our fault.
Actually, it's David's, the dumbass.
Is it bad?
I hope not.
But it could complicate our surrender.
Okay.
I'll be careful.
So good you're coming back, brother.
You'll leave behind the hustle
and shit of that city.
It's not so bad.
I love the trees in fall.
The park looks gorgeous.
I love you, brother. Talk soon.
Okay.
Miss, the valet says
the car hasn't returned.
- I see. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- María.
- Luisa.
What's happening? Claudio hasn't returned?
No. And Diego?
Diego dragged his drunk ass in
at six in the morning.
Okay.
- Bye.
Spell that for me.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Prime real estate opened up.
- You vulture.
You know,
Lopez is probably still at the airport.
Yeah.
Got it.
Thanks. We'll run these down.
And Eddie, hey, congrats again.
Eddie?
Yeah, Kacerosky.
Cornerstone's his. Good haul on Cali.
He's got addresses, numbers,
a couple of names.
Now you and your badass sunglasses
and hockey hair
want to go ring some doorbells?
Cali's the front line, Dan.
More like the express lane home.
I got a soon-to-be ex waiting to serve me
the second I get back.
Well, I didn't transfer to Colombia
to file wire reports
and drink stale Bud at Mr. Ribs.
I'm moving you to Duffy's desk
while you're gone. I feel alone up here.
Okay, knock yourself out.
You got a minute, sir?
Yeah.
Wanted to talk to you about all this intel
coming out of Miami with Cornerstone.
Paper trail from the warehouse they busted
threw up some flags.
- What's this?
- A shitty diagram,
but there's five or six companies
that show repeatedly.
Now, my buddy in Customs did some digging.
They're all owned by Cali or are
the address of record for shell companies.
They're moving Swiss francs
from Liechtenstein,
bearer bonds from Luxembourg,
but even they leave tracks.
- What's your name?
- Feistl.
Chris Feistl.
Feistl, what are you asking me?
Send me to Cali, sir.
You know, I want it, sir.
I mean, these companies,
this is the cartel's financial brain stem.
It's overstating it a little,
wouldn't you say?
It's a start.
We're not sending any personnel to Cali
at the moment.
I don't understand.
Who's the new Cali team?
For now, there isn't one.
There... Sir.
We have arrest warrants for Gilberto
and Miguel Rodríguez, Pacho Herrera...
I'm aware who runs the Cali cartel.
Is there anything else, Agent Feistl?
No, sir. That's... I'm good.
Good.
Nice office, by the way.
Thanks.
I got your message. What's going on?
We have a problem
with the fucking safety inspector.
He won't accept the money?
He has three crucifixes in his office.
Three.
- Reasoning with him is impossible.
- I see.
Tell me, what the hell was David doing
with the chlorine gas?
Do you really want to know?
About a year ago, Don Miguel
and Don Gilberto bought a fungicide lab.
The idea was to replace the gas
with cocaine and send it to the U.S.
They don't check it at Customs...
because it's a poisonous gas.
So that's why David
spilled the gas in Yumbo?
We should let him clean up his own mess.
That's not going to happen, Jorge.
If the fucking inspector doesn't say
what we need him to say,
we're all fucked.
Do you think they're going
to honor the pact?
Do you think there's really
going to be a surrender
between the cartel and the government
if what happened in Yumbo goes public?
Never.
What do we know
about the safety inspector?
Here's everything. We have phone numbers,
his home and office addresses,
bank accounts, income tax, properties.
And the only thing we're sure about?
This motherfucker is clean.
There's no one clean in this world,
Córdova. No one.
Find something on him, then. Quickly.
Gentlemen!
We're going to put all our assets
on this man.
We have to watch his wife, his kids,
even his fucking dog.
We need to watch his house,
from the inside and out,
every single corner, 24/7.
I want to know what he does at work,
who he meets and where.
I want to know his agenda.
Whatever he does, we're going to find out.
We will be in charge of his fucking life!
And, of course,
we have to tap all his phones.
At home, at the office,
and his cell phone.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir!
Come to my house this Saturday
after soccer.
My dad gave me permission.
Awesome, I'll see you there.
Cool, bye.
End of call.
- Recording number two... 2:16 p.m.
- Yes.
The company is registered
under one of the Rodríguez's
fake companies.
- Recording number three...
- 32 p.m.
I want to suck your dick. Tomorrow.
At the same place.
Hello?
Ma'am, I'm so sorry to bother you.
It's María. Is Claudio there?
No. Isn't he with you?
No. He didn't come home last night.
I'm worried.
Hmm...
You're fighting again.
You're the reason
he seeks pleasure elsewhere.
Nobody's seen him.
No one's seen him?
What did you do, María?
- No...
- I'm sending the boys.
No, that's not necessary.
I'll let you know if I hear anything.
Mrs. Salazar,
will you be checking out today?
No...
Hello, sir.
They're always in room 105.
Very good, thank you.
What a woman.
This was well done.
Thank you, sir.
The inspector has a press conference
scheduled this afternoon.
Someone needs to talk to him.
Finish the job.
Don Gilberto, he knows me.
They won't let me in.
Jorge.
Jorge... you should handle it.
You've done such great work.
Great work so far.
And no one knows who he is.
I appreciate that.
But I only gather information.
Sir, the truth is, I'm a man of...
few words.
Look, Jorge, sometimes even the largest
companies depend on a small outcome
to determine their future.
Like the success of one operation...
or an employee who is discreet and loyal.
This is the final stretch.
We all have to do our part. Understood?
Yes, sir.
The Cali cartel
came to New York for the cocaine market.
It's the largest in the world.
But they stayed for the ether.
You can't make coke without ether.
And while export restrictions
had made it hard to come by in Colombia,
it flowed freely in the States.
But maybe not as freely
as the godfathers would've liked.
Was there a problem with your last order?
No. No problems.
I need to add another 300 barrels
to my next order.
300 barrels?
Mr. Crespo, that's nearly double.
I can't do it.
How come?
There's a new buyer. Their orders
are getting bigger and bigger.
We're already stretched very thin.
I've been your most important client
for years.
I understand, but you told me
you were leaving the business.
- However, this other organization...
- Isn't.
I'm sorry.
So who are they?
They're kids.
Hmm.
Dominicans.
Running out of some beauty parlor
in Queens.
I see.
They'll probably end up dead or locked up.
You know, it's a young man's world.
We all have to make way
for the next generation.
This beauty parlor in Queens,
give me the address.
But...
Can I get one of those?
Quit four months ago.
Looks like it's going well.
Carolina Alvarez. El Tiempo.
So...
what conclusions should be drawn
from the fact that the new DEA attaché
has this intimate history with Los Pepes?
And does the fact that the Los Pepes death
squad being financed by the Cali cartel
explain why no one seems to be interested
in going after Gilberto Rodríguez Orejuela
and his partners?
You can call the press office
if you want a comment, Miss Alvarez.
Carolina, please.
Have a nice day.
Have you heard much
about the Cali accident?
Four more people dead.
Children.
Dozens more sick.
An empty chlorine gas canister
was found nearby.
And there's a rumor its manufacturer
is linked to a front company
operated by the Cali cartel.
Looks like you said, it was an accident.
By the end of the day, it will be.
No matter what the truth is.
Thanks for the cigarette.
Transportation came out
to $5 million each.
You can see here
that the product loss was very little.
And the bribes?
Well, the payoffs...
they went up this week.
Went up this week to six million, sir.
- Guillermo.
- Yes, sir?
What happens in six months
when these people stop receiving money?
No more friends.
This is everything, right?
This is everything
down to the last penny, sir.
And we have here coded pages
for all the politicians,
the senators, congressmen, all the cops.
I want an exact copy of this book.
Yes, sir.
It's our insurance
if they try to fuck us afterward.
You think someone would dare
do something to you?
Anything can happen.
If you're a pussy, they fuck you.
Any news about Salazar's wife?
Yes, Don Miguel.
The girl has been asking
about Claudio everywhere.
You want me to handle it?
I understand you have
information on the Yumbo incident.
Yes, I do.
Good. Tell me.
Your wife...
at the Palace Motel at 3:45 p.m.
After she dropped the kids off
at soccer practice.
So?
At your press conference this afternoon...
you will announce that the gas leak
was a municipal accident.
We have video and audio as well.
Look... you bought-off monkey...
take these pictures and fuck yourself.
At the press conference this afternoon,
I'm going to tell the truth,
so that the world will know
what you people do.
And don't worry about my wife.
I already knew.
Sometimes we make compromises
to keep a happy home.
I can appreciate you wanting
to take the high road.
However, you're not understanding me.
The men that I work for don't care
about your relationship with your wife.
They care what your children might think,
what their classmates might think.
And your distinguished family.
Think of what they would say
at your church.
If you don't do what I tell you,
the men I work for will make sure
that the whole world
will have a copy of this tape.
Thank you.
Mrs. Salazar.
So you've never had
a relaxation treatment before?
I've never heard of it.
Relaxation treatment?
That sounds nice.
You have a funny accent.
- Where are you from?
- Colombia.
- Colombian.
- This guy is Colombian, too.
- Check it out. Both.
- Really?
And I suppose that guy at the door
is also Colombian?
What a small world, right?
All right. What do you want?
I want you to go through that door.
The one with the English writing
I don't understand.
Tell the men back there
that Chepe Santacruz-Londoño
is getting a relaxation treatment...
and would like to speak with them.
Go.
You stay.
Cool.
Please, take a seat.
It's better if I stand.
A drink?
No. Thank you.
I'm sorry for the way
you were brought here.
I understand you have a question.
I've spent all day
asking about my husband.
And you think I know the truth?
Yes.
And I don't think
you are afraid to tell me.
And if I don't tell you?
Then I was wrong.
And you are a coward.
Your husband is dead.
He was killed by an associate of mine.
For a personal injury he caused.
This market, we made it ourselves.
It's ours.
We can't just give it up to you.
You haven't heard my proposal yet.
Say what you got to say.
The first thing you're going to do
is vacate this place immediately,
and never come back.
Oh, yeah?
And the second? What?
Second...
There is no second. Just the first thing.
- So you think this is a joke?
- Gentlemen.
Part of being an adult is accepting things
that you wish weren't true.
Recently, I have had to accept
some things that I don't like.
I advise you to do the same.
Look, you and your fucking hair
have ten seconds to get out of here.
- Ten.
- Nine.
- Eight.
You think this is funny, motherfucker?
Seven.
- Seven.
- Six.
- Five.
- Four.
Three, two, one.
- Check on him.
- Got it.
"So then the crow flew up
as high as he could,
losing sight of the dogs,
and returned to the flock.
The crow went to find his friend the cat,
whom he had saved from danger,
and lived with him
in peace and happiness."
And that's where we'll leave off
because it's time for bed.
You too.
Very good.
- Did the girls go to sleep?
- Yes.
How's the book?
I think they understand it
better than I do.
The municipal safety inspector
closed his investigation
into the tragedy in Yumbo today.
Hundreds were injured in a leak,
some are still in critical condition.
Four died, including three children.
The deceased were two seven-year-old boys
and a six-year-old girl.
- Can you believe this horrible news?
- One of the boys was about to celebrate
his first Communion
at the Santa María church.
- Now, instead of celebration...
- Fuck. This is terrible.
- There will be tears at their funerals.
- It's terrible.
I can't find my binoculars.
- Dad, let's go, we're gonna miss the game.
- Sir.
Flaco. You're my fourth wife, buddy.
I love you, man.
Sir, they want to make an announcement
at tonight's game,
in honor of the victims
of the Yumbo tragedy.
Good idea.
And tell them to say we'll donate
half the ticket sales to the victims.
- You got it.
- Now, let's see if we win.
If we get to the game on time.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'll keep this brief.
After a thorough investigation,
we've reached the conclusion...
that the Yumbo chemical exposure
was caused by a faulty valve
in a natural gas line in the area.
And because of that, from now on,
the gas company will be responsible
for the expenses.
Now...
You got a partner, right?
Yeah, kind of.
Good. You're going to Cali.