Oh, and there's a woman.
Yeah. A woman.
Who I love.
And I got close.
In the bleak midwinter...
At some point in the near future
Mr Churchill will want to speak
to you in person, Mr Shelby.
He has a job for you.
We will be in touch.
I'm going to take him.
Oh, thank you.
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
♪ And go across the tracks
♪ Where the viaduct
looms, like a bird of doom
♪ As it shifts and cracks
♪ Where secrets lie in the border fires
♪ In the humming wires... ♪
Some of us know the words.
♪ Past the square, past the bridge,
past the mills, past the stacks
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
with a red right hand. ♪
Trot on.
♪ In the bleak midwinter
♪ Frosty wind made moan
♪ Earth stood hard as iron... ♪
Trot on. Trot on.
♪ Water like a stone
♪ Snow had fallen
♪ Snow on snow, snow on snow
♪ In the bleak midwinter
♪ Long ago. ♪
Here come the fucking
cavalry. Late as usual.
Dearly beloved.
We are gathered here today to
join together in holy matrimony
Thomas Michael Shelby
and Grace Helen Burgess.
♪ It's up in the morning It's on the downs
♪ Little white clouds
like gambolling lambs
♪ And I am breathless over you
♪ And the red-breasted
robin beats his wings
♪ His throat, it trembles
when he sings... ♪
Those flowers need to go there.
Do you, Thomas Michael Shelby,
take Grace Helen Burgess
to be your lawful wedded wife?
I do.
Do you, Grace Helen Burgess,
solemnly swear to love,
honour and obey
till death do you part?
I do.
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Go on, son!
♪ Still your hands
♪ And still your heart
♪ For still your face
comes shining through
♪ And all the morning glows anew
♪ Still your mind
♪ Still your soul
♪ For still the fire of love is true
♪ And I am breathless without you... ♪
Get out of it!
- All right, Arthur, come on.
- Wait for me! Wait for me good self!
Go on, take the photograph!
Go on, boy. Get them on the go.
Tommy.
- Get the bastards in the house.
- I will. I will. John! John Boy!
John Boy. Get them in
the house, all of them.
Go on, all of you! Back
to the house. Come on!
♪ Still your hands
♪ And still your heart
♪ For still your face
comes shining through
♪ And all the morning glows anew
♪ Still your soul
♪ Still your mind
♪ For still the fire of love is true
♪ And I am breathless without you. ♪
All right, Pol. Tell the Lee girls
I've counted all the paintings.
Oh, Pol. Some people
here are not on the list.
Curly, Charlie. Kitchen, five minutes.
Actually, we were told on the
train there'd be cocaine.
Jeremiah, John Boy, kitchen, let's go.
I swear to God, them fucking
cavalry boys are asking for it.
I was told to ask someone
young. Will there be cocaine?
Sweetheart, I am young,
informed and very well equipped.
You chose your man wisely.
Come on, kitchen, now.
Arthur, this lady wants
to play in the snow.
No. No snow today. No snow today.
Kitchen, come on.
I just wish Tommy was here.
- Where are they?
- I don't know, Tom.
Arthur, John, where are they?
- I don't know.
- I am telling you now, we got lost.
You really need to do a map.
Tommy.
Right, boys, you're all here.
Today, this is my fucking wedding day.
Yeah, and you said there'd
be no bloody uniforms.
Nevertheless. Nevertheless, John.
Despite the bad blood,
I'll have none of it on my carpet.
Now, for Grace's sake,
nothing will go wrong.
Those bastards out there are her family.
And if you fuckers do anything
to embarrass her, your kin,
your cousins, your horses, your
fucking kids, you do anything...
Tom?
- .. to... What?
- What about snow?
Yeah, their women are
sports, I'll say that.
No. No. No.
No cocaine.
No sport. No telling fortunes.
No racing. No fucking sucking
petrol out of their fucking cars.
And you, Charlie, stop
spinning yarns about me, eh?
I'm just trying to sell you to them, Tom.
But the main thing is,
you bunch of fuckers,
despite the provocation from the cavalry,
no fighting!
Oi!
No fighting.
No fucking fighting.
NO FUCKING FIGHTING!
Good.
Get the fuck off me!
You're needed downstairs.
Grace, you're needed
downstairs. People are hungry.
I was putting Charles to sleep.
I'll come down, but not
with you like this.
All right, fine.
Tommy.
I thought today was the reason for
the way you've been acting lately.
I know there's business on your mind.
And I know there always will be.
- Yeah. - Look. I am sorry
they wore their uniforms.
Yeah, they fucking did,
eh? They fucking did.
But I can tell it's more than that.
You've been like this for weeks.
I need you to tell me that it's
business making you like this...
and not regret over me.
Say it out loud and
I'll know if it's true.
It's business, Grace.
And bad, bad business it is, all round.
And I'm scared, Grace.
I'm scared for you.
I'm scared for the baby.
And this is how I am when I'm scared.
It is unfamiliar to you but not to me.
I can fucking be scared and carry on.
And it's not pleasant to look
at and no joy to be around.
All right?
I'm sorry.
We just made vows to share everything.
Tell me what it is you're afraid of.
Stand up. Stand up. Stand up.
Arthur's speech.
I'm scared of fucking Arthur's speech.
All right?
Me too.
Tommy, what are you doing?
Tommy, there's half the British
Army waiting for us downstairs.
They're King's Irish. We waited
two weeks in the mud for them.
Tommy.
There are things that if I take them off
I won't be able to put back on.
That's good.
Hello, Mrs Shelby.
I'm sorry for being busy in my head.
Let us complete the ceremony.
Hey, listen. Listen. Listen.
What do you call an animal with
a prick halfway up its back?
A cavalry horse.
He gets it.
Fuck it. Fuck it.
Where the bloody hell are they?
You're best man, Arthur. Go and find them.
Yeah.
That's completely nonsense.
You know, we're part of a serious
political movement and organisation.
They're not "secret little
meetings", they're just meetings.
We talk about the world,
about the people in it,
about our current political
landscape and what's going on.
You know, we really need to re-evaluate
the way our government has...
- Very strange indeed.
- Polly, he's looking over.
But, erm...
He's coming. He bloody is.
Fuck. It's the wrong one.
What do you mean the wrong
one? How many are there?
There's two giving me the
eye. I prefer the other one.
He looked harmless.
It must be that bloody lipstick
Tommy brought you back from New York.
I couldn't help noticing
you are unaccompanied.
I also am alone.
May I join you?
Tommy?
Oh. Didn't see a thing.
Not see a thing. Sorry, brother.
I need you downstairs.
That's all right, we're
done. Are you good?
- Yeah. Never been better.
- Yeah.
- Are you drunk?
- No. No.
Here.
All right, just one drink, then.
Linda's a good woman, Arthur.
Good whisky.
A good man needs to
hold out sometimes, eh?
I won't mention this
in my speech, then, eh?
Not unless you want to get cut, Arthur.
Sorry, sister.
Right. Look. Tell the maids
to break out the champagne.
I'll be down in a minute.
Champagne, yeah. OK.
- Got it right here.
- Good. - I'm ready. - Good.
Where are you from?
I'm a refugee.
From where?
Russia.
In the past few months
Thomas has developed some
business interests with Russia.
I see he has confided in you.
Hm.
You need his permission
to even speak to me.
My senior position within
the Shelby company means
I don't often have to ask permission
from anyone to do anything.
So perhaps you'll just tell me
why the fuck you're talking Russian
business on Thomas's wedding day.
Hold on, wait a second.
- So you're saying I'm not allowed a man.
- It's about your choice of man.
I'm not allowed a man on my arm?
Fucking bastard.
Michael, speeches. Come on.
Arthur. You know why he
didn't come, don't you?
Why who didn't come?
My bloody man.
Oh, you mean the wop?
I just heard there was a
fire at his restaurant.
Midnight last night.
And a smashed back window
and a smell of petrol.
Lizzie, we tried to
talk some sense into you.
We did checks on him.
He's had five different
names in the last six years
- and he's got connections with the
Naples boys. - Come on, Michael.
What do you know about love,
about when lightning strikes?
So, it was lightning, hmm? Not petrol.
- I thought you were off the
whisky, Arthur. - Yeah, I am.
I'm having a couple now and again
to remind myself why I don't drink it.
You set fire to his
restaurant to stop him coming.
You have no right to choose who
I step out with in my own time!
Lizzie, you now have an important
position in this company.
You got the order the same as us.
You can do it.
Until further notice...
no fraternising with the foreigners.
Yeah, well, you can tell Tommy from me
all the girls in the office think
he's losing his fucking mind.
To the bride.
The bride.
And now, according to tradition,
my best man will say a few words.
Go on! Here he goes! Go on, Arthur!
I'd like to, erm... I'm
not one for speeches.
Sing, then!
I will later, John.
But I do, erm...
I do have some words written down here...
.. on this piece of paper.
This doesn't include
everything that I want to say...
(Arthur, just read what
we wrote down, eh?)
I will.
I will, mm-hmm.
But first...
First a few words from the heart.
Erm...
This man here, my brother, Tommy,
helped me survive through
some of the worst times.
It's a wedding, Arthur, tell a joke.
Yeah. Tell a joke.
What I am trying to say is this.
My brother,
and the love of a good woman...
.. pulled me through that time.
Now Tommy also has the
love of a good woman.
Her name's Grace.
Like the grace of the good Lord.
And even though the circumstances
of their union was tragic...
Right, let's... Arthur,
let's raise a toast, eh?
To love, to peace, to marriage.
And to marriage.
Well done, Arthur. Beautiful speech.
Really nice.
Really, really nice.
Where's he fucking going now?
I think I messed it up.
No, not a bit.
You spoke with such truth.
And God heard you.
Can I have a word with
my brother, please, Linda?
What he was going to say was beautiful.
Alone, please.
All right. Come here.
Come here.
We talked about this, Arthur.
That's why we wrote it all down.
Most of Grace's side don't even
know her husband killed himself.
They think it was an accident.
- I know.
- You know.
- Yeah.
What do you think I am, hm?
What do you think I am, Tommy, eh?
You think I'm a fucking idiot...
- All right, boys? - Yep. - Don't you?
Come on. Having a good night.
- You think I would say it?
- That's it. Right.
Yeah. Keep walking. You nosy bastards.
- Hey, you stay away from me, Tommy.
- Fucking hell.
You stay away from me, I've had it.
Ah, shit.
- Yeah. - Argh! - Yeah.
Argh.
Argh!
Ah, shit.
Three shots I've had, that's it.
- I know. - I drew the line. - I know.
I know you've turned a corner.
- Arthur. - Yeah. - I know.
- Yeah. I'm your best man.
- I know.
I wasn't going to tell no-one.
It's all right. It's done.
Get up. Get up.
Get up.
Right...
The Russians have made contact.
We have to get used to how
these bastards operate.
For them, family is a weakness
and they go after them.
For me, family is my strength.
And there's business to be done
and I need you.
Now, fuck speeches, fuck weddings.
You're my best man every fucking day.
OK.
Yeah?
Now go and get John, get him sobered up.
Find Johnny Dogs. It's the
Russians through the smoke tonight.
- All right.
- Good.
Oh, and, Arthur...
In future, it's not always
right to listen to Linda.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's full of gypsies and blacks.
Grace says he exports
automobiles to the colonies.
Pol, now.
So, what does he say?
He won't meet you unless
you give us the name.
What name?
We were told to ask for a code
name when contact was made.
Constantine.
The code is Constantine.
Tommy said no racing, no gambling.
Yeah, he's changed his mind. Right!
Don't worry, Finn, OK?
Cavalry boys ride like a sack of stones.
John, there's an awful lot of
King's shillings around here today.
Now, out of loyalty to the regiment,
they'll all be putting their money
on this bad boy that I filled up
with morphine and water.
Here, Tommy's all right
if I do the book, is he?
He said betting's OK,
but all proceeds go to the
Shelby Foundation charity.
This charity of his for real, then?
He says he wants to be seen giving
back to the poor of Birmingham.
That'll be me, John. Myself, if I
can't earn a shilling here tonight.
- Huh? - They'll make him
fucking Lord Mayor next.
- That's the idea, Charlie boy.
- Fucking hell.
Right. All you lot make as
much noise and fuss as you can.
Especially fucking you.
Ah. So, we're a fucking
distraction, John, is it?
Tommy's doing business on a
night he should be just fucking.
Right, place your bets with me.
Your favourites. Your favourites.
Come on, boys.
Cos I hope my wife's friend doesn't
fall off the fucking horse.
Come on!
For charity?!
Shut up.
Ah, you found it.
We nearly gave up.
Did he tell you what
my business with him is?
The same shit the Turks used to smoke.
I wonder, why does he trust his
aunt more than his brothers?
Go and watch the race, boys.
The Turk's clean.
- I am Russian.
- Same fucking thing.
So you make contact on my wedding day.
You now have very powerful enemies,
at the Soviet Embassy and
within your own government.
You are being watched --
at your house, your office,
your clubs, your bars.
You best be quick or I'll be
missed. Where's the money?
The Duke's niece is
bringing it from London.
I was told money on contact.
10,000 in US dollars.
My employer only trusts members
of his family with cash.
She will be at Snow Hill
Station at ten o'clock.
A woman alone in Birmingham
with 10,000 in cash.
She also has a revolver.
- Oh, I see.
- I thought you trusted women.
I don't trust Birmingham.
I'll have her picked up.
- By who?
- By the police, pal.
This is our city.
Fucking beautiful horse, Tom.
Beautiful.
- He's a natural, that boy.
- Yeah. Good posture.
- Rides like Dad.
- Right, listen to me.
Tell Johnny Dogs and his boys
to light a fire in the woods.
A big one, to take meat.
Send Finn to watch the gates.
Moss is bringing someone.
You don't?
I just needed to bring you
somewhere nobody could see.
But your friend gave this to
me. He said you all did it.
Not me. But it's all right.
Go on.
I see you don't either.
Don't be silly. Everyone does.
- So go on, then. Cut the snow.
- We call it Tokyo.
We call it whatever the customer calls it.
In London we were told
you were all gangsters.
So that's why you got on the
train to dirty old Birmingham.
For a dirty old night.
- You don't look like the others.
- That's the idea.
I put it all together but I don't partake.
See, I've got a bright future, you see?
Mapped out.
But you want me to be
like them, don't you?
There's a cavalry officer
stationed in Ceylon.
When his tour of duty ends
in March, we will be engaged.
So I have a bright future too.
Mapped out.
But you want to try things first.
No. Keep it.
As if I were a whore.
If that's the game you want to play...
Polly.
Hello, Grace.
You look absolutely beautiful.
Welcome to the family.
Oh, I see. Tommy's orders.
No upsets tonight.
Your hair, everything. Beautiful.
Do you know where he is?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
You know, Tommy really wants to
keep certain things a secret from me.
But it's very hard when
you're man and wife.
We were late coming down
because we were having sex.
Afterwards he told me everything.
Royalist Russians buying weapons
to fight the Bolsheviks in Georgia.
A lost cause, Tommy says.
Churchill is the go-between but
it's against government policy
so everything must be kept a secret.
You know it's begun.
They started the business tonight.
No.
I didn't.
But you just told me, so thank you.
Let's not forget, I used
to do this for a living.
Oh, I haven't forgotten, sweetheart.
It's only Thomas that's
forgotten what you are.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The bride and the groom
will now dance alone.
Polly just told me there's
business being done.
I didn't ask them to come.
Tommy, please don't let
anything happen tonight.
Just get this business done and
get away from things like this.
I'll run the foundation,
you run the tracks and sell cars.
Promise me. Hm?
A wedding vowel.
I promise.
No guns in the house and
Charles will never see one.
I love you, Thomas Shelby.
You keep us safe.
I love you.
And I promise I will make us safe.
Ladies and gentlemen, you may now join.
Gatehouse. Come on.
Tommy, Arthur, Collins,
may I introduce you to the Grand
Duchess Tatiana Petrovna...
.. from Tbilisi, Georgia?
Grand Duchess, may I introduce
you to the Shelby brothers?
Small Heath, Birmingham.
And, erm, good luck with this one, Tom.
Give me the money.
I was told to give it to Mr Kaledin.
Whoever it is up there,
he gave the wrong name.
We asked him the name and
he gave the wrong one.
- What name did he give?
- No.
I don't trust any of you.
Now you give me the money.
I know Mr Kaledin by sight
from Tbilisi. Is his hair dark?
The instructions I was given
was anyone using the wrong
code name was an infiltrator
for the Soviet Embassy.
Just let me go to the house.
I do not want this shit
anywhere near my fucking house.
All I know is no variations.
That's from Churchill himself.
Whoever is up at the house, he
gave the wrong fucking name.
And you do this to me on
my fucking wedding day.
The money is in the car, Mr Shelby.
Fetch it out and count it.
Good. Finn.
Yeah. We're good.
You can go. Moss.
Can you do it?
Can you kill?
Moss, you take the Duchess
back to Birmingham.
Righto, Tom.
Go on, love.
That's right.
You've got to tell me the reason,
otherwise I'll never be able to trust you.
The truth is...
.. that I slept with the wife of
one of the colonels who sat for me.
But that was 12 years ago...
.. and the aristocracy don't
believe in forgiveness.
Neither do the Shelbys.
So we kill him?
He's a Red.
We're being paid by the Whites.
It's part of the contract.
Contract!
We should never have got into this, Tom.
There was no choice.
A factory break-in, that's what you said.
Yeah, that's what it is.
There's some shit that goes with it.
And who shovels it? Hm?
Who fucking shovels it? Eh?
- I fucking know.
- Arthur.
- Arthur...
There's ten times where
that's coming from, ten times,
for lifting vehicles off
a fucking shop floor.
Vehicles, Tommy. Fucking vehicles.
Nothing about tanks.
Arthur, you listen to me.
You listen to me, all right?
There are powerful people in this country
who want to help these mad bastards,
including the King, Churchill
and half the fucking Tory party.
And if we refuse, Arthur,
if we fucking refuse,
they will see to it that we
hang for all of our many sins.
Now, we've never earned
money like this. Never.
We'll use it to buy the
wharf at Boston docks.
That's why I've asked for dollars.
And when it's done it's business as usual.
Come on, brother. It's my wedding night.
- Where's John? - Looking
for Esme. - Right.
Ruben Oliver. Portrait artist.
I really enjoyed the depiction
of you in the dining room.
Nice to meet you, Mr Oliver.
Danny, ragtime.
So, where were we?
- Crimea. - I mean before
I bored you with war.
- Politics.
- Yes.
You are the only one in your
family who is a communist.
Some of them are, they just don't know it.
And you are very close family, yes?
Mm, always within punching distance.
What does that mean?
It means yeah, we're a close family.
Arthur?
I do apologise for the interruption.
There is a woman here
to see you, Mr Kaledin.
She just arrived.
- So Tatiana made it from
London safely? - Yes.
- Where is she?
- Out by the stables.
Can I use the lavatory?
You can piss outside...
.. by the stables.
Very sensible idea, Mr Shelby.
Clear the air away from the ladies.
We are rather like
generals here, aren't we?
Watching our men do battle.
We are a bit too close to the
fighting to be generals, surely.
You know, Mr Shelby, some of
us only agreed to come today
to bless this union because
of your exemplary war record.
But as Grace's uncle, and a kind
of father to her for many years...
.. I am still deeply uneasy about
the many stories of corruption
and violence.
Drink the fucking wine and smile.
That's what I'm doing.
Oh, you got me good there.
Oh, you fucking bastard.
- Don't shoot.
- No!
- For the love of
God. Don't shoot. - No!
- No! - For the love of
God! - No! No! No! No! No!
- No!
- For the love of God!
- What was that?
- Probably just a car backfiring.
It wasn't the day I was expecting.
Nor me.
But it's over now.
Tomorrow it'll be just us.
Come here.
The water froze in my car.
They said I could stay.
I know this is preposterous.
Plenty of other rooms to stay in.
- Goodnight, Mr Oliver.
- You have my card.
Any time you're in
London we could have tea.
I went looking for you.
I thought you'd be in here.
I knew it.
I wanted to end with a bit of peace.
Look what I found.
It's beautiful. Thanks.
Arthur, you mustn't worry about
what happened with the speech.
What was in your heart was beautiful.
God hears all the speeches
that don't get said.
And isn't it nice to still be
yourself at this time of night?
Close your eyes, Arthur, and spend
a minute thinking about that.
♪ Come on
♪ Come on... ♪
There.
♪ You think you drive me crazy well
♪ Come on
♪ You and whose army?
♪ You and your cronies
- ♪ Come on... ♪
- Shh.
♪ Come on
♪ Holy Roman Empire
♪ Come on if you think
♪ You can take us all on
♪ You and whose army?
♪ You and your cronies
♪ You forget so easily
♪ We ride tonight
♪ Ghost horses
♪ Ghost horses. ♪
More money than all those
fucking toffs put together, eh?
And you're willing to gamble
it all on one robbery.
I'm a gambling man, Pol.
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
♪ And go across the tracks
♪ Where the viaduct
looms, like a bird of doom
♪ As it shifts and cracks
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
with a red right hand. ♪