- Thomas Michael Shelby
- Today is my wedding day
[Go on,] take the photograph!
- 'The Russians have made contact.
- On your wedding night?'
Whoever it is up there,
he gave the wrong name.
Can you do it? Can you kill?
You know why he didn't come,
don't you? My bloody man.
'There was a fire at his restaurant.'
No fraternising with the foreigners.
He's a cavalry officer.
In March we'll be engaged.
'But you want to try things first.
'Ruben Oliver. Portrait artist.'
You have my card.
What was in your heart was beautiful.
Just get this business done and
get away from things like this.
Promise me.
I promise I will make us safe.
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
♪ And go across the tracks
♪ Where the viaduct
looms like a bird of doom
♪ As it shifts and cracks
♪ Where secrets lie in the border fires
♪ In the humming wires
♪ Hey, man, you know
you're never coming back
♪ Past the square, past the bridge
Past the mills, past the stacks
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
with a red right hand... ♪
Your brothers came to my house.
They said the Peaky Blinders
had business with me.
You're not afraid of me?
So, what is it you want
from a simple working man?
Fear.
Poor Mr Nutley drank too much.
He went for a piss on the train tracks
that run behind the factory.
Train came.
They found his body in
Saltley broken into bits.
I know what you do. Tell me what you want.
There.
The lot, complete warehouse.
Bays four, five and six.
You have the keys?
Yes, I have the keys.
What's in bay four?
Completed type 40s and type 21s
waiting for the paint shop.
Bay five?
Paint shop and parts.
Uh-uh.
So, it's bay six.
What is?
Give me the keys to bay six.
It's just old stock in storage.
For your trouble.
Give it to your charity...
I'm only doing this for
the safety of my family.
So, will it be just boys in
your charitable institution
or girls, as well?
Both.
You must divide them.
You know how the little creatures can get.
Where are your people? You
said they'd be here by five.
They're a law unto themselves.
You can never quite grasp who they are.
Like gripping wet soap.
I've done my research.
Perhaps you know them as
the, er... Economic League.
Only once did I get a letter from
them headed the Vigilance Committee.
Which tips the hand a little.
Nope.
The name I've heard is Section D.
That's what Special Branch calls them.
Businessmen, MPs, army officers.
Yes, it will be fun to bring
such men to a Gypsy scrapyard.
You asked for privacy.
Since the election, the Government
has decided that we are the enemy.
When all we're trying to do is
save the country from revolution.
Are you political, Mr Shelby?
Because these odd fellows believe
that the time is coming soon
when everyone must choose a side.
Are your people coming,
or are they not coming?
Mr Shelby, you will learn that
these men are far too grand
for the clock to govern them.
You'll get used to meeting in
the small hours of the morning.
They're like monks.
So, when is your charitable
institute opening?
When I fucking say.
Well, I'll stop by from time to time.
Hear confession from the little creatures.
You will meet Mr Patrick Jarvis, MP.
He'll probably want to become a trustee.
It's just his thing, to drop by in
the evenings after a few drinks.
We'll make it a formal arrangement
as part of the... bigger deal between us.
I will have an office there.
My God. Some devil gets
into you, doesn't it, boy?
Mr Shelby, if I want to play the squire
in your place of false
charity then I will.
Ambition for respectability
doesn't make you a saint.
Am I wrong?
Oh, Lord. That's six, is it?
Well, I will wish you a good day.
The fuck are you going?
Did I not make it clear?
They said if they weren't
here by morning prayers
then the meeting has been cancelled.
Perhaps Mr Jarvis has been held
up at the House of Commons.
Perhaps Admiral Hall's been
held up at the House of Lords.
Am I impressing you?
Or perhaps they've decided they
don't care for doing business
with Gypsies in scrap-metal yards.
Which would be a poorer outcome for you.
You give them a message from me, priest.
You tell them I've been to the factories
and the armoured vehicles
are in good condition.
How many?
27.
And the foreman is ours.
This is someone you will meet,
today, at the Ritz.
I have meetings today.
You have one meeting.
This one. In London.
So you'd best catch the milk train.
Cold.
My apologies, sir.
And how many times I
asked you to tell them
about sending us the servants' crockery?
I have no control over the
choice of service, sir.
Hmm. And what about the yesterday
egg? And last year's fish?
And last century's tea
leaves in a cracked pot?
Sir, I have a list of
today's social engagements
- if you'd like to hear them.
- Oh, are we in a rush today?
I have duties at the main house, sir.
Luncheon at the Ritz with
Duke Mikhail Mikhailovich.
Cancelled.
What reason?
He says he's unwell, sir.
You're due to have tea at three
with Prince Vsevolod Ivanovich
and Lady Mary Lewington, sir...
Mm. Good.
I miss out on the bore
and meet the beauty.
However, in the absence of the Duke,
the Prince and the Lady
too have cancelled,
Other than that your day is your own.
You do have one business appointment
to discuss automobiles.
With a Mr Thomas Shelby, sir.
You asked for a meeting out in the open.
Fresh air and the fine aroma of shit.
"Neutral ground," you said.
This is hardly neutral ground.
Well, it's what you've got.
So, por favivo, sit down.
- Where is Thomas?
- He got called away.
- He said he'd be here.
- Yeah, he's busy.
I just told you he got
called away. What do you want?
There has been a peace
between the Peaky Blinders
and the Changretta family
for two years now...
Do you want some tea or not?
Here, Finn, pour the Italians
some English tea. Go on.
We don't want fucking tea!
We want an explanation.
Well, I'll have fucking tea.
Explanation for what?
The Little Venice restaurant
in Forge Street was burnt down.
No, no, couldn't have been
us. We was at a wedding.
You burnt it down to stop my
son being at that same wedding.
Yeah, he wasn't missed.
You are such big boys now.
Where once you borrowed clothes
from us to look like men.
How's the tea, Arthur? Is it...?
It's cold.
Please tell Tommy that we pay
him whatever he asks us to pay.
We stay out of the city
and off the tracks.
But you tell him from me
that my son will walk with
any woman in this city.
Any woman he chooses.
Even if that woman works for
the Emperor, Thomas Shelby.
My son is in love...
Sorry.
Do excuse me.
Carry on.
And if he wishes,
he will walk with the woman he loves.
OK.
Y'know...
It'd be hard for your son to walk anywhere
with a bullet in each knee, wouldn't it?
Too much.
You said too much, my friend.
Sabini says, "Suck and
swallow." But no. Too much.
I spit.
Oh, fucking... Bit strong.
Fucking hell.
Isiah. Put two extra men
on our pubs in Nechells.
What you talking about, Arthur?
We're not scared of
fucking eyeties any more.
Don't tell Tommy about the chair
and clean this fucking shit up.
We're not scared of fucking wops!
All right, John.
Arthur!
Hello, Ada.
Tommy Shelby in a library.
I'm here to borrow a book
about the Russian Revolution.
Shh!
Have you got a new wharf
at Maida Vale now?
I've got a new wharf everywhere now.
I sometimes see our trucks driving past.
"Our" trucks?
Shelby trucks.
Why the interest?
I just want to broaden my mind.
Well, this is a list of
the bastards who ran away.
And this is written from the point
of view of the people's struggle.
Uh-huh.
There was a Russian at your wedding.
He wouldn't tell me how
come he got invited.
Well, sometimes exiled Russian aristocrats
get invited to social occasions
to add a bit of class.
Is that why he was there?
Why do you want to know?
He was nice. Maybe I'd
like to see him again.
Would that be possible?
No. That would not be possible.
What business do you have
with Russians, Tommy?
Can I rip this page out?
No, you cannot rip that page
out. Property of the people.
Tommy, when Arthur took the Russian
away he had his killing pistol
under his jacket. And then
Johnny lit a fire in the woods.
You want all the details
because you're bored, Ada.
You used to chase rats
with a revolver, Ada.
Shh! For fuck's sake.
I might just have a job for you after all.
Did we run Kempton yesterday, or not?
Danny Lee got drunk.
Instead of injecting the
horses with the cocaine,
he decided to share it with his cousins.
Jesus Christ.
He's your brother-in-law.
Tell Esme to speak to him about it.
Look. Before I start...
.. I don't want you to
do anything about this.
About what?
Vicente Changretta's son.
The one Lizzie was stepping out with.
What, Angel?
He's no bigger than two
pence worth of change.
He heard you threatened him
directly to shoot him in the knees.
And now he's going around Nechells
telling everyone he's going to kill you.
This is Lizzie's fault to start with,
Tommy's for leaving it up to you.
What are you talking about?
We run London.
We run the North, run the
whole fucking country.
What do we care about some
fucking Nechells Green eyeties?
We don't need to be getting involved
in all these little piss pots.
What does Arthur say?
That's why I'm here...
and not him.
If he said it, there'd be a fight.
He says...
apologise.
He fucking said what?
We own the city.
But we don't need to rub
everybody's noses in it.
If the old man decides to make a stand,
- he might get Sabini feeling
sentimental... - Sabini's done.
They're all done.
And they all pay up.
But we don't... want... rebellions.
What does, erm... What does Tommy say?
Tommy's busy. He left me in charge.
What... What do you say?
Compromise.
Mm.
I've asked Lizzie to do it for you.
She's going to meet him,
break up with him for good.
Apologise for any inconvenience.
Say it was all her fault.
Fuck's sake!
You know what all this is?
This is Arthur's fucking missus.
Turn the other fucking cheek.
We'll be handing out Bibles
in the fucking Bull Ring
- with her cousins...
- John, you don't have to do anything.
- Ah, it's done.
- Lizzie will do it for you.
Then it'll all calm down
and nobody will lose face.
I'll take his fucking
face, how about that?
John, do nothing. Oh!
I believe you have a reservation
for a private room in
the name of Mr Romanov.
You work for Mr Romanov?
- Yes. - For his
household or his office?
Is there a problem?
I'm afraid without the presence
of the Duke Mikhail Mikhailovich
or Lady Lewington we shall have
to ask for payment in advance.
Can I ask why?
Already Mr Romanov has four
outstanding bills with us.
One for accommodation
and three for dining.
And two banquets which we wrote off.
We've been asked to be understanding
of our Russian friends
by His Majesty, but it
has been some time now.
And...
- May I ask your name, sir?
- Shelby. Thomas Shelby.
And in the future I'll be
dining here quite a bit.
- Then I shall put you on our
special list. - You do that.
Here is a menu.
I recommend the teal and the pork.
Although your guest, I'm
sure, will order the caviar.
Myself, my wife and my
niece travelled by train,
then coach, then on foot through
the Villa Ai-Todor in Crimea.
On that journey I lost a toe.
I don't know. I woke up one
morning and it was gone.
All of a sudden I saw a
dog and it was eating it.
They said the British
had taken pity on us.
And we were taken aboard HMS Marlborough.
I immediately kissed the steel
deck. My lips froze to it.
And then of course, I thanked
God and your King for saving us.
Though since then he has done
nothing but humiliate me...
Who? God or the King?
Sometimes both, Mr Shelby.
Mm. So, you met my niece already.
Tatiana.
Are you in love with her yet? Hm?
You would be wise not to
love Russian woman, you know.
Better not speak of Russian women.
That's the worst thing about being here.
Russian women, they know how to hold it
and most important they know
exactly when to let it go.
Your cock, I mean.
English women, they do not
know so much, you know?
Did he die well, the spy?
He begged for his life.
I heard you had your brother do it.
So, you trust your family. Like me.
Like us, Mr Shelby.
Let's talk about trust, then, shall we?
You are not a direct
relation to the Romanovs.
You are Georgian.
And the palace where you
live in Hampton Court
is in fact a grace-and-favour house
donated to you rent-free
by the British Crown.
The maitre d' here tells me
that you are in some debt.
Both here and other places, I imagine.
See, I've been given ten...
but I've been promised 40.
Already I've had to have a man killed.
That sort of work does not come cheap.
Do you understand?
Let me tell you something, Mr Shelby.
Before we boarded the ship,
my niece sewed 16 diamonds
into her velvet dress.
And also she had two sapphires
in her intimate places.
My wife managed two
sapphires and five diamonds.
This is already for the
killing of the spy.
And down payment on future services.
Now tell me, where do you keep
these things? In a... bank?
How could we plead poverty
around London society
if we used banks, Mr Shelby?
Well, you should know
Hatton Gardens is not safe.
That is why we have our own treasury.
Very well. I shall have my
people check its veracity...
Before the revolution began,
we were soft and weak.
We made compromise.
But let me tell you.
We will never be soft and weak again.
Do you understand?
Good day, Mr Shelby.
This way, Mr Changretta.
Just there, sir. There.
I hear you want to kill me.
Get fucking up! Stay away from Lizzie.
By order of the Peaky fucking Blinders.
Going to introduce me, Michael?
This is Charlotte Murray.
Her father makes cars.
I really enjoyed your wedding, Mr Shelby.
Polly said you should call
her. There's been some trouble.
What trouble?
I'm guessing the stuff she
doesn't like to tell me about.
Nice to meet you.
All right, Finn, thanks
for coming. Fuck off.
Finn, you can stay.
Sit down, John. Sit down.
John, you cut Angel Changretta.
Even though Arthur told you to apologise.
Mm-hm.
- Polly told you to compromise.
- Mm-hm.
You chose not to listen to Mr
Apologise or Mrs Compromise.
And now I've got an Italian
walking around my back yard
saying he's going to kill my brother.
So, what do we do, John? Do we
apologise, or do we compromise?
Oh, it was just something
John said as a joke.
Yeah, but he's your
brother as well, Arthur.
Yeah.
And I didn't want to start
a war over something
John said without meaning it.
So, should he apologise in
Italian... or in English?
Or should we ask them which
fucking language they'd prefer?
I'm not clear.
You said while this business was going
on in London you wanted peace at home.
And the only way to guarantee peace
is by making the prospect
of war seem hopeless.
If you apologise once, you do
it again and again and again.
Like taking bricks out of the
wall of your fucking house.
- Do you want to bring the
house down, Arthur? - Ah...
If you're soft on rebellion, it'll grow.
Bloody "soft on rebellion".
You did the right thing, John.
Now we go on the offensive.
We take two of the Changretta pubs.
We take 'em tonight. That's it.
Oh, right. For Christ's sake, why?
- Hey?! - Why? - Why?
Because we fucking can.
Because we fucking can,
and if we can, we do.
And if we lift our heel off their
necks now, they'll just come at us.
Remember, these are the bastards
that wanted Danny Whizz-Bang dead.
You're getting soft, brother.
Soft and weak.
Save the Bible for Sundays, eh?
Finn, I need to get to Hockley, then home.
It's been a long day.
You take the Wrexham,
you take the Five Bells.
You get them signed over
to us in the morning.
You make sure the coppers stay away.
Don't use the fucking phones, all right?
There's someone listening.
Well done.
Not hungry, Mrs Shelby?
Hungry? Oh, no. Sorry, Mary.
You'll ruin your eyes.
Tommy.
Hello.
Sit down.
- Guess.
- Guess what?
- He said yes.
- Who?
The leader of Birmingham City Council
is going to attend the dinner.
- Everyone has said
yes. - Ah.. - Everyone.
I keep having to change the catering.
And my writing hand is almost falling off.
What are you writing for?
I bought you a typewriter.
You don't write letters of a
social occasion on a typewriter.
Oh. Forgive me.
I have the drawings of
what they plan to do
with the grounds of the house.
- There'll be an area for the
children to play. Look. - Mm-hm.
And the Birmingham Charity
Commission have agreed to set aside
the three rotten floorboards upstairs
and grant us a licence within the month.
- You're not listening to me.
- Yes, I am. I am.
Do you think I am becoming obsessed?
Yes.
Should I ask you how your
day was, like a good wife?
No.
I'm guessing that means your day
was not as successful as mine.
Well, depends on how you measure success.
See, personally,
I measure it in sapphires.
Oh...
- Sapphires?
- Mmm.
Close your eyes.
(Close your eyes.)
All right, you can open them.
Where the hell did you get that?
It's beautiful.
You can wear it to the foundation dinner.
Don't you think it is a bit
much for a charity dinner?
Grace, this is fucking Birmingham.
Good taste is for people
who can't afford sapphires.
Oh, Mr Shelby!
Did you wind the clock, Arthur?
We should go to bed.
I need to...
I need to go out.
Some business I need to do.
Business?
But you only just got in.
I won't be long.
It's ten o'clock.
It's pouring with rain.
I'll go. I'll go and I'll come back.
Arthur.
Working in the dark is
for the devil. We said.
Start to do your work in the light.
You have your own light. Inside your head.
It's just paperwork.
I need you to clear your
men out of Nechells tonight.
- I thought you boys were a bit grand
this sort of thing these days. - Moss.
Mind you, I think Tom enjoys the sport.
Something like that.
- Goodnight, Arthur.
- 'Night.
Arthur, what are you doing?
Arthur?
We're going to the Garrison.
No. I'm going home, John.
Go fuck yourself, Arthur.
Yeah. Fuck off!
Come here, Charlie. Charlie.
This big man and his brother are
going to make us a lot of money.
Or lose us a lot of money.
Who cares when they're
such beautiful beasts, eh?
You've got a house, John.
Oh, fuck...
Full of kids.
Well, you've got a maid
to look after the kids.
Yeah, she listens.
Have you even done the odds for tomorrow?
Something urgent came up.
They get worse when they're pregnant, Tom.
John.
Esme, I need you to leave
now. Go out the back door.
And lock it after you.
When I left the office...
There's two truckfuls of
coppers out there, John.
Where the fuck is Arthur?
He goes home to the Madonna Of
Moseley on the stroke of five.
You need to talk to him, Tom.
Esme, please go now. Please.
This is very fucking unusual.
So, call Moss.
They're from out of town.
London, by the looks of their boots.
Since when are we scared of coppers, Tom?
Since things changed.
Scotland Yard!
Flying Squad.
- John, it's the Yard. It's the Yard.
- Put it down. Put it down.
Down on your knees.
Hands on your heads! Down on your knees!
Let her fucking go!
She's fucking pregnant.
- Leave her alone!
- What the fuck is happening, Tom?
Let's go!
Put me down!
Tell Polly it's Russian business, John.
All right.
Peaky fucking Blinders, my arse.
Is he afraid?
No.
Sit.
I'm talking to you, Mr Shelby.
So, the Oddfellows want you to know that
any deviation from your
instructions will have consequences.
What's your dog's name?
You visited your sister.
Eh? What's your name, boy?
Your sister is a potential
security breach.
She has connections
with Bolsheviks in London
who have connections
with the Soviet Embassy.
I think I'll just call your dog, "Boy".
You love your Boy, don't you?
Understand this.
You have the local police in your pocket.
We have Scotland Yard.
They do what we tell them
just as surely as this dog.
Let him off the leash.
Are you hearing me, Mr Shelby?
I can charm dogs.
Gypsy witchcraft.
And those I can't charm I
can kill with my own hands.
You learn it when you
have a dog on a boat.
They go fucking mad in tunnels.
I feel like I'm in a tunnel now.
You know that feeling when
you have to kill or be killed.
Let the dog off the leash and
give the order you give in Gaelic.
Like I'm told you do when
someone displeases you,
when someone reports you.
Visit your sister again and she
will die crossing the road.
Maraigh.
Come on, you say it.
If you wanted me dead,
I'd be dead, wouldn't I?
It's true.
It's true, we do need you alive.
But when you go home today, Mr Shelby,
be sure to check under
your little boy's pillow.
The tooth fairy has been.
We can reach anyone...
.. anywhere.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Everything's fine. Everything's fine.
Yeah.
You promised, Tommy.
I trust you.
I trust you, Tommy.
Yes.
He's fine. He's fine.
Grace... Grace.
Come on. Yeah.
You're not one of those
impressionists, are you?
They are all terribly
political, aren't they?
- And you're not?
- Goodness, no.
The people I work for just
want me to paint what's there.
To me, politics is deliberately
making things better for some people
by deliberately making
them worse for others.
Well, I thought I might wear this.
Oh, God. It's too much. I'll
try something more simple.
No. Don't.
Suddenly I feel incompetent.
I want the portrait to hang in the office,
so I want it to look formal.
It's not formal. It's beautiful.
It's made in Paris.
It was stolen in Birmingham.
My mother stole it from a
house she was cleaning, 1901...
No, no. It's yours. It belongs on you.
A woman of substance and class.
Believe me, I've painted many women
who don't belong in
their expensive dresses.
There'll be no charge.
Your normal rate. I insist.
Mm. There's a first.
So, when shall we start?
I've already started.
Come to my studio this evening.
I'm busy this evening.
Polly, invite him.
Invite me to what?
Ada, this is a professional transaction.
Shelby Foundation dinner.
Polly is going alone.
- You're invited.
- Ada!
I'll come to your studio on Sunday.
And then we shall begin.
A woman of substance... and class.
Tommy?
This is the leader of
Birmingham City Council.
- Hello, Tommy. - All right,
Danny? - How's business?
All right. Holding up,
holding up. How are you?
You know each other?
I have interests in
steelworks in Cradley Heath.
Tommy helps me get my
products to the carmakers.
Congratulations, Mrs
Shelby, on your wedding.
Thank you. I'm surprised
you weren't invited.
Now, how would that look, eh?
Ah, now the party has really started.
Who are they?
Father John Hughes from St
Mary's Boys Reformatory.
And with him is Patrick Jarvis MP.
They are part of an organisation
called the Economic League.
Did you invite them, Grace?
The names sound familiar.
They were recommended by the Lord Mayor.
Oh. On your "best people
of the city" list, eh?
- Do you know them?
- I'll introduce you, Tommy.
No, it's all right, Danny.
I'll introduce myself.
We appear to have taken you by surprise.
I have adjusted.
Since the socialists
got into Downing Street,
we are all being followed.
We have to meet in places
where we'd meet anyway.
You should have stopped by Small Heath.
I could have given you a
more traditional welcome.
- They want to know about ammunition.
- And chains for the wheels.
When the White Guard make
their run for Tbilisi,
it'll be over rough terrain.
The chains are suitable
for snow or wet ground.
They're already stored on the vehicles.
There's a batch of weapons
set aside at the BSA
which is bound for the Turkish Army.
And how will you get it all
aboard the London train?
There will be a strike
that night across the city.
You will have to stop
the train twice. How?
Two drivers will join the
strike at different points.
Rather fun getting the communist unions
to help get weapons to the Whites.
Yes, rather fun, eh?
I'm thinking ahead, thinking
of every possibility,
remembering everything that is happening.
The Russians want to inspect the vehicles.
I'll take photographs.
Mm-mm.
The Duke has sent his niece. She's here.
Tomorrow, you will take her
to the factory and show her.
- No.
- Mm.
The union convenors are
watching the factories.
Not possible.
Anything is possible, Mr Shelby.
You will take her.
You will pick her up
from this hotel at ten.
Now, look.
A priest with an empty glass.
Let's get back to the party.
You know, gentlemen, there is hell...
and there is another place below hell.
I will remember everything...
and forget nothing.
Tommy...
This is Duchess Tatiana Petrovna.
Come on, Tommy, aren't you
impressed to meet a real duchess?
Well, I understand they charge a fee.
Mr Shelby, you are very direct.
Too direct.
But it's true. I attend these
things for the champagne.
And for the chance to be
treated like a duchess again.
You should have kissed my hand, Mr Shelby.
Forgive me.
She was asking about my sapphire.
I thought I'd recognised it.
She says it was Russian.
My husband has business in Russia.
Perhaps you know about it, Tatiana.
Well, tonight's not a
night for business, eh?
Is that why you were in the
concert hall for ten minutes?
I think people are ready
for dinner now, Grace.
No, no, I am not done
pumping people for money.
What is "pump for money"?
It's what I do every day.
You, er...? You know each other, do you?
You see, I am in charge of
compiling the list of guests,
but it's my husband who
seems to know all of them.
I hear he's very well connected.
And where does a duchess hear that?
In certain circles.
All right, enough, Ada.
Grace, there's a lady dowager
wants to speak to you
about coffee mornings.
She mentioned a £2,000 cash donation.
Tatiana, you and I will speak later.
I would like that.
Going to the factory
tomorrow is a mistake.
Nevertheless, we will go.
Also, my uncle ordered me to
seduce you, to give us an advantage.
But with a beautiful wife like
that, it will be difficult, no?
Tomorrow is a mistake.
Have you not heard? We have
no morals, we Russians.
And no fucking sense.
And no options.
I would fuck you for the cause.
What do you think of that?
I think you should not
drink vodka with champagne.
Does your wife know that
the sapphire she's wearing
has been cursed by a gypsy?
What did you say?
Nothing on earth would make me wear it.
Grace... Grace, come here.
Look, I can explain...
Ladies and gentlemen,
- For once, you shouldn't have to explain...
- The loyality toast: to His Majesty the King.
The King.
Dinner is served.
You look beautiful. You look beautiful.
- You need to take this off.
- Why?
Because you think it
would look better on her?
Grace, look at me. Fuck
these people. Fuck 'em.
I need you to be all right.
I need you, Grace.
I need you.
Damn you, Tommy Shelby.
- Shall we go inside?
- Yeah.
For Angel!
Get a fucking ambulance now!
It were awful.
I mean...
she were well within her rights.
I was asking meself,
"What would I do?"
But then she goes too
far. Why? What happens?
She gets up...
and she's got this look in her eye.
It...
No.
I'm not going to spoil it for you.
But I tell you, I haven't
been able to sleep since.