Now, remember last night
when you asked after Mama?
'Do they always have to do the
stock-taking at night, Arthur?'
I'm going to have a baby!
What business do you have
with the Russians, Tommy?
I've been to the factories
and the armoured vehicles
are in good condition...
"A factory break-in,"
that's what you said.
When you go home, be sure to check
under your little boy's pillow.
'We can reach anyone.
'Anywhere.'
'The priest is passing
information about the robbery
'to a Lloyd's underwriter
called Monkland.'
'Why would the priest pass
information to our enemies?'
'The complexities are your business.'
Now get me permission...
.. to kill the priest.
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
♪ And go across the tracks
♪ Where the viaduct
looms like a bird of doom
♪ As it shifts... and cracks
♪ Where secrets lie in the border fires
♪ In the humming wires
♪ Hey, man, you know
you're never coming back
♪ Past the square, past the bridge
Past the mills, past the stacks
♪ On a gathering storm
♪ Comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
♪ With a red right hand... ♪
Watch out, John Boy!
He's got a strong left...
Arthur, John, Finn!
Come here!
All right, what is it?
This letter...
says that Dad's dead.
He was in Boston in a bar
called the Mickey Free.
Two men waiting in an alley.
He was shot twice.
Who's Rosie Rice?
Some fucking whore.
She was a woman who took
the trouble to write to us.
She wanted us to know
that during the night...
.. while he was dying, he
asked for our forgiveness.
The only thing he ever taught us
was how to kill and cut a stag.
- Finn, John, you won't remember.
- I remember.
Cannock Chase, he...
.. parked up at a pub called the Griffin.
He got drunk and sang Silver
Dagger about 100 times.
Yeah, one weekend.
One weekend he was like that.
The stag is to remember him.
We eat.
And then we forget him.
No need to forgive him. Agreed?
John, I have to say this,
you can name your new
baby after him if you like.
No.
Arthur, I won't even ask.
So, his name dies.
It's been in the family for a
long time, but now it's gone.
Right. That's done. Fuck him!
Before we cook and eat,
there's some business.
Boys!
I wanted to say this out here,
cos I don't trust the maids in the house.
There's going to be a robbery.
I wish to confess...!
There's no confessional today.
The name's Shelby.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
Today's a Holy Day...
Look, I came.
I made myself.
Have you been drinking?
I couldn't sleep.
I tried to get enough down me
to get myself to sleep, but...
I just do these night vigils
by myself, thinking...
How long since your last confession?
I don't remember.
Mrs Shelby,
do you have something to confess?
Do you know, it's actually Gray.
My name is Elizabeth Gray.
Do you think God calls
me "Pol" or "Polly"?
This voice calls me Pol.
You hear a voice?
Yeah. Like Bernadette heard a voice.
And what does the voice say?
"Murderer."
It says this to you?
It's in my head. Who else
would it be talking to?
And are you... a murderer?
If you're talking about the law, then...
.. yes.
- I'll be out in a moment, Peter.
- Yes, Father.
Are you saying
you want to confess to a murder?
No.
My confession is that I feel no regret.
He was a policeman.
He was a bad man,
he hurt me.
I do the things I do, so that
my son doesn't have to do them.
It's just the wiping away of
the shit from under your feet.
The taking of any human
life is a mortal sin.
No.
The UNJUST taking of a
human life is a mortal sin.
Look it up. Look who did it.
Moses. Samson.
Lord Kitchener.
Are you saying you took
the life of a policeman?
Oh, Father...
.. now there is another life to be taken.
If there is a voice telling
you to take a life,
you must ignore it.
The voice doesn't tell
me. The voice asks me...
It says, "Pol...
"does this way of excusing
a murder still work
"if the life that is going to be taken...
".. is a consecrated man?"
He's a man of the cloth.
He's a holy man.
What kind of holy man?
It's not fair.
They're off drinking and
shooting rifles as we sit here
and listen to the mugs swearing,
spitting on the bloody floor
for us to fucking wipe up!
Without men here, they'll be
like dogs pissing up the wall.
I was just saying it's not fair.
The men are down there like lords...
Esme, just...
.. get on with it.
I'm bloody five months gone!
Forgot the combination.
24-8-22.
How do you know the
paper cash combination?
Tommy talks in his sleep.
Shut up, Esme.
He's changed the combination.
You've put it in wrong.
No, I haven't.
Your hands are shaking.
And, actually, I am sleeping
with Tommy, OK? Now and then.
Because he wants to. Now and
then. When the mood takes him.
Except we don't sleep. It's hard
to sleep bent over a desk, isn't it?
Happy?
None of it's fucking fair!
It's two hours' work. Bit of
grease on your cuffs, that's it.
Tommy, should I really be here for this?
I've cleared it with Polly,
Michael. There's no way around it.
We need you to know...
Who the fuck wants to buy
27 stolen armoured cars?
- A foolish man. - And how much
is this "foolish man" paying?
150,000 --
cash, diamonds and sapphires.
So, that's 20 for you, Charlie.
Isiah, there's five to you.
The rest we take to America to
invest in legally acquired property.
Assets bought with
untraceable income resold
and the profits reinvested
to make sure it's clean.
And after that, I
suppose, the old business
will be like that stag hanging
up over there, right, Tom?
Well, with profits on this
scale we'll be in a position
to stop the off-track business for good.
Keep the pubs, stop the protection.
Horses for the sport,
race days for the lark.
I made a promise to Charles's mother.
I also made a promise...
to Linda.
I know.
I can see it in your eyes, man.
Part of the reason for doing this last job
is so you'll be set up when
you do decide to walk away.
Look at you, Arthur.
A man who wants to live a clean life,
here you are signing up for
the biggest robbery of all.
I have to hand it to you,
Tom, you're a smart man...
Are you in or out, Charlie?
Curly?
- Shouldn't have killed the stag, Tommy.
- Oh, shut up.
- Bad luck...
- Shut up.
How do we know this foolish man
will hand over the diamonds
- when we're done?
- We don't.
But that's another business.
Right...
let's cook some meat.
Can't wait to part with
their money, stupid bastards.
It's all right, it's me!
Arthur said you'd be short-staffed today
- because they're on a works outing.
- Piss-up actually.
I brought sandwiches and
lemonade I made myself.
I'll make tea and empty ashtrays,
but I won't handle money or slips.
Arthur says what you do here
is illegal but not immoral.
Depends what time you get here, Linda.
And, anyway, I thought I would offer you
my physical and spiritual
support for your time of need.
Oh, Linda, if you want to be
a help, run up to the shops
and get me 20 Senior Service...
- Lizzie'll give you the change.
- No, I won't!
Actually, I'll use my own money, Polly.
And before you ladies decide
to find me so amusing,
- I have a message for you.
- Oh, God, no, Linda.
I've been to church already. Have you?
It's not a message from God, Polly.
It's from Jessie Eden.
Who's Jessie Eden?
She's the lady shop steward at
the Lucas Factory in Sparkhill.
"Lady shop steward"?
She's bringing all the female
workers in the spot-welding
and wire-cutting shops
out on strike for the day.
At protest at being made
to work on a Holy Day,
poor conditions, lack of holidays,
unsanitary lavatory provisions
and lower pay for female workers.
Apparently, all the female
factory workers in the city
are joining the protest in sympathy
and will walk out of their
places of work at 9am
to march on the Bull Ring.
All oppressed female workers welcome.
Them bastards down there shooting deer,
me five-months-gone sat
here like a pudding.
- Only one outside lavatory between
the lot of us. - Not consulted.
Bent over a fucking desk...
Ladies, I honestly believe
those who march on Good Friday
will have God on their side.
It's nine o'clock, ladies!
Open the fucking door!>
(Fuck it.)
I'm not in the mood today.
- Let's go to the Bull Ring.
- Hallelujah!
♪ Yeah, it's coming
♪ Out of this world
♪ Yeah, I'm lucky
♪ The lucky girl
♪ Hell... ain't... half... full... ♪
The foolish man?
Not quite.
♪ .. What a monster
♪ What a night
♪ What a lover
♪ What a fight... ♪
I'm sorry I came unannounced.
What do you want?
We need proof.
Proof of what?
You said the priest is a traitor.
We need to know how you know...
The proof is my word.
If he's involved, I'm
out. He needs to die.
Are you always so violent?
I killed a stag today
and it hurt me to do it.
But I treated it with respect
and the spare meat will go to poor people.
It will grieve me far less to put
a bullet in the priest's face.
Will you not sit when a duchess sits?
I'm told you're part of
the deal. Is that true?
- The royal court in Tbilisi actually
worked very efficiently. - Oh, I see.
And it worked like this, eh?
There were lots of
corridors and small rooms.
Attics. There were no rules there.
Deals were done. Brothers gave
sisters, aunts gave uncles,
fathers gave daughters and servants.
It was my aunt's idea that I came alone.
She's in charge of this.
When there are no rules,
women take charge.
They understand that the power they have
come through silent agreements.
I've promised I will do everything
I can to make this plan work.
My aunt assumed you would
want me as part of the deal.
I will tell her she's wrong.
Tommy, you ain't gonna believe this, man.
I've just phoned the Garrison,
right. I just spoke to Billy,
he says Polly, Esme and Lizzie...
have gone on fucking strike(!)
They what?
They've gone on fucking strike!
Half of Birmingham's out.
The female half, they're all
out, every single one of them.
Quakers put 'em up to it.
Who's watching the shop?
Polly's locked it up.
See, Good Friday is one of
our best days for takings.
All the men get drunk.
The races are all fixed.
It's like picking apples off
the lowest branches, eh, John?
Hmm, yes.
Then your business is very easy.
Was Linda with them?
You know... Billy said that Polly
jumped in the fucking Bull Ring,
she's pissed out of her mind,
started going on about revolution,
screaming to the rooftops.
Was Linda with them?
Yeah.
Then it was Linda's idea.
Linda's a smart woman.
John...
.. there's a Bentley on the drive outside.
I want you to go out and
put a nail in its tyre.
It's Good Friday so
there'll be no garages open.
The lady will have to spend the night.
Then I want you and the
boys to all go home.
You take Charlie and put him with
Arthur and Linda for the night.
They can use the practice.
- You want me to put a nail...?
- Yeah.
- You heard me.
- I hear you.
All right.
Nice to meet you.
Why do you need to put a nail in the tyre?
I want it so neither of
us can change our minds.
We came back early.
Polly didn't finish the count yesterday.
Hmm, so you thought you
could take a tenner.
I thought I'd finish the count.
Esme, I've told you, stay off
the snow till the baby's born.
It does no harm, passes the time...
Knocks down the walls!
Listen...
I know you miss the travelling.
But it's going to be all right.
It's like being a hen in a coop!
Remember that house in Lichfield?
Eh? The one the bailiff
used to throw you out of?
Throw you in the ditch.
I'm going to buy that fucking house.
Big as Tommy's with more land.
If you feel cooped up...
.. we'll take a wagon...
.. and camp out by the ditch.
How?
It's all going to change, Esme.
This is not your bedroom.
This is not where you
slept with your wife...
Do you ride horses?
No.
I would need to open my
legs in a public place
and that is not allowed.
Do you drink whiskey?
No.
It tastes like men.
I prefer wine.
Cars?
No.
So, diamonds are your only love, eh?
Sapphires.
They're just a currency.
Well, you know, if it was me
who had all them jewels...
.. I think I'd just sit with them...
.. look at them...
.. touch 'em.
Izabella does that sometimes.
Late at night.
I swear she puts one of the biggest
sapphires into her body for pleasure
and walks up the stairs to
breakfast with it still in place.
- And it stays in there all day? - Mm.
Wow.
What is your weakness?
Talking about duchesses with
sapphires inside of 'em...
I think already know your weakness.
I can get a fuck whenever I want, love.
Yes.
But I am a duchess.
And I'm under you like a horse.
I'm like a telegram.
"A telegram"? I don't think
your English is so good.
Or maybe you should listen more
carefully to what I have to say.
I have a message for you, Mr Shelby.
As a duchess,
I can show you what is
possible for a man like you.
A man in a house like this.
Right now, you hide inside it
like a boy who's broken
in through the window.
Why do we come to a bedroom for this?
In your own house?
It's a loaded fucking weapon.
We could fuck by the fire
with the maids standing
to attention and watching.
- What can they do?
- Give it here.
Nothing. There are no rules for you.
Give me the fucking gun.
You have maids here. You can
bring a maid into the room.
What can I do about that? Nothing.
- Give me the fucking gun, now.
- You have power.
Everyone does what you tell them to do.
Your brothers, your soldiers.
- No-one can stop you...
- Don't point a fucking weapon at me.
I can be an actress.
Who do you want me to be?
- Your dead wife?
- That's enough! Give me the fucking gun!
If you don't like something,
you say stop and it stops.
Hm?
But you are afraid of it.
You break the law, but
you obey the rules. Why?
Did you know that madness sets you free?
Otherwise, we're just
peasants obeying the law.
There is madness inside your
head, too. I can see that.
Let a duchess show you something.
I emptied the chamber
except for one bullet.
No!
- This is the game
we used to play. - No!
Watch.
Do not fucking do this...
No...
Look at me.
Don't do this.
NO!
Give me that fucking thing!
It brings you alive! You won't try it?
No, I do not want to try!
And I do not want your
mad fucking Russian brains
all over me fucking walls!
I survive each time by the will of God!
Get to fucking bed -- NOW!
I already called a maid.
(Fucking...!)
You see?
You are afraid.
Like a boy who's broken
in through the window.
I need to educate you in how
to run a house like this.
Yes! Come down.
Pour us a drink.
Mary, go back to bed, please.
You go back to bed, please.
This woman is drunk.
- That's all right, sir. Should
I pour whiskey? - Yes. - No.
He will have whiskey...
He will have whiskey,
and I will have wine!
- Mary, go back to bed.
- There. In an old house like this,
- the servants expect it.
- Stop fucking talking.
Mary, go back to bed. Do as I say.
If there is a call after midnight,
the maid who comes in is the
one in love with the master...
This is NOT FUCKING RUSSIA!
(Please, Mary... Go back to bed. Eh?)
I know your weakness, Tommy.
It's freedom.
Madness.
Killing.
I am the first one...
.. who understands you.
I found her perfume.
Put it on.
What proof do you have
that the priest is a spy?
I told you, I give you my word.
Then kill him.
From now on, you must do
everything that you want to do.
There'll be two of us for
breakfast this morning, Mary.
She's gone for a walk by the river.
The lady left, sir.
Left? How?
She took your car.
She what?!
She was in a terrible hurry.
She said she had your permission.
She told David to go to the garage
to get a new tyre for the Bentley.
She said you could use that.
And why the hell would
you listen to her, eh?
The way she said it, sir.
How was she, Tom?
Talkative, yeah.
- I was fucking working,
all right? - Yeah.
From what she said when she
was out of her fucking mind,
I'm pretty certain the treasury
is underneath the house.
What have you got?
Our Ada got this from the British
Library using her scholar's pass.
She talked about her
aunt coming up the stairs
to have her breakfast in
the morning which means
it has to be in the building somewhere.
Wine cellar. Septic.
Kitchen cellar.
- And a tunnel under the river.
- They don't trust a soul in this country.
So, my guess is they've turned one
of the cellars into a strong room.
- Did you find someone, Arthur?
- Moss got me this.
Stephan Radischevski.
He's a kid from Greet, lives
in Cheltenham. Dad's a Russian,
he has dreams of owning a
pub but he's got a record.
- Breaking and entering. And
he speaks Russian? - Yeah.
Their butler drinks in a
pub called the Mason's Arms.
Get to him, tell him who
we are, offer him some money
if he gives the kid a job in the house...
Wait!
Talk to the kid, offer him one of
the pubs we took off the Italians
if he works in the house for
four weeks, keeps his ears open.
All right?.. Come!
The Executive Committee of the
Union of Bookies and Allied Trades
will see you now, sir.
I heard you were giving speeches
off the back of a wagon, Pol.
I can't remember a fucking thing...
Well, Moss tells me you were threatening
to burn down the Town Hall.
Oh, Tommy, we were having a laugh.
Actually, the crowd around me
was bigger than the
crowd around Jessie Eden.
Who's Jessie Eden?
She's too soft.
You're not going to break
the capitalist system
talking about separate
lavatories for women.
Who's Jessie Eden?
She's our new best friend.
Shop steward at the Lucas Factory.
A woman shop steward, I've heard of her.
There's a leaflet here if you
want to take a look, Tommy.
So, a separate lavatory -- is
that it? Is that what you want?
I don't know what you want.
You have to tell me what it is
that you want and then I'll know.
Actually, we want to know about
the robbery you're planning.
Not the factory robbery.
The other one.
The one you're not
telling the women about.
John has a big mouth.
No... Arthur's got a big mouth.
Arthur told Linda,
Linda told me.
- Polly?
- Read the leaflet, Tommy.
Ladies, why don't I
talk to Tommy privately,
then I'll report back to you faithfully.
You're not just going to take payment
from the Russians, are you, Tommy?
- You're going to clean them
out, is that right? - Esme!
So, what happens after?
When they come for us?
When I'm about to give birth?
Get out,
- get back to work.
- Esme, come on.
- Keep us posted, won't
you, sister. - I will.
(Fucking hell!)
So, Arthur tells Linda everything, eh?
She's stolen his soul and taken it
to a better place -- the suburbs --
where men are honest with their wives.
We can trust Lizzie...
Yeah, but I can't trust Esme.
I can't trust the fucking
Russians to pay me or the army
and I can't trust my own brother
to keep his fucking mouth shut.
Did you make progress last night?
Yes.
John said the girl looks like
Edna Purviance from the pictures.
Be careful.
She's an excellent source of
information regarding the location
- of the merchandise.
- Here we go...
You know, there's a general lack of
discipline in this fucking company!
She stayed the night.
I'm working, Pol.
I am working... for the
good of the company.
You're grieving.
And when you grieve, you make bad choices.
I know.
I did it myself.
Look, no more marches.
No more fucking politics.
They can kill us.
All right? Joke or no joke.
- Did you tell Arthur about the priest?
- I only told you.
Thanks for the burden.
You were correct not
to talk over the phone.
What did she say?
She said there was going
to be a killing. A holy man.
And she was with the Shelbys, was she?
I suppose you have something
to say about yesterday.
No.
It's something else, actually.
I believe Arthur has told you about
some business we're planning, Linda.
Oh, there's always business, Thomas.
And Arthur believes, when
this business is done,
it'll all be over.
Arthur believes you, but I don't.
Linda, the people who have
hired us to rob the factory
are very bad people...
They'll not pay us as they have promised.
So, on the night of the
robbery, we will take what's ours
- from their treasury.
- And a bit more on top for luck?
If you're saying you're going
to stop Arthur, I need to know.
That'll be Arthur's decision.
And your plan is still to reform him, eh?
- To the absolute degree
of redemption! - Mm-hm.
Well, Arthur will walk away
from this with £30,000.
We made a deal. And afterwards...
you and Arthur can begin your new life.
Did you say 30,000?
Arthur said the estimated total
proceeds would be 150,000.
- Estimated, yes.
- A third of a 150 is 50.
- Why a third? - For three
brothers. Finn is not yet a man.
- There are expenses.
- 25,000, you said.
As of last night, the expenses
increased. We need to dig a hole.
Arthur agreed to a plan
with a figure of 25.
25 from 150 is 125.
A third of that is...
£41,000
Sugar?
Yes.
Thank you.
So, you've worked this all out, I see?
Only in my head.
I haven't written it down.
Linda, are you saying...
.. if it WERE £41,000...
I've already told you,
that'll be Arthur's decision.
But I don't imagine he'll
accept less than 41.
- May I smoke?
- No.
So, I imagine you have
some plans for your 41,000?
Yes.
California.
For the child's health.
Away from the smoke.
We want to run a general
store on an Indian mission.
The Americans invites Quakers to
do good work with the Indians.
We've already sent our
papers and have been accepted.
Arthur Shelby as a missionary...
No, Arthur will run the store.
- Mm! - I will teach in
the school next to it.
Arthur will swim in the ocean.
I will be on the beach with a towel.
The open air and the sun will get rid of
all the nonsense in his head from France.
That's some plan.
As you know yourself...
.. the arrival of a new
life concentrates the mind
on practical things.
Amen to that.
When is the child due?
September.
When is the robbery?
June.
Then the timing's perfect.
We'll book our passage
through the Panama Canal
the day after the 41,000's paid to Arthur.
Did we agree 41,000, Linda?
I heard nothing to the contrary.
Word association. Right now.
- Oh, God! I hate this game.
- It's Freud. It's terribly fashionable.
I'd rather you put on
that music that I hate.
- Are we going mad in
here, do you think? - Yes.
We shouldn't have drunk
red wine with the cake.
And I believe your vow never
sleep with another man
is a good one.
Good for the painting.
It's not a vow, it's just...
I think when men want
sex, they become hilarious.
Like a dog when you pick up a lead
and he knows he's going for a walk.
May I respectfully point out
that, so far, you haven't
even picked up the bloody lead.
There.
That's the look.
Imperious.
No man is good enough.
♪ Bad habits
♪ Sick puppy... ♪
♪ .. Thigh high
♪ Knee deep
♪ Bad habits, yeah
♪ Bad habits, ooh
♪ Bad habits, yeah!
♪ Deep trouble
♪ Pale faces
♪ All right
♪ Ow! ♪
You idiot, you nearly killed him!
I told you we needed him fully conscious.
We need to stop using
soldiers who've been in India,
- they hit too hard.
- Not fucking hard enough!
Hey, Mr Shelby! Hey!
I heard about your plan to kill a holy man
from a voice in a confession.
Can you hear us?
.. Grace...?
Shelby.
Why were you attempting
to kill Father Hughes?
Maybe we should wait until
he's fully conscious.
I have a dinner appointment.
Hey, Shelby...
wake up.
Eyes front.
Mr Shelby, were you trying
to kill me, were you?
For passing information...
Fuck. He knows.
Where am I?
You are among the Odd Fellows.
Please count from ten to one.
Ah, fuck you.
Whatever else you might have forgotten
about last night, remember this...
I am passing on information
to the Soviet Embassy
on the instruction of Section D.
It's part of a bigger picture.
You explain to the Russians
that you were mistaken about me
and you apologise to me in front of them.
A threat to your sister
was evidently not enough.
You do as we say or we will take your son.
Hear this.
We will take your son.
We can do it at any moment.
We have people in your life.
You will make your apology
to me tomorrow night...
.. and you will repair
the damage you've done.
Or you will never see your son again.
Sir, I don't understand...
I don't understand why, as
a former soldier yourself,
you have sacked all the
former soldiers on the staff.
It means there's only one
man left in the household.
Mary, I want it so that Charles
is never left on his own.
Understood?
Sir, I should call a doctor.
There will be some men
coming down from Birmingham.
And you put them up here in the
house, you put them in the front
- and back of the house and you feed them...
- Why are they needed, sir?
I bought a cursed sapphire
into this house, Mary.
And now I'm paying for it.
And I don't know what to expect.
But neither do my enemies.
Tell David to bring the car
round. I want to go to London.
- Sir...
- And... get me some tea, Mary.
Yes, sir.
- 'Hello?'
- Yes, Arthur...
'Tommy?'
They want the robbery to be sabotaged.
They don't give a fuck who gets hurt.
- 'Are you OK, Tommy?'
- It's a bigger picture now.
- 'What?' - Did John make a
list? - 'Speak clearer, Tom.'
- I said, "Did John make a list?"
- 'John Boy! John!'
Right...
'Gypsies and kin only. Yeah.'
Good.
'Tommy, can I ask you why?
'Tommy?'
No, Karl. I told you.
Go and play in there.
Hello?
Ada?
It's me, it's Tommy.
Ada, I need you to....
I need you to speak to
one of your comrades
and get me a meeting with someone
from the Soviet Embassy... Embassy...
Tonight. Your place.
10... 10pm.
It seems that Mr Shelby
was given bad information
by an informant who was also
in contact with the underwriter
who, as we know, is in
the pocket of the Soviets.
- Wine, Tatiana?
- A little.
Bad girl.
Sorry I'm late, I, um...
There was a body on the line.
Drink, Mr Shelby?
No, thank you.
It was drink that caused
half this trouble.
I have come here to apologise.
I have already explained
that you now realise
that your absurd allegation
against me was false.
Indeed.
And that your base nature made you rash.
And that now, once again,
our plan is back on track.
When a child in my care commits a sin...
.. first of all, he
confesses, as you just did.
And then, I instruct
him to perform penance
in a manner of my choosing.
As a child, you went to church?
Yes.
You remember the Act of Contrition?
Good. Do you remember the
words of the Act of Contrition?
Yes.
As your penance, I would
like you to recite it now...
.. in the presence of our associates.
Go away.
Ah...
Oh, my God, I am heartily
sorry for having...
Instead of "God", say my name.
Since it was me you offended
with your false allegation.
Father Hughes, I am heartily
sorry for having offended you...
.. because of your just punishment,
but most of all because they offend you.
Father Hughes, who is all good
and deserving of my love...
.. I firmly resolve to...
.. with the help of your
grace, to sin no more
and to avoid all near occasions of sin.
Very good.
Thank you.
Amen.
And now that we are a
united band once more,
perhaps we could order some food?
I'm sorry, I'm not feeling
well. I have to go. Goodnight.
Mr Shelby...
My God, Tommy...
- Are they here?
- Yeah.
- Do you have cocaine?
- No.
Tommy?
Tommy, this is the Special
Advisor to the Soviet Consul.
Members of the British establishment..
.. and exiled White Russians are
planning to rob armoured cars
from a factory in Birmingham.
We know about the robbery.
We have an informant...
Your informant is working for them.
They want you to know about the robbery.
Your informant is working
to their instruction.
- Why would they want us to know?
- They want you to...
They want you to stop the robbery.
They want you to commit a
violent act on British soil.
Tommy, do you want water?
A violent act on British...
.. to force the British Government
to break off diplomatic relations.
That's the game.
The robbery in Birmingham
was just the bait.
Why are you telling us this?
Because my family are the
ones who will be sacrificed...
.. if you decide to blow up the train.
The Consul wants to know who you are.
He's Tommy Shelby.
You can take his word.
- Ada...
- Tommy...
Stop... Stop...
Ada, stop...
OK. OK...
Drive me to a hospital, Ada.
If I'm not conscious when I get there,
tell them I have a fractured skull,
concussion and internal bleeding.
- I think I may have haemorrhaged.
- Tommy! - Ada, go on.
Be quick, cos I can't
see. I can't fucking see...
OK... OK...
Except for you, Dad...
I can see you.
♪ On a gathering storm
♪ Comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
♪ With a red right hand. ♪