There are some things
we need to discuss.
Our friend Jimmy McCavern has asked
for control of the racecourses
north of Wincanton.
I said yes.
- In return for what?
- No return.
None.
I'm glad I didn't shoot you.
It would have been a kindness.
Now get out.
This is a cheque guarantee.
Signed by Mosley.
On behalf of a man called Jimmy McCavern.
The consequence of good intentions.
My good intentions.
Push the button.
Unlock the door and come home to me.
I have a job for you.
I'll come for you...
...after midnight on Wednesday.
Barney Thomason...
...is gonna kill Oswald Mosley.
While he's on stage.
While I'm stood next to him.
And then I will take over
as leader of the party.
It's going to be
a busy few weeks, brother.
Mmm.
You prefer Irish to Scotch?
Yes, Mr Churchill.
Irish over Scotch.
Cigarettes over Havana cigars.
And your mother
was probably born in a tent.
Grandmother in a tent.
My mother on a narrow boat.
And always happy to give smart answers
to men born better than you.
A man needs to prove he is better than me
rather than show me his birth certificate.
You see, I don't have one,
so they mean very little to me.
You speak beautifully in the House.
- Thank you.
- And believe
not a word of what you are saying.
Conviction introduces emotion,
which is the enemy of oratory.
You read Greek literature.
I have trouble sleeping.
Is there a reason for your visit,
Mr Churchill?
You are forming an alliance
with a fascist.
So I made some enquiries
amongst the worst people in Whitehall,
and I found out that you are not
forming an alliance with him at all.
You are spying on him.
Yes.
Why?
The honest answer is...
...I'm no longer sure.
Do you dig your own garden, Mr Shelby?
I have a gardener.
In fact, I have three gardeners.
Three generations of men
with no ambition...
...who are happier than I will ever be.
Well, if you ask them, they will tell you
that there are certain species of weed
that no matter how much you tug at them,
poison them,
they continue to grow back.
In the end, the only solution
is to plough up the topsoil,
create a field of mud
and blow up and burn
the exposed taproots.
That's what you and I did in France.
But when I hear that man Mosley speak,
I see the green shoots of another war
growing up around his feet.
And you see exactly the same thing I do.
That's why you oppose him.
Yeah.
Your mystery solved.
What is your strategy?
I won't burden you with it.
You're going to break the law.
I need to sleep.
You said you don't sleep.
I said I have trouble sleeping.
As do I.
Mr Shelby...
...I have no doubt
that there was once a time in Flanders
when you were under the ground
and I was above it,
both working to the same end.
We are in the same exact situation
here in Westminster.
Do what you have to do, Mr Shelby.
And if you need anything, call me.
There are some times, some nights...
...when I don't see the point
of carrying on with any of it.
Oh.
That old dance routine.
I put out a cigar,
and an hour later I want another.
Sometimes, the bridge between hours
is as fragile as that.
But use it anyway.
A tent.
Then a boat.
Then a house.
Now a mansion.
That's something.
Isn't it?
Yeah, that is something.
By the way...
...was it you who killed
that Ulsterman intelligence officer?
I forget his name.
Major Campbell.
Yes, Campbell.
No.
It was my aunt.
I really must come up to Birmingham
some day
and spend an evening with your family.
They sound interesting.
Yes.
They'd like that.
I got to Harold French, refereeing Liverpool.
He just wants cash.
Tom the tatter,
reffing Sheffield Wednesday, wants cash
and a beating
for a bloke who's screwing his wife.
The clap doctor said go easy
on the whiskey, yeah?
Finn.
You don't knock?
No, Finn.
I don't knock.
Right.
Hello, Billy.
How are you, mate?
Good, Mr Shelby.
Yeah, you look good.
That's a nice suit.
Thank you, Mr Shelby.
He earned that suit.
We made more on the matches
than we did on the races last Saturday.
He's a good man.
Yeah, I know that. Mm.
You're coming up in the world, I like it.
How's the missus, hmm?
The old trouble and strife,
as the cockneys like to call it.
She moved out.
Oh, that's a shame.
Mind if I join you, eh?
Mind if I join the party?
Look at this, having some fun. Hmm?
You're a good man, Billy.
You're a good man, eh?
You could sing like a bird in a cage.
And what did we do, eh?
We opened that cage,
and the real man flies out,
reveals himself.
The truth is young, Billy boy.
Yeah.
Here, look.
What have we got here? Oh, look.
Look at that, Billy boy, eh?
Then there's some snow there, look.
Oh, there's more.
Look, snowflakes, Billy.
Now, I know you like that, hmm?
Well, I do too.
So, I'll tell you what, why don't we have
a little line together?
Eh? Why don't we do
a little bit of snow together?
Oh, spilt it all down you an' all.
It's the eyes. Sorry, mate.
Hey, what can I do?
I'm messy, aren't I, Billy?
I do apologise.
And you. Hmm?
Look at you.
Sitting here with your mate, eh?
Your best mate.
Well, while you're sitting here,
talking about our business,
drinking whiskey, smoking and sniffing...
- Hmm?
- And working.
You remember, you tell this man
about our family business...
...and it's his life you're risking.
Cos people talk, Finn.
We... we only ever talk about football
and women, Mr Shelby.
Football and women,
we only ever... we only ever talk
about football and women.
- Oh, do you?
- Yeah.
It's...
Hmm.
Yeah.
Come on.
Family meeting, let's go.
You're not eating right.
You're not getting the natural things
in you, boy, that's what it is, always.
You bearing up, Arthur?
Bearing up for what?
Bearing up to being free, Pol.
Another glass, eh?
Another glass of so what.
Are you all right, Charlie?
Mad bastard Barney kicked me
in the shin when I woke him up.
Where is the mad bastard?
He's tied to a lamp-post outside
with three Lee boys,
shitting themselves.
A drink.
First of all,
an apology from Lizzie -
she can't be here.
Charles has a violin concert.
Also, a welcome to Mr Aberama Gold.
He and Polly are to be married
in three weeks, with my blessing.
From now on, Aberama will be welcome
at our meetings.
First item of business, a bereavement.
Colonel Ben Younger,
who may perhaps have become
a member of this family,
was taken from us,
four days ago,
by dark forces.
We've made some investigations,
and we think we know
who planted the bomb.
In the meantime,
our thoughts are with Ada
and the baby inside of her,
who may one day sit at these meetings,
but hopefully
under happier circumstances.
Let's drink to happier circumstances.
Yeah.
To Ada.
- To Ada.
- Ada.
Item number two.
An announcement,
regarding Michael.
Before you go on, Tommy,
there's something I'd like to say
to the whole family directly,
regarding finances
and the future of this company.
According to your own estimations,
this new venture of the delivery
and shipment of opium
will bring into the company
around £2 million per year.
Therefore,
due to the amounts involved,
I think this company
should be restructured.
Michael, I think this can wait
till outside the family meeting.
Restructured in what way?
Because of the amounts
of money involved,
shipment and dispatch will become
the primary source of income
to the company.
It's simple mathematics.
And with the help of my wife,
I will organise an expansion into America,
where the narcotics business
is just beginning to grow.
So I have very good contacts in Detroit,
New York, Boston,
who I've already spoken to about this.
And Gina has family who are
very experienced in this kind of business.
According to the conversations
I've had with them,
with a regular supply
of pure opium from China,
within a short space of time,
the American narcotics business
will bring in $20 million per annum.
Enough money for you to all enjoy
an easing of the burden you all now feel.
See, I know that the scars
and the wounds,
they're on the inside,
not on the outside.
And as a member of the new generation,
I'm able to take that great burden
off your weary shoulders.
A new decade is coming.
There'll be new opportunities
in new territories.
More money than we've ever had before.
Tommy,
you can still do the good work
that deep down you want to do.
Mum, you can get married
and live in that big house.
Arthur, you can be the man
that Linda wants you to be.
Fuck Linda.
Finn.
You've proved yourself.
You're part of the new generation.
You could come to New York with me.
Here is my proposal.
A full restructuring of the company.
I will be managing director.
And you can be nonexecutive chairman.
But under an assumed name,
to protect your reputation.
I've found the name of a dead man.
You will be registered as Mr Jones.
You will each receive a percentage
of the profits as an annuity,
and you will no longer have to engage
in any of the associated activities.
Take a look at the future, Tommy.
At least read it with an open mind.
It's cold in here, Michael.
Tommy, the Americans want to deal with me.
Item number three.
Tell him the truth.
Go on.
He can take it.
Tell me the truth, Michael.
The Americans don't want to deal with
an old-fashioned backstreet razor gang.
Those days are done.
Tommy. He's bitten through
the fucking rope.
They've got him cornered,
but they need help.
Go and get him!
Fuck the Americans.
I'm doing this for you, Tommy.
It's time.
And you know it.
Tommy, Mum's leaving...
...John's dead, Arthur needs help,
Ada's man was killed in your own back yard
because you fucked up.
Go on, Tom. Go on, cut me.
Like the good old days.
Or...
...see this for what it is.
A natural succession...
...that someday must happen.
I gave you an opportunity, Michael.
You betrayed me.
Don't be here when I get back.
You.
You can tell your family...
Let me guess.
Don't fuck with the Peaky Blinders.
Right?
Well...
...guess we're gonna be forced
to take the second option.
They're not fucking voices!
Whoa! Whoa! Calm down.
- Put the gun down.
- They're not fucking voices!
Barney!
Put down the gun. At ease.
Finn.
At ease, soldier. At ease.
Look at me. You're on our side.
You're at home.
Yeah? Yeah.
Here. Take this, Barney. Jeremiah?
Yeah.
Take him to Charlie's yard
before he falls over.
The devil will now be an angel.
Isiah, Curly, you go with him.
Come, brother.
Let me give you the good news.
Jesus loves you.
So, where the fuck is he?
All right, boys.
A subsidiary meeting of the generation
that actually do the work.
Right.
Let's have the good stuff.
None of that shit ponces' drink.
Here we go, look.
All right, so item number three.
An introduction.
Except now you've already met the man
I was going to introduce.
In France, he was a comrade.
What the fuck is he now, Tom?
He's a man we can use, Johnny.
For what? Put him in a ring with a bear
and take bets on the outcome?
I tell you, I wouldn't put much money
on the fucking bear.
Aberama,
that man is a trained Royal Marine sniper.
Furthermore, he has a criminal profile
which will make his actions explicable
to the police.
What actions?
A killing.
And since when
did you worry about the police?
Barney Thomason...
...is gonna kill an MP.
Possibly the future prime minister
of Great Britain.
What the fuck, Tom?
After the killing,
there will be an investigation
by Special Branch
and Intelligence forces.
There will be a lot of powerful people
as angry as fucking hornets.
We need there to be no connection to us.
Barney Thomason is registered
as criminally insane.
He broke out. He's an old soldier.
He has known grievances.
No-one will question
that the assassination was carried out
by a single gunman acting alone.
And you'd sacrifice an old comrade?
If they catch him,
they won't hang him
on grounds of insanity,
just send him back to where I found him.
He'll have had a very eventful holiday
that he'll probably believe
never really happened.
And where will this killing take place?
There you go.
He'll be on stage.
With lots...
...of witnesses.
During the rally,
there will be
an anti-fascist demonstration.
Amidst the confusion,
a shot will be fired.
And we're organising this demonstration?
Yeah.
Where will you be, Tom?
I'll be down on one knee,
cradling his head...
...while the life drains from him.
Then I'll make a speech...
...saying how the cause he died for
must continue...
...continue safe in my hands.
Holy fuck.
Tommy...
...does your ambition have no limits?
Jimmy McCavern will be running security
at this event.
He'll probably be in the wings.
You can take his life
whichever manner you choose.
What do you want us to do, Tom?
You and Arthur
and a couple of the Lee boys,
you'll be in charge
of getting Barney into position.
He'll be up in the lighting gantry.
We'll need chains and a twitch, Tom.
No. I will medicate him.
So he's gonna be cross-eyed
when he takes the shot?
In France, he never missed...
...no matter what they gave him.
He'll have had plenty of target practice.
Before he takes the shot,
Arthur here will give him some cocaine
to sharpen him up.
So just...
You're gonna be up on the stage
while this criminally insane gunman
filled with cocaine
takes aim at a man
just a yard away from you?
Welcome to the family, Aberama.
What about me, Thomas?
The man with the broken fucking leg.
After the killing,
every copper in Birmingham
will be sent to Bingley Hall.
Use that opportunity
to get that boat full of opium
up to Stourbridge locks.
There, you'll be met
by some Chinese gentlemen.
They will have two suitcases full of cash.
£250,000.
Every man in this room
will receive $30,000 in cash,
in recognition of extra services.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, Tom!
Anyone who wants to leave,
leave now.
Anyone who is tired
of this old-fashioned,
backstreet fucking razor gang can leave.
Anyone who's tired can fucking stop.
Good.
Charlie, go to the yard and light a fire.
Johnny, bring the van round.
What's the fire for, Tom?
There is an item number four.
It's time.
Jeez, Mr Shelby.
If I'd have known, I'd have come in early
and served you drinks, huh?
Here, Micky.
Sit down there.
So I'll have a drink, will I?
Here you go, have a drink.
A few days ago, I went to London, Micky.
To collect some cargo.
I was met by the Titanic boys.
They knew I was coming.
Yeah. When, where, what time.
They even knew...
...the cargo I was picking up.
Jesus.
Four days ago, Micky...
...a soldier was killed...
...outside my office...
...by a bomb.
Yeah, erm, the papers said that was IRA.
No, it wasn't the IRA, Micky.
No. It weren't the IRA.
I spoke to the girls who work
at the Digbeth telephone exchange.
They're friends of mine.
I asked them what calls were made
around the time of the explosion.
They told me that...
...30 minutes before the explosion
a call was made to a man in Sparkhill
who has connections
to the Ulster Volunteer Force.
He now offers his services for cash.
Paddy Rose.
Yeah, me and my brother,
we spoke to Paddy.
At length.
He told us it was him
that planted the bomb.
Yeah, we spoke to him.
We killed him, Micky.
Paddy Rose is dead.
We weighed him down,
we sunk him...
...to the bottom of the Grand Union Canal.
The girls at the exchange
gave me the number
of the man that called, Micky,
before the explosion.
That was your number.
Micky, it was you who called him.
You tipped him off.
You were told to call him
if a black man of a certain description
ever came to Small Heath.
We know you've... you've been giving
the Titanic boys information as well.
We know that.
Yeah.
You've been working behind the bar, hmm?
Seeing what goes on, listening,
taking notes,
and selling your stories
to the highest bidder. Hmm?
Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Oh, Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
I'm sorry, Mr Shelby.
Don't look at Tommy.
The ceiling would be cheaper, brother.
Micky!
Fucking hell, Arthur.
Eh?
Shaking like the hand of a normal man.
What about item five, Tom?
Huh?
There is an item five, right, Tommy?
I'm fucking sinking here, man.
I'm fucking sinking, Tom.
You... you... you said there's an item five.
Say it, Tommy.
Item five could start now, Tommy.
It could start this year, a new decade.
M-M-Michael...
Michael could be right -
we could go, Tommy.
We could go.
We could fucking leave this place.
We could leave it to the kids.
Michael's... He might be right.
- He might be fucking right.
- Arthur!
There is no item number five!
Go and check
that Polly is still on our side.
I have to go to Margate.
All right, Tom.
All right, brother!
Oh, God. Jesus Christ.
You out there, Tommy?
Yeah. I'm here.
I was just having some oil rubbed
into the bits that really hurt, mate.
What do you think of that view, eh?
It's Margate. What can you do?
I'll tell you something, Tommy, right?
I sit all day every day in that chair,
on that balcony,
contemplating the fact, right,
that life is so much easier to deal with
when you are dead!
- Hello, Alfie.
- Yeah.
Did you... did you look
through the binoculars?
Yeah.
I watch ships. No two are the same.
That is how God sees us both, in his eyes.
God, eh?
Yeah, sort of. I mean, you know.
Someone's responsible
for all this fucking mess.
Now...
How soon did you know
that I was not dead?
You wrote me a letter, Alfie.
Did I?
Yeah, you asked about your dog.
They gave me a lot of drugs at first.
Hmm. Yeah, all right.
I was lying out there,
and the tide had come in,
and it woke me up.
I remember looking around
and thinking, you know...
..."Fuck...
"...if this is hell...
"...it looks a lot like Margate."
Maybe that's just what hell looks like,
eh?
No, no, not according
to this holy book right here, yeah?
It gives a very, very vivid description.
You and I are both fucked, mate.
Do you read the papers, Alfie?
No, don't be silly.
But you've heard.
What, fascism, yeah?
Three,
two,
one,
bang.
No?
Fine.
Good Lord, your fucking condition
has got worse, mate.
Mine, on the other hand,
I've been living the dream.
Sometimes, I will shoot
at the side of a ship.
And sometimes I'll sit here,
I may shoot at the old seagull.
Alfie...
...I'm gonna shoot Oswald Mosley.
Right, well...
...I hope you do a better job on him
than the one you done on me, yeah?
I mean, what... what were you thinking?
Was your mind somewhere else, Tommy?
Yes, it was, actually.
Yeah, all right.
Oh, look.
A ship.
Why do you want to shoot him?
I need to organise a riot, Alfie.
Right.
And I hear you still have some... standing
in the Jewish community.
Let me be clear, right?
Since my resurrection,
I am considered to be a god, all right?
In the Holy Land,
someone has made an image of me
out of rock embedded in the sand,
so I'm told,
and I am planning to make
a pilgrimage to stand in my own shadow.
Are you going to shoot him
because this man is evil?
I need men who can fight.
Mosley uses men from Glasgow.
So if the men causing the trouble
are Jewish it will be... explicable.
Since when did you need explanations,
Tommy?
Since I entered politics.
Oh, that's right, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And how has that been for you, Tom?
Gangs, wars, truces...
Nothing I didn't already know.
So you think if you kill him, you...
you will kill the message, yeah?
I will kill the man,
then I will kill the message.
How much you paying?
I thought you might do it for the cause,
Alfie.
Fuck off.
Each man will get £20.
You'll get £5,000.
You know, as a god, Tommy, right,
I am now able to just rise above
those kinds of insults, mate.
Ten?
How is my dog?
Your dog is fine.
In that case, ten should be enough.
Where do you want the men?
Birmingham.
No. No.
20 will not be enough
for my lads to step inside
that fucking shit-hole.
It will have to be 25 at least.
25 it is.
You can take your dog back, then, eh?
No, it's better for him
to think that I am still dead.
As it is also with the police.
Right.
So you're still at it, eh, Tommy?
Hmm.
You ain't got no Margate to go to.
No.
And I have no interest
in shooting seagulls.
Oh, you have
in shooting Cabinet ministers?
Yeah.
And their paid informants.
Mm.
I was on a lot of drugs at first, right,
due to the pain, you know,
on account of it...
Well, you know,
being shot in the face by... some cunt.
I won't bore you with the details
of the trivia.
Nonetheless, I had a recurring dream.
I saw you in a field, right?
With a big black horse.
And you said goodbye, and then... bang.
All right, then. Well, what now?
I will continue...
...till I find a man that I can't defeat.
Hmm.
Arthur asked whose side I was on.
There will be a war.
And one of you will die.
But which one, I cannot tell.
Hmm.
He's gonna do it anyway.
- Yeah.
- You should know,
if Aberama takes his side,
I will kill him.
What about me?
I'll do what I have to do, Pol.
Kill... and kill.
It's the only way to make people listen.
Soon you'll have a stage to stand on.
Millions of people will listen to you.
And you will run the country
like you run this family.
It appears to be what people want.
But not me.
Not any more.
My resignation.
If it's Barney you're worried about,
he's sleeping.
But I can't sleep
because my fucking leg is cracked.
Tell me how my mother went, Charlie.
You know.
She drowned.
I know it wasn't by accident.
Tell me the truth, Charlie.
The truth, Tommy, yeah?
The fucking truth.
Fuck's sake.
She just stepped into the canal.
Your dad was no use.
It was me trying to stop her,
for three days.
In the end, she did it anyway.
- Did she say why?
- Nothing that made sense.
Tell me the things
that didn't make sense.
She said it were the Gypsies
made the nails for Jesus's cross.
That's why we're cursed and restless.
Yeah, go on.
You have to move around
or the guilt catches up with you.
I said,
"Well, why not go on the road for a bit?"
She went to Worcester.
She came back with a white pony.
That one she gave to you.
You used to ride it round, remember?
Well, she seemed happy for a bit,
watching you ride it.
And then she was gone.
None of it made any sense.
Afterwards, whenever I looked
at that white pony, I saw her.
You see, I was in love with her, Tom.
No-one knew but me.
Broke my fucking heart
to pull her from the cut.
You know, your grandfather,
he went the same way.
Suicide.
Sometimes, these things run in the family.
Fuck family, Tom.
You just have to get on with it.
You're a Gypsy.
You have to move around,
or it all catches up with you.
Didn't need all them tablets,
just needed another fucking war, eh?
Perish Judah.
Shalom, my friends. Shalom.
Shalom. Shalom.
In you go, buddy.
Show these fascist bastards no mercy,
brothers.
The Jew and the Gypsy united.
Look, I have got to go, yeah?
I have to go.
Go where?
They're shooting a fascist tonight.
You're gonna do what?
Ssh.
Mosley's in town.
Really?
Look, go into town,
get some drink and some girl
and listen to the radio.
We will not stand by and let this scum
have free rein in our city!
Fascism must not be allowed to voice
its creed of hatred.
Out the fucking way!
We have a right to protest!
Get back!
Anybody heckles you,
beat the fuck out of them.
We have a right to protest!
We got another one. Let's go. Get, get!
Calm yourself down.
It's not against the law to protest.
Out of the way.
Out of the way. Out of the way.
Let her go.
- I don't need the help of a fascist.
- Yes, you do.
At Steelhouse Lane,
they'll do whatever they want to you.
Let her go.
I'm Tommy Shelby, and I'm ordering you
to let her fucking go. Go on.
Fuck you.
Jessie, you can do more damage
from the inside.
Do you understand?
You can do more damage from the inside.
Come on.
Out of the way. Out of the way.
Shut up!
Here, look.
There, look.
I'll join you.
Play high.
Now, you know what you're doing,
don't you?
Yeah. Tommy checks his pocket watch,
I count ten,
then I blow the other bloke's head off.
- Yeah.
There, that's for after.
Thank you. Thank you.
- See you later, Arthur.
- Oh, soldier.
Soldier, you do that, you run like fuck.
- Don't stop.
- Run like fuck.
- Yeah.
In here.
Here, for your face.
At least I have only one face.
What did you mean,
"damage from the inside"?
I have a strategy.
You always have a strategy.
But it's dangerous,
and it can't be shared
without sharing the danger.
You think I'm afraid?
No, but it's only gonna put you
in more danger.
Jessie, before the speeches start,
just go home.
There's gonna be lots of arrests.
You have a mark against your name.
Why?
What's going to happen?
I'm gonna do a good thing.
Whenever I do a good thing,
innocent people get hurt.
So go home.
After this evening, we can meet,
discuss strategy.
That beast out there, he's just a beast.
It's like a horse.
It's the rider that decides
what direction it takes.
And who will be the rider?
Just go home.
Full?
To the fucking brim.
Trouble?
So far, a few communists.
Bullers helped our boys clear them away.
Well, a few hecklers are a good thing.
We can illustrate
how we deal with opposition.
There is a rumour a gang of Jews
are coming up from Digbeth.
No sign of them yet.
Well, let them come.
Welcome them appropriately.
There are a few Peaky boys around.
They are your allies.
There'll be no rifts between us.
Keep your powder dry.
Mr McCavern?
Perish Judah.
No joke, Mr McCavern.
You turn the radio on
and turn up the volume.
I want to listen to the news.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr Oswald Mosley.
Perish Judah!
Perish Judah! Perish Judah!
Welcome, men and women
of Birmingham.
Thank you for coming here
on this cold, dark night,
in spite of the obstruction
and provocation of our enemies.
Our enemies deal in bricks and stones
and bottles. We deal in reasoned
principle, argument and fact.
Among those enemies,
we can number Mr Winston Churchill,
who last night condemned me
in the House as a threat to democracy.
Them's that gone are the lucky ones.
But then Mr Churchill has never been
a friend of the common people.
Faced with the alternative
of saying goodbye to the gold standard,
and therefore to his own employment,
he characteristically selected the latter,
but of course...
...not all attending tonight
will be convinced of our cause.
Some will have come here tonight
to find out for themselves
what we stand for.
Whenever you're ready, Tom.
So here are our guiding principles.
Every citizen shall serve the state.
Not the banks, not factions,
not the Jews!
Perish Judah! Perish Judah!
The barriers of class will be abolished
and a greater Britain will be born
of the national socialist
and fascist creed.
It is useless to hide from ourselves
the fact that ever since 1918,
when our heroes returned from France,
our empire has shown all the signs
of disintegration,
and our people are threatened
by gathering disaster.
Get out of my way!
Out of the way!
Go. Go.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two apple crumble...
I think it's about time
we got off the stage, old man,
until this thing is sorted.
The coppers are here, Arthur.
You gotta get away from the body.
What the fuck are you doing here?
What happened?
I don't know what happened.
I don't know what fucking happened.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
Wait. Fuck, it's us.
Aberama's dead, he's gone.
He's gone, and they came for me, too.
What the fuck is she doing here?
Arthur, they got to Barney.
They knew everything.
They knew fucking everything.
Who? Who knew, Tom?
Johnny, get this woman out of here.
- I want to know.
- Yeah.
Get her out of here. Get her out!
Doesn't make sense.
Doesn't make fucking sense.
Who? Who? Who?
The Chinese, the Italians...
...the Branch, Intelligence,
McCavern, Mosley...
Mosley knew nothing!
He knew nothing!
Who?!
Jesus fucking Christ.
You're fucking frightening me, Tom.
Doesn't make sense.
Who?
Who? Who?
Who? You know, Tom, you must know.
You're fucking scaring me,
what are you doing?
Talk to me.
Maybe I've found him, Arthur,
the man I can't defeat.
- Mosley?
- I don't know.
I don't fucking know.
Doesn't make sense.
Let's...
Let's go inside.
We'll work it out...
- ...have a drink.
- I need to walk.
The work is all done, Tommy.
It's all done.
We can walk away from all of this.
It's so easy.
It's so soft.
Such a small change.