I'll tell you where to find
the guns. What shall I do?
Find out where the guns are hidden.
Raise a hand if you want to strike!
Freddie Thorne is at the very
top of my list.
Well, cross him off.
I'll make him part of our deal.
To hell with them.
The more they try to stop us,
the madder I'll be.
Times like these, a communist
in the family is bad for business.
You have to leave the city.
You are also at war with
the Lees, Mr Kimber, am I right?
Together we can beat them.
Divided, maybe not.
God, he's getting big now.
Do you still love me even though
I am fat? No. Not at all?
You married me,
now you're stuck with me.
So, how was London?
It's crackling with revolution.
The Poplar docks are on strike.
Did our friends give us
what we asked for?
How much? £200.
Who did you meet?
An attache from the Russian embassy.
In a Chinese restaurant.
Our revolution is international.
And it grows by the day.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Jeremiah, Jeremiah...
What do you see?
Your sister
and Freddie got back this morning.
I tried following them...
but Freddie's so good
at getting away.
He's like a fish.
Right, well, keep fishing, eh?
Last bets now!
Don't spend your rent money, Charlie!
That's your starters, gentlemen.
No more bets.
I was here on time. Finished.
I've had a tip-off, I need this bet.
The race has started. Please.
No!
Fine.
Get rid of him.
We said, "no", now get out! All
right. All right, I'm off. I'm off.
Night, lads. See you tomorrow.
It's a good day.
Where's John?
John is in the Garrison.
He says he wants
a meeting about a family matter.
After he's said his piece
he'll come back and take his place
with Scudboat.
Scudboat? John will be here in ten
minutes. All right. Five.
Wait.
Good boy.
John?
Put that down! Put that down!
This is for Cheltenham.
We're just taking back what's ours.
There's money here.
Search everywhere.
All right, John.
There's only one right... No.
There's only one man
guarding the house.
What's troubling you?
Polly, you know what it's
been like since Martha died.
God takes the best first.
The truth is, my kids have been
running bloody rings around me.
Running barefoot with the dogs
until all hours.
Pol, give him ten bob, some shoes.
Is that it, John?
Tommy, we'd be better doing
this without you.
Now, what's your point?
What the kids need is a mother.
So, that's why I'm getting married.
Does this poor girl
know you're going to marry her
or are you going to spring it
on her all of a sudden?
I've already proposed
and she said "yes".
I think there's a shell
about to land and go bang.
It's, er... It's Lizzie Stark.
John, Lizzie Stark's a strong woman
and I am sure she provides a fine
service for her customers.
I WON'T hear the word.
Understand? Do not use that word.
What word is that, John?
You know what word that is.
Everybody bloody knows...
Everybody can go to hell...
"Whore"? That word? Or "prostitute"?
How about that one?
Right, I want it known...
if anyone calls her a "whore" again,
I will push the barrel
of my revolver
down their throats and blow the word
back down into their hearts.
Men and their cocks
never cease to amaze me.
John, Lizzie Stark never did
a day's work vertical.
She's changed. All right.
People change.
Like wi-wi-with religion.
Oh, Lizzie Stark
has got religion, eh?
No, no, she doesn't
have religion. But...
Well, she loves me.
Now, listen, Tommy.
I won't do it without your blessing.
But of all the people in the
world...
..I want you to see it...
..as brave.
It's brave all right.
"Brave" is going
where no man has gone before.
With Lizzy Stark, John, that is
REALLY not what you'll be doing.
Listen, Tommy.
Welcome her to the family.
As someone who's had a hard life.
All right? Because, I need someone.
All right, the kids need someone.
Tommy! We've been done over!
What?
Jesus Christ.
What the bloody hell happened here?
The Lees. All of them.
Cousins, nephews,
even the bastards.
They've taken anything they can
lay their hands on.
Four cash boxes.
They left these....
Wire cutters.
Why would they leave wire cutters?
Nobody move.
I think our friends
are playing the game.
What game?
Aunt Pol. Don't touch anything.
Erasmus Lee was in France.
Shit.
When we gave up
ground to the Germans...
..we'd leave behind booby traps,
set up with wires.
And we'd leave wire cutters
as part of the joke.
Somewhere in here there's
a hand grenade... Holy Jesus.
..attached to a wire.
Don't move any chairs
or open any doors.
Go easy, John boy. Easy.
Boys, no. It's not in here.
If it was in here,
it would have blown by now.
It was my name on that bullet
Erasmus sent.
He's set a trap all right.
But he's set it up just for me.
Finn?
Finn, stay exactly where you are.
I was pretending I was you.
Which door did you open to
come in, Finn?
I didn't. I climbed in.
I want you to climb out exactly
the same way you climbed in, OK?
No, no... Finn!
Clear!
What happened? Are you all right?
It could have killed us.
That's why you should never pretend
to be me.
OK? OK?
I got you ten minutes with her.
You can at least say thank you.
It's easier to get to see
the Pope these days.
Put your hand on the Bible.
I don't believe.
Anyway, I didn't come here to lie.
This war is cutting us all up.
You're all children.
I say enough.
Your boys tried to kill me -
it didn't work.
No wonder you won't touch a Bible.
I have ambitions.
You want to play a switch.
I need your boys.
For what?
Kimber's not the brains.
There's a gadze who runs the races.
I'm collecting smart people.
But I need strong men too.
Now your boys should know this,
we now get the winner in one
of every three races
before the race even starts.
No need for chalkers or rafflers.
I'm talking certainties.
You come in here boasting
you're going to do someone down
and in the same breath you ask me
to trust you.
On my mother's side, we are kin.
Ada, can you do my back?
Ada?
I know what was in the envelope.
I looked. Money.
And that bloke we met in London who
you said was a Frenchman.
He was Russian.
I'm not an idiot, Freddie.
How is it you take all the risks
and Stanly Chapman gets the money?
It's money for the cause.
You're blind.
I would be if your brothers had
anything to do with it.
This isn't about them.
This is about you.
And me. And... this.
You're a dreamer, Freddie.
You give money away
while we rot in here...
and you talk about revolution.
I need to know.
Who are you loyal to, Freddie?
I said, "Who are you loyal to?"
Did you have something to
do with this?
I asked an acquaintance
for an address.
She said she would only give it to
me anonymously.
She was afraid of the
consequences.
Whose address is it? Tommy, I'd like
to suggest a strategy.
Your message said you have
an address for me.
Anonymous tip off.
The address of Stanly Chapman.
You promised me Freddie Thorne.
This is instead of Freddie Thorne.
No deal.
Inspector, Stanly Chapman is
a bigger fish than Freddie Thorne.
He is currently holding
£200 in cash.
Given to the Communist party
by the Russian Government.
That's right,
Chapman has snow on his boots
and all you'll need is a shovel.
If he talks, you'll have proof.
You might even get that medal.
Now...
..before I give you the address...
..I want your word...
..that you will let Freddie Thorne
and my sister leave the city.
Very well. You have my word.
I'd say our little truce
is proving productive
for both of us, Inspector.
I get the information...
and protection and you...
Well...
..you get Bolsheviks.
But on a more pressing matter...
I'm afraid that Mr Churchill
is becoming impatient.
And I fear that...
..if you don't give back those stolen
weapons soon...
..I will be replaced.
That would be the finish of me,
that's for sure.
When my business with Kimber is done
the guns will be returned.
That was the deal.
Then I am in your hands. Completely.
You hold all the cards.
But I hope to God that my dismissal
doesn't come before your decision
to hand back those guns.
I say this for your sake,
because...
..if I were to be fired
and it were your fault...
..I would do things that would
shame the devil.
My fury is a thing to behold.
On my last day in power, for example,
I would see to it that you
and your scum brothers
have your heads stoved in
with mallets and spades.
And your sister too.
That baby inside her
would be of no consequence to me.
The only one to be spared...
..would be your little brother Finn.
He would however
be lifted as a juvenile
and dumped into that part of the
adult prison...
..where men have most appetite for
boys like him.
That would be a dark day indeed,
Mr Shelby.
If my dismissal comes
before YOUR decision.
Do you understand?
And know this...
..the clock is ticking.
Stanly, it's the police.
Stanly, get here!
You're under arrest, mate!
You bastards!
Look what we found.
It seems Stanly Chapman really
does have snow on his boots.
Mr Chapman...
..you're fucked.
He still refuses to say where
it came from.
I'm sure, with a little persuasion,
he'll tell us everything he knows.
Including the whereabouts
of Freddie Thorne.
Sir?
Your face is a picture.
I thought you had done a deal.
Oh, is that is what you thought.
Well, you gave your word.
My word?
Do people still talk about
such things this idiotic century?
My word to who?
To a Peaky Blinder?
Now, go and interrogate Mr Chapman
until he tells us where we can find
Freddie Thorne and his wife.
The source of the money
is of secondary importance.
You think my campaign against
Shelby has become personal?
Correct.
"Spot-on", as they say
in London society.
Now, go and interrogate Mr Chapman
and do not make the mistake
of being too gentle.
Right, sir.
Today's her birthday.
I know you never miss it.
Then I'm lucky you're not a copper.
What do you want?
I came to warn you.
They've lifted Stanly Chapman.
How do you know?
Police don't spill that information.
I know cos it was me and Tommy who
tipped them off. Tommy did a deal.
In return for safe passage
for you and Ada he's given them
Stanly and the money.
Money? What money?
Who told you about the money?
Who do you think?
Yeah, it was Ada's idea.
That's how desperate she is
to get out of that rat-hole
you're keeping her in.
She doesn't mind if you knew she just
didn't want to be here when you found out.
Sometimes the women have to
take over. Like in the war.
Who the hell do you think
you are, you fucking Shelbys.
Don't swear over
your mother's grave.
You play your tune, you expect
the whole world to dance to it.
You don't have time for this,
Freddie.
You did a deal for me?
Don't flatter yourself. For Ada.
And you think this copper
will keep his word.
If he does, you're safe. If he
doesn't, Chapman will give you up,
you'll still have to leave town.
Same result.
So neat! So leave.
Except there's one thing
that you got wrong.
Stanly won't be able to give up my
address because he doesn't know it.
That's how it works.
None of us know each other's
addresses.
So, you've wasted your fucking time.
They'll keep beating him and beating
him for information he doesn't have.
All you've done is sign the death
warrant of a good man.
So, you won't leave.
No! I won't fucking leave!
If you want me out of Birmingham
it'll have to be in a wooden box.
You lay a hand on our Ada,
I'll put you in a wooden box myself.
You raised a stubborn one there,
Irene.
You told me to carry on.
I wanted to stop.
He had some kind of seizure.
So, you killed him?
Did he give you an address?
What's the matter with you?
He fell down some stairs.
This is not bloody Belfast!
Not yet, but if men like him get
their way, it soon will be.
So, find some stairs, throw him
down, and call the coroner.
Use Grayson.
If he has any awkward questions
ask about the welfare
of his mistress in Saltley.
That'll shut him up.
To think I used to live in
a shit-hole like this.
Bloody animals.
But the Shelbys really
are doing an excellent job for us.
We haven't lost a single penny
to rafflers or chalkers
in eight race meetings.
The bookies are purring.
So, we throw the dog a bone.
I think so.
Mr Kimber. Mr Roberts.
Come and have a look around.
After you.
Come on, Fred.
You can feed half of Birmingham
with what you have had for lunch.
Get back to work.
We heard the Lees
had turned you over.
You shouldn't listen to gossip,
Mr Kimber. This way.
Business is good.
Especially since now you know
which horse is going to win
before you set the odds.
Your information is very much appreciated.
Right, well, where are they?
John, Lovelock, Scudboat, in here.
This is my team.
They will take up their pitch
at your convenience, Mr Kimber.
John is the book.
Scudboat is the bag man.
And, of course,
we bring our own protection.
Warwick, next Saturday. At least
fifty yards from the beer tent.
Gentlemen...
And lady.
I have in my hand a legal
betting licence.
Issued by the board of control.
The Shelby family has its
first legal racetrack pitch.
We're a business, Pol.
Congratulations. There you go.
Congratulations.
30, 40, 50...
These cigarettes have
a strange smell, Arthur.
They smell like rotting water.
And look.
Rats have gotten some of them.
They're stolen, are they not?
Don't ask. They smell
because you keep them on a boat.
What do you care? Now, can you come
and check my adding up, please?
You know, you should make a new
start with this place.
Do it properly. These cigarettes
are not fit to sell.
Smells like Gallipoli.
You should find
a new place to store them.
It has to be far away from coppers.
But not rats?
All the wharves have rats, Grace.
What's wrong with a dry warehouse?
Tommy's orders.
What orders? Always keep contraband
near to petrol boat moorings.
Don't boats get searched?
We moor them at junctions...
so there's more than one way out.
No locks within a mile
so we can move that stuff fast.
Your brother doesn't obey the law,
but he has rules.
A precise man, your brother.
Is my adding up right?
It is now.
One.
Two.
Three... and four.
And we'll search them one by one.
Please, Lord,
let that which I seek be found here.
Not so much as a bullet, sir.
Just more cigarettes and whisky.
Arthur tells me
you've been asking questions...
..about how we run our business.
And how we get our booze
and where we keep it.
I am just trying to help.
Let's you and me go for a walk.
Where to? Come on.
Why here?
You're a good Catholic girl,
aren't you?
Yes. Well, then you know it's here
people come to confess.
After you.
Well, here it is, Grace.
I confess.
I need someone.
Kimber has an adviser
by the name of Roberts.
He talks well.
Keeps the accounts.
Runs the legal side of the business.
And you need a Roberts.
Arthur tells me you have ideas.
I'm not an accountant. Nor a lawyer.
No.
No, but you have something I need.
Class.
I need someone who looks right
at the big meetings.
Epsom, Ascot...
Is a job interview? Arthur says
you're good with numbers.
Well, that's relative.
He is quite poor.
You keep the books in order.
They were chaotic.
But you're a liar.
No Catholic girl would
enter a church
and forget to make
the sign of the cross.
You are very perceptive.
First, you lied about that pub
you used worked in.
Now I find out you're a Protestant.
Do you care?
No.
I lied to fit in.
You pull a pint like someone
who's thinking about it.
This is not an interview,
it is an interrogation. Sit down.
Look, Grace...
You washed up in a place you don't
belong for whatever reason.
My good fortune. And perhaps mine.
You know that most of what I do
is illegal. I'm not blind.
And yet, you'd still be
willing to work for me?
Are you offering me the job?
Then I accept.
There's something else you
should know.
A very important detail
about my reasons for employing you.
You disappoint me.
Do you resign?
No.
My appetite for the work
has only increased.
Tomorrow I'll show you around.
Lizzie. Hello, Lizzie.
That bag looks heavy, jump in.
Kids' teas.
You like kids?
Yeah. Good,
cos John's got four of them.
It's all right. I'm not going to try
to talk you out of it.
I just want to talk.
You're not against us?
John is his own man.
And you are your own woman.
Now, Lizzie...
since I came back from France,
I've come to you on many occasions.
Tommy, you didn't tell him?
No, I didn't tell him.
Just like you didn't tell him.
Now, why didn't you tell him, Lizzie?
Why didn't you tell him
that you'd been serving his brother
for the past two years?
Because the past is the past.
I don't want to lose him.
He's a good man.
That was the answer I was hoping
you'd give - the past is the past.
You see our John says
you've changed. And I believe him.
And that's good. Change is good.
These are new times I'm told.
So I wish you both
every happiness.
And I want you to see that
as my wedding gift to you.
And our farewell
to pleasures gone by.
You mean...
..one last time?
One last time. You and me.
It's eight bloody pounds.
So, where shall we go?
Tommy, shall we go to my lodging?
So, the past is not the past.
You can keep the money, Lizzie.
Just get out of the car.
Tommy, please... Get out of the car.
I love him, Tommy. Really.
Really.
John will make his own decision.
But he will have the facts.
Your brother is ten times
the man you are!
Of that I have no doubt.
He is obviously not stupid.
All we found was stolen tobacco
and whisky. Which you left in place.
Of course.
I would never endanger you.
You are doing well, Grace.
I've been working on Arthur -
he's easier. Than Thomas. Yes.
Less intelligent.
Yes.
Is that a word you would
use about Thomas? It's your word.
He has promoted me.
He wants me to be his book-keeper
and secretary.
A cut-throat gangster
with a secretary.
The pretensions of these hoodlums
are quite breathtaking!
Are they not?
Yes. Quite breathtaking.
He has obviously fallen quite
heavily for you.
I thought you would be pleased.
I just hope you remember
who you are dealing with here.
A man who cuts off ears
and cuts out tongues.
I know what he is, sir.
The difficulty with undercover work,
Grace, is to remember what you are.
I come here with good news
and I get this.
Grace!
Tommy. I need a favour.
I want to borrow the car.
I want to take Lizzie for a ride
in the country with the kids.
We're going to celebrate getting
the licence. Not a problem, John.
I'll need the keys.
Look, John, you're my brother...
There's something
I have to tell you.
Yesterday on the front
seat of that car,
I offered Lizzie some money.
And, John, she said "yes".
Now, that's a fact.
You do with it what want.
Take the keys.
Take Lizzie to the country.
Marry her if you want.
But you have to know...
..she said "yes".
Get another glass.
Can you make a toast?
I'm Irish,
I can make a million toasts.
May you be in heaven
a full half hour
before the devil
knows you're dead.
What are we celebrating?
Contract of employment.
Book-keeper.
Shelby Brothers Limited.
I don't like that word, "Limited".
To be respectable, you have to be
"Limited". That's what worries me.
I had the phone put in.
It's in the back.
If we knew someone else who
had a phone, we could call them.
And since we are celebrating...
..I had this delivered from
Rackham's Department Store.
Will you open it?
No.
Save it for a special occasion.
Right, your first job for the
company.
I want you to get that to my sister.
I don't see her?
No-one does. She is hiding from me.
I am told she goes to
a bathhouse on Montague Street
on woman-only days.
She goes in disguise,
so I need to get someone inside.
What am I delivering?
It's an invitation to a family
occasion. I want her there.
So, tell her there will be a truce.
Am I delivering bait for a trap?
If you check that contract
I think you'll find it doesn't say
anything about asking questions.
Just give her the invitation.
And put that in the cupboard
until I say.
What the hell, John? I couldn't
get it lit. Couldn't even do that.
Why would you want to be
smoking that for? Same reason as you.
Pain in the head.
I spoke to Lizzie.
I told her what you told me.
She said, "Your brother Tommy
is a dirty liar."
But then I spoke to her sister
and her cousin.
Bought them a couple drinks.
"Just a few of regulars," they said.
"That's all."
"To keep the wolf from the door,
"she still sees
a couple of regulars."
You must think I'm an idiot.
I think you're the first
Shelby in history...
to have a legal licence for anything.
What would our granddad say, eh?
He'd be turning in his grave.
"Honest bloody money? Eh?"
"In this house? Here?"
You always used to do voices
when we were kids.
We're not kids now, John.
But we still have to look
out for each other, right?
Yeah.
Come on. Go home. Get some sleep.
We've got a big day tomorrow.
We have?
Tomorrow, we finish the war with
the Lees for once and for all.
Since when? Since just now.
Ten o'clock tomorrow.
Be ready for anything.
Out you get, boys.
Ready, boys?
John, ready? Yeah. Yeah I'm fine.
Have a drink.
What? What are you all staring
at me for? What?
Good. Let's go.
What?
Tommy, what you playing at?
We're in shotgun range.
John...
..before we go into battle, there's
something you are going to need.
What are you bloody doing, Tommy?
Smile, John, it's a wedding.
Whose bloody wedding? Now if we'd
told you, you wouldn't have come.
There's a girl from the Lee family
who's going a bit wild.
And she needs marrying her off.
Fuck!
John!
You have no bloody right, Tommy!
Listen to me. Listen to me.
A girl who needs a husband.
A man who needs a wife.
Tommy, I'm not bloody marrying
some fucking mushroom picker!
Shh, John boy, come on. Listen.
I have already betrothed you.
So if you back out now there's going
to be one fucking mighty war
breaking out here that's going to
make the Somme...
It's going to make the Somme
look like a fucking tea party.
But if you marry her,
our family and the Lee family
will be united for ever.
And this war will be over.
It's up to you John.
War...?
..or peace?
Let go of me.
Right... You should see
the size of her dowry.
Her what?
Her dad is giving you a car.
Will he do?
He'll do.
Here she is.
She'd better be under 50.
Come here. Go on.
We're here today to join in
matrimony
this man and this woman...
You look well.
..and harmony and togetherness.
Which is sanctioned and honoured by
the presence and the power
of these two families around us.
Do you John Michael Shelby
take Esme Martha Lee
to be your beautiful wife?
You got my invitation?
Grace said there's a truce.
Family day.
Your husband couldn't make it?
He's not speaking to me.
And when he does he calls me
a fucking Shelby
even though I'm a Thorne now.
Thorn in my side, that's for sure.
..to have and hold...
My God, Tommy.
You admire him, don't you?
There remains one more
part of the ceremony.
It's the mingling of the two bloods.
Where the two families
become the one... family.
I now pronounce you man and wife!
Come on, John, kiss the bride
will you?
# Oh, I slept all night
# In a tinker's arms
# He put his arms around me
# Oh, there was folks
and there was dance
# And Paddy here's lost his banjo
# I wouldn't part from my sweetheart
# Tuppence, ha'penny or farthing
# Another load of wagon men
# Spare a little thought
for the wind men. #
And again.
Come on, spin me round again.
You should tell Ada to slow down.
You think she'll listen to me?
I tried to stop her
but she's been drinking.
Been stuck in that little basement
for weeks. What do we expect?
She's going off like a firecracker.
Oh, Christ, Tommy, please...
Enough now. Come on. Enough.
All right, Ada, come on, have a
rest, sit down. Come and look, Esme.
Come and look at the family
you've joined. Come and look
at the man who runs it.
Chooses his brother's wives for them.
He hunts his own sister down like a rat
and he tries to kill his own
brother-in-law!
Ada, that's enough. And now he won't
even let me have a fucking dance!
Not even at a fucking wedding!
Sit her down.
Calm down, Ada. Ada, calm down.
Holy shit!
Water. Right.
Not now, Ada. Bloody hell,
you do pick your times!
Slow her up. Nice and easy.
Story of your fucking life, Arthur.
Right, we are here.
Come on.
Nice car, John. How's she run?
Yeah, beautiful. Really smooth.
Your sister in there giving birth,
you're talking about the bloody car.
Not much us men can do now, Pol.
Except go get drunk.
Right, come on.
There's one man should be here.
You are right, Pol,
Freddie should be here.
Is that a heartbeat
I hear inside that chest?
The truce lasts till sunrise.
On my oath.
Tell Freddie it's safe.
Ada! Right, boys,
let's wet this baby's head.
Keep going. That's right. Push.
I think it might be
the wrong way round.
I tended three sisters.
Yeah, I think you're right.
We should move her forward.
Come on, Ada.
Right, come on.
It's not long to go now, darling.
Push. Two, three.
Two beautiful women.
I should go. I should go.
It's my wedding night.
No, you sit down.
You don't want to be among the women
when there's a baby coming.
Have another.
So, do you think her husband will
take the same advice and stay away?
Nah. Freddie will be there.
Nothing will keep him away.
Tommy's said it's
all right for him to be there.
Isn't that right, Tommy?
That's right. I'm all heart tonight.
You know what, John boy?
I think it's that lovely barmaid,
that pretty barmaid
that's just walked out
that's made our brother go all soft.
Drinks to that.
Ada!
Come on, open up.
There you go, love.
Oh, he's beautiful.
It's a boy, Freddie.
It's a beautiful baby boy.
There you go.
Welcome to the world, Son.
Welcome.
Open up! Police!
Freddie?
You can't come in here,
there's a baby just been born.
Freddie?
Don't hurt him. Freddie!
You are hurting him,
leave him alone.
You're taking me away from my baby?
Ada! Freddie!
You want me to open
that champagne now?
It's a boy.
Pol? Polly?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Polly! Polly!
But the police came
and took his father away!
Don't you DARE look at me like that!
You liar!
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.