Previously on Prison Break:
I'm through.
See you on the other side.
It can't be done.
We're not getting out of here.
There's only one person who
can really stop this execution.
Would you talk to your father...
for me?
I'm the last person in the
world that my father listens to.
The governor has reviewed your case.
He's not granting clemency.
Let's proceed.
I came in here a man, give me the
strength to walk out of here a man.
Doctor... you can leave now.
It's him.
Mi... Michael...
What's he saying?
Michael... turn around...
It's him.
What do you think he's saying?
Michael... turn around.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
What's happening?
What the hell's
going on in there?
I can't tell you how sorry I am that
you've had to go through all this.
Lincoln...
- What happened in there?
- Judge Kessler called.
- The execution's been delayed.
- What do you mean, "delayed"?
Apparently, some new
evidence has come to light.
- What evidence?
- I don't understand.
How long do we have:
one day, two days?
That's all the information I
have at the moment. I'm sorry.
I'll give you a minute.
You okay?
I need to know how
much time we have.
I'll go and see the
judge and find out.
You're with Michael;
you'll be okay.
- Did you see him?
- Who?
The guy in the viewing room.
No.
It was Dad.
It was him; I know it was.
- That's not possible, Linc.
- It is possible. I saw him.
I don't know how
you could have.
There were only a half a
dozen people in that room--
me, Veronica,
and a bunch of reporters.
- He wasn't there.
- You don't know that.
I do.
I would have recognized him.
You don't remember what he looks like.
I do.
This is a man who took off,
what, 30 years ago?
Why would he come back now,
at the very last minute?
I don't know.
Why is he still alive?
It appears that some information was
anonymously slipped to the judge.
Anonymously?
It was your fat little friend, Hale.
If you had taken care of him sooner--
- It wasn't Hale.
- How do you know that?
If Hale had given
Veronica Donovan
anything that could have
gotten a stay of execution,
I think she would have brought it up
when she made her argument in court.
It didn't come from him.
Well, who else on
your end knows?
Who else on your end knows?
Why all the finger-pointing at us?
Are you sure that the leak didn't
come from your end? From The Company?
Hey, we are all on the
same team, remember?
Absolutely.
Just find the leak...
and plug it.
Thank you, ma'am.
One more thing--
the next time you're
in my office,
I expect you to stand when
you're addressing me.
Absolutely.
All I can tell is... I was working
late in chambers, I left at 11:00,
and there it was,
right under my door.
One is Terrence Steadman's
autopsy report.
In it, his appendix is noted
as present and unremarkable.
The other paper is an operative report
from when Mr. Steadman was 12 years old.
The procedure was
an appendectomy.
- That's impossible. Let me see this.
- I want the conviction overturned
and Lincoln Burrows immediately
released from custody.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, not so fast.
These records haven't
even been certified.
The hospital can tell you.
The hospital does not keep records
going back that far. I checked.
So, as far as we know,
these documents could be a hoax
from some anti-death
penalty advocate,
or, dare I say it,
defense counsel.
Oh, please.
You're preposterous.
Let's just all take a
deep breath here, okay?
I don't know what
these papers mean,
and, for that reason,
I'd like to err on the side of caution.
I'm going to delay the
execution for two weeks.
That should give us more than
enough time to exhume the body.
Exhume the body.
Your Honor, all due respect--
that is a drastic measure.
It's also the only way
we're going to know
if that body in the ground
is really Terrence Steadman.
So that's not Steadman
that was buried?
We don't know.
If it isn't, Lincoln's free.
If  it is,
we're back where we started.
Take care of yourself, Michael.
So that body--
what if it's him?
Well, I'm not going
to sit around hoping.
What does that mean?
That means we get back to work.
God, I was hoping
you would say that.
They're digging
up the body, huh?
To  be honest, I've never been in
a situation like this before.
If nothing else,
you can be glad that
you've got people who'll go to extreme
lengths to get you out of here.
No kidding.
Oh.
Warden... um...
at the execution,
there was a man in
the viewing room.
I was just wondering if you or anyone
in the prison had spoken to him.
Well... according
to this, uh...
those present were your brother,
his attorney, and three reporters--
two women and a man.
The man-- who was he?
Um... he was from the Headline Press.
William Prall.
You know him?
No.
Hmm. Guard.
Hold it steady, please.
What exactly are you
looking for in all that ink?
A new way out of here.
You know all those
plans by now?
No.
Memorizing it would be like
memorizing the phone book.
Yeah, but why not
just tat up Route 66?
Contingencies.
Contingencies?!
You saying you
found another way?
- Maybe.
- What do you mean, "maybe"?
There's always been another way,
but it's suicide.
Man, it's so cold,
my hands are stinging.
You know what they say about
weather in the Midwest--
if you don't like it,
wait an hour.
We're still going out
through the infirmary,
and we're still going to do
it from the guards' room.
It's just the in-between that's
going to have to change.
Wait a minute.
Why are you changing plan, man?
We're already through that
room beneath the infirmary.
That's all we gotta do is to get
through that pipe and we're home free.
There's a reason they replaced
it with a 12-inch pipe, Darwin.
People can't get through it.
The only way we're getting into
that infirmary is from beneath.
We're going to have
to find another way.
The Psych Ward?
It's the only building that shares a
subsurface line with the infirmary.
You telling me
to get to the infirmary,
we gotta go through the whack shack?
Unless you got a better idea.
And there's a subsurface line that runs
from the guards' room to the Psych Ward.
Sort of.
Oh... what do,
what do you mean "sort of"?
We can go into that hole
in the guards' room.
About 40 yards up Route 66, there's
a grate that'll get us halfway there.
What about the rest of the way?
We  gotta do it above ground.
Oh, so just a bunch of cons
taking a stroll in the middle of
the night for all the guards to see?
Yep.
You're right. It is suicide.
This grate that you're talking about,
it's hidden, right, partner?
- The C.O.s can't see it.
- Not exactly.
- Well, where is it?
- You're standing on it.
Hell no!
When we come up on
that ground there,
that tower there...
that tower behind me
is going to see us.
We'll be like ducks on a shooting range.
You feel me?
Hurry it up, cons.
You plan sucks, Snowflake.
I gotta go back into
the walls tonight.
Why?
I gotta get over to Psych Ward,
familiarize myself with
the pipes beneath,
make sure we can get through.
I don't know, Michael.
C-Note's got a point.
We come up in the middle of that yard,
we're sitting ducks.
I know.
Hmm... I might have an idea.
My family and I are more than
dismayed by Judge Kessler's decision
to allow the exhumation
of my brother.
This stunt by Lincoln Burrows'
defense counsel is an affront
and an insult to the
memory of my brother,
a good man who tried to make
positive change in this country.
This is being done in the name
of trying to release a
convicted killer from prison.
Steadman asked for a "green burial",
no embalming,
biodegradable coffin,
it's very environmentally aware.
Or smart if you don't want
the body to be identified.
We haven't hung in months,
and now you want a favor.
You know I love you, cous,
but that's a big ask.
I gotta say no.
- You can't say no.
- Whatever.
If my mom, or worse your mom,
knows I did anything in here to
get you in trouble, forget it.
I'm in prison, pendejo.
How much trouble can I get into?
A lot. Geez.
You owe me.
Like hell I do.
It's your turn, not mine.
Miss Mangene's broken window.
The Terrado sisters.
Your brother's
"lost" El Camino.
Oh, the church
collection basket.
The donkey.
Yo.
We took an oath, bro.
Don't make me break it.
Come on, Linc,
we want to catch batting practice.
Let's hurry. Take my hand.
Great seats, huh?
See #11 over there?
Keep your eye on him.
Watch him closely.
You got it?
Where is it?
Oh, he's cool.
You get caught with this,
they'll kill you.
Hey, I'm going to need
this back by morning.
They'll know if something
like that is missing.
And cous...
...now you owe me.
Hey, you dropped something.
Does that say "Iraq"?
Thanks.
Let's look busy.
What the hell?
Oh, sh...
Damn, bro, what did you do?
It's the cement we dug up.
My God, you cons are slower than
a spelling bee full of stutterers.
Y'all  think you can slow-walk this job,
play grab-ass in here?
Drag it out for months?
Get to work.
You got it, boss.
How about it, eight ball?
Get to work.
Oh, you know, boss,
my leg just fell asleep.
You disobeying me, convict?
The man said get to work.
What the hell is your problem,
old head?!
My problem is young con punks who
don't know how things work around here.
Construction is a sweet gig.
You want to clean toilets,
be my guest.
- Otherwise, grab a hammer.
- All right.
Still got some piss and vinegar
in those old veins, huh, Charles?
I like it.
Close one, huh?
Whoa.
Oh, man.
What are we gonna do with this?
It was Ole Miss,
right, Ole Miss?
Nah, it was a
Midwestern school.
- Iowa.
- No, not Iowa. Hold on a second.
Hey, Bagwell.
Hey, do you know what school
Art Schlichter played for?
Not really sure there, boss.
I really ain't much of a football guy,
boss. Too much violence.
Come on,
you know the guy I'm talking about.
Art Schlichter, the quarterback,
got nailed for gambling.
No, doesn't really ring a bell.
Bet if I asked you what his ass
looked like, you'd remember.
Maybe someone in the
brain trust knows.
Stolte, come on, man,
let's grab some lunch.
Hold on, I just want to figure this out.
It's driving me crazy.
Ohio State!
That's right. He was a Buckeye.
You're not completely worthless,
after all.
How's  your stomach?
Any more vomiting?
Just nauseous.
Must be the nerves.
That's understandable,
considering.
I can give you
something for it.
No, it's fine.
All right.
You, uh, you let me know if
there's anything you need.
Can I ask you a question, Doc?
Yeah. What?
With all that went down yesterday--
head pounding, heart racing--
could that cause me to see
something that wasn't there?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, anxiety attacks are often
accompanied by flashes of light,
black spots...
No, no, no.
I saw someone in the viewing room.
There were people there.
This person couldn't
have been there.
Yeah, Lincoln, you've heard of
post-traumatic stress disorder, right?
Yeah.
I'm going to call you
a prime candidate.
I don't think a lot of people have
been through what you just did.
So if you,
if you thought you saw someone,
it's possible that it was your
subconscious giving you what you wanted.
Whoever it was that
you wanted to be there with you
in that moment to comfort you.
Who was it you thought you saw?
Thanks, Doc. Thank you.
Sure thing.
Seen a lot of
rackets in my time,
but if you're doing what I think
you're doing with those postcards,
yours definitely
takes the cake.
Yeah, how about saving the small talk,
old head,
'cause you and I ain't
got nothing in common.
What do you do?
Write them here and then
send them to a pal in Iraq
and have him mail
them your wife's way?
Why don't you just
shut your word hole
'cause you don't know
nothing about my racket.
A con pretending he ain't
in the hole to his family.
I seen that once or twice,
but Iraq?
Yeah, you the one to talk.
Dede-- is that your
wife or your kid?
Now, you listen.
I don't even want you to say her
name in this prison. You feel me?
A daughter.
Definitely a daughter.
Ah, what'd you know?
'Cause I got one myself.
You know...
after you break
outside these walls,
that's  the first place they're
gonna look for you-- family.
Now, why is it you think
that I'm that dumb that I
would go directly there?
'Cause that's exactly the
first place I'm gonna go.
Turns out maybe we got
something in common after all.
See #11 over there?
Keep your eye on him.
Watch him closely.
Mid-level reliever at best.
But he's always working at it.
That's why he's your old man's
favorite player. Work ethic.
William Prall.
You know him?
The pipe system beneath
the Psych Ward is...
well, it's complex.
Be real easy to get lost.
- How complex can it be?
- Very.
When they build this place in 1858,
the pipes were lead.
A century later,
they discovered lead was a health risk
so they went to copper.
They never removed the lead pipes.
Cost too much.
There's thousands of yards of
the stuff still down there.
Then a few years ago,
they switched to industrial plastic.
Again it was cheaper just to
lay it over the old stuff.
If I make a wrong turn down there
tonight, I won't make it back by count.
You won't make the
wrong turn, right?
I don't believe my eyes.
One of the blues actually
coming into Psych Ward.
Yeah, I gotta hit the head, and
I didn't want to walk all
the way back to A-Wing.
Mind if I use your facilities?
Yeah, be my guest.
I don't know why you guys are
so scared of the whack shack.
I mean,
between the killers and the crazies,
I'll take the crazies.
Because a crazy
steps out of line,
all I gotta do is shoot him
with 40cc's of "shut your trap"
and it's beddy-bye.
So, uh,
which way is the bathroom?
Down the hall,
through the door, make a right.
Hey, blue.
What you doing down there?
Hey. Uh...
I was just looking
for the bathroom.
Down here?
Yeah. You said down the hall,
through the door and to the left.
No, I said through the
door and make a right.
Ah. My bad.
Have a good night.
Blue! Hold up.
Don't you still
gotta take a leak?
Yeah. Which way was that again?
With decomposition
this extensive,
the most accurate identification
tool is dental records.
We made an imprint of
the deceased's teeth
and compared them to the dental
records of Terrence Steadman.
And?
They were a perfect match.
Thank you, Doctor.
That can't be
Terrence Steadman.
If you like, you can bring in a
forensic examiner of your own choosing
to examine the body,
but I can tell you now,
they'll come to the same
conclusion that I have.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
I hope you're proud of this.
You've gotten your
pound of flesh.
Are you done now?
Or would you like to hurt
my family some more?
Come on.
Hey, Mack, you there?
- Yeah.
- What's your 20?
Uh, I got to stop by
maintenance real quick.
I'll be up in a minute.
You okay?
I'm burned.
Oh, god
All right,
help me take this off.
No, it's, like,
burned into your skin.
Take it off.
Are you kidding me?
I can't, it's melted into your skin.
If the guards catch me wearing this,
I'm a dead man.
- Bro, it's just...
- Do it.
Please do it.
Ready?
One...
two...
three!
Michael, it's Sara.
How are you feeling?
Groggy.
It's the anesthesia.
Why did I have anesthesia?
We had to perform a procedure.
So you got so sick of
Scofield's smart mouth
that you decided to deep fry him,
is that it?
I didn't do anything to him,
I swear.
Let's review.
A locked cell.
Two inmates.
One gets branded like
a South Dakota steer.
You think we should call
Matlock in on this one?
Who's Matlock?
Fernando, you're only going to make
things more difficult if you
don't cooperate.
I told you I didn't burn him.
- I found him like that.
- You found him like that?
He was acting kind of weird when
we lined up for final count.
He was sweating, you know?
But he's not a big talker anyway,
so I didn't think much of it.
Middle of the night,
I get up, you know,
to shake hands with the president,
and there he is,
face down on the floor.
My... ass.
Ask him yourself when
the doc's done with him.
I didn't touch him.
Painkillers.
How bad is it?
Uh, I'd take the pills.
Do I get to see it?
No, the bandage stays on for now.
Take your pills.
Your cell mate do this to you?
Sucre? No.
Who did?
This is the part where
I don't answer you.
All right.
I'll have you sent back to your cell.
All yours.
Hey, Katie, it's me.
Listen, uh, can you come up
to my office for a second?
I got something I
want to show you.
What the hell am
I going to do now?
I'm a dead man.
I'm sorry, cous.
It was an accident.
Bull's going to see
this and flip his lid.
Hey, Slim!
You got my uni ready?
Um, there's been a bit
of a problem, boss.
What the hell is this?
I left the iron on it too long.
You are as stupid as you are fat,
do you know that, D-Cups?
My new shirt's coming
out of your kick.
You're going to
tell me right now.
Tell you what?
What the hell you've got going on
that's got you burning up guard suits?
Trust me, Primo,
the less you know, the better.
Any news?
No. No, not yet.
Testing takes a couple of days.
What do you remember of Dad?
- Your dad?
- Mm-hmm.
I didn't know him.
Your mom said some pretty horrible
stuff about him when we were growing up.
I think I saw him.
When I was in the chair.
Lincoln...
It was him. I know it was.
How would you know?
You haven't seen his
face in 30 years.
The name that was used--
William Prall.
So?
It's the name of this guy who
threw for Chicago back in the day.
Dad and me were really into him.
But I'd forgotten all about him.
It's really weird.
Been having these
dreams, memories,
things I guess I suppressed
when he left, but...
This man who came
to the execution,
how do you know he
used that name?
Pope told me.
Was that before or
after you had the dream?
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I don't mean to challenge
what you're saying,
but your dad's been MIA
almost your entire life.
I know what I saw, V.
I know what I saw.
This is the security camera
footage of the courthouse
from the night that Judge Kessler got
those documents. Now check out this guy.
He is very skilled.
He moves casually enough
to avoid suspicion,
and you see how he shifts his hat when
he turns corners to hide his face?
He knows exactly where
those cameras are.
Wait. Right there.
See that reflection?
Rewind it, rewind it.
Right, can you blow that up?
- Son of a bitch.
- What?
I know that guy.
What is it?
It was fused into
Michael Scofield's skin.
I removed it during the
debridement procedure.
What about it?
Well, this fabric doesn't come from
a standard issue prison uniform.
Where'd it come from then?
As far as I can tell,
a guard's uniform.
Open on 40!
Close 40!
How you feeling?
What's wrong?
The blueprints--
the ones we need to get from the
Psych Ward to the infirmary...
our map out of here...
they're gone.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net