Previously on Prison Break...
We leave tonight
Got no electricity
and no running water.
A hundred bucks a month.
Deal.
Ready?
I hope this works,popi.
That book
of yours-
It's just a bunch of
coordinates in there, right?
Among other things.
Does your father still have
that phone number I gave you?
I think so.
Well, tell him to call my brother.
Papa, make that call for my friend.
The American?
If time runs out, and I don't have
the second half of those coordinates,
LJ and the senorita stop breathing.
You have a warrant
out for your arrest
You're not going anywhere
Just wish there was
another way to do this.
To save LJ without
handing whistler over.
Look,man,that's
it- There isn't.
What is that?
Michael: Kesslivol.
When heated to a certain
degree, it eats through steel.
As soon as Linc cuts
the power we go.
What about the backup generator?
There's a lag from when the power cuts
out to when the generator kicks back in.
How long a lag we talking about?
30 seconds.
We only have 30 seconds. Go.
Everything's dark
Move it, move it.
Come on.
Let's go.
Okay, letís go.
Not yet.
We have to go now.
We're running out of time.
Trust me.
Stop, or we'll shoot
Stop!
Whistler: Come on, mate.
What's the holdup, Michael?
Just a little bit longer.
STOP!
What happened?
They got caught.
- What's going on?
- Shut up.
What, what...
Don't try anything.
Man: Bring 'em over
here! Bring 'em over here!
You- On your
knees, get down!
Don't move, or you're like
your friend over here.
What's going on, Michael?
We have an escape in progress.
We have an escape
This sure as hell better work out.
For everyone's sake.
Status?
No other prisoners have been found
You two, on your feet.
Bring them inside
Where the hell's Scofield?
Shut it.
If Scofield doesn't get caught,
he could still fix this mess.
What do we do now?
- The lights are on, they know about the escape...
- What's your plan, Michael?
This is the plan.
- =Www. Ydy. Com/bbs=-
Proudly presents Sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Prison Break Season03 Episode12
Michael, how the hell is
getting caught your plan?
You told them they had 30
seconds to get across when
You knew the generator was
going to kick in sooner.
I must have miscalculated.
We've got about ten
minutes till the sun rises.
And there are soldiers out there, okay.
They'll take count.
- We got to get back to the yard.
- We're not going anywhere.
It's almost time.
What do you think you're doing?
Nothing. It's just probably my wife.
You know, we live a couple miles away
And she must have heard the sirens, so...
You can make your calls
when I'm done with you.
What else you got?
Sucre?
I'm not here. Say what you got to say.
Sucre,where the hell are you?
We're counting on you to be here!
If you're not there, weíre dead, man.
Now call me ck,please.
Put these with his personal effects.
What's going on out there?
Some prisoners tried to escape.
Did they get out?
They got caught.
One of them got shot pretty bad.
Sucre? Sucre?
No, it is Alphonso Gallego.
You where you need to be?
Yes.
I left the suburban on
the side of the road.
The keys are in the wheel well.
Are they still there? Check 'em out.
They're here.
Good, good.
You will be here too, on the 312?
Yeah,yeah,the 312.
See you there.
These all the men?
Si,senor.
Tell me, how did you get out there?
How did you get out there?
Don't want to tell me?
A tunnel.
Where?
Under Lechero's room.
Show me.
How much longer?
It's just a matter of seconds now.
Michael?
The door.
I don't know the combination.
Then improvise.
This is insane.
Let's go.
Vamanos.
Hurry!
Nothing
You're sure?
Absolutely
Son of a bitch sold us out!
Are you certain?
Absolutely
It's empty
It wasn't me! It was Scofield!
He did this!
Just heck the yard- Him,Whistler,
Mahone and that basketball kid-
None of 'em will be there!
Did you finish the count?
Just finishing now, Sir
Sir... we are four short!
This is Captain Solo.
Other inmates are missing.
I want a post-And-Protect around
the entire perimeter of the prison.
General, we see no one.
Are you sure there's
prisoners out here?
You won't find the prisoners here in
No-Man's-Land because
they're already gone.
Faster! Weíre losing them.
This way.
He just started shouting.
To get off the bus
Off the bus now!
Get off the bus!
How would you describe the suspect?
Well, he was tall.
More than six feet.
What nationality?
American
He spoke English
Come on. Move it! Go!
If you saw him would you recognize him?
Yes, of course
What's wrong?
My ankle! I've torn it apart!
Come on.
It's not that far. Help me up!
Mr. Whistler, weíll drag you by
your hair because we got to go!
I'll slow you down. Just go!
Just leave me!
We both know that's not an option.
It's only a quarter
of a mile to the beach.
If we stick to the bush, we can make it.
Alex, a little help?
Go. Come on!
We only have a few minutes.
We got soldiers right behind us.
Cops as well.
We got what we need?
Yeah,we got what we need.
What do we need?
Always picking up the strays,huh?
This way.
Listen, Michael,if you think
the company's just going
To let you swap me for
your nephew, youíre mistaken.
Shut up.
Once they get hold of
me, theyíre gonna kill all of you,
And I don't want Sofia
caught in the crossfire.
Listen,just let me go.
I'll contact them, I promise.
I'll say I'll turn myself
in once I know LJ's safe.
Hey,you got no say in
what happens to my son!
You got it?
We don't need a suntan.
We need to get lost.
The military patrols all
the roads around the prison.
You didn't consider a boat?
They show up here and we're ten yards
off the shore, weíre target practice.
We need to be invisible.
Five guys, four tanks.
Sucks for you, Mahone.
Lincoln and I will share.
Toss your boots in the box.
Yeah?
Tell me you have him.
Yeah,I got him.
Where's my son?
With me.
Put him on the phone now.
Say something.
I'll be there soon.
Just don't hurt anyone.
You happy?
You have 20 minutes to meet me
in panama city where we agreed.
We'll be there.
Hey,I need to put my book in there.
The book?
My book!
It must have fell out of my pocket.
I thought you already
figured out the coordinates.
Well, I didn't memorize them!
I wrote them in the book!
I'm pretty sure they're
still looking for us, guys.
It's gone.
Now get the damn water.
Would you please?
It's a picture of my son.
Can you,uh...
Put it in the bag?
Screw you, Mahone.
Let's go.
Mcgrady.
Mcgrady?
I don't swim so good.
What?
Too bad,kid,you're getting wet.
Get in.
Look it's all right.
We'll share tanks.
Just hold onto me and we'll switch
off back and forth, ten seconds apiece.
Come on. Let's go.
Over here!
Towards the beach!
I could've sworn
They were headed in this direction
Give me the binoculars
Do you see any boat?
Not a one...
...where the hell are they?
Where is Scofield?
I don't know!
He didn't tell me nothing!
Where is he running?
I told you, I don't know nothing!
Well, thereís only one way
to make certain of that.
I want men covering five kilometers
Both East and West
and Check-Points
On all
coastal roads-
Every vehicle is to be searched!
Contact the General...
I need more men
sent to me at once
This is General Mestas.
The men will be sent.
And, Sojo, I expect every prisoner
to be returned to Sona today.
Dispatch fourth platoon.
Hey,hey,look,man,this
is getting crazy here.
Look, Iíll plead guilty
for ignoring the warrant.
I'll show up for the court hearings.
Let me get out of here.
You know, with this alarms and the guns,
they're making me a little nervous.
Until things settle in,
you go nowhere.
So just sit tight.
Fourth platoon goes to
Cabrillo beach Ahora.
There!
Where is he?
Where's who?
Sucre with the boat.
Just hold on. You all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Come on, hang on...
I'm all right, Iím all right.
Lincoln: We're not gonna make it
out here too much longer, Michael.
Sucre is coming. Be patient.
Excuse me?
Boat 312,why is it still here?
Wasn't someone supposed
to take that out today?
Someone reserved it, but
they never picked it up.
Sojo: Yes, general.
Mestas: I want an update.
Still no sign of them.
Nothing on the coast.
I think they may have
gone back into the jungle.
The jungle?
You asked me to send men to the beach!
Capitan...
Just a moment, general.
General, I think we have
to call the coast guard.
Come on!
You all right?
My legs are starting to cramp.
You gotta hold on, buddy.
We're not gonna last out
here too long, Michael.
Where's your friend, Michael?
Sucre's not just gonna
abandon us out here, all right?
He'll show, heíll show.
Man: The coast guard is
launching four vessels...
They've been in the
water this whole time.
They're probably at the
bottom of the ocean by now.
Well, look it here!
Looks like we have more than a drunk
and disorderly warrant for Jorge Rivera.
Failure to pay child support.
What kind of man doesn't
Take care of his family?
Not a good one
Please let me go...
They are waiting on me
You're not going anywhere.
Once we're done processing
you, then you can go.
Until then, sit tight.
I should have heard
something by now.
I've lost all damn track of them.
Burrows will eventually reach
out if he wants his son back.
Yeah,well,that might
no longer be an option.
Look! Look!
Sucre!
He's supposed to be flashing a light.
He's not responding, Linc.
The coast guard.
They found us.
Papa!
What's wrong?
Michael...
Michael?
If I don't get another
chance, I want you to
Know that I appreciate
everything you've done.
You're welcome.
Come on, son.
How'd you find us?
You never showed, and you said
you'd be coming from the southwest,
So I took a chance.
What do you think
happened to Sucre?
I don't know, but we gotta move.
He's done
What about him?
He's even worse off
Guess that just leaves one.
Stand up
Move
Move those feet!
Get up.
Let's go.
I saw the boxes in the back, so I took your car
- Figured you'd need to change.
How's the ankle?
Whistler: I need to get off my feet.
All right,guys,get changed
and make sure
you don't leave
any wet clothes behind.
Listen,uh...
Thanks for everything.
Thank you for my boy.
I hope you get your son back, too.
Yeah,me,too.
Come.
We need to get back to the truck.
Michael?
Thank you.
Go be with your family, Luis.
Yeah?
Where the hell are you?
We ran into some trouble.
We're-We're downtown panama.
No, Lincoln, you're not.
We got company.
How'd they find us?
You have them?
We're right on top of them.
Hold on!
They must've gotten to Gradyís
dad and bugged this car.
Or one of us.
Then why didn't they find
us when we were in the water?
It's because the water
was blocking the signal.
What you do with that stopwatch
that Gretchen gave you?
- Oh,my god.
- Give it to me
I didn't know. I didn't know.
Okay, hold on, guys.
All right, it's time to use
this rig to our advantage.
Go! Here we go!
Uh... this is, like, a
dead end right here.
Stay in the car, then.
This way!
Why don't you just
tell us what you know?
Then you won't wind up being beaten
half to death like your friend.
I know less than you do.
Which is hard, considering
how dumb you are.
I want everything you can find on the
men who escaped and
I want it immediately.
What the hell is he still doing here?
He has an outstanding warrant.
Unless it's for murder
Get him out of here!
Go see the clerk about your stuff.
They're barricaded.
What are you doing? Get back!
All that gunfire and they
only hit your car three times?
Son of a bitch...
Listen, Linc,you've done a great
job getting us out of the frying pan,
But it'll be for nothing if
we end up back in the fire.
There's no fire, just an
exchange, then I'm done with you.
You think it's that simple?
Yeah,they want you,
they get you.
It's that simple.
This is not about me.
It's about Sofia and your son.
Michael- Tell him- Tell him these
people won't just let us walk away.
We already had this discussion
back at the beach, James,
And you were out voted
You're making a terrible mistake.
People might die because of this.
Take off your pants.
Excuse me, Senor?
I said take off your pants.
If I knew you boys
partied in Sona like this,
I never would have tried to escape.
One cell phone.
One wallet.
And some change.
There were some papers.
A boat-rental agreement.
I need them.
I'll check the drawer.
Take them down.
Come on,now,hombre.
There's no need to refry my beans.
Always with the wise talk.
Never saying anything
we want to hear.
Now, all I want to hear
are your screams.
No, no. No,no,no,no,no. Listen.
I told you, I don't know nothing.
No,actually,I don't know nothing.
I swear. I swear I don't.
But he does!
He knows everything!
Not so fast, amigo.
A little help.
What is this place?
Where we're gonna make the
exchange- On our terms.
There's a service road out back,
just in case we want to get lost.
Yeah,assuming you're still alive.
You still talking?
- Linc?
- Yeah.
Gotta commend you on
that boom box trick.
Very sophisticated.
You steal that one from home alone?
You fell for it,bitch.
All right, listen.
If you wanna see your son...
You're not calling the shots anymore.
As long as I have LJ...
As long as I got Whistler, youíre
gonna do exactly what I say.
You got it?
Now, listen up.
We're at an abandoned
warehouse five miles
down the road from the
barrios interchange.
Be there in 20 minutes with my son.
And once I get there?
So now we wait.
Yeah.
Think this'll work?
Yeah,it'll work.
- You, me and LJ.
- Yeah.
I just hope it works
out for Mcgrady,too.
Oh,no.
They must have closed all
the roads out of panama.
Papa, what do we do?
You gotta turn around, papa.
I can't go back to Sona. I canít.
I don't care what he says.
He's a convict!
He's a piece of garbage.
I don't know anything about
this Michael Scofield guy.
Guard: General.
Here is everything we have
on the escaped prisoners.
You don't know Michael
Scofield,is that right, Jorge?
Yes.
You sure you don't want to
change your story, Fernando?
What's this!
WHAT'S THIS!
This should help make
you a decent brace.
Thank you.
Should be able to see
them coming from up here.
You know,Linc...
You did great.
Thanks.
I just want LJ back, you know?
It's just a matter of time.
Yeah.
Considering I don't have
a pony in this race...
I guess this is where I say goodbye
You think you can just walk out
of here after what you did to us?
What you did to my dad?
No.
I was gonna kill you at
the beach, but I didn't
Want to do anything that
was gonna get us caught.
You shot my dad in the back.
I'm gonna give you the
courtesy you never gave him.
Now Turn around.
Turn around.
Linc, think about what you're doing.
I was told to choose between your
family and mine. That was my option.
I chose mine.
Go to hell.
Linc,you don't have to do this.
Mahone!
My truck!
Stop!
What are we gonna do now?
=Www. Ydy. Com/bbs=
- Proudly presents Sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Subs improved by jenilim
www.tvsubtitles.net