Previously on Prison Break.
I want a presidential pardon
for me and my brother.
You tell me what's going on--
I can take care of you.
All I need you to do
is tell me exactly what
Agent Mahone told you.
I have a job to do,
which I've been made to do.
- The phone.
- Wait.
Stay right where you are.
Hey!
What if I know where
you can get $5 million?
- Where is it?
- I could take you there,
if you didn't have to take me back
to the States and turn me back in.
Free tickets,
one cabin, one-way.
Nice.
Sir, in just a few
minutes the president
is going to announce a pardon
for Burrows and Scofield.
I regret to inform you,
I am stepping down
as president of
the United States.
There's only one thing we can do.
We gotta disappear.
Forever.
Aqui es to maleta,
Senor Stammel.
Gracias.
It's very heavy.
What have you got in there?
About 75 pounds of none
of your business, Pedro.
- For your troubles.
- Gracias.
Go! Go! Go!
Please. T-Bag. T-Bag, please.
I need that money.
Andale, you son of
a bitch. Andale!
Please, T-Bag, I'm begging you.
Please. Please! No!
- What time does the ship leave?
- About ten minutes.
I can't believe
we're running again.
It's different now, man.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
We brought the bitch down.
- She stepped down, Linc.
- Because of us.
Yet you're still
wanted for murder.
When you came to Fox River...
Remember what you said?
You said,
"I'm gonna break you out of here."
I'm alive. You did that.
You want to look for
the good you look there.
Come on,
let's just finish what you started.
- Hello?
- Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just heard about the president.
- What, what does it mean?
- It means it's time to go.
Okay... when?
Ten minutes.
How far away are you?
- Five.
- Listen, Sara,
Linc and I are on the ship.
This is it.
There's no turning back now, so, uh...
I know it's not what you
wanted from your life, but
in case your interested,
there is room for one more.
Michael Scofield, you asking me to
sail off into the sunset with you?
Well, it's more of a freighter,
but, uh... yes.
I'll be there.
I'll see you soon.
- She's heading West on Leadwell.
- All right.
Stay on her,
I'll be right there.
- What the hell's this?
- I tried, boss.
You saw how he just took off.
The only thing I'm seeing
is an escaped con,
who's begging to
be taken Nort-ay.
Okay, look, maybe we could call
the cab company and find out
where T-Bag was dropped off.
Now, you're talking.
I saw some phone...
What's it going to take for you
to forget you ever found us?
There ain't enough pesos in TJ.
You sure about that?
Go ahead, shoot.
But it might not be the best idea
seeing as how I'm the only one who
knows where your Chiquita's tied up.
Where is Maricruz?
If I tell you,
I'm as good as dead.
Of course if you shoot,
so is she.
- You're bluffing me.
- Am I?
Let me tell you in words you
might be more familiar with.
She's in "the Hole,"
with enough food and water
to last about three weeks.
Any longer than that your sweet little
plum's gonna dry up like a raisin.
If anything happens to her,
so help me...
Help you? Way I see it,
it's you who's gotta help me.
'Cause you ain't gettin'
your hands on that girl
'til I get my hands
on that money.
Guess that makes us partners.
Here we go.
She's not here.
- Yeah.
- Sara, what's the matter?
The ship is leaving.
- Michael...
- What's wrong?
- Sara.
- I'm already on board.
I'm sorry, I must have just missed you.
Where are you?
- We're on deck.
- Great.
I'm on my way up.
Love you.
We good?
Clear vessels port side...
Yeah.
Son of a bitch.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
No more games, Sara.
You were on your way to see him.
No, I wasn't.
You were just compelled to flee
the custody of a Federal Agent?
I couldn't find her.
Sara... We got to go back.
Michael, you can't,
there's nothing you can do.
There's always
something you can do.
Not this time.
Not this time, man. It's done.
I'm sorry.
- Scofield or Prison.
- I just wanted a donut, sir.
Get her a donut.
Can we get her a donut?
Get her a dozen donuts! Look her up!
One week later.
Where the hell did
you go, Michael?
So, where the hell is Mahone?
I don't know, sir.
He's been MIA for the last week or so.
You think he knows I've been
barking up one of his trees.
Mr. Franklin, good afternoon.
This is Richard Sullins.
Director of Internal Affairs at the FBI.
Which means whenever one of our
people does something wrong,
it's my job to make it right.
How right are we talking about?
Well, let's be clear,
you are a convicted felon
who broke out of a
state penitentiary,
there's only so much I can do.
Well, there's only
so much I can say.
Now, I'm sorry if I seem
a little bit skeptical.
But the last time a federal agent
came up in here offering me a deal,
there was a string attached...
that I was supposed to
put around my neck.
I've been authorized to, uh,
offer you a reduced sentence
in exchange for your testimony
against Agent Mahone,
instead of 18 years,
you'll be looking at 18 months.
18 months?
Hey, you know what?
That man tried to kill me.
So as soon as he finds
out that I'm singing,
I probably won't
even last 18 days.
- Mr. Franklin...
- He threatened my family.
Now, I need to be out
there protecting them.
So until you can offer me
something like that...
I'm not testifying
to a damn thing.
Guard!
Free man.
You and your family.
Witness protection,
fresh start.
Clean record?
Spick-and-span.
You put that in writing and
you got yourself a witness.
Sir?
I knocked, but...
You okay?
What does that look like to you?
There, right there.
- Uh, it's a triangle.
- Yeah, I thought so, too.
- How about this?
- Right there.
It's the mathematical
symbol for Pi.
3.14. I'm thinking date,
area code.
314, that's Missouri.
So you think Scofield's there?
I doubt it.
How's your Greek alphabet, Agent Lang?
I don't know. I guess it's...
What if I told you that triangle
was a delta and that this,
this here was not the
symbol Pi but the letter?
I didn't see any of those in
the photos of the tattoos.
They weren't in the tattoos.
We pulled these from his original
sketches off the hard drive.
Scofield numbered all of
the steps of his escape.
It's how he kept
everything in order,
but it looks like that
he didn't use numbers,
that he used
letters like, um...
A sketch of this tattoo.
Allan Schweitzer
marked with an alpha,
first letter of the Greek alphabet.
First step of his plan.
Epsilon, fifth letter of the Greek
alphabet. Fifth step in his plan.
Here's theta, and kappa...
How about that? Tau?
At the border, right?
Getting closer to the end now;
you with me?
- So you think...
- His omega...
The last letter of
the Greek alphabet...
...is the last
step of his plan.
What is that?
- Christ in a flower?
- A rose.
And these numbers-- 617.
Could be biblical;
chapter 6, verse 17.
6-1-7, 617. June 17th.
- Oh, what's today?
- The 15th.
- So whatever his last step is...
- It's going to happen in two days.
What's he saying?
Nothing. The same as the rest.
Maybe he don't comprende.
What's Spanish for "INS"?
Don't be stupid.
We're in Mexico.
You're the illegal one here.
Hey, it doesn't mean he
ain't got family up north
trying to clean their
way to a green card.
He knows what I'm
talking about.
Oh, you are too
good to me, Suzi-Q.
Just how I like it.
How did I get so lucky?
Oh, no, Teddy Bear.
I'm the lucky one.
The day I met you...
was the day I was born.
- We're out of time.
- No, Susan,
we got our whole
lives together.
No, I mean, the hour is up.
I'll take care of
you plenty, okay?
And since we're rolling here,
so let's, you know, get back...
How's it--
what's cookin', good lookin'?
I would really feel better
if you paid me up front.
And I told you up front
that if you did this right,
I would take care of you, so...
You paid me for an hour.
The hour is up.
If you want me to stay,
I need more money.
Great, great,
you ruined it. Thanks.
You know, for a second there,
I was actually like,
"This chick has a
brain in her head."
Then, if you did,
you wouldn't be a street whore, right?
You know,
I don't know who this Suzi-Q bitch is,
but no wonder she wants
nothing to do with you.
You didn't just call her a bitch,
did you?
Okay.
I am going to count to three,
and if you don't put your arm down,
I'm going to scream.
One, t...
We made it.
Not yet.
First there's someone
we need to see.
Okay, who's got what?
Christ as a rose is a pretty common
theme that runs through the Bible.
Martin Luther adopted
it as his coat of arms.
And there's the belief that
Christ rose from the dead.
This is Scofield's final step,
a new life.
Could be something there.
Right. You... keep track of this
on the board. On the board.
- Where's Wheeler?
- Here we go.
The Harmonists--
first settlers of New Harmony, Indiana--
used a golden rose as
their symbol for Christ.
That's a reach.
There's a flower called
the Christmas Rose.
Wasn't "Christ Rose" a
German code name for, uh,
the counterattack by the Nazis that
led to the Battle of the Bulge?
Where was that?
Ardennes Forest on the
Belgium-Germany border.
Yeah, not a bad place to
hide if they can find it.
- So you gonna look into that?
- Yeah.
All right, what else?
Christ actually rose from the
dead on Easter. Easter Sunday...
- Who's got Scofield's file?
- Um, here we go.
Here.
- Christ in a rose.
- Yeah, what about it?
Scofield's mother's name.
Christina Rose Scofield.
Hmm, but I thought
she was dead.
Well, so did I.
So did I.
The very first thing that Scofield
did when they broke out of Fox River
is he picked up a bunch of supplies
that he had stashed in a grave.
I want you to find out where
Scofield's mother's buried.
And what?
- And see if she's buried.
- Yes, sir.
- What about Panama?
Well, when we found
his hard drive,
it was full of information about
Central America, Panama in particular.
Which he knows you have.
The guy's got all
kinds of hubris,
but he's smart enough to
stay out of a country
where he knows you'll
be waiting for him.
Unless there's something there
that he needs. Or someone.
I want a map of Panama, and find out
if Scofield's mom, Christina Rose,
has any family in Central America,
any property, anything.
The last time I was on a bus like this,
I was heading to Fox River.
This country's amazing.
It's beautiful.
- What's that smell, man?
- Bananas.
And sugar cane.
That's Panama's biggest exports.
Come on.
You've been talking about Panama
and bumpy bus rides ever
since we broke out,
and now that we're
actually doing it...
She should have
been here with us.
We got all the time in
the world for that.
Some ways down the track,
you and Sara...
Can we just get there, please?
Sure.
Oye! Tipo! Espera!
So far, no hits on any connection
between Scofield's mother and Panama.
But there are 38 listings
of Christina Rose
in various combinations of first name,
middle name and last name.
All right, cross-reference the names
with the numbers 6-1-7 from the tattoo.
Maybe it's not a date.
See if it's an address, P.O. box.
Got it.
If anybody pops,
call the Embassy,
have them send an officer to pick
up the woman for questioning.
I don't think we can just arrest
a foreign citizen without any...
Patriot Act, Agent Lang.
I could arrest your grandmother
for missing a stitch in
her macramé if I wanted to.
If anybody's helping Scofield, dead or
alive, I want to know who they are.
- That her?
- Yeah.
Hola, Mrs. Vasquez.
You're late.
It's much later than
the date you said.
Well, we ran into a
little bit of trouble.
Who is this?
It's a business associate.
Christina Rose. I remember.
You will find her here.
- Buena suerte.
- Gracias.
Oh, um...
I'll meet you outside.
- I forgot to ask something.
- All right.
Do you have a
phone I could use?
Yes, uh, I need an
international operator, please.
United States.
It's, uh, 312-346...
What the hell are you doing?
- Making a phone call.
- You can't.
We don't even know if
she's alive or dead, Linc.
If Sara's in custody,
they got her phone.
You want to get caught?
Yeah.
Three things I hate, Alex.
Traffic, hockey...
and calling you with the
same question over and over.
Well, then don't
call me anymore,
but I do believe the
brothers are in Panama.
Is that so?
The key to exactly where is
on one of Scofield's tattoos.
While I'm thrilled you've
narrowed it down to a country,
that's not why we're talking.
- Benjamin Miles Franklin is alive...
- I'm aware of that, yeah.
...and being released
from custody.
That's not possible. They would
need permission from my office.
Good to know you're
on top of things.
Find me Agent Wheeler.
He'll see you now.
Forgive me for asking,
sir, but...
couldn't we be doing this in my office?
It'd be much more comfortable.
I felt we needed to speak freely.
For the next several hours,
this is what those in the intelligence
community refer to as a "blind spot."
Something to do with the
position of the sun, I'm told.
Disrupts long-distance
recording devices.
If I may apologize again,
sir, for...
the unfortunate outcome
with the president.
I know how important she
was to our interests,
and I assure you that
moving forward, I'll...
You won't be moving anywhere until you
can explain to me how this happened.
The brothers...
they're making it...
Still alive.
Yes. It appears they were
able to flee the country.
To where?
Mr. Mahone seems to
believe they're in Panama.
Does our Mr. Mahone know where
exactly in Panama they are?
Not yet.
Why?
How much do you know about Sona,
Mr. Kim?
Only what I've been
given clearance on.
Perhaps what our situation requires...
is a change in strategy.
How long until the court approves
the arrest warrant for Mahone?
Should be anytime now. We're just
waiting for the indictment to come down.
Okay, well,
I've got a question for you.
What if he's in there?
I can't keep avoiding him.
He reads people.
That's what he does.
And if he finds out that
I'm involved in this,
I'm gonna need some
protection from...
Wheeler, relax. Take a breath.
The only thing Mahone can read
is what you write for him.
Can you act normal?
That's all you have to do--
the last thing we want is for
him to get spooked and take off.
- This is all gonna be over soon.
- All right. Thank you.
No. Thank you.
Wheeler.
Where you been?
I got to do this.
What are you doing, Alex?
I'm not wearing a wire.
You gonna tell me
what's going on here?
In old England...
the punishment for a
traitorous act was beheading.
Following the execution,
they would
hold up the severed
head by the hair--
not, as most people think,
for the crowd to see the head,
but for the head to see
the crowd, because...
consciousness sticks around
for another eight seconds.
The idea was that it would give the
traitor one more chance to take a
look at...
You don't want to do this, okay?
Just take a moment...
If you're gonna stab me in the back,
Agent Wheeler,
be smart enough to
cover up the knife.
You go and visit Franklin
three times this week,
called Sullins,
what, twice a day?
Didn't you learn
anything working for me?
You got to cover your tracks,
unless you...
unless you want to get caught.
You wanted me to
know it was you.
- You're a killer, Alex.
- Is that so?
Soil samples taken
from your yard
in connection with the
disappearance of Oscar Shales.
Forensics is prepared
to submit a report
detailing the irregularities in the
shooting of David "Tweener" Apolskis.
There's your blatant disregard
for protocol in the
death of John Abruzzi...
And the escaped con who says
that I told him to kill himself.
You think his testimony is gonna
send you into the promised land.
You can erase me, too.
But it's not gonna
erase the very real fact
that you're gonna spend the
rest of your life in prison.
You know...
you remind me of myself
when I was a young agent.
What?
I wish I could take
that as a compliment.
That's some real
fine work, Wheeler.
Good job.
Don't you let
anyone scare you...
into doing the wrong thing.
Let me take you in.
Whatever mess you're in,
we can clean it up.
There's only one way to clean this--
one way.
Hey. Got a visitor.
- Yeah, who?
- I don't know.
I was just instructed
to bring you down.
Hey, look,
I ain't going nowhere
until you tell me who it is I'm meeting,
all right?
You got to stop it.
Listen to me for a second, all right?
That's all you got to do
is go out there and check.
Guy's kind of tall, okay?
It's the least that you can do. Huh?
What?
- Daddy!
- Oh, my God. Come here.
Oh. Oh,
Daddy loves you so much.
So, um... is it real?
He says you're gonna go free,
that we don't have to run anymore.
I mean, what happened?
What changed?
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't you worry about it.
You just know that your
man handles things.
Ain't that right? That's right.
Okay. I don't
believe it but okay.
Benjamin, if I could
just have a quick word.
Yeah. Hey.
Why don't you go down the hall
for just a quick second. Okay?
- I'll be right there.
- Okay.
Here it is.
New address, new identities.
Now, the prosecutor's gonna
be getting in touch with you
to go over your testimony,
so you just make sure you show up
where he says and when he says.
Yeah, okay, okay.
But I'm a free man, right?
Free man.
Wait a minute.
What about Mahone, you know?
'Cause I don't want to be
looking over my shoulder
for the rest of my life,
you feel me?
You let me worry about Mahone.
You just worry about
staying out of trouble.
You ain't gonna have a
problem with that, trust me.
Don't screw it up.
How much further?
Not far.
You know, for what it's worth,
no one forced Sara to do what she did.
Whatever gets you
through the night.
The hell does that mean?
I didn't ask you to use her.
It's not that simple. Whatever
gets you through the night, buddy.
You know what amazes me, Linc?
Nothing ever registers
with you. Ever.
Just rolls right off your back,
doesn't it?
We ruined Sara's life and it's
like you don't even care.
Is that what you think?
Well, we're here,
and Sara's back there in prison.
- Does that seem fair to you?
- None of it's fair.
Just don't make this
about boy loses girl.
Who should it be about,
Linc? Westmoreland?
- Tweener? LJ? LJ's mom?
- Let me stop you right there.
Remember the name of the guard that was
murdered because of the riot I started?
- Shut up, Michael.
- Do you even remember his name?
I bet you remember Veronica's
name though, don't you?
You mention her name again,
I swear to God...!
What about T-Bag?! Linc, he's out there,
now, because of us! You and me!
Every life he takes,
that's blood on our hands.
And for what?
I didn't ask you to
do what you did.
They were gonna kill you, Linc!
Well, maybe you
should've let them!
Take that back.
As bad as I feel about Sara,
she had a choice.
Veronica didn't.
I listened to her die, Michael.
I listened to her die,
and there was...
there was nothing I could do.
Nothing.
We've lost so much, man.
We can't afford to
lose each other.
We just can't.
- You going somewhere, Alex?
- I don't know. Am I?
Come on. You know I don't
like to get my hands dirty.
It's surprising the things a man
will do when properly motivated.
Wasn't it you who told me that?
You know,
I would kill you right now
if I thought it would give
me an ounce of peace.
And what would give you peace?
I've been able to hold it
together through all this...
because there was a light
at the end of the tunnel.
Life...
at the end of the tunnel,
for me, for my family.
And now what?
Do you see my son?
Do you see my wife?
What have I got?
What have you given me?
What if I was to tell you
that there was something that
could turn that light...
- back on? What would you say?
- I'd say that's the same offer
you made when you dragged me into this,
you little bastard.
And look where it's got me now.
They're gonna drag me
before the public.
They've gonna prosecute me like...
like some kind of murderer.
There's... There's evidence.
Really hard, tangible evidence,
that you can't take away.
You're right...
but I can help you get away.
And at this point, I don't think
you've got any other options.
Theodore "T-Bag" Bagwell
was apprehended in Mexico.
Oh, let me guess.
You want him dead.
Oh, no.
There's been a, uh,
change in strategy.
We're gonna need him alive.
I'm talking about a very
real finish line here, Alex.
You've come so far.
How much further
would I have to go?
Well, you're lucky.
For this,
you only have to go to Panama.
I'm trying to remember the last time
our lives made any kind of sense.
Before Mom died.
When it was just the three of us.
Well, there she is.
- Hello, Lang.
- What's going on?
I mean, there'l kinds of suits over
here going through your office.
- I'll explain later.
- All right.
- Um... did you get the fax?
- No. Why? What do you got?
Some information on Christina
Rose you might find interesting.
Looks like she was commissioned
about four months before
Scofield robbed that bank by a builder
in Panama named Amparo Vasquez.
Son of a bitch.
She's beautiful.
Yeah, she's not the
real thing, but...
- So where to, man?
- Anywhere we want.
So, is it really over?
Yeah. Yeah, baby,
it's really over. Okay.
What is it, baby?
Huh?
Oh, nothing. Let's go home.
Okay, so we checked the
train station in Malinalco,
the bus depot in Puebla,
and just about every hotel there is.
Hello.
Hey, hey, hey,
slow down, Sancho.
Uno momento.
It's for you.
Hola.
Sí?
That was the guy from
the tourism bureau.
- He found him.
- Where?
An E. Stammel just boarded
a plane to Panama City.
What the hell's he
doing in Panama?
You speak English?
Say, uh, "Good morning, Teddy."
Good morning, Teddy.
So then actually, no,
you don't speak English.
Hablan ingles around here?
Say, "Good morning, Teddy."
Good morning, Teddy.
Say, "Good morning,
Teddy Bear."
Good morning, Teddy Bear.
Do you like wigs?
For the right money,
I like anything.
There's nothing.
Nothing on line about Sara's arrest.
Maybe they're keeping it quiet.
What about the message board?
The Goldfinch thing?
Just something
from C-Note and...
There is a message from Sucre.
Still running, huh?
What?
Sucre says T-Bag's here,
in Panama.
How the hell does he know?
I don't know.
It says, "The Bag's still has the bag.
He's in Panama City at the Fin
Del Camino hotel. If you're there
and want to help put that bird back
in a cage, let me know. Sucre."
What the hell is that son
of a bitch doing in Panama?
We got to go after him.
Just let it be, man.
We don't need the money.
It's not about the money, Linc.
Whatever good we do
from here on out,
it doesn't matter as
long T-Bag's out there.
- Michael, we made it.
- Too much has gone wrong. If we could just...
If we could just
make this right.
Panama City is only an hour away.
And now we know where he's staying.
So call the police.
There's a reason I chose Panama--
there's no extradition laws.
- They're not going to touch him.
- So what are you gonna do?
I'll figure something out.
Figure it out? Yon't take a piss
without a plan, man. Come on.
Look at me-- I never think things
through and look where it got me.
Yeah, Panama and a
boat-load of booze.
You got me that. I got me death
sentence. Look, let's just...
get out to sea,
think things through,
when the time's right,
we make it right. Okay?
I'm in.
Let me know when you get there. Michael.
I'll be there tomorrow.
See you there. Sucre.
See you soon.
Home sweet home.
I got the booze,
but the limes are shot.
Michael?!
Michael!
www.tvsubtitles.net