Previously on Prison break...
MICHAEL:
We're losing the light! Go back!
You.
Is it your cell?
You are breaking out
of this prison, Mr. Scofield.
And you're taking me with you.
So with this deal
what specifically are they
expecting from me?
They need to know everything.
They want to confirm
that you have viable,
incriminating information
and that you can be
a cooperative witness.
Show me the pictures.
I can't show you
the pictures, man.
She's dead, Michael.
I thought we agreed it was best
for you to not come here.
I need to know how this delay
is going to affect things.
Four more days.
If I'm out of here
by then,
I can still do it.
I'll let the brothers know.
Michael.
You like this?
Yeah.
It's a special occasion.
My dad's coming today,
so I'm just gonna wait here
till he shows up.
You look sharp.
Thanks.
- LJ. Is he...?
- Alive.
Giving us four more days.
Okay, good.
Listen, back at
the exchange point,
I saw three body bags.
You, me and LJ,
we weren't getting
out of there alive.
That's the last time
I get caught flatfooted.
You do what you gotta do Linc,
As long as I take
care of my end, right?
Michael, I know you're angry
with me about Sara, but...
You lied.
I had to lie.
Your son is my nephew,
and there's nothing
I wouldn't do for him.
But apparently...
...apparently you only think I
only care about myself.
I know you don't care
about yourself,
but you cared
about Sara.
You loved her.
And I'm sorry.
But LJ's my son.
I- I couldn't
let anything happen to him.
You know that.
You used me, Linc.
So I guess you and the Company
have something in common.
I don't know where he is.
I have tried every
number I have.
Well, listen, I will check back with
Headquarters and see what they say.
Never mind.
I found him.
"Carter Blue Label".
You always had such...
...High-end taste
for a girl from Wheeling.
Since I paid for it...
You know how much I hate
to travel, Gretchen...
...but considering the mess
down here, I made an exception.
It was a mess before I got here.
And it's time to clean it up.
We're ending this today.
Bang and burn.
General, that was analyzed.
What you're asking for
is too dangerous,
not to mention
next to impossible
with the given time frame.
I remember
a substantial wire transfer
to an offshore account
that took the word
"impossible"
out of the equation-
or tell me,
did I hire the wrong person?
I am doing my job when I tell
you to seriously reconsider.
And now, I have to do my job.
I don't pay you to
be my advisor.
You're my operative.
You have your instructions,
now get it done.
Because if you don't,
I'll make what happened
to you in Mosul
feel like a massage.
WHISTLER: This was a
big mistake, Gretchen.
You can't make a habit
of coming to Sona.
I won't.
Because we're going
with the bang and burn.
That's suicide.
We have more time.
My boss wants things
to move a bit faster.
Well- tell him
you can't pull it off.
I might get killed
if we do this.
And I might get killed
if we don't.
Between you and me,
who do you think
I care about more?
Look at me, James.
See if you can tell
how serious I am.
If you don't play ball,
I will leave you in Sona to rot.
I promise.
Be ready by 5:00.
That's when it happens.
Everybody goes.
What about Scofield?
Kill him
www.opensubtitles.org
Prison break
Season 03 Episode 08
"Bang and Burn"
MICHAEL (whispering):
Hey.
You know the consequences
if I'm seen talking to you?
The military's reinforcing
the bars on all the windows.
Can you talk to the colonel,
get him to postpone
that for a few days? No.
After your performance
yesterday,
I have no further sway
with the colonel.
Well, then I'm afraid
you've brokered your way
into an escape plan
that no longer exists.
I have an idea.
SAMMY:
Lechero...!
Wait to hear from me.
What?
Some of the men don't feel the
need to pay their debts anymore.
It's been one week, man,
and we lost three men.
Now, if we gonna keep Sona,
we're gonna need numbers.
I don't trust nobody here
right now, especially now.
I work with the men I have.
Really, brother?
You, me
and the gimp over there,
we gonna run this place?
I want to bring on
Cristobal.
He's solid, man.
One of them Darrien
ghetto boys.
Bring him up.
But I promise you nothing.
Find me anything that can
sustain heavy RPGs
and small arms.
A Cougar, a Striker.
Not gonna happen.
I do have a call in to
a Sergeant York, but...
Yeah, that's not going
to cut it.
Call Suezamel,
put him on standby,
tell him we might need him.
Is there a problem?
We're doing this
at 5:00?
Well, we could
wait until tonight
when our guys are
moving too fast
for our night vision
to work properly.
You could even tag along
if you want.
Get it done.
Hello.
MAN: Yes, I'm trying to locate
the family of Mr. James Whistler.
I- I am his- I'm his wife.
Who's calling?
My name is Tommy Day.
I own the apartment building
Mr. Whistler rents from.
There's been a busted pipe
in his unit that's caused
some damage
to the apartment next door.
I'm sorry.
I think you have confused James
with someone else.
He's not renting
another apartment.
Oh, I assure you
Mr. Whistler is my tenant.
I couldn't find anyone
to contact after his conviction,
but when the mail came,
I checked his phone bill.
There were numerous calls
to this number.
If you could please come
to the apartment-
the address is 40 Abel Bravo
in Obarrio,
Unit 4.
(phone ringing) Tell
your men the Intel says
the Panamanians have
no access to SAM.
Yeah.
MAN:
There's been a development.
Hey.
The Company's giving us
four more days.
- Okay.
- Problem is
I, uh, I don't know
how we're getting out of here.
Lechero might have some ideas,
but I'm still waiting
to hear from him.
I'm sorry,
is this a bad time for you?
It's been an intense 24 hours.
I have things on my mind.
Yeah, like your last trip
to visitation maybe.
What, you're a spy now?
Forgive me if I'm wrong,
but she didn't really strike me
as the girlfriend type.
She was Company.
After your failed escape,
she came to remind me
that I have a stake
in this, too,
which you seem to
have forgotten.
So forgive me
if I don't jump for joy
when you say you're
working on a plan
that may very well fail again.
I've got to
get out of here,
and it's getting to the
point where I don't care how
Got what we
talked about?
You never met me.
Oh, my God.
What the hell
is going on?
Shales...
What about Oscar Shales?
He... raped, killed, tortured.
I couldn't turn, turn him over
to some scumbag lawyer who
was just gonna get him off or...
or... no, no, I just...
so I killed him.
And I felt... good.
I felt- I felt really good.
But then, you know,
came the visions
of Shales begging
for his life-
and I couldn't
get rid of them,
so I, I got these drugs
that kept me on an even keel.
And then when I got
to Sona,
I couldn't get my pills,
so I had to...
improvise.
Did you want me to
get drugs for you?
I assume that whoever
set this up must think
that I might have some value.
It's why you came back
for me.
me I came here to help a man
that I respect and care about.
And I appreciate that.
But I can't testify like this.
Please...
Please.
One inch of reinforced steel
on every window.
Nothing would get
through those.
I'll figure
something out.
I know you will.
Listen, man, I'm sorry
about before.
Like I said, things
have been intense.
So much depends
on this working out.
My nephew's life depends
on this working.
I know it does.
I never asked-
how old is he?
Sixteen.
Oh, hell.
T- BAG:
Knocka knocka.
What do you want?
Me? I just came by
to slip something
into your mail slot.
It's from El Patron
himself,
but it was made
for your eyes only.
Grabby.
That don't look
like no invitation
to the Sona-Hawkins Dance.
What do you got cooking up
with Lechero, huh?
It's none of your business,
Theodore.
You want to keep secrets?
You want to treat me
like a pesky insect? Fine.
Just remember,
information, like crumbs,
always trickles down
to the vermin on the floor.
4:00?
It's a sketch of
Lechero's quarters.
To be honest, when a tenant
pays a year's rent in advance
and then gets locked up,
I normally rent
the place out
and double my
money, but, uh,
James was a good man.
I was hoping things would
turn out well for him.
Look, uh, Miss...
a lot of guys have a little
something on the side.
This apartment, I mean,
whoever he brought here,
doesn't mean
he didn't love ya.
You said you have James'
insurance paper?
Right on. Right on...
I'll, uh, I'll go get them.
Oh, God.
There's another door in here.
"4413."
4413, huh?
What about Scofield?
Kill him.
You know, if Lechero
didn't send this,
T- Bag might be setting
me up for someone.
I say we get
out of here.
I'm truly sorry that you got
caught up with my troubles, Michael.
Scofield
I take it there's
another code.
I'm the only one that knows it.
For a man who likes
keeping a secret,
choosing T-Bag as a go-between
might not be the smartest move.
Yeah, by the time he figures
it out, we'll be long gone.
Sammy's on his way back.
Let's go.
What the hell is this?
Underground tunnel.
The old administration
used it
to travel between cellblocks
A and B.
After the riots,
they moved us all to B.
And then the soldiers
came in,
blew this tunnel up.
MICHAEL:
Looks like someone already
tried to get through the debris.
I never planned to spend
my whole life in Sona.
Just didn't expect
it to end so soon.
You're the engineer,
though, right?
You can dig
our way out of this?
Yeah, me and a couple
of payloaders.
LECHERO:
Now, you listen.
You're gonna dig
out of this place.
We're not digging out,
but we might be diggin up.
Hello, Sofia.
Hello. Who are you?
Friend of James.
Old friend.
Well, he isn't here.
I know where he is.
I can see why James loves you.
You are beautiful.
If you keep sticking
your nose where
it doesn't belong,
I'm gonna make him miss you
very, very much.
Do you understand
what I'm saying to you?
Good
You don't need to
worry about this.
Now listen very carefully to me,
Sofia, and you won't get hurt.
I want you to go home
and do your hair
and paint your nails
and get all ready
for when James comes home.
You two will live
happily ever after.
What do you want from him?
See? You're not
listening already.
Don't get in
the way,
or I promise you things
will get very bad for you.
You are truly beautiful.
I hope you can stay that way.
Get the hell out of here.
MICHAEL: All right,
if we can get through
the ceiling, the foundation and
the earth on top of that,
we can make it out
into the middle of no-man's-land
and maybe hit the fence
before we get shot.
Yeah.
Well, we wouldn't want that.
Yes, but you can
dig out, though, right?
Based on gravity and the kind
of sand that Sona's built on,
we're gonna need some kind
of support brace for the tunnel.
Or...
Or what?
The whole thing collapses
and we're buried alive.
Go on and relax, huh?
I'll get some rum.
LECHERO:
How long will this take?
Maybe two days.
I got to get upstairs,
estimate exactly where
in no-man's land
that tunnel's gonna let out.
Where you going?
I'm meditating.
Just getting rum
for Cristobal and his boys.
Rum?! His boys?!
No, I said I'd meet
with Cristobal,
not every half-breed in Sona.
Well, they up there right now.
So, let's go.
- Let me just get some rum, now.
- No, man.
Them drink beer
like everyone else.
Look, man, offer
them something good.
Don't make me look the fool.
The rum is for me, Sammy.
No
You have a problem with that?
No, Sir.
Good Let's go.
Let's get back to work.
Hey, only Lechero has the code.
We don't need
a code.
Now, get inside
before Sammy comes back.
Alex?
Where's Agent Lang?
Agent... I don't know.
But what the hell's wrong
with you? What's going on?
I have a right to be nervous.
My life is on the line,
you know?
What are you
talking about?
You have given live press
conferences your entire life.
I've see you many times.
You're an old pro.
Now, splash some water
on your face.
The panel wants us there
right now, immediately.
- What?
- Get dressed.
Or would you rather
have me
drag your ass
back to Sona?
Water on the face.
Get your suit on. We're going.
Yeah, it's Sullins.
Uh, we're almost ready
to move here.
Where the hell is Lang?
No.
Where are we at?
Everything's in place.
Good. We've done our part.
Now it's time for Whistler
to step up and do his.
Come 5:00 o'clock,
he better be ready.
Tired feet
of concrete and rebar,
plus ten feet
of dirt and sand,
before we see sky.
Are you all right?
To be completely honest...
No,
I have this thing
for, uh, confined spaces.
Are you telling me
you're claustrophobic?
Ever since I was a...
boy.
Um, you know,
I need to be upstairs.
That's not really
an option right now.
Well, staying here is not
really an option for me, either.
I suggest you get
yourself together.
I just need some air.
What the hell's the
matter with you?
I need to get out of here;
I need air. Hey, you walk
through that door with Sammy on the
other side, you'll never need air again.
You don't understand-
I need to get out of here now.
Why don't you tell me what's
really going on here, Whistler?
Why do you keep
looking at your watch?
What are you really up to?
Scofield, the men are gone-
let's move.
I need your cell phone.
No, Sammy's on his way-
get out of here.
I have to call my brother. No, cell
phone stays with me. Now, get out of here!
Well, just so that
we're clear, Americano,
she's got no electricity
and no running water.
Septic's out, too, but there's
an outhouse in the woods.
- It's perfect. A hundred
bucks a month. - $200.
A hundred bucks a month.
Deal.
But I don't want growing
no drugs on the land.
No marijuana.
You got that?
- Welcome home, my friend.
- Thanks.
LINCOLN:
Listen, man, if you want
to get out of here, I'd get
it and Michael would, too.
- You've done more than
enough. - If I had a kid
in the same situation
as your son,
would you and your brother
walk out on me?
Yeah.
(laughs)
Here, this is good.
Put it down there.
Okay, hold on.
You ready?
Yeah.
I hope this works, papi.
All right, let's go.
McGrady.
I need your help.
Not now, bro- my father finally
got here; I'm gonna go see him.
Actually, uh,
I need his help, too.
What you want
from my old man?
I just need
someone to deliver
a message on the outside,
someone I can trust.
Hell, no. My papa's
straight as razor blade.
He don't get into kind
of trouble like you do.
- It's not trouble-it's just a phone call.
- No.
I love my father.
And I love my brother-
and if he doesn't
get this message, something
horrible's gonna happen to him.
Something really
bad is going on.
Please.
Hello, son.
Papa.
You look very handsome.
Like your school picture.
Gracias.
I cleaned a guy's cell
for this shirt.
You should be in school now...
It's okay, Papa.
with your friends.
Papa, please,
don't get upset.
I- I have friends in here.
The American?
Yes. He's nice.
He keeps his word-
it's very rare in Sona.
And, uh...
he needs my help.
Thank God you're here.
Thought you might have
come a little earlier,
just to make sure I was okay.
I read the newspaper;
I knew you were safe.
I am for now-
but you might not be.
Now, listen
to me carefully.
Promise me you won't go anywhere
near Lincoln Burrows today.
- Lincoln?
- It's just too dangerous
to be around him,
to be with him, to be near him.
Just go home
and stay there,
and I will call you tonight.
That's all I can say.
Do you understand?
Call me from where?
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
Promise me.
Say it out loud.
I promise.
Why are you
so scared?
Because I can't
have you get hurt.
Because I love you...
more than anything in the world.
Do you?
Yeah.
James I got a call today
from a man who said
he's your landlord.
Talking about another apartment.
Should I call him back?
Must have been
a wrong number.
He asked for you by name.
The man is clearly confused.
I don't know anything
about another apartment.
Sofia,
all I know is that you've got
to stay away from Lincoln.
Please.
(whispering):
Okay, James.
I'll wait for your call.
McGRADY'S FATHER:
Here.
I have this.
I don't want to see it.
I'll... put it with the others.
I'm not coming home.
Accept that.
You should go.
Make that call for my friend.
Happy birthday, son.
Maybe we should
pick up some locks
and secure the house.
- It can't have anything new on it.
(phone ringing) The place
needs to look abandoned.
Yeah?
McGRADY'S FATHER:
I have a message for you.
Don't come home for dinner.
Who is this?
I'm supposed to tell you,
don't come home for dinner.
What?
When me and
Mikey were kids,
we had a code when
Social Services
were trying to get me
into juvie.
He's telling me
to watch my back.
What the hell
are you doing here?
SOFIA: Why haven't you
returned my calls or my car?
SUSAN B. (over phone):
You have him?
MAN: Yeah, he just
arrived back at his hotel.
But Whistler's girl
tracked him down.
And she's talking
to Lincoln and the Mexican.
After what she saw today, she
could be complicating things.
You have a directive?
SUSAN B:
I warned her.
Take them all out.
What will Whistler say?
I said take them all out!
i don't care about
your boyfriend's apartment
on the side,
I just don't care.
SOFIA:
No, I went there.
And a woman showed up;
she threatened me.
She knows James.
Susan.
You know her?
She's the one who has LJ.
Well, she took
something I found,
a passport.
It had James' picture
and birthday
but his name said Gary Miller.
Lincoln, I don't know
what's going on.
I'll tell you
what's going on-
your boyfriend's a liar.
I told you that from the start.
James told me to stay away
from you today,
that it was dangerous.
Let's go.
Pronto.
LINCOLN: I need to speak
to Michael Scofield.
I'm his brother.
How you get this number?
He called me a few days back.
I- I didn't answer.
But, listen,
I need to speak to him now
Let's go.
You'll never guess
who that was-
Michael Scofield's brother.
Who calls me...
and who I call,
is my business.
Where are your friends?
I don't know.
I don't know,
Please don't shoot. Please.
Drop it.
Why are you coming after us?
Different day,
same problem, huh, Lincoln?
You know how it turned out
when LJ was in this position,
and today
is no different...
so be a good boy
and put down the gun.
Come on, Linc.
I know you've learned
your lesson.
You're right, I have.
MAN:
For the record,
this is an
international hearing,
requested by the
United States government,
for the purpose of hearing
testimony from one
Mr. Alexander Mahone.
You gotta be kidding me.
So, Mr. Mahone,
when were you first contacted
by anyone
from the group referred to
as the Company?
They told me...
that if I didn't kill every one
of the Fox River Eight,
that they would
come after me.
They had all worked
with-with Scofield
on-on-on the escape,
so the Company wasn't sure
what they knew.
Mr. Mahone, I'm
going to ask you
to please keep your answer
related to the question.
It's-it's
all connected.
It's just... it's-it's a web.
And-and it's a web
that I got caught in.
And-and Lincoln Burrows
got caught in,
and Michael Scofield
got caught in.
SULLINS:
I, if I may,
I think what Mr. Mahone...
We're all just like
flies... was trying to say...
Thank you, Mr. Sullins,
but we're here to hear
from Mr. Mahone.
Now, we're going
to try this again.
When were you
first contacted
by the Company?
I cannot say.
You know...
they could be in contact
with you or-or-or...
you could be in contact
with them, you'd never know.
It's-it's... they could be
in contact with us right now.
I know...
it sounds crazy, right?
It's craz...
and...
and it would be, except for
the simple fact that...
it's true.
The government that I had
dedicated my life to
manipulate
and extorted me.
Blackmailed me.
So that I would kill for them.
And I did the things
that they made me do
so I could protect my family.
And so...
I would like to go home.
So can I do that, please?
Hey.
Where have you been?
I came looking
for scrap metal for the support
brace for the tunnel.
Really?
Looks like a pretty
tight squeeze up there.
You sure there's
enough fresh air,
or does the claustrophobia
come and go?
What's it like going, through
life always distrustful?
You tell me, James.
Hate to break up
the brouhaha, gentlemen,
but Lechero
would like to see you.
Says it has something to do
with your big brother.
Give us a moment,
will you, Teodoro?
If your brother should ever
call my cell phone again,
you tell him you're
the one that's gonna pay.
(Lincoln): Yeah?
- You got the message.
- Yeah, you were right.
They just tried to
take us out.
I know.
Whistler got a visit
from the Company.
He's been acting
strange ever since.
I'm telling you, Linc,
something's up.
Doing more than
acting strange, man.
He just told Sofia
not to be
near me 'cause it's dangerous.
The Company's coming after us.
They don't need us anymore.
Here we go.
They're breaking him out
on their own.
(over radio):
We're 100 yards from the target.
Keep your eyes open.
Let's get in and out fast.
Come on
Damn!
Come on!
Keep it coming!
Hey!
Come on!
MAN:
Can't get a clean shot!
I'll get lower,
take 'em out!
Is that Scofield on the
roof with Whistler?
Is that really a question?
He's supposed to be dead.
(over radio):
Man down. Man down.
Let go!
I'm slipping.
(over radio):
We lost Whistler. Abort. Abort.
Mission failure.
Return to Base One immediately!
Alex...
I'm so sorry.
I'm going to have to
take you back to Sona.
You, get up.
Vamos!
Mr. Scofield,
there have been two escape
attempts in the past two days.
Somehow I don't think
it's a coincidence
that you arrived shortly
before they happened.
I had nothing
to do with that.
You've caused too many
problems here in Sona,
so maybe you shouldn't
be here in Sona.
Llevenlo!
Say good-bye to
Sona, Mr. Scofield.
Vamos.
www.opensubtitles.org
Prison Break S03E08
"Bang and Burn"
www.tvsubtitles.net