Previously, on Prison Break:
I want him under
24-hour surveillance.
I have to be there when
they kill this man.
The least you could do
is review his case.
VICE PRESIDENT:
Terrence.
The thing I can't
quite figure is
with the the crap storm
this thing's become
why they haven't killed you.
Have at him.
( stabbing )
( screaming )
Now, out of respect
for what you once were,
I'm going to let
you walk away.
( shouting )
Why don't you hand me
that shank you're holding?
I'm not even sure
why you need it.
Thank you.
Your keys are right over there
by your in-box.
You got a maintenance guy
waiting outside here,
says you want him
to change the locks.
Want me to
call him off?
No, send him in.
It's your last chance,
Tweener.
Scofield
and his whole PI crew...
They're escaping.
You know I can't
let you leave here, boss.
dogs
The numerous times
I've been apprehended
while trying to elude
the authorities
it's always because
of the damn dogs.
Turns out you can run from just
about everything
in your life
'cept your own particular stink.
Yeah, Well, some of us
stink more than others.
Kinte,
you can smell
like a bouquet of bonbons,
but unless you get rid
of your smell
you might as well
send a note to the police
with directions
and some cab fare.
Theodore's right, man.
We got to scrub down our cells.
What about our bunks?
Pillows, sheets, everything.
Either get rid of your smell
or change it.
Well, how much time we got?
MICHAEL:
John?
Three days. That's the soonest
I could get us
into the Guards' Room for PI.
You think you'll have
the extra suits by then?
Probably. They should
be here tomorrow.
Good, so we're good to go.
All we got left is figuring out
how to get through
that door in the infirmary.
And how to get Linc
out of that box.
And you can do
that in three days?
Three days should
be plenty of time.
We got to get out of here.
Now.
ow
how he found it.
He just did.
SUCRE:
The hole's just sitting there?
I covered it the best I
could, but it's just
a matter of time before someone
discovers
Bellick's missing.
What do you mean
Bellick's missing?
SUCRE:
Okay, okay, okay.
Fox River is a big place.
Maybe they won't
notice for a while.
Nothing happens around here
without Bellick's say-so.
Somebody is gonna notice
that he's missing.
And when they do, they're gonna
close this place down
until they find him.
What are we going to do?
As soon as it gets dark...
we go.
SUCRE:
Tonight?
Pretty, we ain't ready
to escape tonight.
Escape already started.
It started the minute
Bellick found that hole.
It's gonna end the minute they
figure out that he's missing.
Then stay!
I'll be sure to read
the papers in the morning.
See how many years you got
when they realized
which crew was working
in that room
and dug that hole.
So what's the play, man?
You think you can have the plane
ready by tonight?
Sure.
You had kitchen
duty, right?
Yeah.
What'd you use
to scrub down the floors?
I think it was some peroxide
or something like that.
That'll work. Get as
much as you can.
I'll work on getting us
that key to the infirmary.
The rest of you find
whatever you can
to get rid
of the scent
in your cells.
None of this matters, if we
can't get in the guards' room.
We're gonna leave after dinner,
during tier time
when the gates are open.
7:00, one by one,
through my cell.
Whoa,
whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Now, we were supposed
to go through
the guards' room.
That was going to give us
a head start hours before
they even found out
we were missing.
T-BAG:
We leave through your cell,
we ain't got no lead time.
7:00. Count's
at 8:00, that's...
60 minutes.
60 minutes to get over that wall
and as far away
from here as possible.
They'll be right on our asses.
PATTERSON:
Quit your talkin'
and start your walkin'.
Ladies, yard time is over!
They already are.
Let's go, let's go.
SUCRE:
You know, there's one thing
we didn't talk about
out there-- your brother.
I mean, he's under
24-hour surveillance.
I'm just saying, if you
can't get to him by tonight,
we still have to go,
you know that, right?
( buzzer )
Hey, boss.
What do you want?
My brother's in Gen Pop.
He's got no clue
I was in an accident.
So?
Well, is there any way
I can get a message to him?
Yeah.
Put it in your will.
And you're sure
all those dots connect?
Okay.
Thank you.
Who was that?
A friend of mine
at the title company, handled
a lot of my firm's business.
She dug up an address for that
phone number in Blackfoot.
Where is it?
It's not the where that's
interesting, it's the how.
It turns out our little
place in Montana
was purchased for $2 million
by an offshore
holding corporation.
That's pretty standard
for a transaction
that size, though, right?
Sure. Only this
holding corporation
was bankrolled by a trust--
a trust financed by the estate
of Terrence Steadman.
Looks like you and I
are going to Blackfoot, Montana.
( muffled yelling )
Have you seen
Bellick today?
No, Why?
Mack was asking.
I guess he ain't showed up yet.
He's probably just late.
Bellick? I haven't beat that guy
to work in eight years.
Scofield, this ain't
Gibson's. Move it.
They're already starting
to ask questions, man.
We're not going to make it
out of here in seven hours
without them
finding answers.
How we coming with
that peroxide?
I'm going to need it before
we meet up for yard duty.
Probably not till later.
You want to tell me
what you need it for?
Makkos, you going
to be eating them there
brussels sprouts?
No.
You mind if I, uh...
Take 'em.
They smell like crap.
Do they, now?
What's up?
Yo, if you...
Tonight.
What?
Change of plans.
Why, did something happen?
Just find Sucre.
He'll tell you
what you need to do to be ready.
What about...?
Tonight.
MAN:
What the hell's going on?
The president changed his mind.
We were given
assurances
he would veto
the energy bill.
Assurances can tell
you everything
that a man is going to do,
until he wakes up in the morning
and changes his mind.
Then change it back.
I don't think you understand.
The president...
Have you enjoyed
our support?
Yes.
Good.
We certainly wouldn't want
you to take it for granted.
Are you threatening me?
Why?
Do you feel
threatened?
Caroline, we've all
been through this before.
The ebbs and flows of
political conscience,
but we've found at the end
of the day, we get what we want.
It's simply a matter
of who helps us get it.
If you can't convince
a doddering old fool
finishing up
his second term
what the best thing is
for this country's economy,
perhaps you're not the kind
of helper we're looking for.
Sara...
I was thinking
about something...
Enough, Michael.
Enough with the-the lies
and the coincidences
and the stories, all of it.
It's not what you think.
I know what you did.
The question is, are you
man enough to admit it?
The keys.
Congratulations.
Is that the first time
you've been honest with me?
It's not...
The second?
What are you after,
Michael?
Is it drugs?
Is it needles?
Neither.
Then what?
Please understand
that I never meant...
I never wanted
to involve you in this.
Well, you've done
a pretty poor job of that.
I came here to
tell you something.
I'm getting my brother
out of here.
Tonight.
And I need your help.
Michael, uh, honestly,
for your own good,
don't say anything more.
You know
he's innocent.
Do what you're talking about
and he won't be.
But he'll still be alive.
You understand that
I'm required to report
everything you're telling me.
Yes.
Then why would you?
Because you're the only one
that can help.
And because I know
you want to be part
of the solution.
Yeah, aiding and abetting
is not part of the solution.
Neither is doing nothing
knowing what you know
about his case.
How dare you put this on me.
I did what I could.
I gave my father
the information from...
No offense
to your father,
but the people who
are framing Lincoln,
let's just say they have
a higher security clearance.
So now it's a conspiracy?
I didn't come here
to have a debate.
You're asking me
to break the law.
I'm asking you
to make a mistake.
Not hurt anyone,
not steal anything.
Just...
forget to lock up.
Leave the door
unlocked when you
leave tonight.
That's it.
Please.
This is where
you're breaking out of?
This room?
There are alarm contacts
on the glass
surrounding the door.
Otherwise I wouldn't
need you to...
I was part of your plan.
Was it all an act?
At first,
yes.
I needed
to be here.
But then I wanted
to be here with you.
Right.
And it's killing me to know
that you'll never believe that.
Whatever you may
think of me,
this is about Lincoln.
Don't make him pay
for my mistakes.
( cell phone rings )
( ringing )
Yeah?
Hi, it's me.
There's been an acceleration.
How fast we talking about?
Fast. Tonight.
Son of a bitch.
I think what you're trying to
say is no problem?
Yeah, of course.
It'll be taken care of.
Good.
The van?
Waiting up Fitz Street,
200 yards...
Behind the old mill?
Behind the old mill, I got it.
One question, John.
Don't you want a bigger plane?
You've only got three seats.
I thought you said there were
seven or eight guys.
Well, not everybody
gonna have a ticket.
You gonna tell me who is?
The three of us still breathing.
Two tickets.
Whatever airport's
closer to Blackfoot.
Aisle, window,
it doesn't matter,
just get us on the next flight.
( cell phone rings )
Yeah, I'll hold.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello?
Change of plans.
We're going to need you
to have the girl
at the airstrip tonight.
Tonight?
Was I not enunciating?
No, it's just that, uh...
things could get messy.
So wear a smock.
( men chuckling )
Patterson and
Pope's secretary?
Come on, man, like you
wouldn't hit that.
I don't know, Vegas,
2:00 a.m. maybe, but...
if she didn't have
such a big booty.
Man, the booty is
the man's biggest weakness.
I know I would've hit it.
( muffled yell )
( muffled yelling )
Find a way to
the infirmary yet?
I'm working on it.
Yo, you seen Bellick today?
Not yet.
I need to talk to him.
Do you know if
he went somewhere?
Do I look like
his mother?
The guy hasn't
shown up yet.
You sure he ain't
showed yet?
'Cause I thought I saw him
here this morning, man.
WESTMORELAND:
Tweener.
Need a hand over here.
Yeah, I'm on it.
All right?
Fine.
Just, uh...
just sore, that's all.
You live to my age,
you'll know all about it.
You know you got
a couple foxes
in your hen house, right?
Who are we talking about?
The bastard
and the born again.
They both want out of here.
They'll behave
until then.
Think so?
I just picked this
off of T-Bag yesterday.
If I would've been there
ten seconds later,
they'd have been serving
Abruzzi with red sauce
over at the morgue.
Now I know you want to be
shot caller and everything,
and that's cool,
but you got to handle
things, man.
Are you picking up
what I'm putting down?
Yeah.
Look, this is it, man.
Ain't no do-overs
this time.
Can't be no complications.
We break out tonight
or we ain't never
getting out.
We got that paperwork
in from the county.
Sara?
Yeah. Sorry.
The paperwork
from the county.
Right.
I got it.
Um... do me a favor,
could you take care
of that for me?
I got to get
out of here.
Sure.
Thanks.
Wait, where are
you going?
Out.
Put your blues on
over your PI gear.
What?
Just do it.
You want to tell us why?
If we don't have time to get
the suits we need,
we're gonna have
to make them.
What the hell
are you doing, man?
We got company.
It's okay.
He's coming with us.
( locker slams )
Hey, whatever happened to
"We got too many
people"?
When the plan changed,
so did the timing.
We'll make sure
we all get through.
Well, for health
reasons, information
like that should be
disseminated
a little more pronto.
Uh-uh, Fish.
One more person means
there's one more thing
that can go wrong.
He is not coming.
It's not up
for discussion.
The hell it ain't.
I owe him.
I don't owe you a damn thing.
You're gonna...
if we get nailed
'cause you didn't want
to cut down on
your damn guest list.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
Hey.
Hold up, cons.
I saw some drops of blood on
the floor of the PI locker room.
Now who's going to tell
me what's going on?
That'd be me, boss.
I, uh, did it
while I was
loading some equipment
back into the shed.
You make sure and
get that patched up.
Will do.
Okay.
Move it.
Are you okay?
Okay enough to make it
out of here tonight.
I swear.
( mouthing )
Hey, Shelly, this is, uh,
it's me.
I, listen, I know I'm supposed
to call you as my sponsor
in case I have a, um...
Um...
( wood snaps )
Whoa!
Right.
I think we should break
a bottle of champagne
across its bow.
Well, if you're intending
to get this thing home
for your anniversary tonight,
I wouldn't recommend it.
No!
Listen, I want you to know
that I... well,
I feel very fortunate
to have met you.
Yeah. I'm guessing not
many structural engineers
make their way
into Fox River.
No, no, I don't mean
because of your vocation.
I mean because you're
a decent young man
and there are not
many of those
who make their way
into Fox River.
Well, for what it's worth,
there are a few down there.
Well, that's good to hear.
Listen, I know this goes
without saying,
but, uh... if there's
anything you need...
well, let's just say
that I owe you one.
Actually... there is one thing
you can do for me.
LINCOLN:
So this whole thing
this whole time,
was never about me.
It was about Dad.
I can't believe...
Michael?
Michael!
What?
You got something you want
to tell me?
Just told you everything
we knew about Dad was a lie
and you barely blinked.
We have to go.
Tonight.
What are you talking about?
Bellick found the hole, so
either we go now or it's over.
Michael...
Look, I know it's
going to be tight,
but I can do this.
Michael, stop it.
The chains on your locks,
they're, uh...
Michael! Michael!
I can do this!
Listen to me!
Go.
You gotta go.
Don't say that.
Look at me!
You can't do this.
There's not enough time.
If you stay here,
they'll nail you
and you'll rot in here.
I'm not asking you, man,
I'm telling you.
Leave me behind.
Go.
What the hell
you think you doing?
Nothing, man.
You trying to run something
for those Wonder Breads
you been running around with?
No, it ain't
even like that.
Tell me something, boy.
Is you steppin',
or is you fetchin'?
I thought I made
myself clear when I said
your punk ass
was no longer in business.
This ain't business, all right?
This is personal.
What you got there anyway?
Some kind of cleaner?
What you trying
to clean up...
Sergeant Franklin?
( grunts )
( crack )
nancy?
NANCY:
Rumors coming out
of Vice President Reynolds' camp
detail a preliminary
short list of running mates
should she, as expected,
win her party's nomination.
Perhaps the biggest surprise
is the inclusion
of Illinois governor
Frank Tancredi.
His consideration
is attributed
to his reputation for being
tough on crime.
And some point to his recent
refusal to grant clemency
to Lincoln Burrows,
the murderer of the vice
president's brother,
which was welcomed
with deep appreciation
from within
the Oval Office.
ANCHOR:
Thanks, Nancy.
Locally, a jackknifed big rig
blocked traffic on the...
What the hell
are you doing, John?
The Lord's work.
The Lord wants you
to spread horse crap
all over your mattress?
It's not our place
to question His will.
Are we clear?
( inmates talking )
Let's cut
the chatter, convict.
Open on 88!
Yo, what's that?
Avocado's gear.
He's getting out
of the infirmary tonight.
Tonight?
So you got plenty of time
to bake him a cake.
Hey...
I heard you were asking
Patterson about Bellick.
Said you thought you
saw him this morning?
Yeah. I was.
No, it was yesterday.
That's when I saw him.
You sure?
Yeah.
You know, time just sort
of blends together up in here.
All right.
Close on 88!
What am I supposed
to do with this?
Pour it in the toilet.
You got C-Note to steal
some peroxide
from the kitchen
so we can clean the toilet?
We got to get all of us
into psych ward tonight
to access the pipes.
A bunch of cons wearing
their prison blues
would stick out
like a sore thumb.
But the inmates
in the psych ward
all wear...
White.
Peroxide acts as a bleach.
Camouflage.
Just a few more hours now.
Looks like we got
everything we need...
Everything except your brother.
You worry about the suits.
I'll worry about Linc.
Could you, uh, give
us a couple of minutes?
Of course,
Mr. President.
You probably know
why I'm here.
If I were
a betting man,
I have a pretty
good idea where
I'd lay my chips.
The energy bill, Richard.
Why did you change your mind?
You've been saying for months
it's so full of pork
the damn thing's
ready to squeal, and
now all of a sudden...
Yes, the bill is flawed, but
it's better than doing nothing.
Frankly, I find it
a little curious
that you're here,
telling me to veto a bill
you voted in favor of.
You're on the way out.
Some of us need
to think ahead.
Actually, I've been doing
some thinking ahead
as well, Caroline--
specifically, about
my endorsement.
What?!
I'm considering
making a switch,
throwing my weight
behind Senator Challis.
You can't do that.
Can't I?
Caroline,
you are everything
that's wrong with politics.
You vote not
to legislate change,
but to profit.
You run not to make
a difference,
but to make demands.
You put me on your ticket
not because
I share your views,
but because I didn't
share your gender.
So don't take
the moral high ground.
We all know how
this game is played.
Richard, please, I...
Good day, Caroline.
Richard!
R-Richard!
( sighs )
You know what I got
my wife for our anniversary?
What?
A scarf.
Well, this is a big one for me.
I had to do something special.
Okay, let's get this thing
down to the car.
We'll do it all together
on three.
Ready? One...
two... three.
Upsie...
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Put it down,
put it down, put it down.
Oh...
All right, get Scofield up here
right away!
( splashing )
It's working.
All right, get 'em out
and get 'em dry.
We got to get 'em on
under our clothes
before tier time,
which is in... 45 minutes.
You think everyone else
will be ready?
We don't have a choice.
As soon as the gate's open,
we go.
We're going to need
every second.
MACK:
Open on 40.
Scofield, Pope needs
to see you, ASAP.
Now?
What for?
A Bar Mitzvah. Let's go.
( whispering ):
It's 6:18, bro.
You can't...
MACK:
Now.
Hey, Pretty-- Tick Tock.
( indistinct conversation )
Excuse me a minute.
( sighs ):
Sara, to what do I owe
the pleasure?
I guess to
congratulations.
Can't believe I had to hear
about it on the news.
Oh, the VP thing--
well, that's just talk.
Is it?
Yeah. What was it
your mother used to say?
"It's always nice
to be invited to the dance,
even if you don't have
the right shoes."
Yeah.
She also used to say,
"You're father's a lying
bastard," but I figured
that was just
the booze talking.
You know, it's always nice
to see you, Sara.
Is there something
that you needed,
or did you just
come by to...
Just tell me something.
Did you... did you look at
the information I gave you
from Lincoln
Burrows' attorneys?
Sweetheart, move on.
The man's attorneys had a window
to present new evidence--
they didn't.
Now that window is closed.
I just need to know, did you
look at the information?
Come on, Sara.
Answer me.
I swear, working at Fox River
has changed you.
You're always saying
you want to make a difference?
At that place?
It's too late.
You should be a teacher,
so that you can get
to these people
before they become...
Did you look at
the information?
I didn't need to.
I supported the findings
of the court.
If you have a problem
with the verdict,
go after them.
But before you do, I suggest
you look at the guy's rap sheet
and ask yourself if the world
will be a better place
with Lincoln Burrows
walking the streets.
Just tell me one thing--
did they promise you
the vice presidency
before or after
you signed his
death warrant?
I will not discuss morality
with an addict and a thief.
You want to talk
reality, Sara?
How many times did I use
my influence to keep
you and one of your junky
boyfriends out of jail?
How many?
Was it three, four times?
I swear, Sara, it's
funny, you know?
You have no trouble whatsoever
with me bending the law...
especially when it's bent
in your direction.
Grow up.
PATTERSON:
You talk to that Tweener kid?
STOLTE:
Yeah, he says he got
his days mixed up,
but I don't know.
What?
Something about
the way he said it.
Oh, come on, man, Bellick's
just taking a personal.
I don't want to get
the guy busted.
And if he's not?
I'm just saying, it's 6:30
and no one's heard from the guy.
We got to tell Pope.
Okay. I'll tell him.
VERONICA:
Did you call the cab
for the airport?
No, not yet.
Why not?
Come on, the flight
leaves in an hour.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm starting to think
that us going to Montana
might not be
a good move.
What are you talking about?
What if you are right,
and the smoking gun
is in that house?
You think they're just
gonna let us walk in there
and make a citizen's arrest?
Look, Nick,
I don't know what
your deal is lately,
but I'm getting on that plane
with or without you.
i can't let u do it
All this time
you were one of them?
Who's pulling
your leash, Nick?
Steadman? Kellerman?
Look at me.
I want you to remember
my face when you do whatever
the hell it is you're gonna do.
Look at me!
You're a coward.
( door opens )
Ah, Scofield's
outside, sir.
POPE:
Okay.
I want you to try
every number we have
for Brad Bellick--
try his home first.
His mother
usually answers.
Mrs. Bellick?
Hi. Uh, one moment, please.
I have Warden Pope here
for you.
Mrs. Bellick?
No cause for alarm, no, no.
We just... we haven't seen him,
and we were wondering
if he might be home
under the weather.
So Brad called you when
he pulled in this morning?
And he said he was here?
Okay, well, uh,
thank you, Mrs. Bellick.
We'll keep you posted.
I'm sure he's fine.
Radio Mack.
Have him check the parking lot
for Bellick's truck.
If he finds it,
have him call me immediately.
BECKY:
457.
This is base.
What's your 20?
MARICRUZ:
I'm pregnant, Fernando.
I'm gonna have your son.
But all I know is
that I'm really scared.
I'm really scared
to do this alone.
John, it's never too late.
If you'll agree to accept
Christ into your heart
and turn from your sin,
He will forgive you
and save you in eternity.
Where's Fibonacci?
I'll give you Fibonacci
when the time is right.
The time is right now.
No, the time is right
when you and I
are both standing
outside those walls.
I'm gonna get
out of here someday,
and when I do...
...don't think I won't remember
what your front steps look like,
Susie.
( spits )
C-NOTE:
I'm... being shipped back off.
How many times I got to say it?
You only got
one thing I need.
POPE:
I've got some bad news,
Charles.
Your daughter's got
esophageal cancer,
and she wants to see you
while there's still time.
How long does she have?
Hospital says a week.
( soft, gasping breaths )
( pained groan )
( gasping breaths )
( electrical buzzing )
POPE:
I read somewhere where
the actual Taj Mahal
appears pink in the morning,
milky white in the evening,
and golden
when the moon shines.
The changes, they say,
depict the different emotions
of a woman.
I can tell you something,
if we don't get this
thing fixed tonight,
I don't want to know
what kind of emotion
my wife is gonna have
if I walk through that door
empty-handed.
It's strange-- I mean,
it just gave way.
We lifted it up, and
the support beam snapped.
What's this?
The support.
The one that holds up that beam.
You took it?
I'm sorry...
but I needed to get
back in here.
I-I-I don't understand,
why would you...
I'm breaking out.
And you're gonna make sure
my brother goes with me.
www.tvsubtitles.net