That's it.
Can I just, you know, look at it for a minute?
You're an artist, Sid.
You're telling me you're just gonna walk out of here and I'm never going to see it again.
There's a good chance of that, yes.
Most guys, you know, for the first one, they start with something small.
"Mom", girlfriend's initials, something like that.
Not you.
You get a full set of sleeves, all in a couple of months.
Takes guys a few years to get the ink you got.
I don't have a few years.
Wish to hell I did.
The vault. Open it.
We can't. The branch manager's not here.
Where is he?
It's lunchtime. He's at White Castle.
White Castle?
It's a fast food restaurant.
They serve those little square burgers.
I know what it is.
I'm not playing games. Open it.
Sir, you have a half a million dollars cash in your bag.
Don't you think it would be better...?
This is the police. You are completely surrounded.
Put down your weapon.
Put down your weapon now.
Rarely in the case of armed robbery do we hear a plea of no contest.
Are you sure about this, Mr. Scofield?
I'm sure, Your Honor.
Your Honor, we'd like to recess if we could.
My client's a bit confused at the moment.
- I'm not, Your Honor.
- He is, Your Honor.
Perhaps you should heed your representation's advice,
take some additional time to consider your response.
I've already done that, Your Honor.
I'll retire to my chambers to determine sentencing.
Court's recessed until 1:30.
Come on, Let's go.
Uncle Mike?
I didn't want you to come.
Go home, LJ.
I didn't want you to see this.
He's not gonna take this well.
Can you blame him? He's your nephew.
He's beginning to get that anybody he attaches himself to is gonna end up in prison...
and he's not the only one who's starting to feel that way, Michael.
Will you give us a minute?
One minute.
Don't you understand?
You just put the book in that woman's hand
and she's gonna lob it at you like a grenade.
Justice and punishment are the same thing to her.
I know.
Then will you please tell me what's going through your head?
We've been over this.
I've known you my entire life.
You don't have a violent bone in your body,
and I know you didn't need the money.
Veronica.
Why won't you let me help you?
You've been good to me. My whole life, you have...
but you've gotta let me deal with this. Okay?
Given your lack of prior criminal conduct,
I am inclined toward probation.
However, the fact that you discharged a deadly weapon
during the commission of the crime suggests malice to me.
For that reason,
I find it incumbent that you see the inside of a prison cell, Mr. Scofield.
It says here that you've requested to be incarcerated
somewhere near your home here in Chicago.
I'm willing to honor that.
The closest level one facility to...
Level one?
That's maximum security, Your Honor.
I would ask counsel to refrain from interrupting me.
As I was saying,
the closest level one facility would be Fox River State Penitentiary.
As for the term of your sentence, I'm setting it at five years.
You'll be eligible for parole in half that time.
Sentence to be carried out immediately.
All right, people, step inside the door and check yourself for bugs.
When you hear the knock, step out. Keep the line moving.
We ain't got all day to get this done.
No more talking in line.
Move it. You got less than five minutes to take a shower.
Keep the line moving. Keep it moving. Move it. Right now.
Let's go. Move, move.
Next!
Next down in the banks, dress. Let's go.
Name and back number.
Scofield, Michael. 94941.
Are you a religious man, Scofield?
Never really thought about it.
Good, 'cause the Ten Commandments don't mean a box of piss in here.
We got two commandments and two only.
The first commandment is you got nothing coming.
What's the second commandment?
See commandment number one.
Gotcha.
You talking out the side of your neck?
Come  again?
I said, are you being a smartass?
Just trying to fly low, avoid the radar, boss.
Do my time... and get out.
There isn't any flying under my radar.
Good to know.
Hey, can a brother get some air conditioning up here, coach?
It's hotter than a crack ho's mouth, man.
To  hell with the A.C., man. Give me the crack ho.
Come on!
Yo, Fish! What you looking at?
You look kind of pretty to be up in here, man.
Fish!
I suggest you take a seat, Fish.
Ain't nothing to do up in here but serve time.
Ain't nobody gonna serve it for you.
Welcome to Prisneyland, Fish.
You wanna talk about it?
No, it's not worth talking about.
If it's keeping you up, it is.
Oh, it's just...
it's nothing, you know.
Michael's case.
You did the best you could.
Yeah, but he didn't.
He just sort of rolled over. He didn't put up a fight.
It's not like him.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't be talking about him.
Hey, if it's on your mind, it's on your mind, right?
Good night.
All wings, guard coming out.
Trey Street Deuces got the hoops.
Nortenos got the bleachers.
Woods got the weight pile.
The C.O.s got the rest.
I'm telling you,
the guards are the dirtiest gang in this whole place.
The only difference between us and them...
is the badge.
Who's the pet lover?
He'll deny it, but he's D.B. Cooper.
Parachuted out of a plane 30 years ago with a million and a half in cash.
Doesn't look like the type.
Who does?
Hey! What up, Wholesale? You okay?
Gonna be greater later.
Yeah.
What you doing with this fish, man?
He's my new cellie.
Wholesale's got it wired up out of commissary.
Anything you want, he can get it for you.
You keep handing out my jacket,
I swear I'm gonna bust your grape.
Man, you couldn't bust a grape in Napa with a set of cleats on.
What are you talking about?
Man, you want to bump your gums.
Oh, no, no. Now you're talking, talking, talking...
I'm looking for someone.
Guy named Lincoln Burrows.
Linc the Sink?
That  what they're calling him now?
Yeah.
As in, he'll come at you with everything but the kitchen... Snowflake.
Where can I find him?
Man killed the vice-president's brother.
and in a month, he's getting the chair,
which means no one up this river is more dangerous than him,
'cause he's got nothing to lose now.
What are they gonna do? Kill him twice?
There a way I can get to him?
Oh, no. The only time those boys get out is for chapel and P.I.
- PI? What's that?|- Prison Industry.
The guys that get along, get to work.
You know, painting, scrapping, making mattresses, you name it.
I wouldn't get excited, though, if I were you, Fish.
You ain't sniffing none of P.I.
Why's that?
'Cause John Abruzzi runs it.
John Abruzzi John Abruzzi?
John Abruzzi John Abruzzi.
Why you wanna see Burrows so bad anyhow?
Because he's my brother.
They denied the motion.
Then do it again.
I can't. That's it.
May 11. That's the date, man.
That's the date they, uh... you know... execute me.
I know.
I didn't kill that man, Michael.
The evidence says you did.
I don't care what the evidence says. I didn't kill him.
Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
But how did they get it wrong then?
The courts, the appeals...
Don't know. Don't know.
I keep thinking, looking back on it is, uh... I was set up.
And, whoever it was that set me up
wants me in the ground as quickly as possible.
What's another word for "love"?
What's the context?
Oh, you know.
The "I love you so much
"I ain't never knocking over a liquor store again" context.
Except, you know, classy.
Mmm.
I'm proposing to my girl, if you gotta know.
In a letter?
You got a better way?
Face-to-face works pretty good.
This place ain't exactly the romantic spot.
I'm gonna have her go get on the Staten Island Ferry.
Then, once she can see the Empire State Building,
She opens the letter.
It's like almost being there.
Except for the fact that I won't be there.
Try "passion."
Ooh! Ooh! "Passion. Passion" That's dope. Passion.
How do you spell that? Is it "pash..."?
No "h"?
LJ, hold up. Hold up.
I don't think I can go through with this.
Everything's going to be fine. Trust me.
We understand each other, then?
Yeah.
Friday. Not Saturday. Not Sunday. Friday.
Totally understood.
I don't want hundreds, I don't want fives, I don't want ones.
I know, I know.
Tens and 20s only.
It's on.
Police!
Abruzzi, I need you to hire me a P.I.
Beat it.
Maybe you ought to hear what I got to say.
You got nothing I need.
Wouldn't  be too sure of that.
My mistake.
Just what I need... a duck.
A P.I., Abruzzi.
You might find I can be of more assistance than you think.
Mull it over.
Come find me when you're ready to talk.
All right, guys, pick it up!
I want to get home tonight!
Maggio.
Yeah? So?
That's the son of a bitch at fingered Abruzzi.
That's Fibanacci?
I thought the punk was gone forever.
Evidently, somebody found him.
Somebody messing with us?
This you're not gonna believe.
What is it?
Tattoo looks fresh.
I guess, being a diabetic, you don't mind needles.
I'm Michael, by the way.
Scofield. I read your report.
And you are?
Dr. Tancredi will do.
Tancredi like the governor?
You're not related, are you?
Wouldn't think you'd find the daughter of Frontier Justice Frank working in a prison.
As a doctor, no less.
I believe in being part of the solution, not the problem.
Mmm. "Be the change you want to see in the world."
What?
Nothing. That was just my senior quote.
That was you?
This whole time, I was thinking it was Gandhi.
You're very funny.
Sit tight.
Put direct pressure on that. I'll be back in a sec.
So,  how do we play this?
You hook me up with a few weeks' supply?
Nice try.
No hypos on the floor.
I'm the farthest thing from a junkie. Trust me.
I got news for you, Michael.
"Trust me" means absolutely zero inside those walls.
The only way you're getting that insulin is if I'm administering it.
Guess we'll be seeing a lot of each other, then, huh?
I guess so.
We're all clear on the Burrows execution.
Good.
Except for one thing.
Bishop McMorrow is not in the fold.
He's got a lot of influence with the governor.
They went to prep school together, apparently.
Look, the closer it gets,
the more I'm worried that the bottom
is going to fall out of this whole thing.
Well, maybe it's time you arranged a visit with the good bishop then.
Look, in one month,
it will all be over.
The Son of Man must be delivered into the hands of sinful men
and be crucified
and the third day, rise again.
And they remembered his words, and so should you.
Good day, gentlemen. May God be with you.
Michael.
Why?
I'm getting you out of here.
Burrows, roll it up. Happy hour's over.
It's impossible.
Not if you design the place it isn't.
Too formal.
Too greeting card.
We gotta make a decision sooner or later, you know.
We have time;
We don't, actually.
I mean, at some point, we gotta pull the trigger on this thing.
I don't want to rush this.
We're only going to do it once. We have to get it right.
Honey, can I ask you something?
Of course.
Are you putting this off?
What do you mean?
I mean, are you having second thoughts?
No. Honey, no.
I'm not.
I don't know.
I just can't help thinking this is about...
It's  not.
I love you...
and I want to be your wife.
Passion? What were you thinking?
Hey, you went for it.
She probably thinks I went sissy up in here.
"Passion." Got more than one syllable, too much talkin'.
That's me from now on.
One-syllable Sucre.
Yes. No. Love. Hate. Love.
- Give it time.
- Are you kidding?
I proposed to her.
That doesn't take time. Si or no. One syllable, man.
She's supposed to come around for a conjugal on Tuesday.
She's always calling me beforehand, letting me know she's coming.
This time, man, I ain't heard a peep.
You spooked her.
Scofield... get it together. Pope wants to see you.
No good, Fish.
No one gets an audience with the Pope.
Not unless he's real interested in what you got going on.
Top of your class at Loyola.
Magna cum laude, in fact.
I can't help wondering what someone with your credentials
is doing in a place like this.
Took a wrong turn a few months back, I guess.
You make it sound like a traffic infraction.
Like all you did was turn the wrong way up a one-way street.
Everyone turns up one sooner or later.
The reason I called you here...
I noticed in your I-file, under occupation,
you put down 'unemployed.'
That's not true, now, is it?
I know you're a structural engineer, Scofield.
Shah Jahan built the Taj Majal as a
monument to his undying love for his wife.
My wife is quite fond of the story.
It appeals to the romantic in her.
Being married to someone in Corrections...
terrible job.
Wouldn't wish it on anyone.
And yet, in 39 years my wife has never complained.
And the worst part about it is, I've never thanked her.
So, because I couldn't say it,
I thought, you know, I could build it.
Come June, it's our 40th anniversary.
But here, look...
you see, the problem is...
I build anymore,
it's all gonna come down like a house of cards.
That's where I was hoping you could be of assistance.
For the favor, I can offer you three days of work a week in here.
And it'll keep you off the yard.
I can't do it.
Son, it's better for me to owe you one in here than it is for you to owe me one,
I can promise you that.
I'll take my chances.
Then we're through here.
Guard!
Two pounds of pot?
What were you trying to do, set a record?
It's not funny, LJ. You could be going to jail.
It's pretty obvious to me you need some guidance.
Hey.
Thanks.
From who, old Daddy Warbucks?
Give him a chance. He's a good man.
We got nothing in common.
Where is this coming from, LJ?
Last semester you were getting almost all A's and now...
It's your father, isn't it?
I don't have a father.
It wasn't an immaculate conception, honey. Trust me.
Maybe it's time we went and saw him.
Mom...
Ma...
Don't.
I'm about as excited by the prospect as you are,
but something's gotta give.
You have got too much potential to be screwing up your life like this.
What if they'd sent you to Taylorville or Marion and not here?
I think I'd be doing the same thing I'm doing here.
Eating Jell-O, drinking Kool-Aid...
I know what you're doing.
It's not luck of the draw that you're in here with Lincoln.
You forget I know you. Both of you.
You two have the most dysfunctional idea of love I've ever seen.
What, he beats you up to keep you off the streets,
so you get yourself tossed into Fox River with him?
To what?
Save him?
I deserve to know. I loved him as much as you did.
Past tense for you, maybe. Not me.
I gave him a shot when I got back from college. I did.
Even with all the stuff that was going on with him,
I did everything I could to make it work. And he threw it away.
You ever think maybe he was hurt that you left in the first place?
Don't do this.
Whatever it is you're doing, don't do it.
There's a better way. I'm already appealing your case.
I told you to leave alone...
I've gotten in touch with the diocese about Lincoln. The bishop...
That won't stop it. It'll only delay it.
You want to do something?
You find out who's trying to bury him.
Nobody's trying to bury him.
The evidence was there.
The evidence was cooked.
Visiting hours are now over.
Take care of yourself.
Someone wants him dead, Veronica.
Something more is going on here.
This is desperation, Michael. You're grabbing at straws. You're in denial.
Maybe. But I can't watch him die. I won't do that.
Gentlemen...
What is it about the Burrows situation that I can help you with?
It's our understanding that you have great influence with the governor.
I wouldn't say it's great or influence.
We're friends.
It's also our understanding that you oppose the death penalty.
I'm a man of God. How could I not?
In this case, we're hoping you'll suspend that position.
At least temporarily.
If the inmate appeals to me for intervention,
how can I turn my back on him?
You have a habit of answering a question with a question.
And you have a way of asking questions that beg more questions.
Are you saying you won't do it?
I'm not a man to equivocate.
You're what...
62 years old now, Your Excellency.
That's right.
I would assume, then,
that you'd be well-versed in how our government's tax system works.
Taking personal capital gains under the church's tax shelter...
well, that would be fraud, wouldn't it, Your Excellency?
I will not be cowed into forsaking my beliefs.
Not by you or anyone else.
Admirable.
Good day, Excellency.
Mr. Kellerman...
What is it about this case that the Secret Service is so interested in?
The man killed the vice-president's brother.
- What'd he say?
- You heard me.
Someone found Fibanacci.
I'm looking at the photos right now.
Son of a bitch has a beard, sunglasses...
Witness Protection, if I ever saw.
Who was this someone?
There's no return address on the envelope.
Just... this folded-up bird made of paper.
Like origami?
Yeah, like that.
Like origami.
You're Charles Westmoreland, right?
Do I know you?
I knew your wife before she passed.
- You knew Marla?
- You mean Anne?
How'd you know her?
We talked together in Boston.
- East Farmington.
- You mean West Wilmington?
No more tests.
I promise.
Seems you know everything about me.
- Who are you?
- Michael Scofield.
How'd you get it in here?
First off, she's not an it.
She's Marilyn and she's grandfathered
back from the days when prisoners were allowed a creature comfort or two.
I heard you were D.B. Cooper.
Every new fish comes in here,
first thing they hear,
is that Charles Westmoreland is D.B. Cooper.
I'll tell you like I tell them...
You want the Cooper story?
I can't give it to you, 'cause I'm not him.
It's too bad.
Sort of wish it was true. The man's a legend.
Nowhere near as much as I wish it was true, friend.
I'd have a million-five waiting for me on the outside.
I'd put some grass under 'em if I were you.
This thing would go a whole lot easier if you'd just hire me.
What is this all about?
Say you were able to get outside those walls?
Would you have the people in place to make sure you disappeared forever?
- Why do you care?
- Just curious.
Where's Fibanacci?
That's not the way it works.
They come at me, John...
I'm coming after you.
I doubt it.
Fight, fight, fight...
I totally misjudged you, Scofield.
I didn't think you were agitating type.
Behavior like that will not be tolerated in my prison.
90 days in the SHU!
That ought to be enough time to convince you of that fact.
90 days.
That's right.
Something you want to say?
It's just...
I'm not of much value to you in the SHU.
Value?
Hm-mm... the Taj.
It'd be a shame for the 8th wonder of the modern world to collapse
because the stress is improperly propagated.
Improperly propagated?
Improperly propagated.
The joints are overloaded.
They won't provide anywhere near
the sheer strength the completed structure will need.
How much work are we talking?
You want it by when, in June?
Yes.
Then we'd better get started, wouldn't you say?
Who's there?
Bishop McMorrow was killed last night.
Someone shot him while he was sleeping.
I thought you'd want to know.
Thanks.
Michael was right.
Sink, you got a visitor.
He was arrested.
For what?
Possession of marijuana.
I figured he could use some fatherly advice before it's...
Gone forever.
I didn't mean that.
I know you didn't. Thanks, Lisa.
Sit down.
Dope, huh?
Using or dealing?
What's the difference?
Then what, you, uh,
think it gives you some kind of street cred?
You got a piece of the good life. Take advantage.
Look, I get it.
The whole thing.
She drags me in here,
you give me a big speech, I walk away a changed man.
Straight "A's."
Harvard. Grow up and be a dentist.
It's better than being here.
You got to realize who's getting punished
when you're doing the things you're doing.
You think it's me; it's you.
I did the same thing--
punished the old man 'cause he was gone.
Look where it got me.
I'm not asking you to love me.
I already screwed up that chance long ago.
I'm asking you to love yourself.
You can still put the brakes on this thing.
So, that's what fatherly advice is like.
Where are you going?
I got homework.
They're putting me to death, LJ.
In a month's time, I'll be dead. You get that?
You're already dead to me.
Yes.
What? You mean yes yes?
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
Oh, there's just one thing.
Of course.
My mom say we gotta wait till you get out.
Of course, mi amor.
She wants it to be in in a church.
Okay. Esta bien.
A Catholic church.
Wouldn't want to mess with the Catholic roots, would we?
You went to Loyola.
You've been checking up on me.
I like to get to know my patients.
I went to Northwestern. Graduated two years after you did.
Maybe we met before-- you know, drunk, out at a bar somewhere.
I would have remembered.
- That a compliment?
- No.
What?
Your blood glucose is at 50 milligrams per deciliter.
So?
That's hypoglycemic.
Your body's reacting to the insulin like you're not a diabetic.
You're sure it's Type One diabetes you've got?
Ever since I was a kid.
All right.
You're not experiencing any tingling sensation, cold sweats or...
Infirmary.
Yes.
Yeah. I did.
No, I did and I do; I need them.
Okay. Um, great, well, I'll call him after lunch, then.
Thanks; I'm with a patient. Okay.
I'd like to run some tests next time you're in.
Last thing I want is to be administering insulin to a man who doesn't need it.
Yeah; sure.
Okay.
How'd you get here, by the way?
Oh, you know.
I don't; that's why I asked.
- You know. Hector.
- What?!
I didn't have any money for the bus, so he offered me a ride.
He was really sweet.
Honey, he's just a friend.
No, he's not "just a friend."
I know Hector; I know men.
Men and women can't be friends.
A guy doesn't drive a girl 500 miles across state lines
because he wants to be friends.
Casanova, wrap it up.
Hey, you got nothing to worry about, okay? It's you I'm marrying.
It's not you I'm worried about.
16 more months.
I love you.
Be easy, son, all right?
Sucre tells me you're the local pharmacy.
What you need, man?
Fugnac.
I only speak English, white boy.
It's an insulin blocker.
Standard over-the-counter variety. You can get it at any pharmacy.
You can get that at medical then.
I can't get it at medical.
Why not?
Because they're already giving me insulin shots.
You're one mixed-up cracker, you know that?
Can you get it for me, or not?
Only if you tell me why it is that you want to keep going back up to medical
to get a insulin shot for which you don't need.
I like the ambiance.
Uh-huh.
We in business?
Scofield. I don't know what you did,
but Abruzzi wanted me to give you this P.I. card.
Congratulations.
You just joined the ranks of the employed.
Kudos, Fish.
You got spine.
All right, cons, break it down!
Move it, guys.
Saw Veronica came by yesterday.
Still engaged to that guy?
Yup.
Could have been me.
If you hadn't self-destructed.
You think I meant to knock up Lisa Rex?
I was just being stupid. Hurt.
Shouldn't have pushed her away, though.
You pushed everyone away.
I'm an anchor.
All I'll do is drag him down with me.
Why did you hire him?
Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
You mean what you said earlier?
I'm not here on vacation; trust me.
Getting outside these walls, that's just the beginning.
You're going to need money.
I'll have it.
And people on the outside--
people that can help you disappear.
I've already got them.
They just don't know it yet.
Look, whatever you got going on, fill me in,
'cause I'm in the dark here.
Chaparral Associates got the contract to retrofit this place in '99.
$4 million contract. Head partner couldn't crack it.
So, he subcontracted out--
an under-the-table sort of deal with a former associate.
That guy was one of the partners in my firm.
We basically ghost-wrote the whole plan--
crossed the "t's," dotted the "i's," grouted the tiles.
You've seen the blueprints.
Better than that.
I've got them on me.
Are you kidding me?
Am I supposed to be seeing something here?
Look closer.
Transcript: RaceMan
Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net