Previously on Prison Break...
This is an overview.
That's just the beginning of
what's on here.
You honor your side
of the agreement,
and I will do
the unveiling
at the conference
tomorrow.
I thought we were working
with these people.
So did I.
Damn well almost got
our asses handed to us,
- getting these.
- These things are for tomorrow.
I want Scylla today!
Vincent Sandinsky.
Yes?
Let's go.
What are you going
to do?
I warned you not to come,
Michael.
Well,
it's not over,
not by a long shot.
Christina Rose Scofield.
That name mean anything
to you?
No.
Yes.
How badly
do you want him, Mom?
Michael,
listen to me.
That's not an answer.
I'll be in touch.
I get the ass-kicking
of a lifetime
and you come back
empty-handed?
- What?
- Linc and Michael's mother--
She's got Scylla,
here in Miami.
Fuel the jet.
We're going to Miami.
The guy knows
something.
Hey.
I don't know what else
I can do to help you guys.
Please let me go.
I-I won't say a word
to anyone
about this.
Never heard of the name
Christina Scofield?
I told you, no.
Never?
Never.
Yeah.
That guy you picked up
at the airport.
There's something
you should know.
What do you mean?
He's not some innocent victim,
Linc.
He and Christina
have been exchanging e-mails,
phone calls,
you name it.
They've got
some kind of plan.
I just...
haven't figured it
out yet.
Thanks.
So what are you going to do
with him, Linc?
Leave town, Michael.
Linc?
Where's Scylla?
No.
Where's Scylla?!
You ready?
Almost.
- Is that Sandinsky's phone?
- Yeah.
Good luck.
Thanks,
I may need it.
It's Michael again
on Sandinsky's phone.
I thought
he turned it off.
Well, now it's on.
Track it.
Michael?
Hello, Christina.
I hope
you're ready to talk.
Let's start with
Vincent Sandinsky.
Vincent Sandinsky,
the scientist?
He, uh,
he's an old friend of mine.
A bit of a bore,
don't you think?
But who cares about him?
I'd rather
talk about you.
I'd rather meet you
face-to-face.
Unless you're bringing me Scylla,
I'm not interested.
No Scylla, no meeting.
That's all I can offer.
What do you hope
to accomplish?
I need your answer
in ten minutes,
and that's
the last time
I'm calling back.
And found him.
He's in an industrial park
in El Portal.
Right up the coast.
All right...
Let's go.
You're lying,
you're lying.
I don't work
for the Company.
Six words
that never prove true.
Come on, man,
this is over, look around!
What are you doing here?!
- I swear I don't know anything, I do!
- What are you doing here?
I don't know anything.
I don't know
what he's talking about.
I am here
for a conference.
That's all.
I don't know
who told you otherwise.
I do,
and Michael's
also full of crap.
He's got
no reason to lie.
Actually, he does.
Michael's leading us off the scent,
so he can get in...
He doesn't want Christina
to have Scylla
any more
than we do.
It's not the first time
he's lied to us.
Where is it?
No.
- Linc.
- Come on, Linc,
he can't talk
if he's dead.
You got
three seconds.
No.
Burrows!
Put the gun down.
Vincent and I
need to talk.
Vincent?
Yeah.
We had a deal.
New deal.
I'm taking charge.
Vincent and I
are old friends.
Where'd you find him?
At an airstrip.
He's got something to do
with Scylla.
Good.
Then you can help me
find it,
can't you,
Vincent?
And you can help me find
Christina Scofield.
Dr. Sandinsky
has been
a Company operative
since--
How long's it been,
Vincent?
21 years.
21 years of service.
Scientist,
statistician,
expert field combatant.
What brought you
to Miami?
Does that help?
She invited me,
okay?
She invited me.
- Who?
- Christina Scofield.
I'm working with her.
Oh, that brings you
full circle,
doesn't it,
Burrows?
But you knew that
already.
When were you
planning on
telling me that your mother
was behind all this?
We just found out.
But bottom line is,
you knew.
All of you!
On your knees.
You heard him,
get down.
Oh, not you.
I don't need
to make deals
with men
who can't do their jobs.
If Bagwell is the only one
who is competent here...
- What?!
- He'll do it alone.
Are you serious?!
Who do you think
found this guy?!
Where's Scylla?
I don't know.
I don't.
She doesn't tell me
where she keeps it,
but I do know
where she's staying.
A place called
Edgewater Tower,
Room 1099.
You have today.
One day.
S04E19:
S.O.B.
You're wasting time,
Burrows.
One day.
You tipped him off.
No, Bagwell.
You stay here.
Yeah, Theodore.
He needs you.
But you'd better
stay away from us.
This is where Michael's signal
is coming from?
Perfect.
Be careful.
Stay here.
Check it out.
Let's go.
Let's go!
He's leaving.
Come on,
he can't be that far away.
Let's go.
Out.
Alright, let's go.
All right.
Where is it?
You don't really expect me
to answer that, do you?
Actually, I do.
Because your life
depends on it,
and considering
your track record,
I think it's safe
to assume
that you're always looking out
for number one.
I've waited 25 years
for this moment, Michael.
There's no way
I can say everything
I want to say.
Why should I let you?
Because
I'm your mother.
That's something
you can't change.
It's something
you can't take away.
It's nice to meet you,
Sara.
In some ways,
Michael's done very well
for himself.
In other ways,
I'm not so sure.
Lincoln has led you down
a dark path.
I make my own decisions.
You break Lincoln
out of prison
and he goes to work
for General Krantz.
And he has his reasons.
But if you're looking for
some kind of common ground
between us,
maybe that's it.
I don't want
to see Lincoln working
for the Company, either.
At least you've stopped
making excuses for him.
I stopped
making judgments.
Something
I couldn't afford.
But that was a long
time ago,
and that's not why we're here.
No.
You're right.
None of us wants to see Scylla
go back to the Company.
So, if we can
put the past behind us,
maybe we can work
something out.
Like what?
Like a deal.
"A deal"?
All right,
you tell me
where Scylla is,
and we'll work out
the details later.
We'll go 50-50.
A mother-son operation?
Maybe.
But first, Scylla.
Please, Michael,
I know better.
We're very similar.
I know what it's like to look
at the big picture,
see all the
little moving parts...
How much easier it is to think
after the surgery.
I know you.
That's why you'll never be able
to manipulate me
like you do
the rest of the world.
You're running
out of time.
All right,
there's no one back here!
Well, they were here,
but of course,
there's nobody here now.
'Cause that's
what happens.
You know,
this...
whole thing...
It's just...
crap!
It's just waste.
We're always
one move behind,
every step
of the way.
Yeah, and it's just going to get
worse now that Bagwell
is breathing down
our backs.
How do you make
that kind of mistake, huh?!
And let that inbred
get anywhere near us.
No, no, no,
no, no, no...
The first mistake
was working for Krantz.
Okay,
that was the first mistake.
What do you think's
going to happen
now that he's in town
and he has his goons
calling the shots?
What's going
to happen now?
Yeah,
I should've known better...
than to get
anywhere near this.
All right, you know what?
We should go.
- Let's go.
- No, we can't go,
because you saw the photos,
right?
You saw the photos,
so you know
what he's going to do
with them.
We should have known
what he was going
to do with them!
- That's what we should've...
- Hey, hey, hey! Just calm down.
You know what,
the deal is over.
Okay?
You know it, I know it.
Everybody knows it.
We're not getting
out of here!
We're going to take a walk
right to the gallows,
or somebody else is going
to stab us in the back!
I did that walk
and I survived.
Even if we win...
Do we win?
You don't believe that,
do you?
Look, I'm going to do
what I got to do.
If you don't want
to roll with me,
that's fine.
What is that?
Rental receipt,
a silver minivan.
What is this?
What do you know
about this?
We found a whole...
box of them
down in Little Cuba.
Guns, too.
What do you know
about this?
She wanted me
to speak there.
About Scylla?
She said
she'd give me the script
beforehand,
that's all I know.
She said her interest
was purely scientific.
Her interest
was financial.
She came to me
about a year ago with an idea.
Rather than
build our organization
with Scylla
as the permanent cornerstone,
she wanted to use
the technology
to make a quick profit.
If certain events
occurred,
various nations
might feel the need
for a more
modern defense system,
and they'd come to us
for the answers.
Solar weaponry.
Water desalinazation.
Now, what do you know
about all this?
I told you all I know.
Well, I thought
it was a crazy idea.
Plan of an amateur.
But I figured
she'd be angry.
She wasn't allowed
to hold a card.
Yeah...
Now,
what was that?
I think
it's more than that.
Really?
What did
she tell you?
I know how
the Company operates.
Shell corporations
like Ecofield,
rampant misuse
of funds.
You're literally,
sitting on a gold mine.
But your leadership
only benefits
you and your friends,
ten generations
in the future.
And you...
would like to see
the Company implode?
I want to see
something happen.
You think too small.
Laos?
We'll all be dead
before that pays off.
Uh, "Laos," sir?
Don't trouble yourself.
Burrows?
I got a question
for your friend.
What is it?
Ask him what the letters
"DMB" mean.
Do the letters
"DMB" mean
anything to you?
I'm sorry.
I thought
you understood me.
She said
her place is
on the same block as
Dade-Miami Bank.
Did you hear that?
I got it.
He'd better be
telling the truth.
See what else
the doctor knows.
- No...
- What's Christina's plan?!
I don't know.
Maybe we should've...
Maybe we should've
followed her or something.
Sit down for me.
Please?
How about
I talk to her?
I might have
some perspective.
She didn't leave me
when I was six.
Okay.
I'm sorry
we had to meet this way, Sara.
we had to meet at all.
Michael's been through
a lot in
the last year
at some point.
It's going to be
too much for him.
Michael can handle it.
He's never known a life
without change.
Oh, you say that
like you know him.
Oh, I do.
Better than you.
I don't see
how that's possible.
Well, you will
when your child's born.
See, I wasn't sure at first,
but you do have
that drawn look.
And I see the way
you protect
yourself
when you sense danger.
You don't even know
you're doing it.
It's instinct.
And what is it you know about
maternal instinct?
I've tried
to be a mother.
Even to Lincoln.
How can you
say that?
You left them...
without so much
as an explanation.
But if Michael
would listen--
You know what?
You can stop.
You can't justify
what you did.
Michael doesn't know
you're pregnant,
does he?
What happened?
Uh...
I got nothing.
- Hello, Joyce.
- Hi.
How are you?
My name is, uh, Don Self,
Homeland Security.
Don't worry,
there's nothing the matter.
I'm just here doing a favor
for my friend.
See, his mother passed away
yesterday.
Okay, and her last will
and testament
is in, uh,
one of your security boxes.
It's actually Box 6468.
Is he authorized
to access it?
See, that's the problem.
He's not.
But we're willing to fill out
all the paperwork...
I'm sorry.
Only authorized individuals are allowed
- to access safe deposit...
- Listen, lady,
I need to get
in that box.
Where's your boss?
Sir?
Sir, can I help you?
Yeah. I need to get in my mom's
safe deposit box.
- Do you have a court order?
- No.
- DMB policy prevents anyone--
- Here's the policy.
Okay,
I need to open Box 6468
right now.
Name's Don Self, Homeland Security.
Excuse me, Mr. Frank?
Number 6468
was accessed a minute ago.
He just left.
It was the guy
with the silver suitcase.
There he is.
Hey, that looks like the guy
from the embassy.
Mr. Banarjee,
how are you?
I'm trying to reach
Christina Hampton.
She's in a meeting
right now.
If I don't talk to her
before five...
The deal is off.
Okay.
This is
my final offer.
You're going to take me
to Scylla,
and then
you can walk.
No questions.
No one
tells the General.
You can live
the rest of your life
like this
never happened,
but Scylla is mine.
Lincoln would never let
that happen.
He doesn't have to know.
Even as children,
you couldn't agree.
You fought about
everything.
The two of you couldn't
be more different.
But you know that,
don't you, Michael?
This isn't about Lincoln.
You have blue eyes,
he has green.
He played with trucks.
You took apart
the television set.
And I don't
need to point out
the difference in IQ...
or temperament.
You know
what I'm getting at,
don't you,
Michael?
I don't have
any idea
what you're talking about.
You've always known it
deep in your heart.
You just had
no one to confirm it.
Lincoln...
isn't your brother.
It's true.
I-I should have
told you before,
but you always
looked up to him, and...
I had no idea
things would happen like this.
You don't know
what you're saying.
Have you ever
seen pictures of Lincoln
as a baby?
- Yes.
- No.
There aren't any.
Your father didn't adopt him
until he was three years old.
His parents
worked for the Company.
They were killed
in an explosion in Manila.
Aldo brought him home
the next day.
He felt
it was his duty.
He didn't ask me
how I felt.
I...
I never bonded with him
like mother and son.
He was always
so angry.
Understandably so...
He was too young
to remember
his mother, but...
He always knew
something was missing.
I can't believe
you're playing this card.
I'm sorry, Michael.
But I felt
differently about you.
And you could tell.
That's why
you always felt guilty.
Why you were always
throwing yourself
over the cliff
after Lincoln was already dead
at the bottom.
It's why you went to prison
and pissed your life away.
You don't know
why I did
the things I did!
You weren't there!
Who knows what
you could have accomplished.
But you always felt
like you had to
make less of yourself...
To make Lincoln look
less pathetic in comparison.
Lincoln was more
of a brother to me
than you were ever a mother.
You left.
He stayed.
He fed me.
Kept me
off the streets.
Put me through school.
How?
By getting in trouble
over and over again,
just like he is
right now.
What do you mean,
right now?
Where is he?
He's out
looking for Scylla,
and he's not going to find it.
Maybe you should call him
and tell him.
Unless
there's too much
bad blood
between you.
Or no blood.
Who's the guy
in the ring?
Is it Michael?
He's gonna be all right.
Just, just relax.
Where is he?
All right,
keep up with him, come on.
I am.
Just shut up.
It's not that I
don't want to help you.
It's just that I hate to see you
go running after him again.
- Come here!
- Michael.
- Michael!
- Where is he?
Okay.
You want to go running after him,
flush your life
down the toilet
once and for all?
Go ahead!
Where is he?
If you don't tell me where he is,
or I'll kill you,
myself, I swear!
I'll kill you myself.
Michael!
Come on!
Tell me!
Where is he?
Where is Lincoln?
All right.
Fine.
There's an energy conference
at the Panda Bay Hotel
in about an hour.
He'll be there.
That's the truth.
I'm sorry.
I don't know
what to think.
Go.
Go, go go.
Go find him.
I got her. Go.
If she gives you
any trouble...
I know.
Just...
Go.
You have surpassed expectations,
Bagwell.
You're much more
than an informant.
I multitask.
Well, if things go
as well as expected here,
you'll be rewarded
accordingly.
As a special liaison
to the Company?
Yes.
What exactly
does that entail?
Well, that would be
up to you.
Most Company operatives
choose their own career path,
though I can't say
what would suit you.
What do sexual predators
from Alabama typically do,
uh, aside
from the obvious?
Those days are behind me,
General.
What I lack
in formal education,
I more than
make up for in...
natural skills
and curiosity.
And as you've seen,
my loyalty knows no bounds.
Then you shouldn't have
any difficulty
passing your final exam.
Now, you didn't
expect that
a few phone calls on the sly
would set you up for life,
did you?
No, sir.
I'm ready for anything.
Good.
Then prepare for this.
When Burrows brings Scylla
back to us,
I will fly it safely back
to Los Angeles,
and you will be the one
to put a bullet in his brain.
Sara?
What's going on
in there?
Sara?
What do you want?
Oh, please,
keep that open.
Why?
So you can
lob more accusations
and assumptions out at me?
I haven't made any.
Lincoln is adopted.
And you're pregnant.
You don't deny it,
do you?
You should tell him.
He'd be happy,
even under the circumstances.
It really isn't
any of your business.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes,
in-laws...
overstep their bounds,
but...
You know,
when it comes right down to it,
I am the only mother
any of you will ever have, so...
You shouldn't
throw that away so easily.
Yeah, you know,
the only thing I get from you
is a great example of the mother
I don't want to be.
Sara?
It doesn't have to be
like this.
Yeah, it does.
That was your decision
a long time ago.
Sara...
Can I just give you
one piece of advice?
Stay out of the bars.
- That's good advice.
- I have friends in AA.
They're only alcoholics.
I can only imagine
what it's like for you,
trying to stay off
the smack.
It's morphine.
Hospital-grade morphine.
Christina Scofield
will not be leaving Miami tonight.
I want eyes at
every airport and gas station
between
here and Atlanta.
And I want the names of everyone
attending that conference.
I thought you might be
asking that question,
so I called the
front desk of the hotel.
Said I was
from the newspaper.
Excuse the spelling.
These are all scientists.
I told you.
Those
are the speakers.
Names below are
"special guests."
Sounded like bigwigs
from all over the world.
"Frederich,
Carlotto,
Linarte,
Ban..."
"Banarjee"?
- Naveen Banarjee?
- Who is that?
The son of prime minister
Nandu Banarjee.
He has a known
interest in
solar weapons technology.
This will all be over
by the end of the day.
Come on, Linc,
where are you?
It's Linc.
You know
what to do.
Linc, it's me.
Call me
when you can.
We got to talk.
Mahone!
This way!
Christina.
Don't move.
Or I'll kill you both.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
There.
- Right there, right there.
- Where is he?
- Lincoln, stop!
- Why?
Wait, wait.
That's the hotel.
The energy conference.
That's right--
It's today.
The silver van.
The rental van.
They want us here.
Something's up.
What the hell
is going on?
Downey.
It's for a getaway.
Linc, no!
Where are you?
Running.
Burrows is on my ass.
Are you okay?
I was worried
you didn't get away.
This whole thing
could go to hell.
I'm fine.
I'm right on time.
See you soon.
Down.
Down!
Good girl.
He'll never forgive you
for this,
and neither
will his brother.
Soon,
this will all be behind us.
Maybe I can meet
my grandson one day.
Namaskar.
(Hello.)
My apologies,
Naveen.
Where have you been?
I was told that
you would call.
I got hung up
on a few details for this evening.
You spoke with Downey?
It did very little
to reassure me.
I need to speak to
Dr. Sandinsky.
Oh, you haven't heard?
Dr. Sandinsky
had a family emergency.
His wife
was in a terrible accident.
I spoke with him
this morning.
He took a private jet out
this afternoon.
It's very late...
to be making
these decisions now.
Yes,
but you've come all this way.
You are prepared
to give your speech,
aren't you?
Fine.
But in light of the fact,
that I did not speak
with the doctor,
I'll amend my offer.
$1 million in
exploratory research.
The rest will follow
in the weeks to come.
That's very generous,
Naveen.
History
will thank you.
Your country
See you soon.
May I have your attention,
please?
We're about to begin.
Thank you.
Welcome to Miami Beach.
And thank you
for attending the
first global conference of its kind,
where great minds will meet
to explore our energy future.
The importance
of finding new ways
to power our world
should not be underestimated.
It's running.
Okay.
They rented this
in Linc's name.
Look at this.
These passports.
It's us.
It's a setup.
- For what?
- It's a setup!
Okay, thank you.
5 o' clock.
If Burrows doesn't call
in the next five minutes,
you're going downtown.
General,
you should see this.
...environmental summit
in the city of Miami.
Today, the venue will be
the Panda Bay Hotel,
where security
has been tightened
for the arrival of
important guests.
This includes
Naveen Banarjee,
son of Prime Minister
Nandu Banarjee,
who is scheduled to be
the event's keynote speaker.
Banarjee's
fragile political position
may leave him vulnerable
to criticism on the world stage.
He has aggressively sought
to place his ideas in the
- forefront of environmental policy...
- Christina's plan.
What she needed to profit
from Scylla.
An incident
that'll domino into global warfare.
For new forms
of greener energy like
sun and wind...
And how these ideas
- were implemented.
- Krantz.
You're out.
It's over now.
No.
You do it.
Do it!
Hey!
You need a pass!
At this point
in our history,
solar power accounts
for less than one-tenth of
one percent of the total power
generated in our world.
And in the next ten years,
that number
should increase
to ten percent,
but it's still
not enough.
We must strive
to seek new alternatives
so that we can break this cycle
of oil dependence.
We cannot do that
without your help.
So, that's why
we're here today.
To explore
our new energy future
and envision
a new tomorrow.
Now, our first guest is
an author and an entrepreneur.
As well as having
a notable heritage,
he has spoken
to audiences
across the world.
Please welcome,
Naveen Banarjee.
Thank you,
thank you.
Good evening,
my friends.
It is my pleasure
to be here with you today,
in this beautiful city
of sunlight.
Throughout
the United States,
I find there
to be great interest
in the changing way
that we all
power our world.
Many times
I have been approached...
No!
With a proposal
to reinvent the wheel.
New resources...
Michael!
Linc!
We've got to go.
She set
the whole thing up.
Do you have it?
Right here.
How'd it go?
The van was there
with the passports.
I just got off the phone
with our contact at the bank.
And they've got
clean video
of Burrows
trying to access the box.
He must have trashed
the hotel room.
His hands were
all over the shells.
You see Michael?
He was
there on my way out.
Lincoln's right back
where he started.
But really it's too bad
about Micheal.
And I know you, uh...
Shut up and drive.
Final Edits By: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]
www.tvsubtitles.net