Previously on Prison Break...
There's one big difference
between you and I, Michael.
You can't kill.
- I will get you.
- This is, uh...
in case you run into
trouble down the road.
Lincoln, he really wants to
see you and your brother.
He hasn't seen Michael
since he was ten years old.
- Why are we going?
- Michael never met your grandfather.
Dad.
- I got Burrows.
- Take care of them.
I think there's a of
me that enjoys this.
It feels to me like
chasing a high.
And I should know
better by now.
Sara?
Hi, Sara.
- Hey, what is this?
- It's for my...
blood pressure.
Geary, come on,
we can make a deal, man.
No deals. You just crapped out
your last bargaining chip, pal.
Ain't that the most beautiful
thing you ever seen.
This is the Tribune Police.
Make yourself known.
Hey, you're in luck.
- Had a case in back.
- Excellent.
Fishing reel oil.
And you want the whole case?
Whole case.
- And the, uh, GPS?
- And the GPS.
- Must do quite a bit of fishing.
- Yeah, a lot of fishing...
not a whole lot of catching.
- $96.23.
- Um...
I'm just going to
take the reel oil.
- Thank you.
Hey! You have to pay for that.
Just take it;
please don't hurt me.
Please.
You have to pay for that.
The vault. Open it.
One for the team.
He wasn't gunning for me,
he was gunning for my daughter.
Give Anna her papa's love.
I'm going cut your throat out.
I loved you, Michael.
You just used me.
Cops found your girlfriend fish-belly
white, gargling her own puke.
And what do you care?
As long as she left the door open.
I feel very fortunate
to have met you.
I'm sorry, Henry.
It's about corporate interests
taking over the government--
buying elections,
fighting wars...
people dying so they
can turn a profit.
We're trying to stop it.
What you, a bunch of spies?
Just a handful of
senators, congressmen,
people like me that once
worked for the company.
People willing to expose the
President for what she is--
a shill working for
these corporations.
We bring her down,
we bring them down.
What's it got to do with me?
Because the way we're
going to bring her down
is also what we're going
to use to set you free.
About a week ago,
we finally got a break.
An NSA analyst
sympathetic to our cause
finally worked his way up and got
clearance to the Echelon program.
E-mails, cell phone calls
all across this country,
if it's transmitted,
it goes through Echelon.
It's catalogued, interpreted,
and then stored for Homeland Security.
Nothing is missed
by them. Nothing.
Including by accident,
for a few months after 9-11...
the White House.
The analyst got his hands on a
phone conversation the President had
with Terrence Steadman...
two weeks after you
supposedly killed him.
Now, the analyst tried to get this
information out of the building...
But it turns out,
someone else was snooping, too.
Someone wanted answers
about the President.
Aldo and Lincoln want
to be left alone.
Sure, I understand.
24 hours later, Tancredi is dead,
the analyst is missing,
and the White House Echelon tapes
have been deleted from the mainframe.
The tape is still out there.
And judging by how hard they're
going after Sara Tancredi,
I'm pretty sure they
think she has it.
And I think they're right.
She's the key to this
whole thing, Lincoln.
LJ, come with me.
I would imagine that
you're feeling slightly
betrayed right now.
I understand.
As you can see,
hi, my name is not Lance,
and I'm not an addict.
Okay.
There is one thing about me
that should mean a great deal
to you right now.
That is I am reasonable.
If you tell me what you know,
you get to go.
Okay, and then maybe when
this is all behind us,
we get to grab a piece of
pie for old times' sake.
Okay. Come here.
I don't know where Michael is.
This is not about Michael;
this is about your father.
He left Washington with something
that didn't belong to him.
- We need it back.
And you killed him for it.
I didn't, no,
for what that's worth.
But I hope that his death
properly illustrates
the magnitude of the situation
that we're in right now.
So, where is it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Where is it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Where is it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Sara, there's a next
step involved in this,
and you don't want
to experience that.
I swear to God I don't know
what you're talking about.
My father didn't
give me anything.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
How long has it been since
your last confession?
This is my first time.
In a long time.
Are you aware of the
nature of your sins?
The nature?
I'm not really sure.
Deep down inside your heart,
you know.
Righteousness, maybe.
Believing the ends
justify the means.
What are those ends?
- Saving someone's life.
- And the means?
I've broken just about
every law you can name.
But it's not just
what I've done.
It's what others have done...
...because I let them.
Because I was doing what
I thought was right.
I should have known
better this time.
This time?
When I was a kid...
I watched a man
bleed out and die.
And I was glad...
because he deserved it.
Life is only for God to give and take,
my son.
Suddenly, there is this
dark space inside of me.
And I knew it was wrong.
But here I am.
There is a way to stop this.
Surrender your will to God.
If I surrender now,
I lose everything that I love.
But do you lose your
soul in the process?
Well, we all have
our crosses to bear.
You okay?
This is never gonna stop.
They're gonna keep coming after us.
Lincoln, don't.
- Is it done?
- You are.
- Lincoln Burrows.
- Your man's dead.
Just like anyone else you
send to take out my son.
We want you.
This isn't about LJ.
There's a very simple way
for all of this to end.
I'll tell you how
it's going to end--
me staring in your dead eye with
my hand around your throat.
You even know who I am.
How much further?
- Right here is good.
- Alright, you got it.
- Thanks for the ride.
- No problem.
Agent Mahone. Bill Kim.
I'm here to pick you up.
- I called Kellerman.
- He's busy right now.
Does anyone else
know you're here?
- No.
- Good.
Can you open the gate?
And I need a new vehicle.
There's something you
should know about me.
I don't like being
out in the field.
I only do so when
there's been a screwup.
- I'm out in the field, Alex.
- Then why don't you open the gate?
You can hurry back to D.C.
before your shoes get dirty.
We have a lead as to where Burrows
will be meeting up with his brother.
It's a place he referred
to as "Bolshoi Booze."
Does that mean anything to you?
Yeah, it's one of a hundred
tattoos on Scofield's body.
- What does it mean?
- I don't know yet.
You'll need to figure it out
within the next couple of hours.
If Scofield and Burrows
cross the border,
they'll be out of
your jurisdiction,
and you'll be of no
further value to us.
- Open the gate.
- So you can do what?
I want to hear it.
Straight from the mouth of the guy
who's supposed to be our closer.
I'll get Scofield
and Burrows...
and all of the rest of them.
And then me and
you and Kellerman,
we're going to part ways.
I just hope you're
properly motivated.
'Cause as long as you do your job,
we'll forget about Shales.
And then you can go back to
Colorado and visit your son.
Cameron. He's five, right?
Don't you ever mention
his name again.
There he is.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Get cracking, Alex.
A lot of people
are relying on you.
Jane will take care of it;
you can trust her.
I know this is hard,
but it will work out--
you have my word.
- Thank you.
- Be careful.
Listen, uh...
I know.
Jane's gonna look after you.
- I don't even know her.
- She's all right.
She's been working
for Dad for a while.
I'll, uh...
I'll see you soon, I promise.
Isn't that the same
thing your dad told you?
Yeah, but I mean it.
Hey.
Hey, it's me.
Just call me when you get this, okay?
It's important.
They're numbers.
Is that my payment?
- Medical nitroglycerine?
- As promised.
Whoo.
You have no idea how hard it
is to get this kind of grade.
Even with my contacts.
It's time for your
end of the deal.
Where's that plane gonna be?
They call me a couple of hours
before with the drop-off point.
It keeps the DEA off our backs.
Since it's going to be a while,
you might want to
stay out of the sun.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Is there a problem?
They're just my cousins.
Now, after your father
accessed this information,
he made three calls from his cell phone,
all to you.
What did he tell you?
Just that he was coming
back to Chicago.
Good. You're being
honest. Good.
Now, there's a half an hour
between when your father landed
and when he got home
that is unaccounted for.
I know you stopped by his office.
Did you see him there?
No. The last time I saw my father,
he was dead in his study.
Did your father have
anyone give you anything?
Do you think that I'm just
withholding information
because I like
hanging out with you?
If I knew something,
I would tell you; I don't.
I don't know anything
about any of this.
Really?
Then why did you give your father
the file on Lincoln Burrows?
Why did you open the door for Scofield,
and help him escape?
Why did Scofield send
you those coded notes?
Why did you come to
New Mexico to meet him?
Don't try to float a
babe-in-the-woods routine by me.
It's really going to piss me off, so...
Come on.
Okay. Come on. Shh. Shh-shh.
You're okay.
Shh. Alright.
Look, Sara.
We're going to have to
come to an understanding.
You know that, right?
Yeah, you were right;
they are coordinates.
Plug them into your GPS.
They'll take you to a spot
in the New Mexico desert.
It's in the middle of
nowhere, basically.
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
Sir, who are you meeting?
What the hell is he doing?
He's keeping us out of the loop,
that's what he's doing.
Constantly running from
the law with a bad heart...
Mexico, where I'm from has got
a lot of great things, but...
health care ain't one of them.
You all right?
- You look a little nervous.
- I don't do this every day.
I just want to get the information
on that plane and, uh...
move on.
- Is that it?
- That's it.
I know who you are.
You don't have to worry--
we can't go within 100 feet of a
federal marshal to collect the reward,
'cause we got U.S.
and Mexican warrants on our heads.
But this plane to Panama...
Sit down.
- This is all for your brother?
- Yes.
I got four brothers,
two in prison.
Accept a call? Yes.
But break them out? Loco.
My brother gave me a baseball
mitt for my 14th birthday.
I owed him.
You're a better man than I am.
Time will tell.
Shouldn't they have called by now...
about the plane?
Yeah. You know, I...
I have a question.
I thought that these
came in glass vials,
- not plastic.
- I thought so, too,
but the guy I bought it from
said he packed it in plastic
for transportation over long
distances to prevent a fire
or an explosion.
Really? I never heard of that.
What's going on?
We're going to do a little
quality control test.
- It's the best available.
- We got time.
For the last time,
some black male, early 20s,
jumped me from behind.
I didn't get a good look at his face.
The assailant attacked
you from behind?
That's what I just said.
Yet he managed to make contact
square on your forehead.
- That's right.
- With what? A boomerang?
Come on,
why don't you tell me what happened?
Look, I'm a retired correctional
officer out of Illinois.
How about showing some
professional courtesy, honey?
This is Roy Geary.
Leave a message.
You thieving son of a bitch.
You better get down on your knees
and pray to God that
I don't find you,
because, if I do,
mark my words,
I'm going to gut
you bow to stern.
President Reynolds was in Tallahassee,
Florida, early this morning,
attending a $5,000-a-plate
breakfast fund-raiser
for Senator Martin Kleinhenz,
who's running for reelection.
Later this afternoon,
her press conference was derailed
when a reporter
asked her to comment
on Lincoln Burrows' escape from custody.
She declined.
It's become clear in her
first month in office
that she cannot separate
herself from this manhunt.
And as long as it continues...
...pundits say that questions
about Burrows will contin...
Ladies. Let's get
this party started.
The last 30 years, I've hated you.
You walked out on me.
You haven't even seen Michael.
I've seen him before.
Not in the papers, Dad.
Been trying to work out what
kind of man abandons his family.
Now I'm doing the
same damn thing.
You'll see him again.
I'll make sure of it.
- How much further?
- About three hours.
It's gonna be a few minutes.
My brother should be here soon.
Maybe I should go outside
and make sure he can see me.
That's a good idea.
I think I'm gonna send Ernesto to do it.
Ernesto, por favor.
Hello.
Si.
Bueno, te veo.
- Was that the call?
- Yes, it was.
- About the plane?
- ¿Como se llamas?
- Agua con azucar.
- Sugar water.
You just made a big
mistake, blanquito.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm not a chemist.
The guy I bought it from
swore it was medical nitro.
We both got screwed.
Yeah, but only one of
us is gonna pay for it.
Look, I just want
to get out of here,
and you want your payment.
My brother's gonna be here soon.
We'll work something out.
Just name your price.
I already named my price.
You didn't come through.
When's your brother
getting here?
You were planning on turning us
in the whole time, weren't you?
When's he supposed
to meet you here?!
Sueltalo.
- Drop it, or I'm gonna shoot him.
- Let him go, or I'll shoot you.
- Suelta la pistola.
- Ey, no estoy judiendo.
Sueltala, cabron!
Quieto!
- Where is it?
- My father didn't give me anything.
Who you risking your life for?
Lincoln Burrows.
Street thug.
And why is that your concern?
I mean, is there somewhere in the
Hippocratic Oath where it says,
"I pledge to risk my life for
those who don't care about mine"?
'Cause they don't
care about yours.
Burrows and Michael
Scofield just used you.
Are you that surprised that
there are people in the world
who will stand up
to people like you?
Are you that far gone?
That's cute.
Sad.
But cute.
A Cleveland what?
Don't worry,
I'll talk you through it.
And we got a glass
coffee table right here.
Hell no.
I'll do it for a thousand.
- $500.
- $1,000.
- $750.
All right.
What the hell?
Leave.
You know, it's amazing
what you can pick up
at an Army-Navy store.
All that torture stuff,
that was Bellick's idea.
And if you ask me,
he took the whole thing way too far.
Why don't I just give you half
the money, and we call it a day?
All right, 60-40.
Come on, T, we can deal.
Where's the plane
going to land?
Kiss my ass, cobarde.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know.
We're not going to get across
the border on the ground.
Without that plane,
we're screwed.
He's losing too much blood.
He'll never make it like this.
He should have thought of that
before he tried to kill us.
We got to take him to a hospital,
or else he'll die.
Please.
The plane,
and we'll let you go.
Dicelo.
Dicelo todo.
Dicelo ahora!
Finley Road...
off of Highway 8,
there's an airstrip.
There, okay? Now let us go.
- Let's go.
- No, no, no!
Michael, let's go.
Por favor... please.
Don't do this,
please don't do this.
Let's go, Michael.
If we were bleeding he would have
not lifted a finger, you know that--
he was gonna kill us both.
- Let's go.
- No, that's not true.
Michael, we're going to
get to that plane...
- Don't do this.
- Let's go now, please.
- Please don't do this, okay?!
- Callate!
Don't do this, all right?
Don't listen to him! Please.
Sara, I care about you.
This is not what
I wanted, Sara.
Kellerman.
What's going on with Sara?
Has she told you anything?
Don't go anywhere.
Not yet.
I trust you've
been... persuasive.
- Yes, absolutely.
- Then kill her.
Well, she knows something.
You disobey me, you are done.
Do you understand me?
Put her in the ground, Paul.
Michael.
Let's go.
- Michael.
- Hold still.
Michael, we're doing it wrong--
let's get out of here.
Now, he's gonna call the cops,
or go get his buddies...
He's not going to make it.
Callate!
We'll call them
when we get safe.
Let's go-- Michael, let's go!
Thank you.
You got to get him to
a hospital right away.
Wait. Wait.
- Hey, man...
- Forget Finley Road.
The plane is going to stop
at the seven mile marker
on Route 4 at sunset.
It's going to stop for five minutes.
Then it's going to go
to Oaxaca, Mexico.
If you miss it,
you're out of luck.
- He bled out on the way over.
- Any ID?
Yeah, Roy Geary,
just an out-of-stater.
- You know him?
- He's a friend of mine.
- Mr. Bellick?
- Yeah.
You mind answering a
few more questions?
Yeah.
It's Pam.
What's going on?
I just wanted to say hey.
Well... are you all right?
You said it was important.
I know things got kind
of ugly toward the...
you know, the end. Um...
I got ugly.
But I want you to know that
there were circumstances
that, uh...
It was better that
you and Cameron
hat you were not with me.
Why are you telling
me this now?
If I had to do it
all over again...
I'd do it different.
We'd still be a family.
I'd give anything for that.
I just wanted you to know.
Alex...
- what's going on?
- Nothing.
I just wanted to call to
say that I was, uh....
...that I'm sorry
about everything.
Where are you right now?
- I can come get you.
- Wouldn't that be nice, huh?
No, I'm serious. Where are you?
One more thing.
If you hear anything in the media...
What? What are
you talking about?
I love you.
Give Cam a kiss for me, okay.
Well... I'm glad I told
you about this place.
I'm glad I figured
out how to work a GPS.
Could you make it a little
more difficult next time?
- I owe you one.
- We're even.
But we got to leave.
- Linc.
- Hey, buddy. How are you doing?
- Where's LJ?
- Safe. The money?
I'll tell you later;
we got to go.
I brought someone.
Dad?
We've met before.
This is happening
right now, okay?
Don't make me do this.
Even if I knew,
I wouldn't tell you.
You wouldn't? Really?
Are you that stupid?
Are you that stupid?!
Because now you're
going to die!
You're going to die,
and all you had to do is tell
me what your father gave you.
I know my options.
I can not tell you and die,
or I can tell you
and still die.
No. Wrong. Sara.
Come on, smarten up!
For once in your life. Please.
Go to hell.
Huh? Drowning is horrific--
don't get me wrong--
but once you give in and let
the water come into your lungs,
there's a certain euphoria...
I hear.
I guess as a junkie,
I thought maybe you'd appreciate that.
You did this to yourself.
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net