- Previously on Prison Break...
- We're gonna get you out of here.
- The escape is on.
- Go, go, go!
Who the hell is the guy?
He's my brother.
Can't die on me now, Michael,
you know, you're gonna tell me
- why I'm your whip hand.
- We found Michael.
- He's been busted up real bad.
- I got to go.
You don't know what
you'd be walking into.
It's not safe.
I can't look my son in the eye
and tell him that I let his father die,
a father he's never met.
Never thought I'd see this face again.
You weren't supposed to.
Lincoln Burrows.
How about you step out
and pay us the 100 grand you owe us.
- There is nobility in you, Lincoln.
- You should rest up.
- We're gonna need you.
- Didn't know you worried.
About the right things.
What's wrong?
It's him. Your husband.
Jacob
is Poseidon.
He's a CIA operative,
deep cover. He runs a splinter cell
called 21-Void.
He targeted me for my skills.
Michael, he's with our son right now.
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.
Did my husband, Jacob Ness,
ask you to work on my cell phone?
He said he was looking to find
the people who were stalking
his wife, so I did a data dive.
Where's my son?
I have him.
And whether or not I
have to threaten him
is entirely contingent upon
you putting the gun down.
Kaniel Outis
has been located on a cargo ship
in the Mediterranean.
They made you.
Run!
_
Hey!
Hey, yo,
where we headed?
Marseille.
- Marseilles.
I own you, Scofield.
I know everything about you.
Even your most mundane
actions, like the zoo.
What's with you and the zoo?
I go there to think.
18 times in the past month?
- A lot of thinking.
- I was figuring out how to get
- your guy out of Barranquilla.
- Hmm.
Turns out he's not
just a rebel leader...
He's a murderous sociopath.
That's the only way to make omelets.
I need to know more about our targets.
If I'm facilitating escapes,
we can't have surprises.
Be proud. You and me,
- we're changing the world.
- Doesn't make it right.
Don't act like you're suddenly
a fan of the status quo, okay?
The system, it's slow,
stupid, and doomed to fail.
That's why you had to bust your
brother out in the first place.
New ink since the last time I saw you.
- Working on a new plan?
- No. No new plan.
Just get tired of looking at empty skin.
Uh-huh.
You know, it was those tats at Fox River
that caught my eye in the first place.
I had to know everything about the man
who wore his plans on his skin.
In plain sight yet so mysterious.
The key to real power is to disappear.
- Hi, Professor Ness.
- Hello, Claudia.
Yeah, the secret to real power
is to never betray your intentions,
to wear nothing on your sleeve.
And to never let anyone
see your face.
Come on in.
Next time I'm sitting in solitary,
I'll think of you in
here, running the world
in air-conditioned comfort.
I've spent my time in the field.
You all set for Myanmar?
It's only a few weeks off.
That's why I'm here.
I want to bring someone on board.
- Oh, really?
- The prison camp
at Sittwe is a two-man job.
I've been watching this
guy. He'll be useful.
Watching him? You in charge
- of recruiting now?
- Trust me.
The last thing I want to do is
suck someone else into this.
He'll have my back and
he'll speed things up,
increase our odds.
Not exactly a distinguished career.
He's held up well in prison.
He's got a mean streak.
And he grew up without a family.
It means he can be manipulated.
If you're planning something,
I'll always be a step ahead of you.
You know that.
I can see everything in your eyes.
It's what's behind the eyes that counts,
Professor.
Hmm.
So you're gonna wait a year
for me to find my way out of Sittwe?
Or are you gonna get me a partner,
so we get on with the
business of changing the world?
Done.
_
I need some food.
I'm with you.
Linc, it's Sara.
She's back in New York.
Are she and Mike okay?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
_
What is it, Michael?
Something's wrong.
Yes, you will.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- I got to get back to the States.
- Slow down.
You're Kaniel Outis, remember?
You're on every no-fly
list in the world.
Jacob's done something
to Sara. Maybe Mike, too.
- How do you know?
- That text.
She referred to our son as Junior.
We agreed we'd never call him that.
He's baiting you, Michael.
It worked.
_
Hey, buddy.
Where's Mom?
Oh. I, uh, dropped her off at work
while you were at school.
That is quite a pirate ship.
Although it would be a little hard
to sail with the mast that far forward.
- Your ship might tip over.
- The mast has
to be there. It's not just a ship...
It's a treasure map.
What do you mean?
It's for Jimmy. We hide
Legos for each other.
I always find his.
He doesn't always find mine.
Wait a second,
how is this drawing a map?
This is the park.
That's the playground.
And this is the sidewalk.
Impressive.
You put a code in the drawing.
So, okay, where did you hide the Legos?
These cannons are pools at the park.
But there's an extra one, in the sand.
That's where I buried the Legos.
Well done, Mike.
Well done.
I've tried everyone. I'm out
of resources in the States.
All my contacts. People who
can go and check on them,
make sure they're okay.
Linc, I got to get home.
I can't spend another
two weeks on a cargo ship.
He's got my wife and kid.
There may be another way.
You told me about the last
seven years of your life.
Haven't told you about mine.
After Sara got exonerated,
she left Panama.
Me and Sofia stayed behind
and opened a dive shop.
We broke up, and
everything went to hell.
You weren't there to stop
me, so before I knew it,
I was in the old hood, doing odd jobs.
Odd jobs meaning what?
Moving things from point A to point B.
For Luca Abruzzi.
John Abruzzi's son.
Yeah.
I just wanted some quick
cash to kick-start my life.
They told me not to look in the boxes.
But I looked in the boxes.
The amount of fentanyl they're
smuggling out of Europe...
Tens of thousands of
pills in every box...
It's just killing people.
So I dumped a box in a Dumpster,
100 grand's worth.
Now you're in hock to Abruzzi's son.
Yeah. He wants to kill me.
But maybe it's a way to get
back to the States real fast.
_
You got balls, Burrows.
You actually think I want to help you?
What if I can get you the $100K?
$100K?
How are you gonna come up with that
crawling around the
back alleys of Chicago?
I'm not in Chicago. I'm in Marseilles.
- Marseilles?
- Yeah.
I've been working on a
couple deals. I got $100K
in my hand. But I want off the hook.
Sure you do. How about you get
over here and hand it to me?
That's why I'm calling.
I need to sneak into the States
invisible, like your pills.
Those flights you got
coming out of Europe...
The fentanyl flights...
I need a few seats.
I'll tell you what.
I'll make a few calls.
'Cause either I'm gonna see you
and get that money,
or I'm gonna see you,
and you're gonna get
something a whole lot worse.
I can't believe I'm doing
this to myself again.
Difference is this
time, you're not alone.
God, these things are disgusting.
What they call 'em again?
Boudin noir.
Not sure what's in them.
I don't think your French is
as good as you think it is.
Yo, be happy you're not eating snails.
Hey.
Do you think they noticed?
Let's not take any chances.
Guys.
Your faces were on the news.
Somebody sees you, this thing is over.
- We got to move, papi.
- We got to go.
Hold. Luca.
If you can get to Lyon by midnight,
I can get you on a flight.
I got a warehouse in New
York. You're coming to me?
We'll be there.
Can't decide whether I want you
to have that money or not, Burrows.
Killing you might be
a lot more satisfying.
Now we know they survived the
strike in the Mediterranean.
We can be pretty sure
he's coming back to Ithaca.
I need some clarification.
Why would he come back here...
to the States
when he's more wanted here
than anywhere else in the world?
Of course.
Because of them.
He had a life before he worked for me,
a name... Michael Scofield.
A family.
And when he went away, I
ended up looking after them.
Ended up... falling for them.
Well...
He wants to kill me.
He thinks I stole his life,
ruined him, which speaks
to his dissociative mind.
I mean, he's a murderer,
a turncoat, a terrorist.
But we'll use it.
I'll be the bait if I have to.
So we can go about taking
him down once and for all.
He's not just gonna stroll in here.
He's too clever for that.
That's why we got
someone even more clever.
Thoreau?
Guy's a pencil neck.
A pencil neck with insight
into Scofield's plan.
So you, in turn, can be the hammer.
Screen-grab of the Skype transmission
he sent from the desert.
He routed the image through a server
to this BlueHawaii guy,
but it could have been
secretly subrouted to another, yet
unknown, recipient to use
the information encoded in it.
Information?
It's actually incredible.
Encrypted in the Arabic, the
images are all sorts of stuff.
Apparently, mundane as hell.
Visiting hours for zoos,
links to defunct message boards
on the Internet.
What message boards?
Truesnuff.com, Hunterspycamporn.com,
both of which carry... this.
Images of the Harlan Gaines murder.
What's the bastard doing
rubbing that in our faces?
Of all the things to encrypt, why that?
What's that get you?
Stegaonographically, a lot.
Steganography is the practice
of concealing information
in the code that makes up digital files.
Russians do it, Chinese, everybody.
He's probably thinking
if anyone sees this,
this'll be as far as they'll look.
But I'm already going inside
the image, breaking down the data
- that comprises it.
- This is making my head spin.
Point is we put big data, AI on this,
we can crunch any codes
hidden in there pretty quickly.
And that's what I'm doing.
Nice work, but the truth
is if I've done my job,
he may reveal his
intentions to us first.
Because I've got him
so far off his game now,
he'll start to play
his cards too early...
Teddy.
"But in return, you must take a life."
show us what the tattoos mean
even before the computers
will, and all the people
he'll be enlisting for the fight.
You have to call this pay phone
in France.
Wait. Chicago? I thought
I was going with you.
Not until you find out
why you're my whip-hand.
I have to go to Chicago
to find that out?
Safe travels.
In the grandiosity of his plan,
he'll lose sight of
the simplest details.
The phone he texted me with
was located in Lyon, France last night.
It was turned off in an
airport terminal at 11:51 p.m...
20 minutes before a direct
flight to New York where
you'll be waiting for him
to put this game to bed for good.
_
Flight 290 to Miami, Florida
will now depart from gate B24.
He just powered back up.
We got him.
Look out!
Back of the plane.
Uh, excuse me! Excuse me.
You're not allowed...
Looks like the game's still going.
_
It's impressive how you get these drugs
in the country just
by bribing small-time
airport officials.
I'm guessing you got about
five million bucks worth
of fentanyl in here.
So what?
You and your brother
here are gonna lecture me?
We were actually debating on whether
I should give you the 100K or not.
He says it's blood money.
- I agree.
- How about you just shut up and pay me, Burrows?
I don't have it.
Grab his guys, bring 'em
to the back and shoot 'em.
I don't think you want to add
murder to your arrest warrant.
Wait.
Arrest warrant?
That guy out there
is a DEA informant.
We have him in our pocket.
He owes us. He's got three vans
full of agents that are
waiting for his call.
They're gonna rain down
on you and your pills.
Unless you forgive my brother's debt.
Then our informant won't make the call.
Have your brother fighting
your battles, do you?
No.
Why don't you tell your
guys to drop the guns,
and you and I can have it out?
What do you say, Luca?
Scare that guy off.
Bring these guys to the back.
They make a move, he makes a call.
Yeah? I think you're bluffing.
I warned you.
We got company.
You shoot us, there's
dozens of witnesses now.
Let's go.
All they had to see
were DEA hats and SUVs,
and they were gone.
Famous Michael Scofield.
Sheba. Thank you for everything.
You have no idea how happy
I am to see you back home.
We're not home yet.
All right, so what's next?
How do we get this son of a bitch?
We don't do anything.
Your part is over.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Tricking Abruzzi's kid is one thing.
Poseidon... he knows your face.
Been tracking you
since you went to Yemen.
You've been a warrior,
and I owe you.
But your face is a liability
now to you and your family.
I don't want you to risk that.
They may know his face,
but they don't know mine.
It's the punch you don't see
coming that knocks you out.
That's my Sheba.
You take care of her, all right?
I take care of him, you mean.
- I love you, brother.
- Love you, too.
Be safe,
- okay?
- You, too.
- Bye.
- All right.
Well...
when you need me again,
you know where to find me.
We'll transport her at 1600 hours.
Lay low until then. Thank you.
Hey?
That doesn't bother you...
What you just saw in there?
Down in the basement
with his wife, the woman
he says he fell for?
Stop.
I'm done with 21-Void after this.
After we get Scofield... Outis...
Whatever his name is...
I'm done.
That's all I ever wanted,
to get Gaines' killer, but
what he's got going in there...
That's not normal.
It's personal.
Something sicker.
There's no leaving
21-Void, Van. You know that.
He hired us because we are the best.
We can do whatever we want.
And if we want to
disappear after this...
we can disappear.
There's no getting out.
If you think that way...
then you're a prisoner, too.
The guy at the gate
said the vehicles split
five minutes after they got here.
Five minutes?
Something ain't right.
The product is still here.
Come on.
It was all staged.
Clever.
But Burrows is gonna die for it.
I don't know how we're gonna find him.
He's in the wind.
Maybe not.
EZ Pass transponders.
Santora's got a guy
at transit authority.
I bet you he can us what roads
they've been taking and when.
Then it's up to us to
comb the neighborhoods,
find the vehicles,
and put a bullet in that son
of a bitch once and for all.
_
Please keep your baggage
with you at all times.
Unattended baggage is a
security risk and may result...
I got a weird request.
If I give you some coordinates,
can you take me to 'em?
See what I can do.
No.
Unless this cab's got pontoons,
ain't gonna happen.
These coordinates are in
the middle of Lake Michigan.
This is it.
No lights.
I don't think they're here, Michael.
Unless that's what he wants us to think.
Come on.
Get ready to get us out
of here as fast as you can.
Linc.
Be careful.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
That's why Sara never responded.
I wasn't allowed to contact anyone,
but she was my wife.
I reached out to her in a way
I thought only she would know.
But he knew my ways, too.
Nothing.
_
What are you doing?
That's not Sara, Michael.
He doesn't know I know that.
_
- _
- That's the right answer.
She's alive.
He must be right there with her.
I'm gonna set a meeting.
And what, you're just gonna
show up and show your face?
Yes.
That means Poseidon has
to show his face, too.
And the endgame begins.
It's high noon, boss.
I'm not seeing him.
And you shouldn't. He's waiting for us
to push the first piece
out onto the board.
Which would be me?
Maybe not.
Black SUV.
Something I can help you with?
Car service. I'm here to
pick up a lady and child.
They got another ride. Hit the road.
Are you sure?
Hit the road.
Mark the black SUV.
No need. They were just here
to make you show your face.
Walk away, please. Now.
Okay, act the tiniest bit flustered.
Now repeat these words back
to me loud enough to be heard:
"They didn't show.
I'm coming back to you now."
They didn't show.
I'm coming back to you now.
Now we have a game.
He's already revealed
his brother, his biggest piece.
Soon he'll have to
show his face. Trailer,
please take him down.
What the...?
I lost him.
Hey.
Can you hear me?
Damn it.
No signal.
What are you doing here?
I lost reception in the garage.
Damn it, you fell right into it.
Now they've got a mark on us.
Black sedan.
He's heading west.
Please!
Please, don't shoot.
You okay?
So that's what the dog
who's destroying my country
looks like.
Talk to me.
Michael, we found the car.
We're on the corner of Third
and Washington by an alley.
Get here now.
He had Sara with him
- but we couldn't see her.
- What do you mean you couldn't see her?
There's no way we could have.
Oh, my God. Sara.
There was no one
- in the backseat?
- No, the windows
were blacked out... We couldn't see.
What's that?
My son did this.
He's good.
There might be something here.
It's a ship.
A pirate ship with three pirates...
Man, woman and a boy.
That's me, Sara and... Mike.
What do you think that is?
It's a... it's a many-headed hydra
reaching up to attack.
Think it's Jacob?
Must be.
- This is a message.
- You're telling me
Mikey's left something encoded in that?
Yeah. Yeah, it's encoded in him.
He's got my DNA.
He didn't even know you were coming.
Sara must have told him. I don't know.
She must have told him I was coming.
There's definitely
something here. Definitely.
What is it?
It's one of Luca's guys.
What?
How the hell did he track us here?
I don't know. All I
know is all the chickens
are coming home to roost
at the worst possible time.
We got to go.
Linc?
I got it.
This ship, this galleon.
The body of water it's
on. I looked at the map.
There's a lake, a lake
shaped exactly like it,
up in the Finger Lakes district.
"Long lake."
This X
would be on the east shore of that lake.
He's telling us where he is.
I'm trying to figure out if
you lost your mind or not.
There's only one way to find out.
- Uh-uh.
- What?
- You're going back to Buffalo.
- What?!
I want you to be with your
family, look after the refugees.
Linc, I'm a part of this fight, too...
What was that?
It's good-bye.
I could never forgive myself
if something happened to you.
_
Can I help you?
Yeah.
Can I rent a boat?
I want to take one out on the lake.
Been thinkin'.
God...
I been thinking.
'Cause a hard bargain's
been presented to me,
and I'm considering something
that's-that's gonna seem like
the old Theodore Bagwell.
T-Bag.
And if that's indeed what's coming...
it won't be the work
of a cold-blooded man.
And it won't be for sin...
or for hate.
If there's blood on my hands,
know this, world...
it'll be for love.
How you doing, buddy?
I'm sick of the lake house.
I want to go home.
I know. I know.
We'll go home soon.
Don't worry.
Is Mom okay?
She's, uh...
she's a little under the weather.
She's just resting.
Everything will be fine, kiddo.
Everything will be back to
normal soon enough, okay?
Michael, go get him. And I'll be ready.
- Thanks, man, that was fun.
- Yeah, anytime.
Yeah, great. Thank you.
What kind of honorific is Whip?
Who's asking?
A man drawn into this by destiny.
Okay. How about you take off?
I don't exactly cotton to
strange men coming up to me
in the middle of the night, you know?
Only one person calls
me Whip... you ain't him.
Nobody calls you that.
Man who gave me this hand. Nobody.
Kaniel Outis.
Or for those of us who know him,
Michael Scofield.
Who are you?
We all got handles, don't we?
Outis. T-Bag. Whip.
But you're Dave Martin, aren't you?
How'd you know that?
Huh?
You better start talking, old man.
You don't want to tangle with this.
Neither do you.
All your answers are
right in here, all right?
West Virginia honky-tonk,
1991, pretty waitress,
bunch of personal business
between us after closing,
and then I git, 'cause Johnny
Law's breathing down my neck.
Lacking a forwarding address,
I never heard from her again.
What are you trying to tell me?
Scofield was looking for
a partner, combing prisons,
looking for someone who
could handle himself.
And with your innate ability to thrive,
rising to the top in
even the worst of cages,
you reminded him of a certain someone.
And so he did a little research.
Wanted to know what we all want to know.
Did you learn it...
or was it ingrained in you?
It was ingrained in you, son.
You got it from me.
Linc, he's here.
- My son.
- Thank God.
Hold on.
Hold up.
I think Jacob's coming back.
I can't believe I'm seeing my son.
Something's wrong.
Sara's here, but...
- something's wrong.
- Don't do anything. He's coming back.
I'm going in.
It's not Jacob.
You're clear.
Get your family. Get your son.
Burrows!
Hi, Mike.
You know who I am?
I got your map.
I'm gonna get you and
your mother out of here.
I... I didn't draw a map.
- Is someone in there with your mom?
- It's not...
We need to run.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net