Previously on Prison Break...
Welcome home, boss.
Where's Mommy?
Mommy is gonna meet us later, okay?
I'm not a murder.
Terrence Steadman,
the President's brother.
I didn't do it.
Mr. Steadman, it's contraband.
I brought it to protect myself.
That's what we're here for.
Can I write a check for the food?
'Cause I don't have...
Hello, Mrs. Hollander.
Daddy's home.
It's Pam.
- What's going on?
- I love you.
Give Cam a kiss for me, okay?
You call this number again,
you're a dead man.
You want my help, Bill,
and I want my job back.
- What's your plan?
- When those brothers get in the van,
it'll be the last thing they ever do.
Kellerman has a team ready
to move on the caravan
just outside of Albuquerque.
When it goes down, there's sure
to be lots of bullets flying.
I need you there to make sure
Paul Kellerman catches one.
President Reynolds ruined your life.
She ruined my life.
You want to take the bitch down,
you just found your inside man,
but it's got to be right now. Let's go!
I know the way out!
I want a team flanking west.
Give me another team down by the river.
Man down! Give me a medevac, ASAP!
Officer Tuggle.
Officer Tuggle?
I'm looking for Alexander Mahone.
I'm his direct supervisor.
Sorry to tell you this, sir, but...
your boy's been shot.
Who are you?
I used to work for the President.
Why are you helping us?
Lay down on the floor, now.
Federal agent. Let me through.
Air support is telling us
that they saw your vehicle
traveling alone down Route 46.
Route 46--
possible exit route for the convicts.
I was securing it.
No offense, sir,
but we're searching every vehicle.
No offense, you either let me through
or you get me your supervisor.
I'm supervising this roadblock,
Agent Kellerman.
I'm sorry, but I need you
to get out of the vehicle.
Sergeant...
Humphries.
Burrows and Scofield have been
on the loose for 10 mins.
That means, that at this stage,
every second is critical.
So if you detain me for one moment more,
I will have all of your jobs,
do you understand me?
- Go ahead.
- What?
Just let him go.
You still haven't answered my question.
Why am I helping you?
Because the enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
You said something
about taking down the President,
I'm gonna assume you have a plan.
I do.
It was a Great Dane.
We had a bird hound.
It was very peaceful.
One minute she was breathing.
The next, she wasn't.
Turn around.
Get up!
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't blow your brains out!
Because I can give you
the one thing that's gonna set you free.
I know where Terrence Steadman is.
2x14
www.sub-way.fr (V.1.00)
How do you know where Steadman is?
Because I arranged this whole thing.
- You arranged to set me up?
- That's right.
You arranged the killing
of all the people I know.
I was given orders,
I executed those orders,
and now I have a bull's-eye on my chest,
just like you two.
I don't trust him.
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
You guys want to keep running, fine.
You want to be free, get in the car.
Last time I'm gonna offer.
What's up, Fish?
Looks like you're having
a tough time of it.
- I'm all right.
- Well, I'm just curious.
Why don't you hang out with
the rest of the ex-guards
that are locked up here?
Oh, yeah.
There ain't any.
It's just you.
Hey, ho-ho-hold up, hold up.
Now, I got what's called a mutual
beneficial arrangement in my mind.
I'll look out after you,
make sure nobody get up in your mix.
And all you got to do is bring me
your dessert after the next meal.
It's real simple.
I'm just looking to do my time.
I don't want any trouble.
Yeah, there's what you want,
and there's what I want.
Your dessert after the next chow.
You bring it to me.
You got it?
Wrong guy.
Break it up, convicts!
We're good, boss.
We're good.
You bring me my treats,
or else this goes next level.
Do you understand?
He asked you a question, boy.
Yeah.
- I ain't hear him.
Yeah, okay.
See how easy that was?
We're gonna be good friends, man.
There's no reason for you to be scared,
Susie Q.
'Cause you see, I've forgiven you.
And you, in turn, can
forgive me for my indiscretions,
which are so far in the past,
they're nothing but specks
in our respective rearviews.
It's been such a long time.
You look lovely.
Okay. Let's go, right now.
We can, we can go away,
spend some time together.
Listen, I'm not a Victrola,
so please don't play me like one.
There's not a white man's chance
in Harlem
you'd ever leave your children behind.
I'm sorry.
Don't fret now.
When you came to Fox River,
and you spat at me
like I was some kind of...
rabid animal...
I was happy.
'Cause such a visceral reaction
could only come from a woman
who still cares.
The children don't know anything.
I didn't want to scare them,
so I never told them about you,
so please don't.
That is so perfect.
'Cause you see what we got here now?
We got ourselves a clean slate.
Right?
So, this is the conspiracy, huh?
Bunch of little boys in suits
running around,
trying to kill each other?
It's pathetic.
Well, you were a little more formidable
than we anticipated.
We don't need compliments out of you,
jackass.
Oh, yes, there it is,
the winning Burrows personality!
Shut your mouth and drive.
The one we really knew
would win over a jury.
Good work.
Mr. Kim?
What the hell is going on out there?
Well, it was touch-and-go there
for a minute,
but I got everything handled.
Mahone's been shot.
Yes, I know, Bill. I was there.
I saw Burrows pull the trigger.
We lost a valuable asset, but...
Mahone's alive.
That's good. It looked bad.
Where are Burrows and Scofield?
Burrows and Scofield are dead.
And they're in my SUV.
I'm heading out to bury them right now.
Don't bury them.
I need visual confirmation.
I'll get you a photo.
I'll say it one more time.
Don't bury them.
You know what'll be nice
to hear now, Bill?
A "thank you."
I'll report back
when they're in the ground.
- You leave that on, he'll trace it.
- Yeah...
Secret Service. It's untraceable.
Thanks.
Hey, baby girl.
What?
What's the matter?
Where's Mommy?
Come on...
I told you that Mommy
was helping a friend.
All right? Now we're gonna see her
real soon.
When?
Baby...
we're gonna be with your mommy
real soon.
I promise you that.
I don't believe you.
Dede!
Yo, Trey, it's me, man.
What's up?
Yo, what's going on with Kacee?
I'm at the courthouse.
She's getting arraigned soon.
Okay. Will you talk to her?
Is she all right?
She's in jail!
So, no, she's not all right.
What the hell happened?
Your stupid ass think
I wanted it to go down this way?
Whatever. Man, I gotta go.
Her lawyer'll be here
any minute.
No. Listen, listen.
Now look, I want you to tell Kacee
to put it all on me, all right?
And that she didn't know what to do,
she was scared.
Okay? All that.
Yeah, I already told her to do that.
I'll do the talking.
- Owen Kravecki?
- That's me.
Hey.
Ben and Phil.
Let's get it going before our wives
figure out this is a fishing trip.
Where's your gear?
- I keep it up north.
- Okay.
How long is the flight?
Hour 40.
We don't have a choice.
Glad you're awake.
Collarbone rotator cuff.
Six inches to the right, you're dead.
Yeah, he just woke up.
Mr. Mahone?
Bill Kim.
You're a lucky man.
Am I?
Kellerman finished the job you couldn't.
But he, unfortunately,
is still out there.
And he's a loose end.
You have to finish
what you were supposed to take care of.
Something funny?
Keller is more of a loose end
than you realize.
He shot me.
That guy...
... you wanted to double-cross
screwed you first.
Scofield and Burrows...
... are probably alive.
and on the run with Kellerman.
Have a good day, Kimmy.
We neutered Kellerman.
He doesn't even officially exist
anymore.
He knows everything.
Reports have been coming in
from New Mexico officials
that escaped convicts Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows
have somehow managed
to extricate themselves
from a transport van that was
bringing them back to the Chicago area.
According to this early information,
the convicts were--
You're great.
Top-notch. I swear to God.
Don't get yourself worked up,
Mr. Steadman.
I was supposed to have my life back
by now!
Playing golf...
Going to movies...
Seeing people...
But because you guys can't get a handle
on an engineer and a petty crook...
I've been a ship in a bottle
for over three years.
Perfectly safe here.
I wish.
I just spoke to Kim.
He wants you to finish the job.
Yeah?
Well, that's not gonna happen.
This isn't a request.
And this isn't a negotiation.
Kim and Kellerman can try
to kill each other all day long.
But I'm out.
You must have forgotten how discreet
we've been with what we know.
Go tell the world about Shales!
In fact I will.
I killed a predator, a man who tortured
and raped women
and I buried him in my backyard.
I'll do the time.
I don't care anymore. I'm out.
Is that clear enough for you?
My man!
That's delicious.
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
We've got a problem.
There's one brownie.
There's five of my boys.
You see the position you put me in?
They gotta stand here
with their stomachs growling
will I savor this delicious treat.
That makes me look like a real ass.
Are you trying to make me look
like an ass?
You said the deal was I was supposed
to bring you one dessert.
Yeah, well...
I'm fickle, bitch.
Now it's five desserts.
Every meal.
Now, if you can't come up with that...
there are other ways...
... to making me happy.
Well, I've got some other candy on me
if you want some of that.
Well bring it out, bitch. It's all good.
Who wants some candy?
If memory serves, I was
at Storytime Village that day, too.
And I'm not in any of these pictures?
I could have sworn I was.
I'm just teasing, baby.
Every woman has burned
the photographs of her paramour
only to later realize her love burns
even harder than the flame she used.
Please!
Teddy!
Uncle Teddy!
How's my girl been?
Good.
You still getting more A's
than an aardvark?
Yeah, I missed you!
Oh, same here, shortcake.
Yes, I painted my hair.
Look at you, Zack.
You are a boy no more.
I'm gonna have to lend you
my razor soon enough.
What are you doing here?
Mom said you got a job on an oil rig...?
That's right, right out
in the middle of the ocean.
But those metallic beasts are dangerous.
Got myself injured.
And don't be frightened now, sugar.
The good lawyers
at Dewey, Cheatham and Howe
got me a million bones
for every digit I lost.
Five million dollars?
Which means
with all that cash,
I can do anything I want now.
And all I want to do
is spend all my money
and all my time...
... with you...
What's the neighborhood like?
No neighborhood.
The house sits on 50 acres.
We coming out the way we go in?
No, there's a back road we take.
- How many guards?
- Usually none.
At this point,
I really couldn't tell you.
The second I feel this thing going bad,
you get a bullet in the head.
I expect nothing less.
I will inform you every half hour.
Understood.
Private jet was chartered
by Owen Kravecki this morning.
- Headed where?
- Montana.
Stop it from taking off.
It's already on the ground, sir.
If that's my sister, I would like
to speak to her.
Right away, sir.
Evac.
Mr. Steadman, do you have a jacket?
We need to leave.
Leave?
What? No.
Agents will be arriving shortly
to take you to a safe house.
What do I need to be kept safe from?
Do you have a jacket, sir?
I don't want to leave.
I want to talk to my sister.
I've been authorized to use force
if necessary.
Now, is there anything
you'd like to bring?
My meds.
Go with him. Car's here in five minutes.
I don't know, Stella.
She won't come out.
Who wants to be up
in the trailer all day, huh?
Would you?
Exactly, me, neither!
You feel like baking a pie or something?
A little cherry or lemon meringue?
Daddy?
Is Mommy in trouble, like you?
Sweetheart, come here.
Come here.
Now, you listen to me, okay?
Mommy did nothing wrong.
She's helping out a friend.
Okay?
Okay, let me go see
how Mommy's doing, all right?
- I wanna come. I wanna talk to her.
- No, no.
You sit here like a good little girl,
okay?
Don't give me that.
Things are looking up.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Man, kick it down to me.
Her lawyer seems like he knows
what he's doing.
He thinks he can get the bail reduced.
Good. All right, listen.
When Kacee gets out,
I want you to deliver this message
for me. Okay?
Tell her
that we can all get lost.
You want her to jump bail now?
You better be glad
you ain't
in front of me, or I'd have my hands
around your neck.
Listen, punk, just deliver the message.
Then what y'all gonna do?
Go live in a cave?
I got a plan, all right?
Well, let's hear it.
This guy back in my unit
when I was in Iraq...
He used to go up to Alaska
and work at these fish hatcheries, man.
They pay you cash
and nobody asks questions.
Alaska?
Yeah, Alaska, man.
They don't bother you up there, man.
You know, me, Kacee and Dede,
we could be a family again.
You feel me?
Man, you don't quit.
You damn straight I don't quit!
Do I get to know where I'm going?
You'll get all the information
you need upon arrival.
We need to move Steadman
to Location Beta.
We're sending a car to pick him up.
It's already here, sir.
Couldn't be.
The car just left.
Weapons down!
Now!
Down!
Put your weapons down!
Don't get stupid!
Put your weapons down.
On the ground. Now!
Terrence, step away. Get in the car.
You look pretty good for a dead man.
- Get in the car!
- Wh-where? Why?
- Who's there?
- It's Kellerman.
He's got Steadman.
Do not let him escape !
Kill Steadman. Kill them all now.
- Paul, please. Don't, don't...
- Get in!
- Don't kill me.
- Get in the car!
Let's go.
Vomiting.
It's the worst side effect
of anesthesia.
That should be the last of it.
You figure I'm on empty by now?
Yeah.
Pam.
Alex, Cameron's been hurt.
- What happened?
- It was a car,
a hit-and run. He's at the hospital.
His leg is broken in 2 places.
I'll be on the next plane to Colorado,
okay ?
He's in surgery now.
I'll be right there ! Just hold on !
They won' let me see him.
They call me at work, I come right here
and now they won't let me see him !
Pam, please..
Keep it together until I get there.
Can you do that for me?
Please, please, hurry !
Mr. Mahone, you can't get on a plane.
You need to stay at least another day
for observation.
You were shot !
Mr. Mahone, please.
- I gotta go see my son.
- Mr. Mahone, I understand.
Please.
At least stay and talk to a doctor.
How's your boy?
Tib-fib fractures are bad.
but if the growth's plate is affected,
there's a whole host of problems.
- You made a mistake.
- No, you did.
You think you can just quit
like you work at a post office?
Now you're needed back in.
Go clean up your mess.
Maybe there won't be another accident
on the streets of Durango, Colorado.
Understand?
Every road shut down,
every car stopped and searched.
I don't care if it's
a group of nuns touring Yellowstone.
Their camper gets turned inside out.
Logistically speaking,
- every road's gonna take some time.
- It's Montana.
Not Manhattan.
Get it done.
Yes, sir.
If we get a camera, we can
we can take a picture of him
holding a current newspaper.
If we put that on-line, well,
that'll prove he's still alive.
It'll prove that we found a guy.
that looks like kind of
like the president's brother.
Fingerprints, dental records?
We white-washed him.
pullet out his teeths,
burnt his fingerprints.
DNA.
To compare against the homeless guy
who was killed and put in his car
but
we destroyed all exterior DNA samples,
so that
there'd be nothing to compare them to.
There's gotta be someone somewhere
who can identify this man.
Which is why we did the surgery.
Cheek bones raised two centimeters,
ears lowered a quarter of an inch.
Not so much that someone
who knew him wouldn't recognize him,
but enough that any forensic comparison
of a photograph of that man
would conclude that he is a look-alike.
A hoax.
Trust me.
We are very good at what we do.
Please just let me go.
Terrence, you've made
every man in this room a prisoner,
including yourself.
It's time to set up free.
Nothing you do will work.
They will not let it.
Cut the victim act, Terrence.
He was more than happy to play along
when he was lining his pockets
with taxpayer money
funneled through EcoField.
And then,
when the indictment is about to fall,
who do you come running to for help,
Terrence?
Now we are gonna stay here
for a day or two,
until they think
we're a thousand miles away...
and then we're gonna make our way to DC.
Okay?
So that's the plan?
We take him to a city
crawling with Company and feds?
And government agents, still in power,
who've been working
from inside with your father,
people who can get
that pain in the ass
to safely tell his story, on the record.
And we just stroll right into
he lion's den then, huh?
Pray we don't get mauled.
I don't think
they're gonna come to Montana,
Scofield, so we're gonna go to them.
No, leave her alone!
What do you want with her?
What I want is...
to date her.
I'll make us some more popcorn.
Honey,
if any of us could eat any more corn,
I'd be a-maized.
See what I did there, Gracey?
Indian word for corn is maize
and I said "a-maized."
I don't get it. I'm corn-fused.
You are smarter than a bee sting.
Second female president
of these United States,
right here watching TV with us.
Look what I did.
- Honey, that's all right.
- No, I'll get a rag.
No, I can...
I thought we had wiped the slate clean.
Please.
I thought we had put
the past where it belonged.
We did.
We did put the past where it belonged...
Do not...
lie to me, woman.
After turncoatin' me to the authorities,
after ruin' everything we had,
after breakin' my heart
into so many pieces
that I will never
be able to find them all,
you can at least...
do me the favor as to not stand there
and lie to my face!
Mom?
Zack,
you get your ass back on that couch.
Get Gracey! Go!
I gave y'all a chance.
Remember that.
Open on 22.
Dude, you're crazy.
Is that what the other cons are saying?
Yeah.
- Good.
- But you took it to Banks!
I don't think
you want to be messing with him.
I'll mess with anybody
who tries to punk me out.
Hey, you know I just been..
- testing you.
- Yeah,
well, the test results came back.
And top bunk's mine now.
You got a problem with that?
Hey, what's up, Stolte?
You screwed up, Brad, big-time.
No, I had a message to send,
and that message got delivered.
The guy you schlocked-- Banks--
he's got connections
with the guards working nights.
Word is, Banks is gonna have you
pulled out of your cell tonight.
Well, can't you do nothing?
Yeah, I can warn you,
which is what I'm doing.
Well, can't you talk to
some of the guys working nights?
They're working nights
'cause you put them on nights.
You should've treated the men better
when you were here.
They ain't gonna do you any favors.
I treated you right, didn't I?
Come on, Stolte.
Can't you do something?
Please?
You did treat me right,
but there is nothing I can do now
except warn you.
Watch your back.
we can use the fire roads
that the park rangers use
in Glacier National Park.
They don't patrol them at night.
We get up into Canada, we head east,
we cut down through New York.
The borders won't be a problem.
No, nobody will look for us there.
This is...fun for you, Terrence, really?
No, this isn't fun.
What was fun was when Caroline and I
would talk about you,
and the schoolboy crush
that you had on her.
He proposed to her.
You actually thought that you would be
the First Husband,
the serf who would be king?
We laughed so hard...
You stood there
and watched them kill Veronica!
And you did nothing!
She died because of you!
- What I was supposed to do?!
- Shut up!
Burrows, he has no value to us dead.
He has no identity.
- You kill him, you have a John Doe.
- Put your gun down.
When he puts his down.
Linc, we're so close.
Was it worth it?
- Killing those people, ruining my life?
- Scofield, get a handle on your brother
Shut up. You're not helping.
Linc, you don't want to do this.
Trust me.
This isn't what you want.
You don't want to do this. Okay?
Trust me.
So many people dead.
And he gets to live.
Hello ?
They denied bail.
What?
Judge didn't buy that it was all you.
Case is going into the system now.
Aiding an escaped con.
She's looking at major time, man.
All right, uh...
I want you to tell her lawyer--
all right, you listen to me--
you tell her lawyer...
I love you.
Tell her lawyer I'll turn myself in,
okay?
Kacee said you need to run.
If you get busted or turn yourself in,
Dede won't have either of you.
And they'll just throw her
into foster care.
Look, man, I'm gonna hang up this phone
right now,
'cause I feel
I might say something I regret.
You just take care of Dede.
You know that...my daddy wasn't
really in the picture much
when I was growing up.
So as a result, I never really learned
the art of carpentry.
But I figure, Jesus was a carpenter,
and his daddy wasn't around to teach him
so, I taught myself.
Over time, I got to be
a pretty good swinger of the hammer.
Now, the good news is,
unlike my papa and the Great Almighty,
I'm here for good.
Don't make no mistake about it.
We will be a family...
if it kills us.
So sweet.
Car's out front.
Let's get covered up and move out.
These 2 are never gonna make it
in a car together.
You'll have to keep your brother
- in check.
- You don't know him.
Then get my gun from him.
We don't have time for this.
You still think you're running the show,
don't you?
You still think I'm not?
Yes. I'd like the number for
Channel 11 News, please.
What are you doing?
This is not the plan.
Hang up.
Yes, connect me. I'll hold.
Scofield, you call the news,
they call the cops.
Yes, put me through.
Hang up.
Hang up the phone now!
Hang it up!
Channel 11 News. Can I help you ?
This is Michael Scofield.
I'm at the Cutback Motel, room 11.
And I want to turn myself in.
Brad... ley...
Warden's gone home, bitch.
Mice are gonna play.
Brad... ley...
If anything jumps off,
you get my back, I won't forget it.
Why don't you just forget it right now?
You're in this cell, you're top bunk.
Out there... you're on your own.
You want a piece of me,
you sons of bitches?!
Come and get me!
You hear me?!
I ain't scared of you!
I ain't scared of nothing!
Start praying.
Mr Kim...
I just wanted you to know
that I'm getting back to work.
Good.
So, I take it you got my message.
Oh, yeah.
Loud and clear.
Please, don't do this, please, come on.
I'm sorry, Terrence, it's too late.
The press is already on their way.
You can put the guns away now.
This goes wrong,
you guys are on your own.
- If I go back home, OK, let me, please.
- You can't go back home.
Terrence, none of us can, okay?
So just relax and keep your head.
I'm leaving!
- We can't let you do that, Terrence.
- Terrence, all we need is your mouth.
I will shoot out
both your knees right now.
I never liked you, Paul.
I won't hesitate to take your life!
All right. Just...
Terrence, listen to me.
Just listen.
Terrence, for once in your life,
do the right thing.
All right?
So many people have suffered
because of this, because of you.
But when the press get here,
you can tell the truth.
You can end this.
Where does it end for me?
Disgrace, life in prison?
You're already in prison, Terrence.
How many more people have to die
so you can stay locked up
in some cabin in the woods?
It's over.
- Sorry.
- Terrence, no!
All right. We have to go.
Go where?
We got Steadman.
No, we have nothing.
All we got is a John Doe.
Michael, let's go.
www.tvsubtitles.net