Previously on Prison Break.
We're through the hard part.
Another 18 inches,
we'll hit that pipe.
We'll be there by Friday.
Now we got a hell of a lot
to talk about, don't we?
This guy says he's
on the job in here.
Concrete is my specialty.
Okay, boss, sign him up.
Whites don't want you,
blacks don't want you.
You're just caught in the middle,
aren't you? A regular 'tweener.
- Hello.
- It's me.
- It's time.
- Yes.
Why are you so cynical?
Michael, I think there's cynicism
and then there's realism.
There's optimism, hope, faith.
Thank you for trying to make me smile--
not today.
You never know.
You want the Cooper story? I can't
give it to you, 'cause I'm not him.
The lawyers you tried to blow up,
they're still running around.
Same thing goes with the kid.
You got to hand the
reins over to me, now.
First of all... Ow!
You and your partner are off
the job until further notice.
That one.
- Nice choice.
- Thanks.
Platinum.
Brushed.
- Six point two five?
- Six point two five.
She's a lucky woman.
Yes. She is.
You kept it.
Kept what?
The flower.
I'm a pack rat,
I never throw anything out.
Yeah, all this clutter,
it's, uh... overwhelming.
You should see my apartment.
Haven't even had
our first date yet,
and already you're
inviting me in.
Thought you were a nice girl.
Oh, Michael,
we all know nice girls finish last.
So where do you finish?
That depends on where I start.
Deep breath.
Exhale.
Inhale.
Sara, we're backing
up out here.
Right. I'm sorry.
I'm going to get your shot.
This is not what
I signed on for.
What do you want us to do? Want us to
wave the white flag? Call a time out?
I just want to get
Lincoln off death row.
Lincoln?
We just learned that Vice President
Reynolds funneled millions of dollars
in research grants into
her brother's company.
That money was filtered into
millions of small accounts,
that made millions of small
donations to her campaign,
setting her up to be the next
leader of the free world.
This doesn't end with us
stopping an execution anymore.
For me, it does.
Okay. Let's rotate.
Sergeant Sodomy,
you're up next.
Yo.
Come on.
I don't know about you all,
but, uh...
this room is getting a little
too dark for me to dig.
You telling me that there's a hole in
Fox River that you don't want to
get into?
What?
Hey, no one gets hurt.
You know, I got a question.
How come Fusilli over here
ain't grabbing a shovel?
I'm handling arrangements
on the outside.
Really? So what is
that transpo? Paper?
Exactly. That makes
me management.
And that makes us just labor.
Mm-hmm. Now you're getting it.
You know, management better keep a
close eye on the conditions up in here.
Or the labor's liable to go on strike.
You feel me?
Get back to work.
Whoa, whoa. CO's coming.
Put that back up there.
Scofield.
Move it.
It's time for your conjugal.
Your wife is here.
So you're Mrs. Scofield.
You ever done this before?
Had a conjugal, I mean.
No.
Don't worry,
I'm just trying to make conversation.
Clear.
She look familiar to you?
Mm. No, Captain.
I know her from somewhere.
You came.
Of course.
How have you been?
Fine. I found a job.
Good. I'm glad.
Is it awful being here?
Remember the first
place you stayed?
That hotel by the airport?
Only  difference is $69
and the free shampoo.
Always the brave face.
You're still wearing it.
Every day.
I worry about you.
Don't.
Is there anything
else that I can do?
Just what we agreed on.
I  was so nervous when
they were checking.
One question.
Why would you need a
credit card in prison?
See, I don't think the
riot changed anything.
Have you seen the latest
budget cuts for this place?
Another ten percent
from health care.
35% from prevention.
He might be the governor,
but he's also your father.
Maybe he thinks if he cuts
enough they can't afford you.
You understand this is standard
procedure following a
conjugal, Scofield?
Never can be too careful.
All right, bend over.
You have a good time in the
romper room with that Euro?
Whatever you say, boss.
She come around here before?
- First time.
- You sure?
'Cause damn if I don't
recognize her from somewhere.
Maybe she visits
some other con.
Killing two birds
with one bone.
- Catching my drift?
- I wouldn't know.
All right. He's clear, Captain.
Make sure you take
a shower, Scofield.
You never know what some
women can give you.
Swing low
Sweet chariot
Coming for to carry me home
Swing low
You know this one, don't you?
Sweet chariot
Coming for to carry me home.
Come on, give me something.
I thought you was
the musical people.
You know,
parents must be so proud of you, man.
I mean,
hitting the trailer park trifecta.
Racist... pedophile,
and stupid.
You know, it vexes me that...
that I'm made out to be
the bad guy in the room.
It's not like y'all are incarcerated
for stealing Girl Scout cookies.
None of us murdered any
Girl Scouts in the process.
Michael's coming back
from the bone yard.
Alone... alone.
I tell you everything
about me and Maricruz,
and you can't even tell
me you're married?
Later.
Rough day, huh, Scofield?
While the rest of us are
in here slinging concrete,
you got some little girl to play
on your rusty trombone, huh?
The man's got a point.
Just doesn't seem equitable-like.
You know what I'm saying?
Shut up and dig, T-Bag.
I think what the idiots inside
here wants to know is...
while we're digging this hole...
what are you doing?
I'm  going shopping.
We're good.
All clear.
A credit card?
The bulls catch you with that, they'll
be so far up your doggy door, you'll...
Don't worry.
They won't be
catching me with one.
- How you so sure?
- Because...
I don't have a credit card.
Nick?
Help! Please!
I had an accident...
my car... is totaled.
I just need... please...
is anyone in there?
We can't just ignore him.
The hell we can't.
Please!
Help me, please!
Oh, God.
What happened?
Uh... I must have dozed off.
I was driving for 12 hours.
Should I get some
water from the well?
- The well's dried up.
- Oh, God, my leg.
I think there's a
medical kit over here.
No one's going anywhere.
All right.
Say good-bye to junior.
No!
You know how many pints of
blood the human body has?
The answer is ten. Ten pints.
How many do you think Prince Charming
over there on the floor has left?
Eight? Going on seven?
Tell you what-- I'm gonna take him out
to the woodshed, have a little talk.
In the meantime,
I want you to chew on this.
You tell me everything that you have
discovered about the Burrows case,
and who else you've told about it,
and there's a chance
that I might let you go in time
to get Mr. Savrinn to a doctor.
You decide whose life
is more valuable--
the guy waiting to
die on death row
or the guy wishing he'd
die out in the woodshed.
One suit, black.
One pair of socks, black.
One pair of shoes.
Shoelaces.
One small tape recorder.
One gold watch.
You ever stay at
a fancy hotel, LJ?
You know, you leave your room
in the morning, it's a mess.
Wet, dirty towels on
the bathroom floor,
last night's room service
stinking to high heaven.
But then, when you come back at night,
it's all gone.
Fresh towels, clean sheets,
candy on the pillow.
It's just the best feeling
in the whole world,
'cause someone else
cleaned up your mess,
all you had to do
was walk away.
Don't you hurt them.
Okay.
But you got to tell me exactly what
they know and who else they have told,
and nobody has to die tonight.
You just walk away.
Let me clean up your mess.
I don't know what's going on.
I swear to God!
I wish I could believe that.
Bellick assigned me
a new cell mate.
Who'd you get?
Some new fish.
Ran a bump and swipe on an off-duty cop.
Fast hands, faster mouth.
Yo, what's crackin',
my peoples?
Speak of the devil.
Michael Scofield. David Apolskis.
What's up?
I seen you before, right?
You're part of that PI crew.
Maybe you could hook me up.
You know,
a brother needs to make some green--
some cash-eesh,
you know what I'm sayin'?
It pays 19 cents an hour.
19 cents? That's slavery, yo.
That's prison, yo.
And besides,
PI's all full up for now.
All right. I feel you.
But  keep a brother in mind, all right,
if something opens up, you know?
Hell, I'll pay 19 cents an hour to
get me some more time out the block.
Like having another kid.
Already raised one,
I'm too old to do it again.
You ever hear of anything
being stolen from R and D?
Of course.
Bulls steal from
personals all the time.
The problem is,
you never know what's gone until
you're on the outside of the walls.
At that point,
you can't do anything about it.
What if you knew now?
Look, I told you, leave me out
of whatever it is you got going.
I just need to know if you've
seen a guard with a gold watch.
There's a lot of people that can
get you a gold watch in here.
Yeah, but I need this
specific gold watch.
Westmoreland!
Pope wants to see you!
Let's go!
Look, I haven't seen nothing.
But there is this one CO--
word is,
he's the worst thief in here.
My wife just faxed this over
for you from county records.
Copy of Scofield's
marriage license.
She says you owe her big time.
Looks legit. He wasn't trying to
sneak in some whore for a conjugal.
Says here, they got married the day
before Scofield robbed that bank.
Why the hell would he do that?
- Heard from Veronica?
- No. You?
Just a note from LJ saying he's
with her, that he was safe.
But, you know, it's been awhile.
Doesn't feel right.
Feels wrong.
Really wrong.
I, uh...
I've come to a realization.
Either Miss Donovan and that
boy don't like you very much
or they have an unreasonable amount of
faith in your cardiovascular system.
So tell me, Nick,
this all you got?
This  paper trail of an indictment
that never even happened?
Is this it?
We know you don't have a
surveillance tape anymore.
We know you don't have
anybody to testify.
So is this really
all you've got?
Mr. Savrinn, that bullet went
through your teres major,
ripped the lateral
margin of your scapula,
leaving you absolutely no
medial rotation of your arm.
So, if you try to swing that
piece of lumber at me...
...it's gonna feel like your arm
is ripping out of its socket.
Come on, Nick. Mr.
Project Justice.
We both know why you're really here,
don't we?
And it ain't to save
Lincoln Burrows' life.
Inside these walls, I creep and I crawl,
looking for a way out.
But I know it's gonna
be no easy route.
This is gonna be a 12 round...
12 round bout.
With Bellick and
T-Bag on my mind...
...it's grindin' here...
Still interested in
getting in on PI?
Does my mama got
big breastices?
I wouldn't know.
Hell, yeah, she does,
and hell, yeah, I do.
All right, look,
I need a favor.
Word is, you made your
trade as a snatch and grab.
That's right.
I need you to steal something
back that was stolen from me.
What kind of somethin'
we talkin' about?
Just a watch.
Uh-uh, there ain't no such
thing as "just a watch."
Every design has
a different clasp,
every clasp has a
different swipe.
It's Italian, a Remedi.
Gold band,
pearl face, all-weather.
- What year?
- 2003.
There's a butterfly
clasp on that bitch.
- Which means what?
- Hidden deployment.
There ain't no way to snatch it
without the mark feeling it--
which just means I'm gonna have
to get whimsical on this ficky.
I get you this watch,
that mean I get in on some of that PI?
It means I'll think about it--
no promises.
Why you need this
watch so bad anyway?
Let's just say it means a
lot to someone in my family.
Come in, Charles. Sit down.
What's going on?
I've got some bad
news, Charles.
Your daughter is very sick.
She's got esophageal cancer.
Now, she's at Sacred
Heart in Indianapolis.
And she wants to see you
while there's still time.
How much time?
Doctors  say a few weeks.
The problem is, the D.O.C.
is not gonna let you go.
They think you're
still a flight risk.
- She's my only child.
- I know that.
Believe me, Charles,
I've lobbied on your behalf.
It's state policy.
They will only extend furloughs
in the case of funerals.
You're telling me
I have to wait until she
dies before I see her?
Mr. Scofield, looks like I'll be
administering your shot today.
Where's Dr. Tancredi?
We've got a busy schedule today.
She's with another patient.
Hold him down before
he jumps off the cart!
Hold his legs!
Hold his legs down!
Hey, we need a doctor here!
All right. What's happened?
I don't know. The kid was in chow.
Then all of sudden,
he collapsed,
and he started spittin' up his food.
Looks like he's having
some kind of a seizure.
Get him up here,
get him up here.
And make sure he
doesn't hurt himself.
I gonna O2 and a cardio...
Hold him, hold him!
So, Ms. Donovan, how is that background
in real estate law going for you?
It's a big help? Hmm?
You know, frankly,
I think we caught a break.
Lincoln had nailed a
girl with half a brain,
she probably would have brought
this whole thing down already.
But you know what
the worst part is?
That you dragged these
people into this,
knowing that you had no
clue how to get them out.
I mean, if you had just
minded your own business,
people like Leticia Barris--
she wouldn't have a mouthful
of maggots right about now.
Your fiancé would not be
lying in his apartment
waiting for the smell
of his rotting corpse
to let the neighbors know that
something had gone horribly wrong.
That's right--
their deaths are on your head.
You made this mess.
Nobody else. You.
But you're also the one person
that can end it all right here.
All I need to know is
who else you've involved.
So, you just nod,
and I'll know you're ready to talk.
You know, Ms.
Donovan, I think that, uh,
you look a little cold.
Maybe you'll find it
easier to talk...
after you've warmed
up a little bit.
Where is he? What happened?
We got to move.
Come on, we don't have time. Come on!
Come on,
we're getting out of here.
Where are the keys?
My pocket.
Start the car!
Okay. Is he gonna be all right?
Go start the car, LJ!
We're gonna get you to a hospital,
all right?
A gift from my cell mate.
Thank you. And thank him.
The watch--
what's it for anyway?
Thought you didn't want to
know about any of this.
Things have changed.
I want in.
Why the sudden change of heart?
I have my reasons.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but everyone who's in is
bringing something to the table.
How about money?
- How much we talking about?
- I think you know.
I seem to remember several conversations
that ended with, "I am not
D.B. Cooper."
- I lied.
- You lied?
We're cons. We tend to do that.
I checked your alibi.
According to records,
you were incarcerated at the
time of the Cooper hijacking.
My father and I share more than
just a weakness for easy money.
We also share a name.
Charles Westmoreland,
Senior was the one locked up that day.
Now, do you want
the money or not?
No offense,
but it's a little convenient.
You want in, and suddenly,
you're the guy.
How do I know you're
not lying right now?
Hey, Old Man River,
keep it moving.
Hey, Sucre...
I got a question about you
and the rest of the Mexicans.
I don't think I'll
be able to help,
seeing as I'm Puerto Rican.
Geographical semantics, amigo.
I'm speaking about the
general "Latin-o" population.
How is it that a
people so historically
lazy ended up being such a big
part of the nation's work force?
The way I see things,
it's everyone else that's lazy.
Otherwise, there wouldn't be
any jobs for the immigrants.
The ones sitting at home collecting
unemployment, the lazy ones--
it's not us.
You gonna let him talk
about your people like that?
Uh, whatever, Deliverance.
You know what?
We may be a team in here,
but just so that you know,
the minute we get over that wall,
it's every man for himself.
Or sooner.
LJ?
Do you know how the
Russians do things?
They let you live, and they kill
everyone else in your family,
and, well,
any-anyone you've ever loved.
How does that sound?
- Go to hell.
- Oh, come on.
Is that any way
for a lady to talk?
Oh.
What, do you think
I'm an idiot?
I'm just going to
walk into a well?
Seriously, Ms. Donovan.
You all right?
Scofield, no sitting
down on the job.
I want you out here working
where I can see you.
I'm on it, boss.
Move it, Scofield. Move it!
Hey, Brad. Good to see you.
Hey, baby.
All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together for
our next lovely young lady.
Up on the main stage,
it's Jasmine.
Would you like a private dance?
Why don't you sit down
and chat for awhile.
See if we hit it off.
- So, what's your name?
- Brad.
- Yours?
- Jasmine.
Come on... your real name.
- It's Nika.
- Nika.
Now that's a pretty name.
Tell me, Nika, how's your husband
feel about you working here?
I'm not married.
I hope you're lying for
the sake of titillation.
Otherwise, your little visit to Fox
River this morning would have been
breaking the law...
Mrs. Scofield.
We are married.
But they tell all the girls to lie.
It's better for
making business.
I'm not here to
get you in trouble.
I just want to know a little
more about your husband.
Well, he's a very good man.
I'm sure he is.
But even good men do bad things.
Your accent. You're from--
now, don't tell me-- Budapest, right?
- Prague.
- Prague...
How recently did you come over?
Only a couple months, I bet.
You like it here in America?
You know,
I really have to keep moving.
They don't like us to spend
too much time in one spot.
Now I don't want to have to check
into your immigration status...
I just need to know
what Michael Scofield wanted from
you in exchange for the green card.
Nothing.
We met while he was
studying overseas...
I don't want to know what
you memorized for the INS.
Now, either you answer my
questions about Scofield,
or I call my guy in
the Chicago P.D.
And maybe he starts asking
some questions about you.
A credit card.
He asked me to bring him a credit card.
That's it.
Yeah. Trace this call.
Come and get me-- now.
New Glarus, I'm in New Glarus.
No, thanks, I brought my own.
Dorothy Andrews Elston Kabis.
United States Treasurer, 1971.
The year of the D.B.
Cooper hijacking.
DI192589--
the first number in a series of
bills used in the ransom drop.
Thanks for the history lesson.
All it proves is you
did the research.
Same as me.
So, you're married.
Uh, well... not in the
traditional sense of the word.
Michael, we're both adults,
put your cards on the table.
Okay, I'll got first.
Um... as one of the very
few women around here,
I'm used to a certain amount of
innuendo and flirtation
being thrown my way.
I'm not used to enjoying it.
Look, Sara...
It's "Dr.
Tancredi," and please let me finish.
I'm not a jealous woman.
But I am a careful one.
And for some reason,
when I'm around you, I'm not. Careful.
- You don't have to be.
- Yes, I do.
There are so many questions
surrounding you, Michael.
There are way too many.
So here's the deal. Um...
From now on, your shots,
any medical concerns,
they're all fine,
as long as it's doctor-patient.
But personal questions
and favors of any kind,
are no longer a part
of our relationship.
The questions you
have about me...
there are answers.
Quinn!
I was getting worried.
You guys get lost?
We tried to call you again
to pinpoint your signal,
but you never picked up.
Yeah, the battery went dead
on the damn cell phone.
What are you going
to do, right?
So, uh, how'd it go?
I have a broken leg down here.
Yeah, listen, you know, I think
maybe we got off on the wrong foot.
You have bosses, I have bosses.
but at the end of the day,
we're all on the same team.
Right? We're both just trying
to tie up some loose ends.
I could not agree more.
Yeah, so, can you guys get a
rope or a ladder, or something?
What the hell is that?
Hey... Hey!
Just tying up some loose ends.
You stupid son of...
Hey, guys! Hey!
Hey, don't do this!
Don't do this!
Please! My leg's broken, I can't stand!
You have to help me!
You can't just leave him down there.
He'll die.
He's the only one who knows we
don't have the Burrows kid.
The only one.
There's room for you
down there too, Danny.
Don't leave me like this!
Don't leave me! Please!
Please!
You coming back to PI today?
It's getting kind of testy in there,
you know?
Yeah.
I just needed to
find something out.
What the hell is that?
Listen.
Am I supposed to be
hearing something?
Shh. Just hold on.
- There.
- What?
We sat around here for 20
minutes waiting to hear that?
18 minutes, actually.
And, yes.
- What was it?
- Keys.
The guards' keys.
18 minutes is how long we
have between each time
the guards pass beneath the infirmary
windows on their rounds at night.
Cons aren't allowed
outside after hours.
It was the only way I
could find out the timing.
- What does that mean?
- It means...
Four days from now,
on the night of the escape,
we'll have 18 minutes to get the
bars off the infirmary window,
and for all seven of us to get
across the wire and over the wall.
- Is that doable?
- Of course.
What's up?
Nothing.
Hey, I know that look.
What's up?
I hit it! I hit it!
There it is, the pipe!
We're there!
Guys, guys.
Come on, Michael, talk to me.
You want the good
news or the bad?
The good.
Westmoreland and
his money are in.
- What's the bad?
- I've done the math.
It'll take at least 5 minutes for us to
get the bars off the window in
the infirmary.
And two minutes each for us to get
across the wire and over the wall.
So?
We've only got 18 minutes.
We've got too many people.
One of them has to go.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net