Previously on Prison Break
You have hypothalamus Hamartoma,
the doctor feels you need surgery
Otherwise you could die
You are not following direct orders?
Oh, I'm following direct orders, sir.
Just not from you anymore.
I would've died on this table if it weren't for you, Doc.
What?
Time to come home now.
You're going to help me find a new buyer for Scylla.
His name is Vikan, and he's not a buyer, he's a conduit.
Let's go.
And Bagwell's staying here.
I warned you not to screw me over.
It's been a long time, Gretchen. Who's he?
I'm the guy that's holding Scylla.
It's incomplete. There's a piece missing, slick.
I believe you have something that belongs to me.
Come and get it.
Just so it's fresh in your mind, this isn't a magic elixir.
You still need a hospital.
You need real equipment.
Could probably use a doctor
who's still got a license to practice medicine.
First we get Scylla.
Then I'll go to the hospital.
You finished?
Just about.
So, I take it you're ready to talk now?
Actually, I'm ready to meet.
I got a better idea.
Everyone out!
You're surrounded.
Come out with your piece of Scylla, Michael.
You first.
Come out, or I'm going to gas you out.
If it's the latter, I have a full magazine with 30 rounds.
Want to bet at least one of them could outrun you?
What makes you think I'd even keep the piece on me?
Oh, I know you, Michael.
You're not letting that thing out of your sight.
I stand by my original offer.
Come and get it.
Okay.
Stay low. Let the gas rise to the ceiling.
This is a big space, but it won't take many more of those
before we start to asphyxiate.
Where's Lincoln?!
Here we go, Michael.
更多字幕 影视 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
All right, now we take a ride and we pick up Scylla.
Or I put a bullet in your head.
It ain't gonna happen.
Try me.
Good morning.
Okay, all right, now that we all have guns pointed at us,
let's talk, okay?
Fine.
You could start by telling me who I'm talking to, Don?
You're talking to a guy who spent 17 years
in service of his government, all by the book.
You know what the sum total of it was?
Nothing. Nada.
But we're very similar, Michael,
and fundamentally, we want the same thing.
And I have a way to get it.
How's that?
I got a buyer for Scylla.
A guy who wants to destroy the Company as much as you do.
And he's willing to pay a lot of money for it.
How much?
Nine figures in an offshore account of your choosing.
So, there it is.
Or...
you could stand by your principles.
I'll pass.
Look, I burned you, right?
And I'd apologize, but what's the point?
We're all out in the cold now.
But we're not going to be able to hide from the Company
on a shoestring budget.
Who's the buyer?
He's an ex-Company guy with a bone to pick.
Just like your father.
Michael?
I'd need to meet him first.
That can be arranged.
And just so you know, this...
This wasn't personal. This is just business.
We'll be in touch.
We stick to the plan, all right?
We're going to get Scylla.
We wait for Alex to come through on his end.
All right?
WHEELER: Hello, Alex.
You came.
I always do,
to the detriment of my pay grade.
These last few weeks,
I've been part of an off-the-books operation
under the hand of Homeland Security.
Felicia, the people I'm working with,
we're this close to coming up with
the one thing that can destroy the Company:
their little black book. We can get it. Names, numbers.
Look, I don't want to get caught up in some interagency politics.
So, if this is Homeland's show...
Homeland buried the operation. We can't come back in.
But we could still take the Company down.
So, my question to you is:
Who do you know in the Bureau that you can trust?
It used to be you, Alex.
I've lost a lot of things these last few months,
not the least of which is your trust.
But I don't come to you hat in hand.
Scylla is real.
But if you don't want anything to do with it, it's okay.
It's all right; I could walk away.
Yeah, there is someone who might be able to help.
FERGUSON: Sir, there are over ten million faces in Los Angeles.
Even with NSA and CIA satellite links, we're going to be sifting
through millions of gigabytes of image data.
The chances of finding Don Self,
Scofield and Burrows... it's not good.
Well, let's improve the odds.
Self and the brothers
may have stolen Scylla but none of them have
the connections to off-load it.
Add Gretchen's face to the search.
She won't be welcome in Scofield's camp.
So, connect her image with Self's.
We find those two within five feet of each other
anywhere in Los Angeles, and we've found Scylla.
Are you friends with my Auntie Gretchen?
Go play in your room. Mommy will be in soon.
Where's her daddy?
Gretchen doesn't talk about him.
So, Emily doesn't know that you ain't...
That Gretchen's her mama?
No, and I'd like to keep it that way.
Cute girl.
Don't hurt my little girl.
If you have to do something, do it to me.
What do you think I am?
A monster?
You're holding us prisoner in our own home.
I'm just as much a prisoner as you.
Eggshell white. Bold lettering.
Double embossed. I was Cole Pfeiffer.
Respected businessman.
Top salesman in the Northeast Region.
Now I'm back being prisoner
of my own identity.
Theodore Bagwell. Convict.
To hell with it. We are who we are, right?
What were you selling?
Never you mind.
You just pray your sister comes through.
The Company gets destroyed  and we get paid.
It's a great deal.
This guy is just another General Krantz waiting to happen.
Let's say we do sell it to him and the Company burns,
You know what happens then?
Another company is built right on top of that one.
We're not selling.
Sucre pulled it off.
Great.
Is this going to work?
It's like an ultrasound.
It can see through everything.
You're building up a tolerance.
Then we'll up the dosage.
Yeah, I have,
and at this point, a higher dosage would have
more side effects than the tumor itself.
I'll manage without it.
Sit this one out.
Let me and Sucre handle it.
I'm going.
Why can't he understand I need to finish this?
Everything that happened,
it all started with the Company.
Maybe not for Lincoln.
Maybe for him, this all started
with his little brother breaking him out of prison.
Michael, you saved his life.
If anything happens to you,
he spends the rest of his life feeling guilty for that.
Tell me something,
at what point does a noble deed become fanaticism?
Fanaticism is the only way to beat them.
Even if it kills you?
Hey, pop the trunk.
Micheal?
Sucre just sent a text. He's found Gretchen and Self.
Good, good.
You all right?
Yeah, for now.
All right.
-Linc?  -Yeah?
After your trial that day I came to see you at Fox River...
What about it?
I thought you did it.
I thought you killed Terrence Steadman.
Along with everyone else?
But by the time I left, I...
I knew you were innocent.
And I had to get you out of that place.
So, however this plays out,
I have no regrets.
Scofield's hiding something in the washroom.
I think we just found
our missing piece of Scylla. Call Vikan.
I want to talk to my daughter first.
Just call him, okay, they're fine.
I have a history with Vikan.
No money exchanges hands unless I tell him you're legit.
I want to talk to my daughter. Now!
Yeah?
Put the daughter on the phone.
Is there a problem?
Just put her on the phone.
Hello?
Emily, baby, it's your Auntie Gretchen.
Where are you?
I'm not far. Are you okay?
There's this mean man here.
Emily, baby, do you remember the mean man
that used to live with your mommy Rita?
The one that used to yell at you all the time?
Roy?
That's the one.
And what happened to Roy?
He went to the store one day
and never came back.
That's right.
And I think that if you don't like this mean man,
then very soon, he's going to leave
and he's never coming back.
You think so?
Baby, I know so.
All right, that's enough.
Emily, baby, put the mean man back on the phone.
Listen to me. I'm going to call you
in two hours with the exact location of the exchange.
If you don't hear from me,
kill them both.
You expecting somebody?
No.
Look lively.
Hey, buttercup, why don't you
go play with your dollsies or something.
It's okay, honey. Go to your playroom.
Hi, there.
My name is Ralph Becker, and I'm selling Bibles
to raise money for the Church of the Holy Trinity.
And I wonder if I could spend five minutes
of your time and talk about the Gospel with you.
We're a bit, uh, indisposed at the moment, Ralph.
Can you come back tomorrow?
Well, actually, today is the last day of the fund-raiser.
I said we're busy.
We're never too busy for God.
And what's a few minutes
of your afternoon for a place in His kingdom?
You're a bit pushy for a Bible salesman, ain't you, friend?
I'm on a mission.
You're on a mission, right?
-What are you doing?!  -Close the door!
-This guy is Company!  -What company?!
Get me some rope to tie him up with.
This guy is a Bible salesman.
Get me the rope, now!
Good choice for a meeting spot, Alex.
Crowded place. Two exits.
Corner table with a full view of the room.
Looks like you're getting acclimated to life on the run.
I hear you got promoted.
Your own field office, Wheeler.
That's impressive.
When you're neither a disgrace to the Bureau
nor a drug addict, good things can happen.
He's clean, Mark.
Thank you, Felicia.
Look, I know you, Mark.
You're a good agent, ambitious.
So, let me appeal to the side of you
that likes to see your name in print.
Want to be on a short list for Deputy Director? Huh?
Right. Lang filled me in.
You've got solid gold intel.
I don't know if I'm more skeptical of a burned out ex-Fed
or the mythical cabal known as the Company.
You came all the way here for a myth?
What do you want, Alex?
Felicia tells me you have the attorney general's ear.
That's right.
The Bureau is compromised.
Homeland Security is compromised.
I need someone I can trust. Can I trust you?
You get me credible intelligence against the Company...
I'll walk you into the
attorney general's office myself.
We'll get it.
Alex, talk to me.
I think I found someone in government we can trust.
How close are you to getting Scylla?
Very. Michael...
We're in escrow here. You've got to come through with the house.
Don't worry.
We're getting Scylla.
All right.
Look what I found.
Problem is, there's no way to shoot them.
Yeah, we do.
Sucre, go buy some hairspray and a lighter.
What's this?
My resignation.
Lisa, I tried to shield you from everything
I didn't think you could handle.
The only thing you shielded me from
was knowing who you really are.
Now I know.
I wanted a son.
FERGUSON: Sir...
Taken less than an hour ago.
You were right-- Gretchen's with Self.
What are the coordinates?
GENERAL: Your mission is the safe retrieval of Scylla.
one of the Rules of engagement?
there are none shoot on side
Fauntleroy Hotel, downtown.
Who sent you?!
The Church of The Holy Trinity.
Liar!
Are you out of your mind?!
You're beating up
a Bible salesman!
I ain't Scofield.
I ain't Burrows.
This ain't my lot! Leave me alone!
I'm not a part of this
Company!
I don't know anything, I swear.
Look at him! Please, please, just look at him!
Does he look like some kind
of a undercover agent to you?!
They blend in!
That's how they get you!
Okay, his wallet, okay?
He's got a California driver's license.
"Ralph Becker," okay?
He's got a library card and a prayer card.
That is pretty convincing.
Look at this.
"Freedom, Honor, Country.
Southeastern Military Academy, Class of '98."
How many Bible salesman do you know graduate
from a military academy?!
No! I didn't go to Southeastern! It's my kid brother's ring!
He died in Baghdad last year!
It was a car bomb!
I swear!
RITA: Listen to me.
That made sense.
Okay...
that made sense.
BECKER: Please!
We're not going nowhere!
Not till I get a phone call!
It's $25 for the hour.
We don't need a room.
I, uh, I'm looking for my sister.
Her name's Gretchen Morgan.
Can you tell me what room she's in?
You want information, call 411.
How about now?
No Gretchen Morgan.
No refund.
She's about five-seven.
She's got black hair and blue eyes,
and I imagine she'd stand out
in a fine establishment like this one.
Room 308.
Thank you so much.
No urinating in the stairwell.
That's the golden rule.
Yeah?
Yeah, they're on the third floor,
front of the hotel,
just to the left of center.
Got it, thanks.
Third floor up, just left of the balcony.
Why don't you set up on that rooftop over there?
Scylla's almost complete.
Is everything ready on your end?
Let me talk to Gretchen.
No, you're talking to me.
The buyer has touched down.
This isn't the kind of person you keep waiting.
Likewise.
Just make sure he has the money ready.
Listen to me, you mook.
You're in the deep end of the pool now.
At least act like you can swim.
And the next time I call, I want to talk to Gretchen.
No, no, no, you listen to me, okay?
The next time you call, it better be
to tell me that the money's ready, you understand?
Uploaded by Alooloo
Ali-rabeh@hotmail.com
Hello.
I thought you should know
a man and a woman came in looking for you.
Scofield found us. How?
Who cares? Just get ready.
How long ago?
A couple of minutes.
I don't want no trouble in my place!
I'm gonna recon the hallway.
Anything goes down, get Scylla, get out.
I will find you.
Okay.
Michael, like I said before, this is just business.
My ear!
FERGUSON: Don't move!
Get in!
Help me get him in the back of the van!
Michael!
What is that?
It's the warehouse.
The chip.
You sure it's here?
Yeah, I'm sure.
From the schematic, it can only be in one place.
Look, don't be stupid, okay, Gretchen?
You're gonna get your daughter back and your money.
I'll see you in the car.
He was brought in like this.
Who's there?
I'm giving him 10cc's of clonazepam
and taking him downstairs. We'll know more soon.
Try and relax.
Don't worry, we're gonna get Michael back.
How? Self took the piece.
We got nothing to trade for Michael.
SARA: He's sick, Lincoln.
If they haven't killed him already...
We'll get him back, I promise.
Hello.
Hold on.
It's Alex.
Yeah.
Did you get it yet?
No, Self's got it.
All of it.
What?
Just forget about Scylla.
The Company's taken Michael.
Your friend in government-- can he do anything for him?
No, I don't think so.
There's no reason for you to come back, Alex.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
Should have known.
Vikan's meeting us here?
We'll be off the Company's radar here.
Yeah.
We got a problem.
Well, whatever it is, it can wait.
We're in the home stretch here.
Grab the sister and the girl.
I'm going to call you back
with the exact location of the exchange.
I'd love to, but a, uh...
third party has been introduced into the mix.
Who?
I'm not sure yet.
He might be a Company operative.
So kill him.
He could also be a Bible salesman.
Then he should have no problem
getting past St. Peter. Kill him.
Go back in the bedroom
with your daughter. What are you going to do?
Go now!
Please... please, please don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Please... Look, I won't tell anyone!
I won't tell anyone, I promise!
Please don't kill me!
I swear I won't tell anyone.
Don't do this.
I told you to go back yonder, okay?
You don't want to see this!
Cole Pfeiffer ain't here no more.
Just ol' T-Bag.
Our Father who art in Heaven
hallowed be thy name...
You want to be free?
Start now.
Right this minute.
If you pull that trigger...
Cole Pfeiffer is gone forever.
Don't do this.
You know, my daddy was a religious man, too, Ralph,
just like you.
We used to... pray together
in my room at night.
I used to go down to the floor crying
just like you now.
Sometimes when I just couldn't take it no more,
my daddy would recite a particular piece
of Scripture that he was fond of...
"Weeping
may endure through the night..."
"But joy cometh in the morning."
Psalms 30:5.
Rita...
Yeah?
Have you got a car?
My car's in the... it's in the garage.
You get in that car right now
and you drive far, far away from right here,
right now, okay?
Here.
Take this.
Rita...
Thank you.
What are you going to do to me?
I want you to go.
I want you to be free.
Be as free as me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, I got one.
Not Gretchen. It's Bagwell.
I'm bringing him in.
DOCTOR: The growth is malignant.
It's pushing up against his temporal lobe
and it will kill him if it's not removed.
Have you seen
anything like this before?
This advanced?
Once.
Sir...
You'll never guess who just came through the door.
I want to see my brother.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Mr. Burrows, won't be a problem... will you?
This started with me. It ends with me.
Let Michael go.
I think you made the right decision.
Let's go downstairs and see your brother.
Gretchen.
Don... this better be the real thing this time.
It's all here.
Well, no offense,
but I'll check it myself.
So the buyer's on the way?
He will be here shortly.
And he's bringing the money?
Yes, Don, he is bringing the money.
Scylla is complete.
Gretchen, you did it.
What I wouldn't give to see
the look on the General's face.
What the hell are you doing?!
We need him alive to sell this thing!
You heard what he said.
Buyer's already on the way.
You think I'm going to give this clown 30%
for just making introductions?
BECKER: It's the one with the glass door in front.
Okay, we're coming out.
Well?
The attorney general is willing to hear you out.
You know, from where I'm sitting, it looked like...
Your flight to Dulles leaves in 45 minutes.
Can I trust this guy?
We better go.
Come on, Alex, short trip to the airport.
Attorney general's waiting.
There is no meeting
with the attorney general, is there?
Thank you, Felicia.
For everything you've done.
Everything.
What did you do to my brother?
GENERAL: Michael needs an operation to remove a tumor
from his temporal lobe, and he needs it now.
The Company can provide
such an operation at a cost.
What do you want from us?
Not "us," Link...
you.
The price of the operation
is the safe return of Scylla.
You bring back to me what you stole,
and I will make sure Michael gets the finest medical care
in the world.
The Company has science and technology
that's years ahead of anything available to the public.
And it's all right here--
in this facility.
Now I would imagine
that working for me would be difficult for you to accept.
What's this?
Added incentive.
www.tvsubtitles.net