previousely on PB
What are you doing?
I'm trying to remember
those blueprints--
what we lost
to the burn.
Without them, we'll never be
able to navigate those pipes
beneath Psych Ward.
But I need to know
where you got that burn
right now.
Otherwise, your ass
is going to solitary.
I put my blood into this.
Why don't you
elaborate on that?
How about you stop
with all the questions?
You are a glorified
bodyguard, that's it.
Okay, I got it.
Put it down.
You're not a killer.
Get out of the way.
( retches )
You know, maybe they give
you those things for a reason.
Yeah, to keep me in their
invisible freakin' handcuffs.
Hello, roomie.
You were right
about my tattoo.
It is a path.
And I need you
to remember
when you saw it.
Who are you?
Scofield.
Michael Scofield.
Doesn't ring a bell.
We met a while ago
in Gen Pop. Cell 40.
Gen Pop?
General Population.
Officer Bellick assigned
you to my cell.
I have a tattoo,
you drew it.
Haywire, do I look
even vaguely familiar to you?
Are you the guy
who stole my toothpaste?
Yes, yes.
( chuckles )
I stole your toothpaste.
So you do remember.
NURSE:
Candy man.
Mr. Patoshik.
Mr. Scofield.
No, thank you.
NURSE:
Medication is mandatory.
Just a mild sedative prescribed
by Dr. Tancredi. Come on.
MICHAEL:
Then I'll talk
to her directly.
I'm feeling better.
Oh, really?
That's great.
Now take the pill.
Take 'em.
They're good.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Carter, can you come here
a sec?!
Scofield went J-Cat?
Sure did.
I saw it coming, too.
I knew he was going
to crack first time
I saw him.
So he's not coming
back here.
Doubt it.
They got him
in the whack shack.
What about Sucre?
He's in Ad Seg. Why?
Middle cell,
middle tier,
prime piece
of real estate.
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
Maybe.
We promise to keep
it a single for a
couple of months,
auction it off.
Make it happen.
I don't need medication.
Swallow it, or it's going
in the rear door.
All gone?
Nice.
You were right,
Haywire.
I did steal your toothpaste,
and you drew that tattoo
from memory,
and I need you to do it again.
Middle cell, cool in the summer,
warm in the winter.
How much you asking?
How much you got?
$200.
Got a deal?
Deal.
Now get your ass
out of here
and I'll put in
the transfer.
Hey, man,
the toilet's leaking.
Look, it's dripping.
I'll put in
a work order.
It'll be replaced in 24 hours.
You got it, boss.
I heard you was
moving some real estate.
Already been moved.
That Scofield's cell?
Not anymore.
Close up 40!
Is that your daughter?
My wife game me this
when she was born.
Outliving your wife
is bad enough.
Outliving your daughter--
no man should have
to endure that.
How long does she have?
Hospital says a week,
maybe two.
( sharp knock )
( hushed ):
We got us a problem.
Mojo's moving in
Scofield's cell,
and that ain't all.
He's bitching about the toilet,
so Geary's putting in
a work order.
They move that toilet...
They find the hole.
We are all screwed.
How much Mojo
promise him?
$200.
Oh, Gomer, see,
you had me scared
there for a second.
I hear you got a cell.
Not anymore.
And if you were smart,
you'd keep quiet about that.
Hey, look, I'll double
what you're getting.
I'm getting $250.
$500? Ain't a problem.
I ain't talking
cigarettes
and extra chow line
desserts here.
I'm talking green paper
with dead white guys on it.
I said it ain't
a problem.
Come on.
Where?
It's a surprise.
I don't wear a diaper.
I never said you did.
Then what are
you doing?
You got something
in your teeth.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Right there.
I don't.
It's right there in the back.
( gagging )
Come on.
( retching )
Why are you doing this?
I am helping you.
Remember what you used
to call those little pills?
"Invisible handcuffs."
Handcuffs on your mind.
You hate them,
remember?
You got a phone call.
Who is it?
Your son.
It's an emergency.
Oh, L.J., what were you
thinking, kid?
I don't care what happens
to me anymore, okay?
They won. They'll always win.
I just wanted to take one
of them down with me.
Put Veronica back on.
Lincoln?
What are the charges?
Attempted murder.
He's also being arraigned
for the murder of his mother
and his stepfather.
I guess bail's out
of the question?
Exactly.
Anything you can do?
Right now, his only shot
is if we can get him tried
as a minor.
But he needs to show
some remorse.
I need to sell to the court
that he was just a scared kid.
Where his head's at right now,
he won't listen to me.
He'll listen to me.
I need to see him.
Lincoln, there's no way.
He gets tried as an adult,
he may as well sit in my lap
in the chair.
You got to do something,
Veronica.
Okay, I'll petition the D.O.C,
but it's a million-to-one shot
they'll let you out to see him.
All right.
Yo, Trumpets.
Yo, I got to round up
all outstanding debts
that are due ASAP,
all right?
Do it right now?
Like yesterday,
all right?
I'll put it
out there.
Good.
( tires screech )
Are you insane?
You are done, bodyguard.
Lincoln's son,
a 16-year-old pothead,
managed to track you down
and shoot you.
You are now a witness
in his criminal investigation.
I can still
do my job.
You are not to make
a move on Burrows
under any circumstance.
We make that call.
You know what, Trixie?
There are actually higher
agendas here.
Yes, there are,
and they don't belong to you.
Paul Kellerman no longer works
for the Secret Service.
You're just good ol'
Owen Kravecki from now on.
Have I made myself clear?
( fingers snapping )
Hey.
( pats leg )
I need you to focus.
I need you to remember
what you drew.
( sighs )
ORDERLY:
Haywire.
Time for group.
Come on, buddy.
Let's go.
There we go.
HAYWIRE ( whispers ):
It's a path.
MICHAEL:
Yes.
It is a path.
Let's go.
So, what's up, man?
Here's the thing.
You got nothing coming.
All your outstanding markers,
they're mine now.
Is that so?
You got a problem with it,
go cry to your new crew--
T-Bag and the white boys.
Oh...
'Kay, so that's what
this is all about.
This is about staying true
to your own.
C-NOTE:
Well, you know what, man?
I can have tea with
the Grand Wizard of
the KKK if I want,
and I still get my money.
You got that, little boy?
No. We don't got that.
Now, out of respect
for what you once were,
I'm gonna let you walk away.
you were right
The pills don't let me
see the pathway.
That's a pathway to hell.
No, it's not.
It's just the opposite.
I remember.
Whoo! Looks like the
Bank of Africa wasn't
allowing any withdrawals.
Look, we are gonna have to find
another way to get that money,
okay?
Well, then I reckon
it ain't too much
of a problem for our friend here
to rummage up, ain't that so,
D.B.?
A) I'm not D.B. Cooper,
and B)
there's no
visitation today.
Which means that none
of us can get any money
from the outside world.
( frustrated sigh )
I guess that only leaves us
with one real option.
The Kitchen Game.
C-NOTE:
Gambling?
That's your solution?
Uh-huh. Son, trust me.
When I play cards,
it ain't gambling.
There's maybe five people
in this country that can do
what I do with a deck of cards.
So why are you just
bringing this up now?
'Cause if Jesus over
there catches you
sleeving aces in
the Kitchen Game,
well, let's just say
there are lots of knives handy.
Of course, you need 50
bucks just for the sit-in,
and since we don't
have any money,
I'd say we're
in a catch-double-deuce.
You sit right here.
All right.
Take this.
And this.
Oh, no...
It's gone.
That's why I need you
to fix it.
That's why I need
you to remember what
was there before.
Oh, this is bad.
( whispers ):
You can't break a path.
Then it doesn't lead anywhere.
That's right.
That's why I need you
to remember
what was there
before it was broken.
( quietly ):
I remember.
I remember the demons.
Wait, maybe they were pilgrims.
They were pointing the way,
they were saying,
"This is the way,
this is the way."
( exhaling )
I can't see it.
I can see it,
but I-I can't see it.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
( whispers ):
I need you to give
Sucre a message.
Tell him I'm okay,
and that I'm trying
to fill in the blanks.
He'll know what
that means.
You're trying
to fill in the blanks?
Just do it. Please.
What the hell am I gonna do now?
You've been down on 13
as long as I can remember.
Why the sudden interest
in moving?
Second-story units
like this don't come
on the market too much.
I figure since
I'm getting on in age,
maybe it's time
I retired in comfort.
Open on 40.
Make it quick.
Hey... Bob Vila,
it's a cell.
Quit kicking the tires
and make a decision.
I'll give you
100 bucks for her.
You wasted my time.
Get the hell
out of here.
Sorry, boss.
I thought it was a good bid.
Close on 40.
Hello, Benjamin.
Now, let me see,
minted in 19 and...
seventy-two.
That's your buy-in.
The rest is up to you.
( quietly ):
Damn...
Keep walking, peckerwood.
Got the buy-in
for the card game.
Go get our money, boy.
T-BAG:
Unfortunately, you and I
are gonna have to be partners
in this endeavor.
Oh, hell, no.
I don't play cards;
I'm a dice man.
Look, all you need
to know is this:
every time I deal,
you bet big and never fold.
See, if I'm winning every time
I deal, I end up
with a Colombian necktie,
you know what I'm saying?
But if you're the one
raking in all the cash,
well, I seriously doubt
anyone would ever think
you and I are working together.
Excuse me.
I've been all over town--
I can't find a charger for this.
Well, let me check.
Thanks.
How you doing, Savrinn?
Where's your girl?
She's doing her
job, all right?
Filing a petition
down at the courts.
She'll... she'll be at my
place in about an hour.
See, that was easy.
I shouldn't have
to chase you down
to get that information.
Why don't you just
take a step back?
Why don't you remember
who you're talking to,
who I work for?
You need to keep an eye
on Veronica Donovan.
Not some of the time;
all of the time.
'Cause pretty soon,
we're gonna call in our favor,
unless you want
to go back on our deal.
No.
Good.
Be in touch.
Haywire.
Haywire...
did you take your meds?
Come on.
You got something
in your teeth again.
You should be careful
when you tell people
to remember things, Michael.
Because I remember
everything now.
I remember
how you set me up!
How you smashed
your own head...
and had me sent back here.
I also...
remember this.
The pathway.
Your map.
( whispers ):
Your escape.
Give me that.
Don't. Don't.
Now, do I tear this up...
...or do you tell me
exactly where and when
you're doing this?
It starts in the basement.
Okay.
This line leads
from a hatch in the coal room
to this pipe
system here.
And that runs to
the infirmary.
That's how we'll get out.
I just need to get out of
Psych Ward to set things up.
Three days after I'm gone,
I'll come back up
through the basement
and get you out.
You're just telling me
what I want to hear.
No, I'm not.
I need you to let me
get us out of here.
I need you to trust me.
If you try to screw me over
again, I'll kill you.
Hey.
Hey. How did it go?
Filing the petition was easy.
Getting it approved,
that's a whole 'nother story.
You found the charger?
Oh, yeah.
Why didn't you
plug it in?
I was just, uh...
just thinking for a minute.
About what?
Nothing.
We're in business.
What is it?
His entire phone book
is still in here-- 322 numbers.
No open seats. Gotta wait.
C-Note,
crap or get off the pot.
I'm thinking.
We ain't betting
on CPT here, man.
Either you going to see his bet
or you can go outside
and Million Con March
or whatever your people do.
Either way, get on with it, son.
I'm in.
Three bitches,
bitches.
What you holding?
You tell me.
Full house.
Full house?
That's a concept
a Mexican should
be quite familiar with,
eh, Jesus?
She said what?
She said,
in unequivocal terms,
that I was not to
move on Burrows.
Whatever their agenda
is with Burrows,
it is not
the same as ours.
This whole business
with his father--
it interferes with
the one thing
that we set out to do
in the first place--
put Lincoln Burrows
in the ground.
If he lives,
you're the one
that stands to lose,
not the company.
They get themselves
another candidate,
and you're the one that
suffers the brunt of it.
Then maybe it's time
we broke ranks.
We do that, they'd
pull support for the campaign.
You know that, don't you?
That is... if they know, Paul.
( sniffs )
Mmm! Smell that kitty.
Jacks or better,
trips to win.
Last hand. I'm tired
of losing all my money today.
How much you up?
I don't know. $300.
Does it hurt?
What?
The horseshoe up your ass.
Rather be lucky
than good, Ping-Pong.
Misdeal.
Bury the card.
Man, I don't care
if y'all saw my card.
Yeah, I bet you don't.
Bury the card, young blood.
Hey, chill, Wrinkles.
Ain't my fault Saltine here
got a sloppy deal.
Aw, that there
was just uncalled for.
Now, all right. You know what?
I'll tell you what.
I'm going to deal another hand,
you gonna be such a baby
about it.
On a misdeal, you bury the card,
finish out the hand.
House rules.
Warden.
I have some good
news for you, Linc.
Somehow, your lawyer's
petition went through.
The Department
of Corrections
is allowing you a one-
hour visit with your son.
I've never seen one of these
granted before... ever.
Good lawyers.
No lawyer's that good.
I'll make the
travel arrangements,
but this is not going to
be a ride in the country.
You're gonna be Y-cuffed,
and the men are gonna
be heavily armed.
I don't want any problems.
There won't be;
I just want to see my son.
I'll bet all I got.
$82.
You better have some aces
shoved up there
with that horseshoe,
or that pot's mine.
You in or out?!
I'm in.
And I raise you $74.
I said I only got $82 left.
Then I guess you're out of luck.
You never heard of
a gentleman's game?
Yes, I have, but this ain't it.
You want to borrow some money?
Ask your boys.
But I'm in here
to make money, bro.
You want welfare,
you'd better vote Democrat.
If you know
what's good for you,
you'll stay away from me
in the yard.
( sighs )
You think you're smarter
than me?
( alarm ringing )
No! No! No, no, no!
( indistinct shouting
in distance )
There's a pathway--
no, there's a pathway!
There's a pathway!
He's trying to escape!
He's trying to escape--
this is his map!
He set me up!
Zap him!
( electricity surging )
( alarm blaring )
There he is.
Hey boss, I think you
dropped something, man.
That's half a Gino.
So when do I move in?
You don't.
What?
Come on, chief,
now, we had a deal.
Renegotiation:
the price is $700 now.
That ain't right.
I just gave you $500.
What you gave me
was a down payment.
If you can't come up
with the rest, well...
No, no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
One minute, all right?
Man, he's trying
to shake us down.
I'm gonna need that watch.
Not an option.
Look, would you rather
be looking at a picture
of your daughter or
holding her in your arms
once you get outside?
( metal jingling )
Look, man, Father Time
owed me a few bones.
He gave me this in trade.
That should be more
than enough to cover it.
Eh, not bad.
Your problem is somebody already
gave me $700 for the cell,
so you're S.O.L.
No! Hey, whoa, whoa!
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
So you're just gonna
take my money and walk?
Yeah, well,
write your congressman.
Hey.
Hi.
They said you wanted
to talk to me.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
( whispers ):
Please.
Thanks.
Okay.
I made you something.
It's an ashtray.
Um...
I don't smoke.
Yeah, I know. But, uh, they only
let us make these and jewelry,
and I didn't figure you for
the macaroni necklace type.
It's very sweet. Uh...
How about we talk about how
you're doing?
Hmm...
I think we both know
I don't belong here.
I don't remember much
about that night, but
being locked up in Ad Seg,
something must've snapped.
What I'm trying to say is,
I think I've had enough
of arts and crafts.
( giggles )
But that's your call.
And the doctors here do say that
you've been acting fine.
The problem is that
if you don't tell the
Pope who burned you,
he's gonna lock you back up
in Ad Seg.
And after a couple days of that,
you're gonna be right back here.
Michael, I hate
what happened to you,
and I hate that you're here.
But you have got
to let me help you.
If you want to get out of Psych
Ward, and stay out,
you've got to tell the Pope
the truth about that burn.
Out with the old,
in with the new, cons.
I got a message
from your cellie, bro.
He says he's okay
and he's trying to
fill in the blanks.
Did he say he's trying,
or that he already got
the blanks filled in?
Yo, man, I don't know.
I didn't write it down.
Okay. Now you gotta tell him
that I filled in the hole.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm done with
your little secrets
and messages, bro.
I saw Scofield's back.
He's got a burn in the
same spot as the burn
in that guard's shirt.
I don't know
what you're doing
but I have an idea, huh?
And I'm through helping you
until you tell me
what's going on.
I can't, bro.
Then good luck
in the hole, jefe.
No, no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait.
LINCOLN:
Manche.
Who's that?
That's Linc, bro.
Linc the Sink?
Yeah.
LINCOLN:
Come here.
I think we can work
something out.
All I can say is, before I get
out of here, Geary will pay.
Believe that.
No one's getting outta here
if Maintenance goes to replacing
Scofield's toilet.
I got a way
to help you with
your Scofield problem.
What'd you say, Slim?
I said I got a way
to help you with...
Who the hell said
we had a problem?
It's cool, man.
Relax.
Lincoln and Sucre told me
everything.
What in the hell
did they tell you?
Exactly what did they tell you?
MANCHE:
Everything. They said
I can come with you,
you know, on early parole,
if I can help get the Fish
outta Psych.
What're we, the A-Train?
Everyone gets to ride with us?
Why don't you take a walk,
before I give you a smack?
You got another solution
to our situation?
I didn't think so.
Me and my cuz and Lincoln...
came up with something.
Now, it can work...
but it's risky.
( whispers ):
You ready to get out of
this aquarium, Fish?
( wheels squeaking )
Assure me I'll be protected.
Michael, you know
me well enough by now.
Such assurances
are not necessary.
With all due respect, Warden,
if I had been protected
in the first place, none of this
would have happened.
A name.
Geary.
Geary?
He shakes cons down for money,
anything he can get
his hands on.
He knew I went to college,
so he must've...
he must've thought I was rich
or something.
Anyway, when, uh...
when I couldn't pay up,
he held me down with one arm,
and burned me
with the other.
I don't know
what he used, but...
it was hot as hell.
What a surprise.
Disconnected.
250 businesses, 72 residences,
covering all 50 states...
London, Martinique,
Jakarta, Dakar...
All the numbers out of service.
As soon as Quinn
disappeared,
they must've erased
the paper trail within days.
Is there anything
they can't do?
( sighs )
My P.I. buddy in DC.
What if I send him
all this, see if
he can make a connection
between the numbers?
I'll tell him I need it ASAP.
Thank you.
It's no big deal.
I'll just overnight him
all this stuff.
No.
For everything.
For hanging in there,
keeping me going.
Thank you.
Sure.
GEARY:
Guy with a six ERA signs
for four mil a year.
Sucks at his
job, he still
gets a raise.
You suck at your job.
You should ask
the Pope for a raise.
Very funny.
BELLICK:
Warden, what brings you
to our little clubhouse?
Hey, what gives?
Hey, that was a gift
from my old man.
Since when is your name Charles
and your Dad's name Ann?
This is a railroad.
I didn't do nothing!
Don't look at me
like I'm some con.
You're as crooked as scoliosis.
( whispers ):
I don't get caught.
When we get there,
I'll take you out of the Y-cuffs
and put you in a four-piece.
Got it?
Got it, boss.
You play nice,
I play nice.
Understand?
Got it.
She's here.
I've got her.
POPE:
Scofield.
For readmittance to Gen Pop.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
I never thought I'd be so glad
to be back in my cell.
( chuckling )
Um... Pope...
wanted me to
give you this.
TRANSPORT GUARD:
What the hell are
you staring at, anyway?
Everything.
www.tvsubtitles.net