Previously on Prison Break.
I'm so sorry.
They got me and Sara.
LJ and Sara will be traded for Whistler.
Are we clear?
I want a picture of my son and
Sara to prove they're alive.
I will have a court date one of
these days, and you will be there.
- You're on your own.
- Sofia Lugo.
I'm James
Whistler's girlfriend.
- Why does he want this?
- He's just a fisherman.
Tell your fisherman friend
Scofield's brother has this.
- Just take the bounty off Whistler.
- Whistler don't mean nothing to me.
There are ways I can
be of assistance.
Whistler's clear?
Clear as the blue sky, brother.
- So, how are we getting out of here?
- I have no idea.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I just...
I need some money, and I didn't...
I didn't know where else to go.
- I've got about $50.
- No, no.
I'm talking about the millions, papi.
The backpack?
There's all sorts of
cash in that thing.
Need a place to crash, I got your back,
but the backpack's gone.
Any money I dig out
is for my brother.
Remember him? Tall guy, kind of thin.
Busted your ass out of jail.
I feel bad about Mike.
I do, Linc.
But not all of us got exonerated,
you know.
- Pretty clear on that.
- I can't ever go home again.
- You got problems, Sucre?
- You ain't the only one, Linc.
That's right.
We're all guilty of something, man.
All of us. Not them.
I want to help.
But it seems like it's only
getting deeper and deeper.
Look, I just want money to get back
on my feet and that's it, Linc.
Linc?
Never mind.
Doesn't take too long for
a man to become animal, no?
The smart ones go
for his bunk first.
What do the dumb ones do?
Hey, I was here first.
Mampi bitch,
you been here two days.
I was the first one to the shoe,
you sack-in-the-box--
now hand it over.
You're asking for a chicken foot,
friend. You want this shoe?
You're gonna have
to come and get it.
Leave him. Leave him.
I just wanted to express
my thanks for, uh...
for Whistler.
I'm afraid I have no idea
what you're talking about.
My mistake.
Anyway, I thought maybe we could
make some kind of arrangement.
Maybe I could help
out around Sona.
Come here, boy. Leave.
You help me?
I'm the bucky massa here, boy.
Me. Not you.
So if anyone want
anything at Sona,
it's me them will come to.
So do not walk in here
asking for some favor
like we have some understanding.
No, no, no, no, no.
We do not.
The next time you roll
in here like that, boy,
the only thing you ask
me for is mercy. Si?
Scofield, visitor.
Go on, boy.
Now, run along,
your momma calling ya.
That bad, huh?
It's not good. You?
I followed that message
you got from Whistler.
It's all about some book.
A bird guide. Names and numbers on it.
Any clues as about
who he might be?
No. We weren't the only ones
following his directions.
His girl was there,
says he's some kind of fisherman.
Yeah, sure he is.
Listen, man,
I want you to check something out.
Oh, my God!
The way she's holding the paper it's
like she's pointing at something.
- It's too small I can't read it.
- This is today's paper.
She's pointing at Santa Rita.
It's a small town 20 miles from here.
She's trying to tell
us where she is.
I have to talk to her, Linc.
Even if they let you
talk to her, man,
they'll be listening to every
word you say. You can't do that.
We're gonna need more than
the name of that town.
I'm coming up
empty-handed here, Linc.
It's already been
three days and...
I got nothing to show for it.
So, if I can't break
Whistler out of here...
you're gonna have to
break them out of there.
Trad: Fako et Cels (Bloc team)
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
So, what's the deal, mate?
When's moving day?
I'll tell you the plan when
you tell me who you are.
- I'm a fisherman.
- Really? So am I.
You're worried about trusting me?
My life is in your hands.
How am I supposed to know
that I can trust you?
You don't.
- Boo-yah!
- Hey.
Stuart Scott.
Number one, right?
- You watch the SportsCenter?
- Not recently.
Look, I need to get
my hands on a phone.
I need to get my
hands on some pechos.
But that ain't gonna happen either,
is it?
Who you got to call
so important anyway?
Sara.
Absolutely not.
It ain't a request;
it's a dictation of terms.
My brother ain't thinking about
escape till he talks to Sara.
Aw, that's sweet.
I can assure of two things, Lincoln.
One, that Sara's fine and two,
you have a better chance
of banging me on that bar
than you do of talking to her.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'll pass.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, what if that's a
dictation of terms.
It's not a matter of negotiation.
Government rip out all the phones
when they find out bad men in
Sona still setting up deals.
Making bang-bangs just like before.
They just did it over the phone.
Well, if they cut the lines,
maybe we can fix 'em.
There's nothing to fix, bro.
There used to be a whole row
of them all along the wall,
but they're gone now.
If you have no more questions
I'm just gonna get going.
Michael got the bounty off
Whistler's head in two days.
That's more than your people
could do in two weeks.
Show some goodwill.
He'll get his goodwill
when Whistler's out.
One thing you should know about
my brother, he's very stubborn.
You want him to fetch,
you throw him a bone.
How does Michael think he's gonna
get his hands on a phone inside Sona?
What about cell phones?
With all the traffic
moving in and out of here.
Cell phone big no-no.
Only one man has access to it,
and he would never let
a zanahoria like you...
- ... get his hands on it.
- Let me guess.
What is it?
The weekly from your
operations on the outside.
Grave digger dropped it off.
That couldn't be.
This envelope way too thin.
Stuff just moving a little slow
on the outside these days.
Oh, stuff moving slow.
Somebody making it move slower.
Teodoro.
Set up something at the
barber downstairs for me now.
Yes, sir. No problem at all.
You tell that bitch she nick
me with the razor again,
I'm gonna use it 'pon her.
- You're still alive.
- And you're still lovely.
Oh, please,
I haven't showered in three days.
Whatever you smell like,
it's a significant upgrade.
- When I didn't hear from you, I...
- I'm sorry.
- I warned you it might be a bit...
- I know, I know.
It's just...
every time they dragged out a body...
Look at me. I promise you when I leave
this place, it won't be like that.
Okay.
- Were you able to find my book?
- Yeah. But there was this guy.
- He followed me.
- What guy?
- I don't know.
- Did he hurt you?
No, but he took it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
- What did he lo like?
- Um... shaved head, kind of big.
He said to tell you that
Scofield's brother has it now.
- Who's Scofield?
- Okay.
- Hmm? No one.
He's just, um...
he's someone I'm working with.
- He's gonna help me get out of here.
- He's a lawyer?
Basically.
That's why you want
him to have the book.
Look, Sofia, the less you know
about this, the safer you'll be.
The less I know,
the less help I'll be.
Exactly. I just need you to lay
low for a while. Okay, sweetheart?
What the hell is
going on, James?
What is so important
about this book?
Nothing. It just has notes in it,
you know, phone numbers.
It's people who know people who are
going to help me get out of here.
You're lying.
Why would I lie to you?
You're the only person the
world that I can trust.
Come here.
Now, I just need
you to trust me.
- And do what?
- Nothing.
Sign out, please.
- You looking for something, blanquito?
- Yeah, yeah, I am, I am.
- What you looking for then?
- Just a little, uh...
- Little something to pass the time.
- You got paper?
Go down to the lost and
found with the rest of them.
- They'll hook you up proper.
- All right.
I find you sniffing around
where you don't belong,
you'll find yourself
in that ring again...
against me.
I don't like your odds.
Hello?
I want you to check something out,
all right?
Look at her left hand--
like she's pointing at something.
You'd better tell my cousin he'd
better make himself available.
Better him short money
than me short patience.
No comprende, boy?
I need a charge.
Teodoro, go on,
get me laundry, no?
Sure thing, boss-- oh, almost forgot.
I talked to the barber.
She's gonna squeeze you
in today around 2:00.
If that pleases you, patron.
Patron.
I think it's time you made good on
all the bad you've done, Theodore.
You and me, we're going to make a deal.
Lechero has a cell phone.
- I need it.
- No problem.
Shall I turn water into
wine while I'm at it?
Maybe give the guy's
mother a good rodgering?
She'd be a little old
for your tastes, no?
Careful, Pretty. Don't bite the
hand you trying to get fed out of.
I'm not looking for food,
I'm looking for a favor.
Why the hell should I
do you a favor, huh?
Cause unlike your new compadres,
I know who you are,
what you've done and
who you've done it to.
- Let me get this straight.
- You're saying you gonna tell on me?
This here is a religious country,
and I'm willing to bet the good folks
down in Panama don't take too
kindly to rapists and pedophiles.
You want to bet against me?
Listen, mate.
Here's what I know so far.
I know you've got a brother
helping on the outside,
I know he ran into
my girlfriend,
and I know he took a book
from her that belongs to me.
- I'd like it back.
- What's so special about this book?
Well, unless it has directions
out of this prison,
I don't think it should
really matter to you.
You don't know what
matters to me.
You can get that book back
when we get out of Sona.
Oh, yeah?
And when the hell is that exactly?
Because so far I haven't seen bollocks
in the way of breaking out of here.
Okay. Let me tell you
what I know so far.
Some very bad people who have
done some very bad things
want you alive and
out of this prison,
which is why every bone in my body
is telling me to do the opposite.
Then why are you doing it?
You're upset because someone
took a book from you.
This is what they took from me.
So let's be clear.
This is what matters to me,
not you and not your book.
- Hello.
- Cousin, how is it?
- Hey, Augusto. You tell me, man.
- Oh, business is cyclical, don dada.
Ebbs and flows.
Seems like there's more ebbing
than flowing these days, huh?
- You think?
- I'm gonna tell you what I think, man.
I think a black heart is
trying to steal my business.
Is taking advantage
of my situation.
If there are mistakes have been made,
all I need is some honesty, man.
No mistakes, patrón, I swear.
Well, maybe the problem
isn't on the outside.
Maybe the problem is...
Augusto. Augusto?
Battery dead.
The bloodfire!
How me phone come unplugged? Huh?
My battery dead.
None of you know nothing, huh?
Mr. Mahone? Raul Darinda.
I am the public defender
appointed to your case.
That's, uh...
uh, that's great, that's great.
I've been putting together
some notes that I...
- Looks like I have some great news.
- We got you a trial date.
That's really... thank God.
Thank God-- when?
June 13.
Oh, no, no, wait, wait, wait, the...
13th, 13th, that was last week.
- What, we missed it?
- June 13 of next year, Mr. Mahone.
Next year.
How the hell is that great news?
It usually takes
two and a half years
for a non-citizen to
get before a judge.
I've got a guy in, in here,
his name is Michael Scofield
and he will testify
that he set me up
and that he put the
drugs on the boat.
Which will all be taken
into consideration...
A year from now!
I'm going to have to ask you
to calm down, Mr. Mahone.
It's open and shut.
It's a no-brainer for you.
I got a guy who can cop to...
The notion of one inmate taking the
fall for another is not exactly fresh
and usually means someone was
pressured into the confession.
Well, here's the thing, Raul.
I require a certain
medication that they,
well, they just don't provide here,
and I am...
Let's just say that it would
be good for everybody if, um,
- if I got this medication.
- Is that a threat?
No. No, it's a reality,
it's, it's...
It's called Varatril
and if you...
Look, if you are asking me to smuggle
drugs into this prison, then...
No, no, I'm not...
I'm not asking you to smuggle it.
- If you could get...
- Good luck, Mr. Mahone.
So... Wait, you son of a bitch!
- Uh, boss, it's almost 2:00.
- All right.
You want your cell
phone, brother?
No, just be a half hour.
Leave it for charge.
You got 30 minutes
until he gets back.
If that phone ain't back on the cradle,
we're both dead, you hear me?
'Cause my Alabama ass is
not going down alone.
- Yeah?
- Tell Sara to call me at this number.
All right, but this Susan chick,
she hasn't even agreed to it yet, man.
What?
I only have 25 minutes
with this phone, Linc.
I'm meeting her right now, but listen,
Santa Rita ain't a one-horse town.
I hope that Sara can give
us some kind of clue as to where...
Just get her on the line.
Just get her on the line, okay?
- This is a one-shot deal.
- Yeah, I know, man.
- 23 minutes.
- I'm nearly there.
Hey, looks like we got off
on the wrong foot here.
I'm not a violent guy.
It's just that I need that shoe.
I can't hardly walk, and this place--
it changes people.
Oh, I never even got your name.
- Pistachio.
- Pistachio? Now, that's just...
- That's a beautiful name.
- What you want then?
Well, I was hoping we could make
some kind of a deal. Trade.
The only thing sell,
me no want to buy.
I like me men a little more...
How you say, uh... ?
- Not fat.
- Fat? This is all muscle. And I'd prove it
to you if I didn't think you'd take
things south of the border.
Now, hold on. This is a negotiation.
You don't have to...
I no gonna cut you.
I got clients.
Get.
Welcome, patrón.
I'm so honored to have you.
Let's make this quick.
- Where the hell have you been?
- A girl's got to look her best.
- This ain't a game, sister.
- You'd better back the hell up.
It's becoming pretty clear you need us,
so stop pretending you're in charge,
and give us what we
want when we want it.
Starting with the
damn phone call.
- Hello?
- It's me.
- How are you?
- I'm tired. Where...?
- Where are you?
- It's a long story.
As it turns out,
I don't appear to be going anywhere.
I know. I know.
I'm working on that.
Listen, Sara, I miss how we used
to talk. Do you remember...
How we used to talk?
- Yes.
- Oh, good.
Good, because I saw
your picture totay,
and I want you to
know I understand...
I understand the
difficult place you're in.
Michael, listen, I...
I don't want you to think like that.
- Why is that?
- You have to know it's a lost cause.
LJ and I-- we can see it now.
- It's a lost cause. Do you understand?
- No, no. No, I... I don't. I don't.
Help me understand.
All I can think of to help is,
maybe you just need more time?
It's like... It's like they're
giving you until midnight,
and I'm sitting
here at 3:00 a.m.
They're saying I
have to hang up.
- Sara, I love you.
- I love you, too.
Sara? Sara?!
Linc, they were
never in Santa Rita.
- What?
- She said it was a lost cause.
She said she could see
it was a lost cause.
So?
The patron saint of lost
causes is Saint Rita.
She was never telling
us where they were.
She was telling us what they
could see from where they were.
He's on his way. We need to get
that phone back, like, rapido.
- One more thing, Linc.
- Come on, Pretty!
Stall them!
She said, it's like they were
giving us until midnight,
- but she was sitting at 3:00 a.m.
- What the hell does that mean?
I don't know.
Maybe they're near a clock or something.
That's all I got.
Listen, I got to go. It's up to you.
Leave him alone, huh?
Lechero!
There's something
you should know.
What?
I think that barber
might have...
Uh... cut me?
Hmm. No. No. My mistake. I...
In fact, that there might just be
the best shave I have ever seen.
Boy, you look like
you need one today.
I might just do that.
Can't be walking around,
looking all, uh, bhuttu.
Butu.
¿Que paso, jefe?
Who is this?
Find out everything you
can about this number.
Yo!
Don't move.
I want to know what the hell
you're doing to James Whistler.
I'm doing nothing
to James Whistler.
Listen, we're on the same team,
all right?
Take it easy. Just...
Put the knife away.
Put... the knife away.
We're not on the same team.
You want your boy out of Sona,
right? Right?
Of course.
Well, I'm one of the guys
who's going to break him out.
No. I talked to him this morning.
He has a lawyer.
I don't know what he's told you,
or who he is.
- I know who he is.
- Right. A fisherman
that people want out so badly
they're willing to kidnap
my son to get him.
Listen, you need to talk to him.
You need to talk to him.
Where to, my friend?
I'm looking for a statue, a monument.
Uh, Santa, Santa Rita.
- The lady of the lost causes.
- Yeah, that's it.
The red light district.
You looking to party?
Yeah.
- You all right?
- What do you want?
Let you know you don't
have to watch your back.
Make sure I don't
have to watch mine.
My head was a free
ticket out of here.
I don't begrudge anyone who did what
they had to do to try and get it.
Besides...
...you never know when you'll
need a friend in this place.
Where are you from?
Boardman, Ohio.
- Kalbarri.
- Australia. Good fishing.
- You've been?
- Passed through.
Small world.
What the hell are
you doing in Panama?
I'm not really in the mood.
You're that cop, are you?
You know,
I was looking at that Scofield.
I was trying to figure why he
looked so bloody familiar.
Then, just now,
hearing your voice,
I remember watching the press
when that first happened.
And now you're in
here together.
Small world.
You trying to get him out of here?
Extradition or what?
I'm not really in that
line of work anymore.
- What's he all about?
- Scofield. I mean, is he dangerous?
What's it to you?
Just curious...
as to what kind of
chap I'm dealing with.
I guess that depends on why
you'd be dealing with him.
Like I said...
- you never know when you'll...
- Need a friend.
Yeah.
See, one thing about
Scofield is that,
for those that he cares about,
he'll do just about anything.
But he'll screw you three
ways to Sunday if he doesn't.
I can guess which
side you ended up on.
Well...
Thanks for the chat.
You know,
I really just came by...
No, you came by 'cause you wanted
to find out more about Scofield,
but that's cool.
We're squared away.
There. She is there.
That the only thing about
Saint Rita in this town?
That I do not know, my friend.
Excuse me? Is there a clock around here?
A clock, uh...
No. No comprendo.
Excuse me?
Have you seen these people?
- No, senor.
- Huh? No?
Clock.
Clock. Clock.
She said, it's like they were
giving us until midnight.
Give us till 12.
But she was sitting
at 3:00 a.m.
Three...
Sara.
Dad!
LJ!
LJ! Sara!
Hello?
They made a move.
Burrows made a move.
When?
It was the right place.
I just couldn't get to it in time.
Did you see them?
Do they look all right?
As far as I could tell, yeah.
You can keep that.
Keep it as a souvenir and give it
to Sara when this is all done.
Michael, we can do this.
They wouldn't have gone to all
this trouble to put you in here
if it wasn't
possible to get out.
We can do this.
We can do it.
I think we need to talk.
Your friend,
the one in the picture,
you say she's the
reason you're here?
Then we have
something in common.
The woman your brother met on
the outside, her name is Sofia.
She's the reason I'm here.
Well, unless this Sofia is
being held at gunpoint,
we got nothing in common.
But maybe you can start by telling me
why the Company's so
interested in you.
What company?
I don't have time for games.
Okay, okay, look. Look,
I've been splitting time between here
and the Pacific Northwest
running charters.
- Fishing?
- Fishing, sightseeing--
whatever was paying
the bloody rent.
Now, about a year ago, I took a guy out.
He was some sort of naturalist.
He was, uh... he was taking
water samples, measurements.
- What for?
- I don't know.
I didn't really care as
long as the check cleared,
but here's the thing.
A few months later,
I get a call from somebody wanting
to know where I took the guy.
And I told them I
couldn't remember.
But then these, um...
then these government types,
they started showing up at
my flat asking questions,
and I didn't know what to do.
So I got low,
I came down to Panama,
and I moved in with
Sofia full time. Until...
Until the fight at the bar.
Yeah, and then I end up here,
where those same people show up
at visitation saying
they're going to get me out.
And when they do, I'm to take them to
the same place that I took that guy.
That's why I need the book your
brother copped. It's my trip log.
I write notes in the margins,
you know, coordinates, landmarks.
I need to retrace my steps and find
that location. I don't have a choice.
That's a really
interesting story,
but if that book's as
valuable as you say it is,
maybe I should hold onto
it for a little while,
make sure they hold up
their end of the deal.
- You don't get this, do you?
- I need time to be able to...
The only thing I'm responsible
for is getting you out of here.
Whatever's between you and
them is between you and them.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Do you have any idea how
we're going to do this?
All I keep hearing is how no
one gets out of this place.
I think I've heard
that one before.
The sugarcane's so sweet.
The mangoes' so sweet,
the women so...
Well, if it isn't
the entertainer.
- How about a joke for us, boy?
- Not now, fellas, I got to get...
Why don't you do a little
dance for us, huh?
How about a little jig, huh?
Maybe you need an extra hand?
- You got me.
- Yeah, that's right.
I do get you, boy. You might've fooled
him, but you're not fooling me.
- Excuse me, boss.
- I asked you for privacy.
Just came in here to, to...
thank you
for giving me a hand up in here,
but if it's all the same,
I'd just like to be
relieved of my duties.
- What are you talking about?
- There's some, um...
loyalty issues going on,
and I do not want to end up
torn between my fidelity to you
and the reality of having
to keep my nose clean.
I've been around long enough to know
that when the dominoes start falling,
it's the new guy that gets
blamed for bumping the table.
You better stop spinning
and start talking straight.
No! I ain't no rat.
I'm not asking you to be...
a rat.
I'm asking you to
be a friend, huh?
- As I've been with you.
- Okay.
I was walking earlier,
and I heard some voices talking about,
"To hell with Lechero.
I want my cut."
Now, I couldn't tell who it was,
but when I got around the corner,
I recognized the faces-- the very
same faces I've seen in this room.
Now, I got nothing
to gain here, okay?
I'm a nobody with no
hope of being anyone.
But those that surround you have
everything to gain if you fall.
I hope this makes us even.
But what I've given you...
can't be repaid with one favor.
So I deny your request,
and you're going to stay on as my ears.
You'll report back to me everything
you hear when I'm not around.
- How've you been, Michael?
- Better than some, apparently.
You know, it's interesting how
you don't seem rattled at all
by our current accommodations.
Could it be because maybe you're not
planning on being in them much longer?
It's like I told you before, Alex,
this is the end of the line...
- for both of us.
- How about this?
You stop me when I'm wrong.
The Company wanted you
here in Panama alive,
but framed for murder,
and then for some strange reason,
you seemed to really care about
the fate of this Whistler guy,
and I got to tell you something,
he's really curious about you, too.
Let's see, what special talents
do you have that the Company
might make the decision that you're
worth more to them alive than dead?
What do you say there, Mike?
Am I getting warm yet?
I think you better pop another pill,
'cause that's crazy.
Oh, so you don't mind if
I kill him? Whistler?
I think the question is,
"What would the Company mind?"
The question is,
"What would they do to you?"
To the ones you love?
Be careful, Alex.
- Yeah?
- Busy day?
- Not as busy as I'd hoped.
- Look, you had to try.
I probably would've done the
same thing myself if I were you.
But let's be perfectly clear.
You're never going to try
anything like that again.
I understand.
Yeah, but just to make
sure that you do,
I left you a little
something in the garage.
It's by the trash.
www.tvsubtitles.net