- Previously on Prison Break:
- I'm breaking out,
and you're going to make sure
my brother goes with me.
I'm sorry, Henry.
This message is for Maricruz.
I'll be there
in the airport in
Ixtapa waiting for you.
Sucre, down the road,
if you're in trouble,
- post a note on the message board.
- What's it called?
- Europeangoldfinch.net
- That's a bird, right?
Go pack your things.
We're moving.
We will be a family
if it kills us.
Pull this off and
you're halfway home.
- You remember what home is like?
- Stay away from my family!
She needs that medicine--
she can't go two days without it.
- I don't feel good.
- Oh, sweetie...
Michael, I want for
this to be over.
That makes two of us. It's just a
question of looking at whatever it is
your father gave you.
It's just a key.
It's in a lockbox at the
Corona de Oro cigar club.
I'm not a wanted fugitive.
Give me the key. I'll do it.
You want to take a walk?
Miss Tancredi?
I need to have a word with you.
- Miss Tancredi?
- Of course.
Ma'am?
Miss Tancredi?
It's time to go.
Ma'am? They're
going out the back.
Come on, come on.
Pediatrics, please.
Hello.
- Cameron.
- Hi, Dad.
- How are you doing, big guy?
- Good. I'm eating my lunch.
- How is it?
- Pretty disgusting.
Maybe your mom can bring
you some dinner from home.
- Did you see the doctor today?
- Yeah.
He said I can go home this week
as long as I stay
out of the street.
You're a smart young man.
You know how to cross the street.
Are you mad at me?
Listen to me.
No one is mad at you.
And this wasn't your fault.
- I'm the one who should
have been looking out for you.
- You weren't even there.
But I should have been.
Hey, buddy, listen. I got to go,
but I'll call you back later, okay?
Okay. Bye.
Cameron... I love you.
Cam?
Yeah. What have we got on Franklin?
- Nothing new since this morning.
Another witness from the Minnesota
diner robbery gave a positive I.D.
Good. 'Cause I just landed in
Minneapolis 15 minutes ago.
Anything else?
Yeah. The girl. Dede.
Apparently, she's been ill,
some chronic condition.
Fax Franklin's mug shot to every
hospital in southeastern Minnesota.
Already done. With any luck,
she'll get sick enough to need one,
then he'll show his face.
- You don't have kids, do you, Lang?
- Nope.
Call me when you have something else.
I'll take that.
- We didn't get it.
-  What?
And we need to get back in there soon.
Once the Company finds out Sara was
in there,
it won't be long before
they start wondering why.
Find a spot close to
the club and sit tight.
We're going to take the car.
We'll be back in a couple of hours.
Where you going?
Turns out that maybe there's one
member of the club who can help us.
Who?
Pope?
Just a minute.
Henry.
What are you doing here?
Aside from jumping bail and
evading the authorities?
There's something that you need to hear,
but, first,
I need to know if
you'll listen.
I can assure you, Sara,
we've got nothing to discuss.
Sir, please. I need five minutes. After
that, if you want us to, we'll leave.
Who's "us"?
I don't want any trouble.
Good. Because that's
not why we're here.
What the hell are you thinking about,
waltzing in here?
You're a wanted criminal!
In case you've forgotten,
I dedicated my career--
my entire life--
to keeping people like you behind bars.
You're talking about guilty people.
My brother is innocent.
And we may have the
evidence to prove it.
Well, I don't care;
I want you out of here.
It's in a lockbox at
the Corona del Oro club,
- and you're a member.
- Out!
Henry, please listen.
Sara, I'm tempted to say you
should have known better.
But after what you did...
My father was looking into the
Burrows case when he was murdered.
This key is the only thing I
could recover from his body.
Where are we going?
They're hungry.
We've been driving all day.
Chick-O-Stick.
They need real food.
Soon enough, pumpkin.
Alackaday.
Miscreants.
Defilers.
Defacers.
Despoilers.
What is this?
My home.
Aw, no, no, no!
No.
Por favor, please, please.
Okay. All right, sweetie,
why don't you sit over here, okay?
All right. I'm going to go over there
and I'm going to talk to the lady.
All right? You need anything?
You sure?
Okay.
My daughter, Dede,
she's really sick.
She's had this kidney thing
since she was real young.
- Where is she?
- She's sitting right there.
- Have you been here before?
- No. I'm from out of town.
Can I see your insurance card?
Um... no, no. I don't have any
insurance. After I left the army,
- they discontinued my insurance.
- Are you a resident of Hennepin County?
Like I said,
we're from out of town.
You have a driver's license?
Look, I don't have
a driver's license,
an insurance card, or anything
like that, but I do know the law.
You have to see my little girl.
Let me go get my supervisor.
Good.
I don't give a rat's ass
about you or your brother.
I trusted you,
I took you under my wing,
I treated you like my own son.
I believed you!
Day after day, you lied to me.
What kind of a man does that?
A desperate one.
Yeah. Well... you two made a
big mistake coming here today.
You give me no choice.
I'm going to notify the
authorities right now.
I'm sorry...
...but I can't let you do that.
I don't want to
hurt you, Henry.
Said by the man with the gun.
If it's the only way I can convince you,
so be it.
Well, you're not going to
convince me by doing that.
I'm not the man you think I am.
Yeah, well, I have a pretty
good idea who you are, Michael.
If that's true,
then you already know I never
wanted to be in Fox River.
I never wanted to
meet you, Henry.
I certainly didn't want
to ruin your life.
Yeah. Well,
you've done a pretty damn good job.
You're not saying anything to
him I haven't said myself, Henry.
I've looked into this. What he's
saying to you is absolutely true.
I just want my
brother's life back.
I want people to
know the truth.
I'd give anything for that.
I'd lay down my life.
Well, that's easy for you to say,
standing on that side of the gun.
What if I'm standing
on this side?
There are places that can
better serve your needs.
Look, I know my rights, okay?
This isn't a primary
care facility.
We provide necessary care in
life-threatening situations.
Look, I know what this is.
Are you going to wait until she's
dead before you give her some help?
Is that what you're
telling me?!
I'm not going to
argue with you, sir.
This is a hospital,
not a homeless shelter.
A what?
What did you just say to me?
I can't believe you people.
Come on.
The line is a little bit too long, okay?
We'll go somewhere else.
Where are we going?
We got to find another
doctor, sweetie.
Let's go.
Move!
Come on, baby.
Franklin!
Move out of the way!
FBI! Stop!
Stop!
Okay. Okay. Okay, okay.
Just one second, baby.
Baby, you got to get down, okay?
-No! No, sweetie, you got to get down.
- You got to let him go, honey.
- Get down. Get down.
- Honey, you got to let him go.
- Get down.
- No.
Man, she's not letting go.
Don't let her pay
for your mistakes.
You hear me?
I could shoot you right now
and not even think twice.
But you won't.
You spent too much time around prisons
to throw your life away like that.
What the hell are
you trying to pull?
It's simple-- that's the key
to an innocent man's freedom.
Come on, Henry.
We both know there's
something going on here.
Too many people have died.
Look me in the eye,
tell me you don't believe there's
a cover-up going on right now.
I've got no moral
obligations here, Michael.
As far as I know,
Lincoln is as guilty as hell.
Then take a ten-minute drive with me,
and we'll find out.
That's all I ask.
Henry, you've looked into this before.
You've thought about it.
I have.
And I've come to
one conclusion--
this has nothing to do with me.
But I am a man of the law,
and right now, I've got a convicted
felon standing inside my house.
Well, maybe there's something I can
offer you to make you change your mind.
What do you intend
to do with us?
You grease monkey.
You don't deserve minimum wage.
The hell I don't,
working graveyard.
There ain't no man
deserve more pennies
on a dollar per hour than they
got IQ points in their head.
I ain't stupid.
Seems equal stupid
as the rest of you.
Seems to run in the genes.
Teddy. Ten symonyms.
Pick a word.
Destroy.
Ten synonyms for "destroy."
Annul.
Mutilate.
Liquidate. Abrogate. Quell.
Ravage. Expunge. Demolish.
Extirpate. Extinguish..
- Whoo, you see that?!
- Stupid, my pail,
my boy's gonna be president.
How come you ain't studying?
'Cause I'm tired.
'Cause I feel like
a circus freak.
Well... now...
it's in your own best interest.
Don't you understand that? Hmm?
Now, you're going to
be president someday.
You mark my words.
Theodore.
Theodore, do you hear me?
What are you going
to do with us?
We're gonna put
down some roots.
You wanted me dead, Paul.
Just following orders.
Sent me to the chair for
something I didn't do,
all for your president.
You were willing to do that.
Just... following... orders.
Steadman said you loved her.
Steadman was a deranged man
that lived in a locked box.
You don't love someone that
loves power more than life.
Bitter, huh?
Am I?
No offense, but
you're not capable of
understanding the relationship.
Okay, any way you look at it,
there is no light at
the end of this tunnel.
One way or another,
you and I, we die.
Your brother, too.
Which is a shame given
all he's done for you.
I have a sister I haven't
talked to in 15 years.
- Think she's better off for it?
- We'll make it.
What is that, faith?
Yeah, that's faith.
All I see is a black hole.
And sooner or later,
they are going to suck
each one of us into it.
But when they come for me,
I'm going to take as many
of them with me as I can.
She must have really
broken your heart, Paul.
President Reynolds attended a
Chicago fundraiser last night
as part of her two-day
stop in the Windy City.
Reynolds' popularity continues
to soar in the Midwest
with appearances scheduled
in Indianapolis, Detroit
and Flint,
Michigan later in the week.
Mr. Kim...
Sarah Tancredi
surfaced in Chicago.
She was spotted at the Corona
de Oro Club about an hour ago.
- Corona de Oro Club?
- It's a cigar club.
Her father was a member.
He kept a private
humidor there.
Get me a jet to Chicago.
Tell me you're not still
thinking he's going to show.
He's let you down so many times.
You know that.
Maybe it's the baby in me that's telling
me that this time it's going to
be different.
I don't mean to burst your bubble,
but he's not going to show.
Bubble's not burst.
- I got three words for you.
- Yeah?
We gotta run.
Good seeing you, Theresa!
I'm so glad you came.
You're crazy.
How did they know?
You're certain...
about what's in the box?
No,
but it's all we've got.
Thank you, Henry.
You sure about this?
No.
Either way,
you still owe me dinner.
Is that so?
Yeah. First week in Fox River,
you promised me, if you ever got out
of there, you'd take me to dinner.
Well, maybe, after we wrap this up,
we can stop off
and get you a burrito on the
way back to Pope's house.
Scofield, I don't know
what you're used to,
but anything short of a filet mignon
is not going to cut it with me.
It's a date.
Give me the phone.
Hey.
- How did you pull that off?
- I'll tell you later.
- Is he in yet?
-  Yep.
This shouldn't take more
than a couple of minutes.
Any longer than that,
we'll know we've got trouble.
This way. Mr. Pope.
Thank you.
Hey, Warren How's it going?
Did you hear what
happened this morning?
Sara Tancredi came in.
Yeah. So I heard.
Next time,
don't let her get away. Thanks.
Excuse me, do you mind if I borrow
your computer for a moment?
- No problem.
- Thanks.
Pitch in, chitlins!
We can't do this.
We can't live here.
No, of course not like this.
We gonna clean.
We are cleaning!
We gonna rebuild!
You can't do this to them.
Look at them.
Y'all mind coming along
here for a minute.
Come on. I think we're past me waving
that gun around, don't you think?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing is gonna happen to them.
Susan. Susie Q.
Do you think I'd
bring you here to
so sacred a place to me as
this if I meant you ill?
Look at me!
I am not the animal you
think you see before you.
I am the laws of karma
all come down wrong.
Don't you understand?
I don't.
What I'm trying
to say is that...
I am the sin of my father.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I love you.
Because I want you
to understand me.
I am the last in the
line of Bagwells.
The tail end of a
corrupted breed.
The earth, thank God,
shall see no more of our generations.
I cannot procreate, Susan.
And yet,
there's something in that
that gives me great hope.
No more Bagwells shall
roam this planet.
Not with that vile
blood in their veins.
All I want to do is
end the bloodline,
extirpate it,
and start another, afresh.
- A new family.
- Oh, Teddy.
Those children
are my salvation,
my chance to make this
world a better place.
I will be good, Susan.
I will love them.
I will love you.
I will take communion,
be baptized under a truer light.
All I ask is that
you love me back,
just a little.
Or learn to do so in time.
Can you do that, Susan?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Teddy. Teddy. Please, please.
Teddy, I'm sorry.
- Where are we?
- At the doctor's office, sweetie.
Hello. Hello,
I have an emergency in here. Hello?
Hello.
- Hey, you the doctor?
- Need to wait your turn.
No, it is my turn.
This is an emergency right here.
I need you to look at my daughter, okay?
She's not feeling too good.
Please.
Sweetie, hold on, so I can...
All right, look, this is all the
money I got, okay? That's $400.
Please look at my daughter.
What's the matter with her?
She has a kidney disease-- PKD.
Normally, we have it under control, but
I don't like what I'm seeing right now.
Her stomach hurts, okay?
And she's always hot.
How's her appetite?
It's gone. She's always tired,
ain't that right, baby?
All right.
- Hop up here.
- Thank you.
He just wants to take a
good look at you, okay?
May need to run a few tests.
Just do what you
have to do, man.
I'm gonna be right here,
okay, baby?
Okay.
Yeah.
- What's going on now?
- Still in there.
This is taking too long.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here he comes.
- What's happening?
- We got company.
Hello, Henry.
I didn't know you
were a cigar man.
- Who are you?
- Uh, a friend. A colleague, in fact.
We're both in law enforcement.
- I'm not anymore.
- That's right. You're, uh,
retired.
- Know the guy?
-  Yeah.
Looks like the lifestyle's
treating you well. Yeah?
Socializing over
Cubans and cognac?
But that's not what you were doing,
is it?
Henry.
You don't mind if ask you
to empty your pockets?
As a matter of fact, I do.
I'm not going to play
any games with you.
We both know why
you came here today.
I suggest you get out of my way,
young man.
I can't do that.
Unless you'd like to cause serious
trouble for yourself and your family,
I advise you to hand over
whatever it is you found.
Now.
Michael?
Get in!
Let's go!
Linc!
Sara!
Whoa, whoa, it's okay, it's okay.
Easy, easy, it's okay, it's okay.
Ma'am, are you all right?
I don't understand.
We got a call.
Someone said there's a
hostage situation here.
No one knew we were here.
Are you okay? Okay.
Hey, so what's going on?
I'm afraid your daughter
shows signs of renal failure.
She ever had hemodialysis?
No, hemo... No.
No, this has never really gone that far.
What, are you planning
on doing it right here?
We're not set up for it.
And neither is she.
But there is a county dialysis
clinic a few blocks away.
But we're gonna have to
place a catheter in her neck
so she can be examined.
Hold on, sweetie,
this is gonna be a little cold.
It's okay, baby.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, what, what is that?
It's a trocar.
It's used for placing the catheter.
Do we really have
to go this far?
Look.
I'm doing the best I can here,
but you got to
understand something.
Your daughter is sick.
Now, this may look like a
desperate measure because it is.
This is gonna hurt
a little bit.
Stop! Stop.
Come on, baby. Come with me.
I can't do this.
What's going on?
I made a deal with Pope.
You made a deal with Pope?
What kind of deal?
If he came with us and if
we got what we needed,
I said I'd turn myself in.
What?!
We don't even know
what this thing is!
It could be nothing, Michael.
- You know about this?
- Not until it came out of his mouth.
It's the only thing
I could think of.
You two can still finish this.
You'll just have to
do it without me.
I'm not gonna let
you do this, Michael.
There's no coming
back from this.
Hold on.
What's the holdup?
Your brother's right. I wouldn't count
on the courts to show you any leniency
in this.
That doesn't matter.
I said I'd hold up
my end of the deal.
You already did.
I listened to this.
You have something here.
There's gonna be a lot of people
who wish you didn't, but you do.
Listen, Henry...
I'd go now if I were you.
And don't consider
this forgiveness.
In fact, I'm about ten seconds
away from changing my mind.
Thank you.
Okay...
Here, listen...
let's tuck you in, all right?
Come on. Let's go.
Let's just...
let's just sit for a bit longer, okay?
We're gonna go in
a little bit, okay?
You know Daddy loves you
with all his heart, right?
I love you so much.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, baby.
- Yeah.
- Got a call for you.
I'll call back.
I just heard from some clinic up north.
They had contact with
Franklin a half an hour ago.
I think you want to take this.
Put it through.
- Yeah? Mahone.
- Is this the man in charge?
- Oh, yeah.
- My name... is Benjamin Miles Franklin.
And I want to turn myself in.
But I got one condition.
My wife, she goes free.
My little daughter,
she needs her mother.
I don't think I need to make
a deal with you, Mr. Franklin.
And what if I got
something you need?
Your wife was
released an hour ago.
She'll be here soon.
You promise me that
she will be okay.
Just hold up your
end of the deal.
I will.
I'll get you Scofield.
Come on. Here we go.
You think it's a conversation?
One they don't want us to hear.
You ready?
Let's do it.
Synch: Travis
Transcript: Raceman - www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net