Rough night?
I got your message.
What's the problem?
I lost my keys.
Where'd you find them?
Four feet that way.
Must've dropped them.
How you doing?
It's been a while.
Fine. How are you?
Cold.
I, uh...
I need to talk to
you about something.
- Grab some lunch at Fascastti's?
- I have to get back to work.
Speaking of which,
I heard you got fired a few weeks ago.
What was it this time?
You really want to know?
Or you're just enjoying the
view from your high horse?
You know what I want?
To not have to be the older
brother to my older brother.
What you doing here, Crab?
Long time no see, Mr.
Linc. Where you been?
- Here and there.
- Mm.
I'm gonna get your 90 grand,
all right...
Oh, relax, man,
that debt's already been paid.
By who?
Someone who likes to
do people favors.
I don't know what it is you're
thinking you're getting,
but let's be clear
about something.
It's gonna be a few days before
I get the money lined up.
Let's not kid ourselves.
You can't get anywhere
near that kind of money.
So let's talk about
what you can do for me.
Allies are like family.
We have disagreements,
but we always seem to smooth
things out by Thanksgiving.
Okay, if you had to choose...
Vice President Reynolds
or Kathy in HR?
I'll take door number three.
Come on, if you had to choose.
The chick in HR.
Michael never cared much for blondes.
V.
How you doing, Michael?
Um, good. I'm good.
How are you?
I'm okay.
You know, I'm over at Glazer & Ross.
Lawyer #97.
Benefits are good.
How's Lincoln?
You guys haven't talked?
No, not for a few years.
He kind of dropped off the radar.
How is he?
He's, um...
He's... He's Linc.
I don't care who the guy is.
I ain't killing no one.
I must have missed the part
where I gave you a choice.
Black leather jacket.
Two buttons down the front,
three on each sleeve.
One missing on his left--
no, right arm.
Jeans. Faded.
Stain on the right knee.
He does bad things
to good people.
Think of this as
a $90,000 bullet.
You start fresh,
and you keep me
from finding out
if there's someone in your life
you will do something for.
Uh, I should...
I should call you a cab.
You know how you can
tell God is a man?
Shoes.
Oh!
Easy.
I'm sorry.
What?
It's, uh...
You're gonna answer it?
He'll leave a message.
He always does.
Michael, it's Linc.
I need your help, bro.
I'm in something real bad.
I can't get out of it.
I need you to straighten me out.
My head is all messed up and...
Anyway, it's real important, bro.
You gotta call me.
You gotta call me now.
We can't do this.
I know.
I'll call you a cab.
Did we get him?
I believe we did, partner.
Whoo!
Are you kidding?
Nando, we should've
whooped that guy's ass.
Please, only time I
seen you whoop some ass
is when that old man cut
in front of you at Arby's.
And he was, like,
102 and blind.
With a plastic hip.
Oh, my God.
What?
Hey, they're waiting
for you in 4B.
Oh, pull his film.
I'll be there in a  minute.
Okay.
Sergeant Franklin,
you never cease to amaze me.
Is there anything
you can't get here?
All  right, a deal's a deal.
Prison guard duty.
Away from the front.
Safest place you could be.
Thank you.
And my wife and daughter back
home thank you, too, sir.
These cold seams are
pretty significant.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Would you give us
a minute? Thanks.
Have  you been
watching the news?
Why?
It's Lincoln.
I didn't do it.
Terrence Steadman?
The Vice President's brother.
Do you have any idea what
they're gonna do to you?
I didn't do it, man, it was a setup.
I didn't do it.
You knew him.
- Who?
- Steadman.
No.
- You worked for his company.
- So what?
From which you were
fired a few weeks ago.
I loaded containers in the warehouse.
Never met the guy.
What the hell, Mike? You sound
like one of the damn detectives.
- I'm just saying...
- You think I did it?
I heard you owe
someone 90 grand.
- Who told you that?
- People talk.
And I know Steadman
had a lot of money.
I may be a lot of things,
but I'm not a murderer.
Then what were you doing
in that garage last night?
You admitted to the
police you were there.
Honestly, Linc,
I don't know how it's come to this.
And you can't keep
blaming Mom for dying
and Dad for leaving,
because I was there, too.
Difference is, I got out.
Mom had life insurance, I took my half,
put myself through school,
What did you do with
your half, Linc?
Everything's not how
it looks, Michael.
I hope for your sake,
that's true.
Here... here is where we
want the turn to anger.
Trust me,
that won't be a problem.
Now remember to stress his
record as a repeat offender.
We need the public behind us
if we want the death penalty.
And where are we with
Governor Tancredi?
He has aspirations.
He won't be a problem.
Uh, 30 seconds,
Madam Vice President.
The papers have
already crucified him.
The police say they got a phone
call right after the murder
from someone claiming they saw
Lincoln running from the garage.
He was into someone
for 90 grand.
What do you need that kind of money for?
Drugs? Bribes?
Forget about what
you want to be true.
Let's look at this objectively.
- Maybe you should, too.
- I am.
All right, you know what?
I promised I wouldn't say anything,
but I'm getting tired of
you talking about him
like he's some guy from the
neighborhood that you used to know.
He's your brother.
I know, and I know he helped you
out with your dad back in the day,
but you should see the
kind of person he is now--
the kind of people he
keeps friends with.
You want to know what
the 90 grand was for?
- I think I do.
- You.
What  do you mean?
The money you got when you were 18 years
old from your mother's life insurance.
The money that paid
for your degree,
that got you this job,
that bought you your loft.
Your mother never had life insurance.
That money came from Lincoln.
- How?
- He borrowed it.
Knew it would be
tough to pay back,
but that didn't matter,
because he thought you deserved it.
He also knew you'd never accept
it if you knew it came from him.
Michael....
you are where you are
because of your brother.
You're telling me he is
where he is because of me?
Why?
Why didn't you tell
me about the money?
- No need to.
- Lincoln...
Who told you? Veronica?
What did she make of all this?
About me?
I don't know.
Glad she got out
when she did, huh?
You know how she
feels about you.
It's been the same way
ever since we were kids.
Yeah.
Linc...
- I owe you an apology.
- For what?
The night you called.
If we talked,
maybe I could have stopped you...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's not your fault.
Then whose is it?
Listen up.
You need to forget about this.
Move on.
Work hard, do what you do.
I can't do that.
Oh, yes, you can. And you will.
Here's the part I
don't understand.
All the evidence is lining up in
a path that leads directly to you.
They say they have you on tape.
Pulling the trigger.
If you didn't kill
Terrence Steadman...
How the hell did someone
make it look like you did?
Perfect.
Perfect's a strong word, Cuz.
I got strong feelings, bro.
I'm telling you,
she might be the one.
- She from the block?
- Nope. Uptown. Pill hill.
Do you think you could hold
on to a girl from the PH?
I want to take
her out to dinner.
You'll see.
Someplace real nice.
Come on, Fernando.
How are you going to
afford a place like that?
- Open the drawer!
- Hey, hey, okay!
- Open the drawer! Yo, yo!
-Okay, okay!
- Quick! Quick! Quick!
- All right, okay!
Now!
Actually... This is all I need.
Okay.
Appreciate your business, man.
Ah...
I brought you a gift
from the hospital.
Oh! Oh...
I brought you a gift
from the hospital.
I'm telling you,
this is like Christmas.
And you...
work at the north pole.
If the north pole had
gunshot wounds and...
Seriously, I don't know
how you work there.
What do you mean?
I like to help people.
And you like helping yourself.
And you like
helping your friend.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Call somebody!
Who's got a telephone?! Call 911!
Help!
Are you a doctor?
Well, do something!
At ease.
The whiskey that you ordered, sir,
will be here in a couple of days.
That's  fine. I actually brought you here
to talk to you about something else.
Prisoner abuse
report you filed?
Yes, sir.
I need to know how far you're
willing to go with this.
Whatever it takes, sir.
I particularly have no love
for the desert donkeys,
but I do have some for
the Geneva Convention.
Something like this gets out,
might open up our boys to
similar treatment from the enemy.
I understand that, sir.
But I'm not planning on
calling a press conference.
What I'm saying is,
what I saw was wrong,
and someone needs to take
responsibility for it, sir.
All right.
Please take Mr.
Franklin into custody.
What? What the hell
is going on, sir?!
Sergeant Franklin,
I'm hereby recommending
that you be dishonorably discharged
from the United States Army.
What?! For what?
For engaging in illegal,
black market...
You asked me to get that stuff!
I kept it to myself.
Maybe you should learn to do the same.
You can't do this.
You can't do this!
You cannot do this!
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
What say you?
In the matter of The People of The
State of Illinois v. Lincoln Burrows,
on the count of murder
in the first degree,
we find the defendant guilty.
The defendant will remain in
custody until one week from today,
when we commence
the penalty phase.
Lincoln.
I'm so sorry, Linc.
Don't be. It's not your fault.
- Know what I like?
- Hmm?
How after we make love...
you  get this little puddle of
water in your belly button.
Fernando, that's sweat!
And get out of there!
It's disgusting there!
I think it's beautiful.
I think you're beautiful.
What do you want, Fernando?
Oh, you got to give me
a few more minutes.
Stop!
From the future.
What do you want from the future?
Would you run if I said you?
Would you chase me if I did?
I don't get it.
All these commercials show brothers
learning computer skills,
new technologies.
Uncle Sam didn't teach me
nothing but cadence and kill.
You check over at
the Price-Mart?
Ain't hiring.
Especially with a brother with
a dishonorable discharge.
Goes right to the
bottom of the pile.
How long you think you
gonna keep this up?
Until somebody gives me a job.
Nah, I'm talking
about lying to Kacee.
Your unit's been on leave
for a long damn time now.
Pretty soon they gonna stop
thinking you're lucky,
and she's gonna start
asking questions.
Yeah, well, then I need to
start finding some answers.
Look, I happen to know of
an employment opportunity.
Come on, man,
you know I don't get down like that.
- It's just driving a truck.
- Yeah.
A to B. That's it.
Uncle Sam taught you how to
drive trucks, didn't he?
Yeah. He also taught
me to look inside.
It might be illegal,
but it's also rent.
A to B, your call.
Yeah.
They didn't even
let her testify.
- Who?
- Leticia Barris.
And that cop?
Changed his story
a dozen times.
What part of "move
on" don't you get?
After Mom died,
and it was just you and me.
I remember having
trouble sleeping,
never knowing where you were.
But when I'd wake
up in the morning,
there'd be this paper bird,
an origami crane,
sitting next to my bed.
And I never knew what
it meant exactly,
but I figured it was your way of letting
me know you were checking in on me.
Anyway, I looked it up.
The crane.
It stands for
familial obligation...
watching  out for your own.
Maybe it's my turn to
watch out for you.
So, same time tomorrow.
No, man, they're, uh,
transferring me to a prison where
I wait until they execute me.
- Can I still visit?
- Yeah.
It's not that far.
Place called Fox River.
- Fox River?
- Yeah.
Why?
Nothing.
How come there's four?
Well, uh, Mommy's new friend is
coming over for dinner again.
Again?
He just came over last night.
- I like him.
- Well, I do, too.
And I want you both
to be extra polite,
because he's stopping by Malarkey's
on his way home from work,
and he's bringing us
a really good meal.
In fact,
you two go wash your hands.
Evening, Mrs. Hollander.
Don't you look
lovely this evening.
Ay...
- I'm gonna do it.
- Do what?
I'm gonna propose to Maricruz.
Are you serious?
When?
As soon as I can
afford the ring.
So what, like, 10, 20 years?
What's your problem, man?
Why can't you just
be happy for me?
I'm just trying to protect you.
What, you think you can give
her everything she wants?
Takes more than
money to do that.
You know I love you, Cuz.
Just think you should
look at the reality here.
Seriously, Primo,
how are you gonna afford a ring
for a girl like that, huh?
- Open the door!
- Hey, hey, hey, okay, okay!
Now!
Hey, this fine?
Actually, I'm gonna need a
little bit more this time.
Okay, okay.
Here you go.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Anyone asking questions?
Not loud enough to hear.
God, I can't remember the last time
I was this much of a nervous wreck.
School Board,
second term, 1992?
Secluded, no real access roads,
perfect for what you're looking for.
- Only one problem.
- What's that?
It's over $2 million.
Didn't my poor brother, Terrence,
leave something for me in his will?
You'd have to ask your
accountants, ma'am.
Tell them to use that money.
I'm paying for his mistake;
he can pay for the damn house.
And I've been clean
for 18 months now.
I'll tell you,
I've never been happier.
That actually might
be the wrong word.
I'll be honest, there were times I
was using I left pretty damn happy.
But... what I feel is different now.
I feel, uh...
I feel joy.
So here I am.
I know that...
all I can do every day
is the next right thing.
And I think, for me right now,
that means going back to work.
I, uh... I don't know, maybe...
maybe counseling, um...
I want to help people get from
where I've been to where I am.
Hey, Sara.
You used to be a doctor, right?
Uh, I still am, in theory. Why?
Well, I was just thinking that
I might know of a job
opening where I work.
Really? Where's that?
- You ever heard of Fox River?
- The prison?
Yeah. I know it sounds
like a strange idea.
Uh, maybe...
maybe you and I could, uh...
maybe we could talk
about it over dinner.
I got a gift card to the Red
Lobster over off the interstate.
Oh, my God. Um...
Thank you. Really. Uh...
I... Tonight's kind of my night
to work on my resume. Um...
Oh.
Yeah. 'Course.
Sorry. I, uh...
But thank you, really,
for the, um, the referral.
- Fox River.
- Yeah.
You know, math was never my best
subject, either. But, um...
I got through it by
learning some new tricks.
You want to learn
some tricks, Gracey?
- Like what?
- Like your nine-times tables.
Ready? Nine times one is...
Nine.
Nine times two is...
- Eight... een.
- Teen. Yeah.
- Nine times three is...
- Twenty-seven!
Exactly. You got it.
Now keep on going.
Mommy, Mommy,
did you see what Teddy taught me?
Yes. That's great, honey.
Go show your brother.
Zack, look. Nine times one...
Thank you.
Right, right, left, left...
Hey. Um, thank you.
Let me get your change.
You want your change?
Keep it.
- Hey.
- Daddy!
- Hey, sweetheart, come here.
- Hey, there.
- Hey.
You know, I got, uh...
I got to tell you something.
And it's going to be
really hard to hear.
- Okay.
What?
Well, the thing is...
...I'm being shipped back off.
What?
Yeah, um,
my unit just got called back
for another tour, baby.
I can't believe it.
Deployment orders
just came down.
With the Italians pulling
out and everything...
- Tell them no, Daddy!
- Aw.
Yo, B!
Come here, baby.
Can you give me a hand
with something out back?
That's my sister you're
lying to in there.
Which is why I know you're gonna
take care of them when I'm gone.
This is crazy.
Maybe.
So is the way I got
kicked out the Army.
So's the way I got busted
for driving that truck.
And so's the way I feel
about that woman up in there.
She married a military man,
who knows how to take
care of his business.
Now, if I look like one
of these thugs, now...
what do you think
she's gonna do? Huh?
How long you think she's gonna
wait for me while I'm inside?
I don't know, man.
You owe me this, man.
Don't you ever let her know where I am.
You feel me?
Usually, I do this
the other way.
- Why do you want to...
- I want what I want.
You show this to anyone else...
I am calling the
whole thing off.
My therapist said...
she said that I'm
holding too much in
and that I need to confront you
to let you know how
betrayed I feel.
I let you into my life,
my home...
My God,
I let you near my children!
I never touched them.
You should have told
me what you were.
You think you're the only
one who feels betrayed?
I... loved you, Susan.
Real love.
For the first time in my life.
And then to have
you do me like that,
to just throw me out to the dogs,
just toss me out the back door like...
- You're a murderer, Teddy!
- That's not...
I have sinned in the past,
but when I met you, that
person, that one that did all
those terrible things, he died,
and I was reborn.
By the grace of your love,
I was a...
a new man, a better man.
No. That doesn't just erase the man
who killed 6 students in Alabama.
I guess that's
where you're right.
'Cause when you sent me here,
to this place, with these people,
it brought that old,
dirty bastard right back home.
In fact,
there was a candle in the window,
just waiting for me to
walk up them front steps.
You know, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get out
of here someday.
And when I do...
...don't think I won't remember what
your front steps look like, Susan.
It's almost over.
Burrows will be dead soon, and then
things will start getting back
to normal.
I know that you've
been through a lot,
but I promise you,
the worst is now behind us.
My dear sister...
...you have no idea
what I've been through.
Good night, Terrence.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net