Previously on Prison Break.
- What are the charges?
- Attempted murder.
He's also being arraigned for the murder
of his mother and his stepfather.
Don't look at me like some con.
You're as crooked as the scoliosis.
I don't get caught.
- This is as far as you go.
- Come on, bro.
You an we're not bros.
When were planning on telling
us about the money, man?
What money?
$5 million that Westmoreland
planted in the desert in Utah.
I found Steadman.
I'm with him now Linc. He's alive.
What are talking about?
You found Steadman?
Oh my god!
My hand has been in that box
for hours now-- it is dying.
- I can promise you nothing.
- Story of my life.
These?
Keys to a car that's waiting for us
a couple hundred yards from here.
That's the two of
us or five of us?
That's the two of us.
We got company.
How did he know?
It's only a matter of time
before we know everything
that is in Scofield's head--
where he plans to run to,
how he plans to get there.
So when the time comes
that he does get there,
we'll waiting for him.
Canadian and Mexican border
patrols have all the mug shots.
BORTAC is on high alert.
See if we can get the Mexican Border
Patrol to set up checkpoints 50
miles in.
The warden over at Fox River called,
asked to be kept in the loop.
- What should I tell him?
- That he's no longer in it.
That info that you asked for is
on your desk when you get in.
Thank you.
What's the plan, man?
No bars on these doors.
Do what you like.
With what?
We're supposed to be
in Mexico right now.
Sipping on margaritas, waiting for
the heat to dip. That was the plan.
You see, they just used us to dig, man.
We're gophers, that's it.
- Where's Michael?
- He'll be here.
Okay. You know what, Sucre?
Maybe you and I should go and get that
$5 million, you know what I'm saying?
I mean, it's just sitting there in
Tooele, Utah ready to get some air.
You want to stay here?
Then shut your mouth!
You got one more time
to touch me, man!
- All right, guys, chill.
- What?
Hey!
Relax.
Honey, are you sure
you packed everything?
Yummy.
Mm.
Our photos are in the paper.
We're probably all over the news.
Yeah, and you didn't
see that coming?
What's so funny?
The two of you cracks me up.
Here's to amateur hour.
What do you say, saludo?
Yeah, yuck it up, funny man.
Last supper, boys.
This is the part
where we say good-bye.
It's not much.
It's enough to get you started.
Hey, uh...
No, I'm not telling
you where Fibonacci is.
Well, I didn't ask.
I only ask for a quarter
for a phone call.
Make four.
Thank you.
I wonder what happened
to the other guys.
They all had a head start,
except T-Bag.
Yeah, he was,
he was bleeding pretty bad.
Think he's dead?
Are you done?
No. I still have to clean it.
- But you're done?
- Yes.
It's time to move.
We got everything we need.
Just a quick stop in Utah
and then we're off to Mexico.
LJ has a hearing today to determine
if he gets tried as an adult.
I can get him.
It's not the right time.
- When will it be?
- After we go to Mexico.
After we're off the news.
They framed him for
a double homicide.
As soon as he
loses his hearing,
they're going to ship him
out to an adult facility,
so today in the courthouse is
my only chance to get him.
They took Veronica,
they're not going to take my son.
I know. I know.
I would never leave LJ behind,
but we can't do this now.
There's no plan in place.
Believe me,
I know that courthouse.
I've been there more
times than I can remember.
The only person guarding
him's the bailiff.
He carries Mace
and a big stick.
So you're going to bum-rush the
courthouse, that's your plan.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Hey, yo, we're headed out, man.
Well, good luck to everyone.
Stay out of trouble.
This is it, buddy.
I hope you find
the girl, buddy.
She's all I have.
I'll die trying.
- Good luck.
- You be easy, man.
- Adios.
- See ya.
Maybe we'll see
each other again.
You never know, Michael.
Never know.
Tell me everything you
know about the courthouse.
- You get any sleep?
- A couple hours.
Eight of 'em,
I still can't believe it.
This is Exhibit "A" why you don't
let women work in the military,
the police force and especially
inside a male prison,
'cause look what you get.
Dr. Sweetcheeks leaves the door
open for Scofield and here we are.
Sounds like there's a
little bit more to the...
If Tancredi doesn't leave
her office door unlocked,
those eight dirtbags would in the
shoe right now, okay? Bottom line!
- Brad.
- Any updates?
None. They were last seen
at that cemetery in Oswego.
- We'll get 'em.
- They'll get 'em.
It's been handed
over to the FBI.
Well, that doesn't
mean we can't work it.
It does, actually. You and I have
been pulled off the pursuit.
Why?
We're going to
find out shortly.
We have to report to the DOC
headquarters. I will meet you there.
Sir, we can get these guys.
Just give me a couple more
days and I swear I'll get 'em.
Brad!
We've got to go.
No family with
Patoshik, nothing?
Yeah, until about 4 years
ago when he killed them all.
Updated rap sheet on Apolskis.
Take a look when you get a chance.
Oh...
Man, I'm so sorry. My bad.
My bad, bro. I'm sorry.
Scott Kolbrenner.
It's this one here.
Don't touch the radio.
Yeah. Hi.
I'm with the Des Moines Herald.
I'm covering the LJ Burrows hearing.
What time does that start today?
Come on.
Thank you. 3:00.
The hearing lasts a half hour max.
He'll be taken down to transport bay
at ten till to catch the 4:00 van.
So how do we get close to him?
Well, when I was locked up,
I had nothing to do
except study the briefs.
Nick Savrinn's bar number is on
the front page of every one.
We want to talk to LJ,
we just...
- We pose as one of his attorneys.
- Yeah.
Hogwash. That is
absolute hogwash.
Please answer the question.
How was Scofield able to have
exclusive access to you,
pull a shank on you,
and bind you to your chair--
the warden of the penitentiary?
I trusted him.
Obviously, he
betrayed that trust.
Officer Bellick,
is it true that almost all
the inmates who either escaped
or tried to escape worked
in Prison Industries?
That's right.
Why did these inmates have so much
time to dig a hole in the floor
of the guard's break room while
working Prison Industries?
I can answer that.
With all due respect, if any of you
have ever worked a day in a prison,
you would know that, since an
inmate only gets 19 cents an hour,
some are bound to
drag their feet.
Officer Bellick,
is it true you sold the right
to run Prison Industries
to the highest bidder?
- No. Who the hell told you that?
- This is unbelievable.
While we're wasting
time in here,
there are eight escaped
convicts out there...
Were you employed at Fox River as
a correctional officer, Mr. Geary?
Yep.
Yeah, until he was fired
for shaking down inmates.
That will be your last
outburst, Officer.
Were you aware of
any arrangement
Officer Bellick had with any inmate
regarding Prison Industries?
Yeah, he sold it
to John Abruzzi.
John Abruzzi--
who was one of the escaped convicts?
Yep.
We'll get other C.O.s to substantiate
this if we have to, Officer Bellick,
so I'm giving you one chance
to get in front of it.
Did you sell Prison
Industries to John Abruzzi?
Yes or no?
Yes, but at no time was I
aware of any talk of escape.
That'll be all, Officer Bellick.
That will be all!
Warden, you and Officer Bellick
can step out into the hallway.
We'll call for you when
we've reached a decision.
I'm going to get some coffee.
Well, I did my best
under the circumstances.
The good news, sir,
is you had the hand iced,
so I was able to restore
blood flow and...
The bones are bent.
However, I recommend you
get medical attention ASAP.
Meanwhile, some aspirin will help
thin the blood and avoid clotting.
Some antibiotics
and painkillers.
I usually tell the owner of the dog,
cat, whatever, to
coat them with peanut butter so they're
easier to chew but, obviously...
- You did one hell of a job, Doc.
- Well, thank you.
Well, uh...
it's okay for you to leave now.
Oh, I'm leaving. You're not.
- What?
- You heard me.
Look, sir, I haven't seen
anything and I won't tell anyone.
Well, you know...
you know, I fell for that bill of
goods once before. Never again.
Sir, I swear to God
I will tell nobody.
You would,
and I would die in prison.
Please, please, please.
Shh!
Now, you did me a solid,
so I'm going to return the favor.
This can go down humanely
if you don't fight,
but if you pull a
stunt like that again,
it's going to get
inhumane right quick.
Your call.
But, one way or another...
I am putting you down, Doc.
- Lincoln Burrows Junior?
- Yeah.
In here, you got a visitor.
You must be LJ.
Agent Mahone, FBI. Thank you.
Please.
I'm assuming you've heard.
Yeah.
I have to tell you.
What your dad and uncle pulled off...
very impressive.
I've been doing
this 14 years, and
most escapes can be attributed
to dumb luck or brute force.
The level of planning and
sophistication that went into this one,
and eight guys got out.
I really do,
professionally speaking,
have a lot of admiration
for Lincoln and Michael.
Cool. Now we're buddies.
What do you need?
Help me bring them
in... peacefully.
I don't know where they are.
I don't know where they're going.
There's another
way you can help.
- How?
- Go on TV.
I can have a camera crew
down here in a half an hour.
You know what, man?
The murder charge
they put on my dad--
the two murder charges
they put on me--
Everything's been a setup
coming from way up top.
So the fact that you work
for the government--
I got nothing to say.
I'll give you the same advice
that you'd get from the guy
working at the deli downstairs.
Start thinking
about yourself now.
In fact, the sooner the better,
because no one--
not your father, LJ, not your uncle--
is going to do your time.
And, at 16 years old,
you're looking at a long stretch.
How much time you get,
where you serve it,
who your cell mate might be.
You need to start thinking
about yourself. Now.
I want your dad, I want your uncle,
and I'm willing to deal.
Don't wait and let someone
else get the reward.
What's up?
Hey, man, you look familiar.
Did you rush Sig
Ep last semester?
Sig what?
- Sig Ep.
Nah.
Next in line.
- Where to?
- Utah.
How we doing here?
Nothing until tomorrow.
All right, yo, I got 45 bucks.
How far will that get me?
Nick Savrinn.
His bar number is 56437.
I've got a call time with my client,
an LJ Burrows.
- Hello.
- Know who this is?
Yeah.
- Yeah. Nick Savrinn.
- How you holding on?
Doing what I can do.
How about you?
I'm worried about you. I'm sorry
about what you're going through.
Thanks. Word is, uh...
after this hearing, because of my
dad being so high profile, they're...
they're shipping me to an adult
facility in Kingman, Arizona.
Yeah, well, hopefully,
that ain't going to happen.
You hear from Veronica today?
She didn't show up.
They gave me some court-appointed clown.
No. I haven't heard from her.
Hey, this, uh...
this fed came by and
talked to me today.
Yeah?
He wanted me to help try in
getting my dad to turn himself in.
Well, knowing your dad,
I doubt that's going to happen.
Listen up, LJ.
This is real important.
All right.
On the third,
look out for Otis Wright.
You got that?
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
Until then, keep you head up.
- What?
- Just remember that.
I'm going to do everything
I can to get you out.
Hey, Nick...
if you talk to my dad...
tell him no matter what,
I love him.
- Hey.
- Did you get him?
- Let's do this.
Got one more stop.
There is a belief in my religion
which I know to be true
and it applies to everyone,
Hindu or not.
The acts we commit in this life
determine where we go in the next.
And he who commits evil can
never hope for eternal happiness.
Never been a goal of mine, doc.
I'm more a here and now type.
I'll tell you something
I know is true.
The Indians here, the Tomahawk variety,
some of them believe--
well, used to believe before
most of them were slaughtered--
that when a warrior
kills another in battle,
he absorbs that fallen
warrior's spirit.
So this isn't the
end for you, Doc.
You're with me now.
And how are you
doing this fine day?
Uh, I'm great. How are you?
Couldn't be better. Anything in
particular I can help you find?
Just looking, thanks.
Well, if you need any assistance,
just give a holler.
- How are you this fine day?
- Great.
- Can I help you find anything?
- I'm good, thanks.
- Hey.
- We gotta go.
- I just need to pay up.
- Now.
How are you today, officer?
Yeah, they were right, uh...
Well, they were--
they were right back here.
We can make it to the
courthouse on foot from here.
You don't understand--
everything is in that car.
Forget the damn car. We don't have time.
Come on, man, let's go.
Hi.
It is the finding of this
panel that Warden Pope,
you'll be docked two weeks,
placed on three months probation.
Officer Brad Bellick will be
terminated-- effectively immediately.
Mr. Bellick, you can retrieve
whatever belongings you may have
from Fox River;
that will be all.
I've... I've worked at Fox
River since I was 18 years old.
- Being a C.O. is my life.
- And we appreciate that.
Look, you know, we could have saved
a lot of time if you would have
just told us in the beginning that
this was going to be a railroad.
That'll be all, Warden.
There is only one person responsible
for this escape out there.
His name is Michael Scofield.
It's not Officer Bellick. It's not me!
But you need a fall guy, fine.
But you're not gonna be just
taking Officer Bellick's job.
Because even though I am not
proud of many of his actions,
it will be a cold day in hell when
I turn my back on one of my own men.
I quit. That will be all.
If this thing doesn't work out and
you end up going back to Fox River,
I ain't coming to get ya.
I mean,
you are the brains and I am the brute.
Seriously, Michael,
you don't have to do this.
Let's go.
We're good.
You got a call from Nick
Savrinn earlier today.
What was that all about?
He's my attorney.
That's privileged.
Hmm, that's odd because
Nick Savrinn was found dead
in his apartment an hour before
that call came in to you.
Listen up, LJ,
this is real important.
All right.
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
You got that?
You know for someone
who's so convinced that
the government is capable of
so many underhanded things,
you sure are playing
fast and loose with me.
What are you going to do,
throw another fake murder charge on me?
Who's Otis Wright?
- I have no idea.
- I think you do.
And if you don't tell me,
after you're convicted,
I will be in that courtroom
when you're sentenced
and I will hang you out to dry.
Take it to the bank.
Yeah, put me in touch with the
prosecutor in the LJ Burrows case.
I want a meeting.
On the third,
look out for Otis Wright.
Until then, keep your head up.
Otis Wright.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Move it.
I'll escort the boy.
Otis Wright.
Otis elevator on the right.
What is he planning?
Keep it in the holster
and no one gets hurt.
Keep it in the holster.
All right, LJ, hit stop.
He's coming with us.
So just stay cool, stay cool.
Hey, buddy, give me his gun.
Hey, hey...
LJ, give me your hand.
That a boy. Come on.
Hey, back off!
Back off! Back off!
You're not shooting anybody,
neither are you.
Give yourself up and
your kid can walk.
It's the only way he's
getting out of this place.
It's the only way!
Dad!
Dad, you got to let me go.
- No.
- Dad...
You got to let me go!
Up there. Scofield is in the building.
Take him!
You guys go, cover that way. Scofield
and Burrows are in the building!
Freeze! Do not move!
The truck!
- Bradley?
- Yeah, Ma.
What are you doing
home so early?
I had to take...
my personal day, you know,
before they went away.
Shouldn't you be looking
for the convicts?
They got somebody
else doing that, Mom.
You okay?
I'm good.
Okay.
Whoa. All right.
I think we should break a bottle
of champagne across its bow.
If you're intending to get this thing
home for your anniversary tonight,
- I wouldn't recommend it.
- No.
Listen, I want you to know I...
Well, I feel very
fortunate to have met you.
I'm breaking out.
And you're going to make sure
my brother goes with me.
Thank you for calling AutoStar,
Dr... Gudat?
Am I pronouncing
that correctly?
Uh... dead on.
How can I help you today?
I need, uh... directions.
- Where to, sir?
- Utah.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Are you Scott Kolbrenner?
I am. Yeah.
You must be Debra Jean.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes, same here.
It's so funny, 'cause I was almost
ready to leave when you called.
No one else responded.
I guess there's not a lot
of Utah people out here.
- Are you from there?
- No, I just, you know...
I'm headed up there to, uh...
collect an inheritance.
My grandpa died.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
It's all right.
He went out with his boots on.
- So where's your stuff?
- Uh, I mailed it yesterday.
Mailed it?
I've never heard of that.
You know,
you don't want to lug it around.
Plus, I got a boy who works for UPS,
so he hooked it up.
So you want to bounce?
Okay. I'm parked out front.
- Bradley?
- Yeah, Ma.
They just announced
the rewards on the TV.
- What reward?
- The convicts.
For the convicts--
the ones who escaped.
- How much?
- $100,000 apiece.
$300,000 for the animal who killed
President Reynold's brother.
Every whacko in the country is going to
be after those bums now, wouldn't
you say?
Police!
Step out of the vehicle
with your hands up.
- We got to move.
- I can't.
Oh, my God.
I failed him.
Sorry. Sorry.
I sure hope you packed a lunch.
It's going to be a
long ride to Arizona.
Move your ass.
Get men at all the
area hospitals.
Wherever they are,
one of them's bleeding good.
Which means...
they either come to us...
or they die.
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Transcript: Raceman
Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net