Think of this place
like a map of the U.S.
Our cell over there--
that's New York City.
The infirmary, our exit--
that's California.
The pipes beneath our feet,
they're connected to...
- Route 66.
- Our ticket out of here.
Route 66 runs directly
beneath that building.
It's the only building sitting
on top of those tunnels.
All we got to do is
get in there on P.I.
and dig ourselves an on-ramp.
- Which one?
- Right there.
This goes down four feet,
connects to the main line below.
All we've got to
do is widen it,
and we've got ourselves
an on-ramp to Route 66.
I'm going to find out,
you know--
what it is you're
doing up there.
You told me that you had
been up in the crawl space
for P.I., and...
P.I. was never
assigned to go there.
We got you a little
get-well gift.
What's your name?
There was an explosion.
Gas line.
Everyone inside was killed.
The people we're dealing with
won't stop until we're dead.
We can't hide forever.
How about that kid,
the one they say killed his parents?
- Oh, they got him.
- They did?
He's in custody.
I know what you look like,
you son of a bitch!
Philly Falzone.
Words is there's
someone in here
who knows where Fibonacci is
and you're not doing
anything about it.
Help me.
Please.
You'll have to forgive my boy.
He has the, uh, propensity to be a
bit gregarious when he shouldn't be.
Fraternizing in the prison shower.
Come on.
Maybe you ought to
cut the kid a break.
You wouldn't be meddling in my
affairs now, would you, Scofield?
You can't be that stupid.
Not when I'm so fully
invested in your affairs.
What's between you and him...
is between you and him.
That's what I thought you said.
You've got to help me.
You're talking to the wrong man.
This is a matter for the police.
This is my son
we're talking about.
For God's sake, he's missing.
Do something!
You have got to understand,
I am the warden of a prison.
When it comes to the law,
there is absolutely nothing I can do.
Whatever happens out there
is out of my jurisdiction
until it comes
through those gates.
It just did. Let me out.
What?
Let me find him.
I know how he thinks.
I know where he'd run.
Burrows, I would've thought that by now,
under the circumstances,
you'd understand your position
as a death row inmate.
There is no way I can
honor that request.
That ain't true.
You got the power.
In case of a family emergency, you
can grant an inmate supervised leave.
Your son is a prime suspect
in a double homicide.
Hey!
What do you think
this is, siesta?
You see that?
See my face up there?
Any idea how it got there?
Work ethic.
Those two words mean
anything in your country?
You're on PI.
Quit slow-walking me.
I'm not going to warn you again.
What are you looking at?
Bulls find this stuff,
they'll know we're digging.
That's why we got
to get rid of it...
one piece at a time.
Freshmen.
Best put on a jail face, BG.
These crabs see you puckerin',
they gonna bitchify
you in a heartbeat.
Looks like I got to find
something else to call you now.
Why is that?
'Cause you ain't a fish no more. You
ain't the newest con in the tank no...
I could've done something.
No.
T-Bag had his hooks in that kid.
There was nothing you could've done.
I could've told the pope.
He could've transferred the kid
to AdSeg. He would've been safe.
Go easy, Michael.
You didn't even know him.
That makes it okay?
I turned my back on him
because I didn't want to make waves.
It was just...
easier...
to look the other way...
keep the plan safe.
And you did.
But at what price?
That's not how she raised us.
A man's down,
you give him your hand.
She'd roll over in her grave
if she knew what I'd become.
No, she wouldn't.
You've  given me
your hand, Michael.
My son's out there with
a bull's-eye on his back.
Do whatever you got to do to
get us out of here, please.
What are you doing?
I was just looking
for some coffee.
Yeah, there isn't any.
They belonged to my father,
if you were wondering.
How long they been in there?
I  don't know, five years.
You know, Veronica,
we've been through a lot, and, uh,
I'm freaking out here
as much as you are.
But you get this look in
your eyes sometimes like...
like I'm the bad guy.
I don't know who you are, Nick.
You just magically show up like
some knight in shining armor,
ready to save the day...
You know, I... I think you seem
to be forgetting something here.
I'm in the crosshairs
the same way you are,
all for your ex-boyfriend,
who, unlike my father,
is a scumbag criminal
who just happens to be in prison
for the one crime he didn't commit.
You know something? I've got enough
of my own crap to deal with.
You want to go, you go.
Mind if I lamp with you, Cuzzo?
Roll, snowflake.
Hey, man, I'm just...
I'm just-just new, you know?
I'm lookin' for some homies.
I said roll.
What? I... I'm just lawnchin'.
Yeah? Well,
lawnch somewhere else, white boy.
A'ight, y'all.
I'm fittin' to bounce.
Peace.
Boy's a bit confused
about his pigmentation,
but he sure does have spunk,
doesn't he?
Abruzzi?
Yeah?
What are you doing?
What do you mean,
"What am I doing?"
First of the month's
coming up, John.
Yeah, so?
I haven't got my monthly.
What?
I checked my balance online,
it's looking seriously deficient.
Got to be some kind of a mistake,
like an accounting error or...
Yeah.
Tell Falzone that I don't
stand for "accounting errors."
I'm going back into my office
at the end of the day.
Going to check my
balance again.
If it's not up to where
it's supposed to be...
all these privileges you got,
like running P.I....
they're gone.
Get it done, John.
- Falzone Enterprises.
- Get Philly.
Mr. Falzone's not available.
You tell him it's
John Abruzzi calling.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
Well, now you do.
I'm sorry,
he's going to have to call you back.
What? Hey...
I'm sorry.
About  before.
Pressure's getting to us,
that's all.
Good news is nobody
can reach us out here.
My old man made sure of that.
Never even hooked
up a telephone.
Same with the well
and the generator.
You know, I used to think he was some
kind of conspiracy theory wacko.
Turns out maybe he was right.
I can't stay, Nick.
I got to get back.
He's got less than two weeks.
The old man used to call
this his "serious" tie.
He only wore it
when he really...
really meant business.
Be dangerous, you know,
showing our faces again.
Not if they're not
looking for us.
They think we're dead, right?
I know.
How long's that going to last?
Got to be quick,
be smart about it.
Way I see it, we're just
going to be running in circles
if we think we're going to find
exculpatory evidence before
the execution--
proof he didn't do it.
I've gone up against pretty much
every prosecutor in Cook County.
A man gets murdered,
the first person they want to talk to
to see who his real enemies were--
the wife.
You want to go after
the queen bee herself?
Leslie Steadman.
Everyone in town knows the old bird
lunches at the Lexington every day.
With the society set.
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Hey, slow it down.
Slow it down!
Easy, my man.
You're going to give us away.
Bull's coming.
Let's move.
Hurry up, guys. Move it!
Everybody out.
What?
I said, everybody out! Now.
Move it!
Where are we going?
Down there. Around the corner.
And don't move a damn
muscle till I come get you.
Go.
What the hell's going on?
We're so bad, aren't we?
Damn skimpy. Let's go.
You got to give us more
of a warning next time.
I'm sorry.
He just showed up.
Oh, we're going to get caught.
- By who?
- By the warden.
Baby, right now, in this room...
at this moment...
I... am the warden.
Say it.
No, I'm not going to say it.
Come on, baby. Say it.
Say it, baby. Come on!
You're the warden, Louis!
The sneaky son of a bitch.
You think he found the hole?
Another inch and
he'd have found it.
We need to find something
to cover this hole ASAP.
Broke? What do you mean broke?
The C-Corp.
The investment accounts.
Even the offshore stuff,
Caymans, Bermuda.
Philly Falzone
liquidated everything.
Hey, I told you
from the beginning
what would happen
if you screwed me.
And I heeded it.
That's why I warned you from the get-go
not to give Philly power of attorney.
We had that
conversation, remember?
Look, the only real
funds you have left
are the 30,000 in your
wife's pocket account.
-  Now, I could...
- Don't...
Don't touch that.
Nobody touches that but her.
What do I tell her?
You know, about all of this?
Don't tell her anything. Okay?
The statements
are going to come.
- She's going to know.
- Hey, I told you...
Don't... tell... her. Right?
Is that a problem?
Okay, John.
You know where to contact me
if you need anything else.
The same goes for you.
Hey.
Hey!
Philly.
How are you?
So good to see you.
For you,
the answer is always yes, Philly.
Sit down.
Come on, John.
Looks like there's no record of
a Fox River Medical Practice
on our list of
participating HMOs or PPOs.
Okay, that's because we're
a state penitentiary,
and we're actually in kind
of a unique situation here.
Mr. Scofield's insurance policy from
his previous employer hasn't lapsed yet.
For that reason,
the state's demanding that
you pay for his treatment
and not the taxpayers.
Okay... Well, it says here he
already met his deductible...
Okay.
Oh, no, wait, that's his psych
deductible, not his medical.
Sorry, "psych" as
in "psychiatric"?
I give you permission
to call to Philly?
Hey, I asked you
a question, man.
Listen, there, uh...
there's been a restructuring.
This comes from Philly himself.
You  couldn't
deliver Fibonacci...
so I'm The Man in here now.
Hey, jelly wad...
run to the commissary,
get me a bag of chips,
we'll pretend this
never happened, right?
Yeah, I'm telling you, John.
the sooner you face these facts,
the better off we will all be.
I could kill you
in a heartbeat.
Somehow I doubt that.
The sooner you face facts,
the better off we will all be.
You're yesterday's news, John.
What's the word, brother man?
You all cooking brownies or what?
Act your race, milk chicken.
What's your deal, yo?
You got tough buckets or somethin'?
You're a disgrace to your skin,
you know that?
The boy just slipped.
Ain't that right?
Come on, stand up.
All right, cons,
back to your cells. Go!
What's your name, boy?
Who's that?
Shearing.
Shearing, you've heard
about my kid, right?
Take the tray, Linc.
I, uh...
I just need to call him.
Just...
take the tray,
or I'm going to shove it in there
and you can eat it off the ground.
You had a son.
Josh.
Don't do anything stupid, Linc.
I'm not, I...
I just want to ask you a question
then I'm going to let go.
What if it were, Josh?
What if it were your son?
Please.
- Dad?
- LJ. Thank God.
Are you all right?
No. I'm nowhere near it.
What do you mean?
Where are you?
What they're saying about me--
it's not true.
I know it's not true.
They-They killed her.
They killed her. They...
Right in front of me,
right in front of my eyes, man...
- You got to... you got to...
- Why are they doing this?
Listen, listen, you got to step up.
You got to be the man now.
You understand me?
You understand me, LJ?
Y eah.
Okay, I want you
to call Veronica.
Her number is disconnected.
I already tried.
Nick Savrinn. You call Nick Savrinn,
works for Project Justice.
You call him once we're done.
You got it?
Nick Savrinn.
Okay. Okay, I'll call.
I'll call.
All right then.
It's gonna be all right. Okay?
They're here.
Who's here?
LJ? LJ?!
Did you hear that?
Did you hear it?
Do you know what that means?
Why don't you ask your
mom what it means?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You might have trouble getting an
answer out of her right about now, huh?
LJ?
I saw that.
Just getting connected,
that's all.
There she is.
Mrs. Steadman?
I'm Dick Sisler.
This is my associate, Francette Kelly.
We're with the National
Victims' Rights Association.
We provide assistance for
victims of violent crimes.
Gather support for tough-on-crime
political candidates.
Bravo.
Look, if your organization's
looking for a handout, young man,
you can go  through
my business manager.
Ma'am, that is not why we're here.
Actually, may we sit down?
We were hoping you could help us
with one of our more public cases--
the Lincoln Burrows case.
As you know, he's making unfounded
claims that he's innocent.
That others had motive
to murder your husband.
I really don't have time
for a long conversation.
Mrs. Steadman, it doesn't have
to be a long conversation.
If we talked about who had motive to
kill Terrence, we'd be here all day.
- I'm sorry?
- Look around.
Half the people in this place
were shareholders in his company.
Every one of them sat at
my husband's memorial,
and every one of them was
thinking the same thing.
"Thank God he's gone."
Why would they think that?
Money.
As soon as rumors of
the indictment started,
you should have seen
them run for the exits.
I wasn't aware of
any indictment.
It never came down.
He died before it could.
Have anything to
do with EcoField?
Do the math.
CEO of a corporation gets indicted for
fraud, investors start losing money.
Lots of money.
If I didn't know for sure
Burrows pulled that trigger,
I'd say it was any one of these
people in this restaurant.
We're talking half a billion of dollars,
Mr. Sisler.
People have killed
for a lot less.
Not a good position you
find yourself in, is it?
Whites don't want you,
blacks don't want you.
You're just caught in the middle,
aren't you?
A regular Tweener.
We're different,
you and me, lot of ways.
But, you know,
the funny thing is,
we're also a lot alike.
Couple of dogs with runny
noses that nobody loves.
How's that knee, by the way?
What the hell you doin'?
No. No, no, no. Don't get me wrong.
I'm just a friend.
Yeah, a fruity friend.
I don't need none of that.
- Easy now.
- No, no, no.
You think you gettin' up in this,
you got another think comin',
you homo.
You got a foul mouth,
you know that?
Yeah, I do, and you come near me again,
I'm gonna kill you.
Well, then, you're just gonna have to,
little man.
You got to sleep with
one eye open, girlie.
- Bring it on, bitch.
- Oh, I'm gonna.
I'm gonna bring
it on in spades.
Maybe you ought to
leave the kid alone.
And maybe you're in no position to
be telling me my business, hmm?
That's what I thought.
I'm sure you can understand my
reluctance to discuss past patients.
Absolutely.
Uh, my understanding is that under
HIPAA, we're allowed to
share information
as long as it furthers
the care of the patient.
I'm not accustomed to making
inquiries like this, but, I, uh...
I feel like I can
get through to him.
I can help him.
I imagine he needs it in there.
What did you treat him for?
Well, Michael suffered
from a couple of things.
One was a condition called
low-latent inhibition.
I'm sorry.
I'm not familiar with the term.
Well, people who suffer
from low-latent inhibition
see everyday things
just like you or I do.
Like this lamp, for instance.
But where we just process
the image of a lamp,
they process everything.
The stem, the bulb, the bolts,
even the washers inside.
Their brains are more open to incoming
stimuli in the surrounding environment.
Other people's brains--
yours and mine--
shut out the same information.
We have to do it in
order to keep our sanity.
If someone with a low IQ
has low-latent inhibition,
it almost always results
in mental illness.
But if someone has a high IQ,
it almost always results
in creative genius.
Do you think
Michael's a genius?
Well, I think
that word's been derogated
in the media these days,
but in the classic sense of the word,
yes, I do.
You said there was something
else you treated him for.
He came to me with absolutely
no sense of self-worth.
The loss of both parents very
often does that to a child.
But with the
low-latent inhibition,
something interesting
happened to Michael.
He became very attuned to
all the suffering around him.
He couldn't shut it out.
He became a rescuer,
one of those people who are more
concerned with other people's welfare
than their own.
I didn't know all
this about him.
Then maybe you don't
know Michael Scofield.
Yeah.
Oh, Tweener
I... I'm a-comin' I'm a-comin'
Oh, my Tweener Oh, Tweener,
I'm a-comin' for you
I'm a-comin', comin' for you
Is you ready?
Are you ready?
However you want to say,
I don't care
I'm comin' for you
I'm comin', comin',
I'm comin' I'm comin' for you.
Checking my voicemail at work.
Lincoln's son LJ just
left me a message.
He's in trouble.
Hello?
LJ, it's Veronica.
Where are you?
Oh, Veronica, I don't know.
You got to come get me.
We can't, okay? We're not in Chicago.
You have to come to us.
All right. Where's that?
Oh. Oh.
How the hell do they
know where I am?
What's going on?
How the hell do they
know where I am?
LJ...
LJ, I want you to listen to me.
You don't understand.
Everywhere I go, they're there.
I want you to
listen to me, okay?
I need you to come to us.
We're in Lake Mercer.
Where's that?
It's a small town. It's on the Iowa
border. There's a bus station.
Buy a ticket,
and we'll meet you there.
They're still alive.
Looks like a bird in the
hand just became three.
Let's go.
- But the kid's right...
- Let's go.
They're leaving.
LJ, I need to know that you hear me,
okay? Lake Mercer.
Lake Mercer, okay.
All right, bye.
What the hell are you doing?
Delivering yesterday's news.
Your bus leaves from depot
six in just a few minutes.
Thanks.
I, uh...
Uh, just wanted you to know
that if you're looking for someone to
talk to in here, you're not alone.
It's part of my job to counsel inmates
and help them with their problems.
I think I have things
pretty well figured out.
I sort of backed into some
information about you.
I hope you don't mind.
But you have to understand that
there's a reason I became a doctor.
It's in my nature
to want to help.
From what I understand,
it's in your nature, too.
You did a lot of good things
before you were in here--
a lot of community work,
a lot of charity work.
What happened?
The man you're talking about died the
moment I stepped inside these walls.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
United States Secret Service.
Please remain calm.
Remain where you are.
Hey.
Come here.
It's okay.
They're leaving.
Dump the phone, they're tracking you.
We're in New Glarus.
You're safe now, all right?
Received communication
from your attorney.
Please sign this document,
certifying that I inspected the
communication for contraband,
without at any time breaching
attorney-client privilege
by reading the materials
enclosed herein.
It's LJ, I'm with Veronica.
I'm okay. I love you.
What are you grinning about?
Just the fact that I'm gonna be out on
the real world here in a little bit.
The fact that I'm gonna get me one final
piece of tail certainly don't
hurt either.
Nothing like tail,
eh, Scofield?
Son of a bitch!
It ends right now.
Oh, you just screwed some
major league pooch, Pretty.
I'm gonna sing like a whole
tree full of birds now.
Badge!
You want to sing, then sing.
But you know what I think?
You don't have the guts.
You want out of here just
as much as the rest of us.
We got a problem here?
No.
I, uh...
I thought we was, uh,
missing some tools here. My bad.
Get back to work.
Now...
You and I may be stuck together in this
little dance, but I call the shots.
First shot: that kid out there?
You don't touch him ever.
Do we understand each other?
We do.
Out of the way, Julio.
Abruzzi.
You and me,
we got to have a conversation.
How come he didn't
fall through?
What?
I warned you.
I'll get it together.
You got to give me more time.
You've had your time, John.
You tripping on
something, Alice?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Lamp it up in here again,
I'm fittin' to wreck some shop.
Uh-oh. We got a problem.
Bellick.
Boss? Boss.
What's happening?
What they doing?
Fixing the break room.
What are you talking about?
That's P.I.
I run it.
Not anymore you don't.
Transcript: RaceMan
Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net