Previously on Prison Break:
I didn't kill that man,
Michael.
The evidence says you did.
I was set up.
Put down your weapon.
I find it incumbent that you
see the inside of a prison cell.
I'm looking for someone.
A guy named Lincoln Burrows.
The man killed the Vice
President's brother.
Why you want to see
Burrows so bad anyhow?
- 'Cause he's my brother.
- I'm getting you out of here.
That's impossible.
Not if you designed
the place it isn't.
- You've seen the blueprints.
- Better than that.
I've got them on me.
I took some time to
speak to your mother...
If you're talking about
that guy at Fox River...
He refuses to call
him his father.
Take the only thing
Burrows has left.
The chair isn't the only way to
take a man's life in prison.
And now,
scenes from last week's episode.
Constantly coming
up here for count
won't let me do what I need to
do to get through that wall.
Only way to stop
count is a lockdown.
You've got to get
the inmates riled up.
All right, that's it!
Lockdown!
Somebody made an
anonymous phone call.
Whoever made that call
couldn't have seen Lincoln.
How do you know?
Because the phone call
came from Washington, DC.
This is Bellick.
Our wing has been breached.
Hooke's Law of Elasticity.
If we drill holes in
strategic locations,
we compromise the load-carrying
capacity of the wall.
Take the cuffs off.
A rookie CO.
Get out of here, T-Bag.
I think we can work
something out.
No deal.
Where's my daughter?
Not to worry, sir. She's fine.
The guard there assures us
that everything is fine.
We have everything under control,
Governor.
You better hope you do.
They're breaking out.
They're breaking...
Shh.
We need a favor.
Some heavy hitters
want this done so...
Burrows is as good as dead.
- You looking for Scofield?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Hey, yo,
Big Stroke's about to get the doc!
Sucre,
I need you to finish what we started.
No one touches the CO. No one.
- Any word from the governor?
- Not yet, boss.
Bellick!
Get those guys in line!
Get them into formation.
- We going back in?
- Not yet.
We cut the water off
about an hour ago.
The stink alone should
drive them out of there.
- You think that's gonna work?
- No, but it's protocol,
and we're all gonna
do this by the book.
It's the best chance we have of
everybody getting out of there without
getting hurt.
Hey!
This is the warden!
What's happening in there?
Hey, we got some demands!
Tell them we need
the air back on.
We need the AC!
We've got a hostage:
the guard.
We got a hostage!
The new jack!
Find out who's in there.
They got Bob.
That girl doctor--
tell him we got her.
Why don't you do it?
I don't want to get shot.
And we got the girl doctor!
- The doctor?
- There's only one.
How the hell did that happen?
How did they get
their hands on her?
I thought she was safe.
She was in Sick Bay.
We've got to get her out of there.
Somebody has got to go in there, now.
- We can't do it, sir.
- Why not?
It's not by the book.
Sir,
I've got some updates for you.
Help!
Scofield's in here?
He's in here?
Turk?
Turk!
You ain't gonna use that.
You makin' up the rules now,
ese?
It's my house.
You got a problem?
Yeah, I got a problem.
We all do.
No problem.
I swear to God.
I'm not gonna say anything.
- I didn't see anything.
- That's right, badge.
You didn't see nothing.
W ait.
Don't leave.
Sorry. I'll be back.
Don't worry.
I'll cover for you.
Don't worry, CO, all right?
I'm not gonna hurt nobody.
I'm part of the team now.
Help a brother out.
Drag that over.
Cat's away...
Mm-hmm, hmm, hmm.
Ladies  and gentlemen, please return to
your seats and fasten your seat belts.
We are making our final
approach into Washington, DC.
We need to focus on
the real question.
Who wanted Terrence
Steadman dead?
The call came from DC.
What does that tell you?
You got to think past the government,
though.
Anybody could be here.
A business partner, a rival...
Before Steadman was killed,
EcoField introduced a prototype electric
engine at the techno conference.
$60 barrels of oil would be obsolete
if that thing ever hit the mainstream.
Could be oil, oil companies...
Suppliers, consumers,
everything in between.
Or the government of an
oil-based economy...
like the United States.
- Can I take your soda?
- Oh, sure.
- Thank you.
At any rate, we land,
we meet my guy,
and even if we don't find the person who
tipped off the cops, we find his phone.
The paper trail begins.
That's the governor.
Whatever happens,
don't say anything.
Governor,
I appreciate your coming.
Now, you should know, since our
conversation, the situation has
escalated.
But not to worry, we're making
good progress with our contacts.
Just cut the crap, Warden,
and tell me where
my daughter is.
Help!
We got a... "Tyler Robert
Hudson." That is fancy, CO.
Look at that address:
144 Oak Park...
What's this?
Terrace.
How do you swing that, CO?
Sounds like you're about
something living on a... terrace.
I can't wait to kick it on a terrace.
What...
Aww... aww...
This here must be
your daughter.
Put it back.
Prom?
You know what they say about
a prom dress, don't you?
She ain't come home that night,
did she?
No, she wore that all....
night long.
Next morning
she had to throw that dress in
the trash can behind the motel,
so her mama didn't see the...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm just kicking it with Deputy Dawg,
you know... talking women.
I'll be very clear here because you
and I face an evolutionary cap...
You ain't gonna hurt this man.
We're locked into this thing now,
understand?
And  he's the only
leverage we have.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Now,
do we have an understanding?
I'm on your side now.
Do you understand me?
I'm just going with the flow.
You let me know when you're
done with your, uh, "leverage."
Let me out!
Let's smoke the bitch out!
It ain't gonna hurt real bad,
if you make it easy...
If you make it hard, though...
Open the door! Come here.
Come open this door!
Open this door!
Come on.
Grab my hand.
Come on!
I've got you.
You're all right?
It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
See these pipes?
We're going to stay on them.
They go through the wall
and over the hallway,
and they're going to
get us out of here.
All you have to
do is follow me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where did she go?
Where are we meeting him?
Georgetown,
in a parking garage.
He's a private investigator.
He used to be my roommate,
freshman year at Duke.
The disturbance has escalated
at this Chicago-area prison.
Oh, my God, Nick, look.
At least two hostages
have been confirmed
in what is now being
called a full-scale riot,
here at the Fox River
State Penitentiary.
Should we go back
or keep going?
Just keep going.
You want to go back and stand there with
the rest of the people who aren't
helping?
Come on.
The National Guard responded after
Illinois Governor Frank Tancredi
declared a state of emergency
shortly after 3:00 p.m.
Come on, honey.
It's time to go.
Hold on. Hold on.
No word on what caused the initial
disturbance, but sources with the...
That's not Fox River, is it?
- What are you doing?
- We have to go. Come on.
No, Dad might be in trouble.
Look, your father's already in trouble.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Just don't make a scene, okay?
He gets very uncomfortable
with this thing. Just...
Let's just go, okay?
- Oh, God forbid, man!
- Please!
We're just talking about my
old man here and his life.
If-if that's all
right with you.
- Leave me out of this.
- I am leaving you out of it.
I left you out of it
the day I met you.
Okay, L.J.
Because nothing in her life or
mine has anything to do with you.
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear that.
Oh, yeah? Or what?
You see,
this is what I'm talking about.
This is the kind of crap
I have to deal with.
Just let me handle it!
The kind of crap you
have to deal with?
- L.J., do you want to talk...
- Oh! You got no clue, do you?
- Honey, look.
- Leave me alone!
- Get off me!
- What the hell are you doing?
You don't talk to
her like that.
Stop it!
Stop!
Go upstairs, L.J., now!
Go!
- You love that man?
- Just go.
- You love that man.
- Do what I say.
Turk, why are you doing this?
Who sent you?
Why?  Why?
Why'd you do this?
What's it all about?
Who sent you?
Man, you've got to help me.
You've got to help me. Please.
Talk!
Who's your friend?
You scared the hell out of me.
Who you talking to?
It's the Fish's idea.
The devil marks the walls so you
know where to drill the holes.
You're making holes
with an egg beater?
I know. Crazy, huh?
It's called the Hooker Law.
It says that if you poke the exact
right holes in something big and strong,
it gets very weak.
That's true.
When the wall is weak,
we can take it down.
At least that's the plan.
Yeah. It's always the plan.
You should never
underestimate a wall.
You see...
sometimes, no matter how hard you try,
it just won't give in.
Are you all right?
I'm okay. I'm fine.
You know what?
I need a minute. I'm sorry.
- It's not much further.
- Just a sec.
We can stop if you want,
catch your breath.
Yeah, I could use a minute.
Things should be
winding down around now.
Pretty soon the powers-that-be
will break in and...
it'll all be over.
It's just a matter of time.
What's happening anyway?
All hell is breaking loose.
But I think if we stay up
here we should be okay.
I can't believe
this is happening.
You ever been to Baja?
-  Mexico?
- No.
There's this great
place down there.
20 bucks a night,
hammock on the back deck.
Beers are 50 cents.
25 cents at happy hour.
You ever been to Thailand?
Thailand's great.
Michael, if you're trying to calm me
down, you're doing a terrible job.
But I am trying.
Shh! You hear that?
- Why are you here?
- What do you mean?
Crawling around in the ceiling,
risking your life.
You needed help, and, uh...
I came to find you.
How did you know where to go?
When everything
went off in A Wing,
the COs left the station.
I saw you on the monitor.
One of my first assignments on PI,
we were up here,
cleaning out toxic mold.
It took days. So,
I'm kind of familiar
with the layout.
I hope you wore a mask.
Excuse me?
To prevent inhalation.
Mold can be really dangerous.
Yeah. I wore a mask.
Get up. Get up there.
The door to the visitation room,
did you ever use it?
Um... not usually,
but my access card should work.
Get up. Get up.
Psst!
Let's go.
Let's go!
Yes, sir, I understand. But believe me,
Sara is our top priority.
The hell she is. I ordered a
state of emergency an hour ago.
Soldier,
get me your commanding officer.
Now what the hell is
going on out here?
Negotiating, sir.
They can't hold
out much longer.
Negotiating?!
It is 100 degrees in there.
They're almost out of water.
We are trying to avoid
doing anything extreme.
Look, I don't care if it takes a
massacre to get her out of there.
Do you understand me?
Now if you're not gonna do it,
I am!
Captain, spread the news.
You're going in.
It's time to do this my way.
All right.
Hey!
Fish!
You gonna keep that
nurse all to yourself?
S troke!
Somebody help me.
Come on, this way!
Good call, Governor,
bringing in the big guns.
I appreciate your support.
Captain Brad Bellick.
I sent you a letter earlier this year.
My views on penal reform.
Oh. And what are they?
These inmates don't mess around.
Us COs need to get tough.
Warden Pope's a good guy.
Don't get me wrong.
But he doesn't understand
that sometimes
you got to grab the situation
by the gonads and take control.
And is that what you would do,
Captain?
Yes, sir,
that's exactly what I'd do.
Give me that. Give me that.
- I don't know...
- Give me that thing.
Demolition runs in the family.
The whole trick is pressure.
Where should I... Here?
- Yeah...
- Good, good.
You see, you should push hard,
but not too hard.
Just like when you, you know.
Yeah, well,
you got to be careful, though.
- Yeah, I know it.
- No, I mean it. You...
One slip,
and you-you'll hit the gas pipe.
Gas... pipe?
Yeah, you know,
as in pipe that carries the gas.
We can't go this way.
We have to.
There's no other way to Visitation.
This is it.
No, it's not.
- It's back this way.
- This won't help.
- Trust me.
- Michael, if you're wrong...
We don't have time.
Not too hard.
Not... too soft.
When I was her age,
I had such bad skin.
Oh! Ooh! Eee!
Acne they called it.
Yeah. She looks just like all
them girls who made fun of me.
After I kill you,
I'm gonna crawl out that hole
and call me up a limousine,
and me and your baby
is going to the prom.
Captain,
what's the news with Sara?
We're still trying to find her,
sir.
You don't even
know where she is?
We're on it.
Soon as we do, we'll let you know.
You should've listened to Captain
Bellick and gassed the whole block.
Captain Bellick?
He's right on the front line.
He knows what these guys can do.
You better pray that Sara gets
out of there in one piece.
I do, Governor,
but this is still my prison.
Whatever happens,
I take full responsibility. Excuse me.
It's this way.
Uh! Yeah.
Ooh... yes. We're through.
Time to put this
theory to the test.
I guess we start
chipping away now.
Right on.
She's all yours, pal.
The smell. The sm...
We did it.
That's it.
But I can't leave you here.
You don't have a choice.
I'm one of the bad guys, remember?
Do you see the assailant?
Number eight, affirmative.
I've got him in sight.
What are you going to do?
Go back to my cell.
Stay out of the way.
- Michael...
- What?
They see us.
You have to go.
I can't. They'll kill you.
You go out the door,
I'll drop to the floor.
They're sharpshooters, Michael.
They won't miss.
That's why you
can't stay here.
- What's going on?!
- I'm coming, Doc!
Go!
Who's this?
That's my guy.
Hey.
Nice ride.
Yeah, you like that?
Cop auction. 300 bucks.
You must be Veronica.
Whoever tipped off the cops about
Lincoln Burrows called from this number.
That wasn't an easy trace.
I hope you're not too bummed.
- Why, what's the problem?
- It's a pay phone.
This is it,
11th and Constitution.
Anyone could have
made that call.
Any one of the million people
who pass through here every day.
That's empty.
What about that?
Federal Energy Commission,
that's interesting.
Where you going?
I'm gonna go see if this
guy knows what was in there.
Excuse me.
Do you know what was
in that space before?
Okay, thanks.
Hey.
It was the regional headquarters
for a company called EcoField.
- Terrence Steadman's company.
- That's right.
- Hello?
- Veronica?
- Who is this?
- That's the problem, Veronica.
You ask too many questions.
Now I have one for you.
Is Lincoln Burrows
really worth it?
Gove me the phone.
Who is this?
Nick Savrinn,
I just wanted to let you know.
As of now,
both of you are dead.
Come on, let's go.
Michael! Michael!
Michael!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I didn't touch him, man.
I didn't touch him!
Ask him!
Things have changed since we last met.
Relax, partner.
I'm in on it now.
The rabbit plan.
Know all about it. So does the CO.
Sucre!
Why'd you take Abruzzi down there?
I didn't take him down there.
And the pedophile--
he thinks he's in!
- Shut up!
- Where's Michael?
Where's Michael?!
Michael!
Where have you been?
All over. Are you all right?
- Yeah, are you?
- Yes. Yes.
Move!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Bellick.
She's walking.
That's a good sign.
Yeah. Astute observation.
Maybe you'd like to share
that with the governor?
I was tense. I was just...
Next time you bad-mouth me
to one of my superiors,
there are going to be
serious consequences.
Do I make myself clear,
Captain?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Sara!
Sara! Sara!
- Dad?
- Sara!
Thank God. Are you all right?
Are you okay?
I told you when you took this job, I
knew something like this was going to
happen.
Didn't I? I knew something
like this was gonna happen.
God, Dad, how about,
"I'm happy to see you alive"?
Oh, sweetheart, I just want you to
see what you're doing to yourself.
I mean, there is nobody that
is forcing you to be here.
I know. Thanks, Dad.
All right. Clean this mess up.
What's going on?
You won't believe it, Fish. We did it.
We never seen nothing like it.
Those little "Hooker"
holes were right on!
All right, let's get everyone
out of here, especially him!
I'm getting him out of here.
I'm going to take care of him myself.
- You're not gonna kill him.
- I'm not coming back here.
It's over!
We don't need him no more.
You're not gonna kill him.
You so stupid you're gonna let
him walk out that front door?
- That ain't for you to decide.
- After all he's seen?
- Get up.
- Get out!
Keep your mouth shut.
Turn left.
Get out!
If we have a problem,
we know where to find you.
Bye-bye.
Forget about it.
Just forget about it, all right?!
No!
One for the team.
Okay, so this is the complete
list of the injured and the dead?
- And it's the whole list?
- Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, Ron.
Dr. Tancredi.
Glad to see you
made it out alive.
Yeah, me, too.
- Um, question.
- Mm-hmm.
Why'd your department
assign inmates on PI
to do a toxic mold
removal project?
What toxic mold project?
In the crawlspace in A Wing.
PI didn't go there.
We'd never assign
inmates to do that.
- Okay, sorry.
- No problem.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net