We're gonna get you out of here.
_
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,
but then he abandoned us.
Ramal is Poseidon's guy, not ours.
The escape is on.
He's my brother!
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?
A frustrated policy wonk
in the CIA, who created a cell
within the CIA called 21-Void.
And he needed my help
breaking out people
imprisoned all over the world.
We've awoken something.
Any chance Poseidon will
just let us kill her?
- Point.
- It's three and four.
The man, and the woman was the shooter.
Step back! That's not gonna happen.
Go to hell!
Let's get the hell out of here!
The only way out now is up, brother.
I'm so sorry. Sorry, brother.
_
We got to move.
No. We go out on the
streets tonight, we're dead.
You know it and I know it.
Even on the outside, I
feel the world crushing in.
That's what being locked up does.
You carry the prison
with you on the outside.
I can't live that way.
I've got to know the walls disappear.
It's called being scared.
Happens when you're sober.
Don't give me the pill talk.
I won't give you the
poor little orphan talk.
How your friend here
isn't the father figure
you thought he was gonna be.
This isn't helping.
The walls are going away, brother.
We're gonna make 'em go away.
We're getting out of this country.
All of us.
Oh, really? Which
contingency's that gonna be?
You burned through them all.
Truck to border, train, airport.
None of those.
We're exactly where
I don't want to be: improvising.
Well, we need to improvise
something real fast
or it's gonna be us down there,
strung up like that.
Omar. Sheba's guy.
She said he had a way out.
We can trust him?
No. But he's our last option.
You made bail. You're being released.
Don't be a stranger, sugar.
Poseidon got you out first.
I thought I was his favorite.
Son of a bitch really escaped.
Yep.
But why kill Ramal? I
thought they were allies.
It's not our job to ask questions.
Maybe we should.
Poseidon says we find
Kaniel Outis and kill him.
That's what we're gonna do.
And I think I know how to do it.
Omar.
What are you doing here?
You're radioactive, my friend.
You killed Abu Ramal. Really?
That was a very stupid move, man.
Just tell us where you're headed.
300 miles across the desert. Phaeacia.
Old smuggling friends.
Uh, autonomous zone. No ISIL.
Perfect.
Not perfect.
Four of you, one of
me. Not enough seats.
Okay, okay, all right. What
about getting another vehicle?
Tell you what.
Because it's Sheba and I owe her,
maybe we can help each other.
I have another vehicle.
A Land Cruiser.
I was going to leave it behind,
but if you can get it,
it's in a parking garage
two blocks from here.
I'll let you follow.
Deliver my second vehicle,
and maybe I get the Phaeacians
to get you a boat somewhere,
to Europe, France, Italy,
Spain, wherever you want to go.
How's that sound?
Keys are here.
Uh, left side, the
red brick. First floor.
Battery might be dead, so you might need
- all of you to push.
- We got it.
Whip, you stay with him. Let's move.
He always give you orders like that?
It's complicated.
I got an order for you.
Load up.
One more bag inside.
There!
Give it a push on my say.
Battery's working perfectly.
How far away is this garage?
Only two blocks. No problem.
Someone says there's no problem,
there's always a problem.
He set us up. Get in!
Hold on.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Nothing personal, my friend.
In another life, no doubt
we smoke the hookah together.
No! No, you don't!
Whip, you okay?
Thought you were gonna
be a millionaire, huh?
I didn't have a choice.
Come on! Coldcocking son of a bitch!
Hold on, hold on. Easy
now, we may need him.
Yes. You need me.
I want a map to this Phaeacia place.
You do realize this is Yemen, don't you?
Phaeacia is a hundred people.
Mud huts. There is no map.
But I can lead you there.
You want to trust this guy?
Well, if he screws with us,
we'll just let Whip
finish what he started.
And I will kill you.
I can't wait to kill him.
You coldcock me, I end you.
Rule number one in my country. Okay?
And rule number one in my country is
when things get bad, go to the desert.
We are desperate, desperate men.
Not as desperate as Omar right now.
If there's one man you don't want
to get on the wrong side of, it's Whip.
That might apply to you, too, Michael.
I get the sense the kid thinks
you betrayed him somehow.
I could understand why he thinks that.
I really am sorry, my friend.
When I'm scared, I make poor choices.
Zero comes out of your mouth. Okay?
I'm having a really bad
couple days. Just the worst.
Agent Kishida.
Settling into your new office, I see.
I still see this as
Kellerman's office, ma'am.
As you probably know,
before he was killed,
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.
I knew that. Yes.
I need Paul's files.
Obviously, he was
getting close to something
and they killed him for it.
Actually, I've been
looking into his leads,
and there's nothing there.
I hate to say it, but this
file is full of dead ends.
There's nothing here.
There must be something.
Look, I don't want Paul
to have died in vain,
but we need to look at this
whole thing with new eyes.
Read it for yourself.
Okay, you want to put
new eyes on this? Fine.
Now that you report to me,
I need you to look into the possibility
that there was an insider involved.
Here? At the State Department?
Anywhere along the evidence chain.
Will do, ma'am.
Agent Kishida.
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.
I just wanted to follow up
on our earlier conversation.
The situation in the Middle East?
Situation's developing.
We need to meet soon.
Fair enough.
The moment we're back, we'll call you.
You worked at NSA?
Team Eye in the Sky for ten years.
Watched the most heinous
crap you can imagine
by satellite.
Stonings, rapes.
Just had to sit back and watch
it like a horror film, helpless,
until Poseidon tapped my shoulder,
gave me a chance to
do something about it.
Emily, good to see you again.
Likewise.
You got my message? Kaniel Outis?
You gonna help us locate him?
Look, protocol says no.
We stay clear of CIA,
any offensive action.
We're surveillance only.
We just want to put eyes on him.
I think I can get you in as observers
under interagency auspices.
I knew I could count on you.
But you owe me.
That B&B we went up to in Connecticut,
I want that weekend again.
That exact weekend.
What you got back here, anyway?
What is this, guns, drugs?
Fireworks?
You don't understand the Phaeacians.
They are beautiful. Generous.
They just want to smile.
Unlike you.
Oh, is that right?
Ah, holding grudges.
It's very bad for the heart...
You know what else
is bad for your heart?
If I shove a Roman candle
through the middle of it.
Ja, please.
Don't check out on us.
Still trying to figure
out why you got me out.
I need that great big mind
of yours clean and clear.
It's the number from
the airport last night.
C-Note, what's up?
Lincoln, it's Sheba.
I got Benjamin's phone.
Oh, hi.
Did you find Omar?
Yeah, we found him.
We're traveling.
You okay?
Yes. We're in Jordan.
Leaving for the U.S. tonight.
How's C-Note?
He's fine.
We all are.
Everyone.
We're going to make it.
It's because of you.
Because of my money.
Come on.
Hey, uh...
when I get back, I'll,
I'll buy you a drink.
I don't drink.
But I'll buy you a drink.
How about that?
Sounds good.
We got a hit,
Franklin's cell phone lit up in Jordan.
The one he bought with a credit
card in Yemen a few days ago.
Making an outbound call
to an unknown number.
Currently right outside Sana'a, Yemen.
Rerouting a drone to that target now.
We just found our man, didn't we?
There. Two vehicles heading west.
Drones in position.
Let's take a peek.
They're stopping.
Pull up all known data on that location.
Why did we stop?
Phaeacia is 300 miles that way.
We need to fill our
gas tanks up to the top.
- As-salamu.'alaykum.
- Alaykumu s-salaam.
Michael, where you going?
Been under Poseidon's thumb
for the last seven years.
It's about time I got out from under it.
Internet?
_
Shukraan.
They have no clue
we're watching, do they?
Not at this height.
_
Who is this?
A friend from far away.
Your government has always
considered us an enemy.
Officially.
But some of us have a
more enlightened view.
Abu Ramal was a great visionary.
You have our sincerest condolences.
What do you want?
The same thing you do,
to eliminate the men who killed him.
And as a sign of good faith...
we'll tell you exactly where they are.
Hey, can you see me?
Not yet.
Blasted computer camera thing.
Who makes these things?
All right, I see you.
Come on, hurry. Get this off of me.
Hold your hand still.
Just do it already.
Do you want to stay like this?
You're lucky we cut you loose.
The men who killed Abu Ramal,
Leaving Sana'a, heading
west on Highway 80.
- Okay.
- Highway 80.
We're leaving now.
- I'm coming, too.
- No.
This is not your fight anymore.
Understand?
_
You know it's been four years
since I've had air conditioning?
I'm done with the heat.
Kind of like it out here.
No walls.
No walls, okay? Ain't about walls.
My opinion, you know what you need
more than anything else in the world?
Got to laugh more.
If he wants to laugh,
Phaeacia 's the place.
I always wanted to bring Sheba;
for her to see the people.
No technology, no politics,
no modern nonsense.
They know how to enjoy life.
No technology?
Freddie Mercury here couldn't hack it.
Freddie Mercury?
I could hack it.
I was alive before cell phones.
You're more addicted to
that screen than you are
to them pills, and that
is saying something.
Be ready.
Ah, my friends. We got problems!
Michael, we got to go!
Michael? Let's go!
I got to go.
Hold on, let me try something else.
Can you see me now?
No. Take a screen capture.
What of?
A screen capture. Take it.
ISIL militants coming from the east.
This should get interesting.
Don't think one bullet is
going to get us out of this.
One bullet? Who the hell
carries a gun with one bullet?
The man who would kill himself
before being captured by ISIL.
Get closer. Zoom in.
Hold on.
These militants, how'd they find them?
Damnit, what are you
waiting for? Shoot back!
We only got one bullet.
- One bullet?
- Exactly.
We're seriously screwed here.
Unless I can make this one bullet count.
What?
You sure as hell made it count, kid.
Hell yeah, you did.
Oh, my God.
Michael.
He's in a bad way, Linc.
More coming, we got to
get the hell out of here!
What are they stopping for?
Don't know.
We can't go any further.
We can go a lot further.
We've got to get to Phaeacia.
There's no roads, Whip.
The roads are in Omar's
head along with the map.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Our map is dead.
We got to head back.
To what?
He's right.
We'll die out there without a map.
We don't know that.
We 99% know that.
Guess we're not out of the woods yet!
We got to lose this guy, whoever he is!
- Let's go!
- Then move it, damn it.
All targets now bearing 2:15.
Stay with them.
No. Pull the drone.
Time for our visitors to leave.
What are you talking about?
We find Kaniel Outis in Yemen,
and then rebels show up to take him out?
Was I supposed to think
that was a coincidence?
This isn't surveillance, is it?
This is assassination.
You're using me for some sort
of black work, aren't you?
This is way over your head, Tricia.
Stop asking questions.
If you don't get out of my
sight, I will blow the whistle.
Right now.
Would've been a hell of
a weekend in Connecticut.
It's playing with fire,
co-opting other agencies like that.
You think she'll talk?
Run it up the flag pole?
You got designs on killing her?
I'll kill you.
Relax, will you?
I'm getting pretty
tired of chasing Outis.
- Always being behind him.
- Me, too.
That's why I keep thinking
about all that time that he spent
in that gas station in Yemen.
ISIL on his tail,
and he just hangs in there?
What was he doing in there?
The sun is directly overhead.
I can't tell which way is east, west...
We got to stop.
Hey, Ja.
You got a compass on that phone?
No signal.
We're flying blind.
Completely blind.
But he's not.
We're leaving him a beautiful
set of tire tracks to follow.
Who the hell is this guy?
It's the guy who killed Sid.
Son of a bitch is like
a dog with a bone, huh?
You kill someone's spiritual leader,
they'll follow you to the
ends of the Earth, apparently.
Why is he stopping?
He's refueling.
Now?
He knows he's got more gas than we do.
All he has to do is follow our tracks.
Then wait until we run out.
There are four of us.
Let's just swarm him, take him out.
Not out here.
Not with an AK-47.
We wouldn't get within
a hundred feet of him
without taking a bullet.
Then we got to outthink him.
What you gonna do with that, flog him?
Gonna transfer gas from
that tank to this one.
Almost all of it.
It's not gonna help.
It's gonna help this
one get to Phaeacia.
We pile into one vehicle?
He still has more gas than us.
He can still follow our tire tracks.
That's why we leave a little
bit of gas in that one.
And make two sets of tracks.
He's gonna have to choose.
I got four rocks in my hand.
Three red, one white.
Get the red rock, get in
the Jeep, go to Phaeacia.
Get the white rock,
deal with our friend.
Stick out your hand.
Red.
Whip.
Come on.
Red.
Linc.
No.
You knew the rules, Linc.
He's picking up again.
I'm not leaving you out here to die.
I have no intention of dying.
Anyway, you've got the harder job.
You've got to find Phaeacia
out there somewhere.
Leave tracks so I know how to find you.
Just one.
You want to play, you son of a bitch?
Now how the hell am I
gonna get out of this?
We're driving blind.
It's the same damn
thing everywhere we look.
There's something to be said for that.
Makes you use your senses.
Will you stop talking crap
and talk elephant in the room, please?
We just left Michael back there.
It's completely wrong.
I'm the last guy you
want to say that to.
Well, why are we doing it, then?
Because he said, that's why.
One thing you don't understand.
When Michael takes on the world,
the world always loses.
We've been looking the whole time.
That's the problem.
What?
Stop the engine.
You hear that?
Birds?
Not just birds. Gulls.
As far as I know, gulls got
no interest in the desert.
They only got interest in the sea.
It means we're close.
All you got to do is follow them.
Maybe we got GPS after all.
Is this Phaeacia?
Phaeacia! Phaeacia!
Omar! Omar!
Omar, Omar.
Hello.
You bring Omar car, but not Omar?
Omar had to go somewhere safe.
Because of the war?
Yeah, the war. That's right.
He told us to bring this stuff for you.
Also said you could
arrange a boat for us.
Back in the city...
I told you you would die.
We will both die out here, American!
Turns out that gas
station outside Sana'a
had a computer with Internet access.
He sent this image from Yemen. Why?
We're gonna find out as soon as we talk
to the guy he sent it to.
Blue Hawaii in Portland, Maine.
Think we got a snowbird?
I don't think that's quite it.
Welcome to Graceland.
Don't just stand there
and let the AC out.
Come on in.
What can I do for you fine folks?
Linc, where are your tracks?
Tracks, tracks.
No, no, no, no!
No, no. No.
Come on. Come on!
Come on, Mike, come on.
Where are the tracks?
This is for you. Look.
W-Wait, go easy, go easy.
Start with the small stuff.
Flowers, snakes, we'll move
onto the artillery later.
Fireworks okay?
Yes, yes, of course.
- It's okay to use?
- Thank you.
Omar was right.
This place.
It's like the rest of
the world doesn't exist.
I'll go check on Linc.
Hanging in there?
You're right. I shouldn't
have abandoned him.
If he doesn't find those
tire tracks by nightfall,
he never will.
Where are you going?
Going out to find him.
You can't go out there at night.
You'll never find him.
Doing nothing's not an option.
I didn't say do nothing.
You got to have faith.
Sarah.
Michael!
That's it.
Michael.
Thank God, you made it.
He poisoned me.
- What?!
- Antifreeze.
Need a doctor.
Get the doctor now.
The doctor, the only
doctor is in Sana'a.
We can't go back to Sana'a.
We just came from there.
It's 300 miles across
the friggin' desert.
We got to do something. He's dying.
Michael, Michael.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net