- When?
- Tomorrow.
I messed up.
- What do you mean?
- I mentioned Whistler.
So you're Feng.
- Susan?
- That's right.
The wall itself is
fortified with steel fiber.
The bad news is that
there are both weight
and microphonic sensors
that will alert
Company security
to the presence of any
breathing human being
that weighs more
than two pounds.
You have a
hypothalamus hamartoma,
and the doctor feels
that you need surgery.
- Two days.
- No, tomorrow.
Otherwise, you could die,
and there's no alternative.
Just a little
bit more.
Go slow.
No, there's no way he
deserves any of this.
Sing it, sister.
After what he
put me through?
I can hardly
believe it myself.
Look, what we
must do is
make sure that cosmic
justice rains down upon him,
for once we obtain the
good General's card,
there ain't hardly
nothing standing
in between us
and Mr. Feng's
$125 million.
I was born on
a mountainside.
Just keep both
hands on the camera.
Let's go.
That's great.
Thank you so
much, Dr. Malden.
Yeah, he can see
you today at 3:00.
- No.
- We're going.
We need to finish
what we started.
We can
do this.
I need one
more day.
Michael, Dr. Malden
can see you today.
He's given
us his word
he won't alert
the authorities.
If you put this off
and you, you collapse,
you're going to be
treated by another doctor.
Do you want to
roll the dice
that they're not going
to call the cops?
There's still
so much to do.
All right.
Three o'clock?
Last time I drilled
a hole in the wall,
it was with an eggbeater back
in Fox River with Michael.
I just can't believe it's
all coming to an end,
and he's
not here.
He'll be
all right.
How do
you know?
I don't.
I'm just trying to
keep us focused.
He's sick,
but I guarantee
you one thing
that'll make
him worse,
going back
to jail.
If we don't get in there...
that's where we're all going.
He's going
to be okay.
I'm scared, too,
but a hospital's the best
place for him right now.
He won't go without a
plan to complete the job.
Well, Alex and Fernando
should be back soon
with the video, right?
Should be, yeah.
So, then, all we need
is the sixth card.
Gretchen's working on that.
You really think
we can trust her?
With the card?
Absolutely.
Anything else?
Nope.
Eight guards will accompany
Scylla from the basement bunker
up to the garage, where an
armored truck will be waiting.
One truck is not going
to be enough security.
That is why I have a full
Secret Service escort
to March Air
Force Base.
There, it will be
brought aboard a C-130.
We need air support all
the way to River Rock.
Colonel Rififi is lending
us three of his F-18s.
It may be hard
for you to believe,
but I do have
this under control.
There's nothing for
you to worry about.
When the plane lands, the same
precautions will be taken.
Armored truck
to guards to
final location.
That's fine.
Are you going
somewhere?
- I have an appointment.
- Today?
You told me there was
nothing to worry about.
Just tell me it's
not Gretchen.
This is
ridiculous.
It's a personal
matter.
I'm not going
to discuss it.
I don't
trust her.
That's
nothing new.
I'll be back
in an hour.
What'd you
find out?
You'll be awake
the whole time.
The only anesthetic
you're going to need is
4 minor injections
of local
2 in your forehead and 2
in the back of your head.
And that's for
the brace?
The frame,
yeah, and...
attaching that is going to be
the most uncomfortable part.
They're going to have to
secure 4 pins into your skull
and they're going to need
a small drill to do it.
Do we have to
listen to this?
I want to hear
this, Linc.
And then
what?
Uh, another
CT scan.
The doctor
will use
the 3-dimensional
imagery to pinpoint
the exact location
of the growth.
And once you
have that?
Then it's the
Gamma Knife unit.
They'll fit you
with a helmet,
they'll calibrate it so
that each of the 201 holes
are aimed directly for the
tumor, and at that point...
I've got two more
boxes in the car
that you guys got to
bring in yourself.
All right.
You okay?
- Because the last time I saw you...
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just a
little dehydrated.
All right, good.
This is the stuff
you requested.
You sure this is
gonna get you in?
Let us worry
about getting in.
You worry about how
we're getting out.
I got someone keeping an
eye on Gretchen and Bagwell.
If they try anything,
they're getting taken out.
Nothing is going to get
between us and Scylla.
You sure you're
all right?
Yeah, it's just, uh,
you know, we're breaking
into Company headquarters,
and, uh, you'll understand why
we're all a little on edge.
Understood.
You know, I
was thinking,
when your father approached
me about doing this,
I felt like
I was, uh,
chasing a ghost
or something, but...
'cause of the work
you guys have done,
today is the day, we are
taking these bastards down
You get it?
Got it.
We got
four hours.
How come?
I'm going in
for treatment.
Here
we go.
Scylla.
Obviously, we've got
a lot to figure out.
We have to break
through two walls..
one concrete,
one glass..
and do it without
making a sound.
Hypersensitive
parabolic microphones,
pointed in
all directions.
The floor sensors
can detect
an added surface load
of just two pounds.
So...
we have to traverse the
distance between the two walls
without touching
the floor
and do all that without
generating any kind
of body heat
whatsoever.
These are the latest in
heat-sensing technology.
We make one
wrong move,
the camera goes on, and General
Krantz will know we're inside.
It's amazing.
All this security
and only one man
has access to
video surveillance?
The Company doesn't
want any record
of what's going
on down there.
Can we access
that elevator?
No, it's right
in the middle
of the Company building..
there are ten layers
of security. We have
to go where they're
not expecting us,
starting with
the concrete wall.
Sucre, you were
drilling there, right?
It's fortified with steel
fibers, just like you said.
All right, in
order to get
through that, we
have to generate
an electromagnetic field...
We have to generate an
electromagnetic field...
To have, uh,
an electromagnetic field
with the force that we
want, we're going to need
at least a couple
of car batteries.
Can you
get that?
Yeah, yeah.
We can
do this.
Uh, what time are we
expecting Gretchen
to get that
sixth card?
What took
you so long?
You know how I get
when I'm hungry.
It wasn't easy getting
away from the office.
I could have
come to you...
like old times.
I almost wish there was
a mahogany desk in here.
Oh...
you're tense.
Take off
this jacket.
Let me get
in there.
I didn't bring
it with me.
My card.
That is what you're
looking for, right?
What are you talking
about? Your card.
You forget.
I'm the one that
taught you how to lie.
I never thought that
at the age of 63,
I could still have
my heart broken.
Why did you feel you
needed to steal my card?
Don't you know that if you'd
waited just a little bit longer,
you'd have had
one of your own?
I'm sorry.
I'm...
Who are you
selling it to?
That's-that's
not why...
Who?
I'm the mother
of your child.
Please, for
Emily's sake.
Please,
Jonathan.
Please.
I love you.
If I ever see
you again...
I'll shoot
you on sight.
Is everything
all right, Cole?
I got something
important you need to know.
We're gonna
be rich.
So, here's
the question.
How much is it
gonna cost me
to get that
jacket off you?
Excuse me?
Last day I'm ever
gonna see you.
You're all
covered up.
I cannot
abide. $100.
You want to pay me to
take my clothes off?
Not all of them.
Just the jacket.
- $200.
- I'm not gonna strip for you.
Pity on
an old man.
You're
disgusting.
And lecherous
and vile.
And soon to be
wealthy beyond belief.
$1000
Why so modest
all of a sudden?
Cole, I need to see
you in my office, now.
Thank you for calling
GATE. How can I help you?
It was Mr. White in his
office with the lead stapler.
Cole, yesterday with
that Idaho Group,
you made this
company $35,000.
And I would like to
return the favor.
It's our
annual cruise.
7 days and 6 nights
of non-stop pitching.
I personally clear
$50,000 on most trips,
but for everything
you've done,
it's all
yours.
The least
I could do.
It leaves
today?
Go home
and pack.
I'll see you
in a week.
Unfortunately, I
have some business
I need to take
care of right here.
Okay, so here's
how it works.
As soon as the sensors pick
up any kind of a heat source
90 degrees or more,
system goes into standby,
a yellow light
comes on.
After 5 seconds
in standby,
if the heat source isn't
gone, we have an alarm.
So we got 6 seconds to
make it across the hallway
and through
the glass wall?
Basically.
If we get our hands on
some liquid nitrogen,
we could regulate
the temperature.
Yeah.
Kill two birds
with one stone.
See if you can
get some of that.
Hey.
I'm not going to ask
how you're feeling.
Good.
About 4 years after
I joined the Bureau,
my first Special
Agent in charge..
he was diagnosed
with liver cancer.
But for him,
the hardest part
wasn't the treatment.
The hardest part was
leaving the office,
because we had this...
we had this big RICO case
that was about
to go to trial,
and we're talking
thousands
of man hours, 5
years of research.
And the guy was
going to be in chemo.
And he was scared.
He was scared that we
were gonna lose the case,
and that a lot of bad
men were gonna walk.
Let me guess: He had a
ragtag band of criminals
ready to pick
up the slack.
It was something
like that.
We're not going to
let you down, Michael.
What happened
to your boss?
Oh, he was there
to see us win.
You're sure
she's a Fed?
Wouldn't take off her
jacket for a $1000.
She's got a
gun under there.
It's a
complication.
Well, that's a
nice way to put it.
Sort of like you not
getting the sixth card.
What are we calling
that now, a setback?
Relax.
You have any idea what
I'm giving up here?
I was guaranteed
50 grand.
You're crying over
$50,000? Are you serious?
I have
a job.
I make money.
I get mail.
People call
me 'Sir'
Working 12-hour days and
eating leftover Lo-Mein.
Something tells me
Theodore Bagwell
wouldn't last long
in this situation.
Yeah, maybe,
but Cole
Pfeiffer would.
You want to pout,
you do it tomorrow.
We have
work to do.
Is it really worth
$125 million?
It's worth
twice as much.
What if they refuse
to hand it over?
Either we pay for Scylla,
or we kill for it.
Feng, we
need to talk.
Hey, give me a second h
ere, guys, just a second.
We can't make any
noise above 10 decibels.
You got two
of those?
Absolutely.
This is gonna
work, right?
It should.
No, not
just that.
The whole thing.
I mean, do we
even have a chance?
Just make sure the hole
is in the right place.
So, where
are we?
Gretchen didn't get
us the sixth card.
We need that
sixth card, Don.
I know.
If we don't get the sixth card,
we're never gonna crack Scylla.
I know it.
Well, we know they're
moving Scylla today.
We know we can't just waltz
into the General's office
and steal that
last card,
so where does
that leave us?
There's got to be a way.
There has to be a way
Not without losing
another man.
Believe me, I spent the last
week trying to figure out
how to get that sixth card,
and every scenario ends
with a gun to someone's head,
and that is not acceptable.
You know, Gretchen did
pass on this one piece
of information
for you.
This could
be helpful.
The buyer just
showed up.
All right, well, find
out what they're up to.
Mr. Feng, so glad you
could come and see us.
I was expecting
the next time
the three of us would be
in the same room together,
that you'd have
something for me.
That was our
expectation as well,
but we've hit a few
bumps in the road.
Now, to ensure
the item's
safe recovery,
we need your help.
It's time
to go.
"All that
avails is flight."
Maybe my father
was onto something.
If they
all die
because we tried to
take down The Company,
and I survive
because...
because I called
in sick...
how am I gonna
live with myself?
You're gonna get
through this.
I'm not going
to the hospital.
What?
Linc, just
get in the car.
I'm going
with you.
If I still had a
medical license,
I'd lose it
over this.
This is usually
given to epileptics.
It will suppress the
rapid firing of neurons
for the next
three hours,
making it
unlikely
that you'll have a
seizure in that time,
but Michael, any added
mental or physical stress...
I get it.
I mean it.
I don't want you to move
unless you absolutely have to.
And as soon as this is over,
I'm taking you to the hospital.
Hey.
You all right?
This is gonna go
exactly as planned.
I promise.
I'm not
praying for me.
Let's go.
You wanted
to see me?
It's the second
Tuesday of the month.
Don't you have your
Eagles and Angels luncheon?
I figured I'd
skip it today.
You called me in here to
confirm my lunch plans?
You were right.
If it weren't for you,
this would be in the wind.
- Is she dead?
- Let's just say
she won't bother
either of us anymore.
But I do want Scylla
moved right now.
Our mechanics are on the
tarmac inspecting the C-130.
When they sign off,
we'll be ready to move.
Call the other card
holders, get them in here.
Did, uh, Self call
you, uh, regarding
a little snafu
with the General?
Get out
of my way.
Just for uh,
clarification's sake,
the sixth card is part of the
to-do list, right gentlemen?
The game's
afoot.
Does Michael have a
way to get the card?
I've worked with
Michael Scofield before,
both with him
and against him.
There's no way he's
going down there
without a plan
to finish the job.
I got a call from
an old friend.
Heard Scylla
was in play.
He wants to know if
he can get in on it.
A bidding war?
He's prepared
to offer 200.
Is he
for real?
I don't know. I've
set up a safe house
where we can hear him
out. Do you have a pen?
Just a
minute.
1917 Piermont.
1..9..1..7
Piermont,
got it.
I'm on
my way.
Uh, good
afternoon.
Thank you for
calling GATE.
I got some last
minute negotiations
with the buyer
to speak about.
I'll be back
lickety-split.
See you
later.
Can you hold,
please?
All right.
This is it.
Now, does anyone
have any questions
about what they're
supposed to do?
That hole you drilled
in the wall this morning,
once we get over there,
if we make too much noise,
the sound waves will
travel through the wall
and get picked up by the
sensors on the other side.
So, from this point on,
we need absolute silence.
Alex,
good luck.
You, too.
Ready?
We have to break
through two walls..
one concrete,
one glass..
and do it without
making a sound.
In order to get
through that,
we have to generate an
electromagnetic field.
To have
an electromagnetic
field with the force
that we want,
we're gonna need
at least a couple
of car batteries.
starting  with
the concrete wall.
Sucre, you were
drilling there, right?
It's fortified with steel
fibers, just like you said.
You sure
this is it?
1917 Piermont
Avenue.
Okay.
When was the last
time you swept a room?
The Academy.
All right, just
follow my lead, okay?
Because Gretchen and Bagwell
have no respect for human life.
- Okay? They go for a weapon, you shoot.
- Okay.
They try to
run, you shoot.
If they do anything than
kneel down and put their hands
- behind their heads...
- I shoot.
Don't miss.
Agent Self.
We've been
waiting.
That's Feng.
He's got them.
When Scofield and Burrows
walk through the door,
give them an
opportunity to surrender.
If we can avoid confrontation,
that's the best case scenario.
There's no way they're gonna
hand it over without a fight.
If they take that position,
we'll respond in kind.
$125 million.
Only cherry that could
top this sunny day.
You can keep your Burrows
and your Mahone and your Sucre.
Just leave
Scofield for me.
We got a green
light on the C130.
It's time.
Thank you.
Oren, Tuxhorn and
Edison are standing by.
Scuderi was
in Las Vegas.
You think we could get
the state of Nevada
to outlaw
gambling?
I somehow
doubt that.
His plane will touch
down within about an hour.
Then you can make
your luncheon.
I would
rather stay.
Now more
than ever,
we need the support
of law enforcement.
I will
call you
- when we're ready to move.
- General, I...
There's nothing more
for you to worry about.
Lisa?
Very good work.
I need to go
downstairs, now!
www.tvsubtitles.net