Previously, on Prison Break:
Excuse me, ladies,
I need to ask you a few questions.
And then that dirty Southerner,
he snuck out the back.
Do you really think the
diaper sniper got all of it?
If you were Bagwell, and you just
got your hands on $5 million,
where would you go?
All right, listen,
- in the Rainbow Room.
- Restaurant in New York City.
I am gonna be
waiting in that spot.
And that's all that I want...
In this whole world, is for my two
girls to be waiting there for me.
3 dots, 3 letters.
Question is "where"?
What? What are you trying
to tell me, Michael?
I think I owe you an apology.
Because I lied to you.
About Oscar Shales.
Right there.
That's where I put the bullet in him.
What are you doing, man?
You've been hired to do a job.
The reasoning...
does not concern you.
You don't ask any
questions about us,
maybe we'll continue to make sure no
one asks any questions about you.
Are we clear?
They all die.
Hey.
Are you new?
Yeah.
No one told me we were
getting a new volunteer.
I've been working, uh,
night shifts, cleanup and...
Jimmy said I could
change my shift, so...
You know what you're doin'?
Yeah.
- I'll see you around.
- Right.
- This might be Scofield.
- Copy that.
You take that side.
- Freeze!
- Take it easy, man.
- Stay on the ground.
- What's the deal?
He's gone.
How you feelin'?
Okay, I guess. Tired.
I'm a target, kid.
As long as you're with me,
so are you.
Things could get a lot worse before
they get better. You understand?
But after we meet up with
Uncle Mike and get to Panama...
Panama ain't a sure thing,
your uncle's plan is dangerous.
I mean really
dangerous. Listen...
all the charges against
you have been dropped;
you're free and clear to
start a new life. A good life.
Not be constantly running,
looking over your shoulder...
You want me to leave?
No.
Good, 'cause I'm not.
Here you go.
Turn the sound up
on the tube, Jenny.
Beth Wilson, Chicago Gazette.
Do you have any thoughts on
the death of David Apolskis?
It was unfortunate.
Oh, David.
Was there any opportunity
to subdue him...
Let me remind you
that despite his age,
David "Tweener" Apolskis was a fugitive
who made a move for my weapon.
I did not want to
have to kill him,
but sometimes things happen that
are just out of your control.
That good ole boy's huntin'
'em all down, ain't he?
Mr. Mahone, sources claim that you've
recovered Scofield's hard drive
and have obtained
substantial data from it.
What sources?
Allegedly you've retrieved
information detailing
not only how Scofield broke out,
but how he plans to stay out.
- Care to comment?
- No.
The event at Blanding Botanical
Gardens earlier today,
that was a result of
hard-drive data you collected.
No comment.
You found other locations where
Scofield might be headed? True?
I believe I said no comment.
There's something
about this guy,
it's like he knows where we're going,
what we're thinking.
What role will the hard
drive play in your search?
Heard it came back from the lab,
any findings?
Yeah, 3,200
nitroglycerine ampules.
Scofield knew these needed to be
stored in a cool, moist area.
Best place for that in the Utah
desert is the Botanical Gardens.
- It's stable?
- All medical grade,
safely used by heart patients all
the time. But in the aggregate...
It could take out an entire building.
That box right there.
This is why we can't have...
leaks...
coming from this office.
God help the agent who goes behind
my back and talks to the press.
Can you elaborate on any of
your tactics in this manhunt?
Sun Tzu said,
that if you know your enemy,
you need not fear a hundred battles.
I know these men--
who they are, where they came from,
where they want to go.
These convicts are in
a constant battle.
Not only with me,
but with themselves.
Second guessing every
decision they make.
Do I turn left?
Do I turn right?
Stay or go?
My job is to know how they'll
answer these questions.
The only way to win a war is to
try to know your prey completely
and then you get to go after your
enemy with everything you've got.
Our half-priced
stuff is in the back.
I'm looking for
something very specific.
Okay.
This is it.
- This is exactly what I need.
- Great.
We were just inches
away today, inches.
I want these blown up, huge.
Put them in my office on the walls.
- What are these?
- Somewhere in there is
information regarding a
rendezvous that Scofield set up,
and we're going to crack
that code today. Lang!
Today's the day
Franklin told his wife
he's going to meet her
at the Rainbow Room.
That's right.
Wrong. Today's the day Franklin's
going down. Are you ready?
Everything's arranged.
- It's all here?
- Yeah.
Hey, yo, D. Wassup, baby?
- I know that ain't you.
- Ain't a ghost, man.
You holding up all right?
Yeah. Just catching a whole bunch of
buses just to get here to Chi-town, man.
How you think I'm
supposed to feel?
Chris. Jay. Wassup, Flam?
You look like you lost a few, bro.
- Slim-Fast, baby.
- Is that what it is, huh?
The Feds been in your old
lady's business, no joke.
Up in your crib,
and following her around sometimes.
Yeah, I know, man. I know.
Yo, I know you love Kacee,
but I don't know if it's a good idea
for you to be coming around here.
You're a wanted man.
I'm wanted because I
kept my mouth shut,
and I kept you
out of Fox River.
See, man, we feel that,
and we owe you one.
Good, 'cause I'm
collecting right now.
My wife is waiting
for me today,
and I am not leaving Chi-town
without my family. You understand?
Now, y'all going to help me.
Let's roll out.
Where you going?
Take my kid to school.
I know about the Rainbow Room.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Phone lines are tapped.
We heard your entire telephone
conversation with your husband.
And, since you and Dede aren't
booked on any flights to New York,
don't tell me the Rainbow Room
is a restaurant in Manhattan.
Now, you can tell me where
you're meeting your husband,
or I can arrest you right
in front of your daughter.
You go to hell.
I haven't done anything wrong.
You spoke with an escaped
felon about meeting him today.
You've already done enough to be
charged with attempt to aid and abet.
Please, okay? Listen to me.
One phone call and
Child Welfare is here,
and you're going to County and
Dede will be in foster care.
- No.
- Don't worry.
I hear the families in the
foster system are top-notch.
You are asking me to choose
between my daughter and my husband.
Exactly.
Anything?
I'm on the phone with Fox River.
Checking Bagwell's file.
Hey, what you got for me?
Really?
52 times?
Where?
I owe you, Patterson.
We got a lot of road to cover.
We're good?
No more stops until
we get to New Mexico.
- You forgot your change.
- Yeah, thanks.
- You were in such a rush.
- Thanks.
Keep walking.
Come on, keep walking.
Damn it.
You don't have to ditch the car.
We can keep driving.
Can't. The waitress made me and the car.
It's useless.
Sorry, you know.
Maybe we can find another car.
Cars ain't exactly
growing on trees out here.
We've got 400 miles to go
and no way of getting there.
We don't get to Michael in time,
he's going to leave without us.
Uncle Mike wouldn't do that.
He doesn't have a choice.
It's a one-shot deal out of the country.
I said I was sorry.
There was a sign back
there for a train station.
- It ain't that easy.
- We'll follow the road...
- We won't be seen.
Hey, I'm not an idiot.
I was on the run,
too, you know.
Yeah, you were on the
run and you got caught.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry I'm not a
pro at being a con like you, Dad.
Maybe I should have just left
when you gave me the out, huh?
- It's not like you care.
- Whoa, whoa.
Take it easy.
I'm sorry, all right?
Sorry, I'm just...
Let's get out of here.
Mrs., uh, Mrs. Pamela Mahone?
- Yes?
- I'm Agent Wayne Merrick, FBI.
I'd like to talk to
you about your husband.
I'm surprised...
that you're coming to me for
a background check on Alex.
It's standard procedure.
We run these kind of checks when an
agent is about to be promoted to a,
to a higher security clearance.
No, I know that. I did this dance
the last time he was promoted.
I just figured that
since we were divorced--
I mean, I rarely speak to him and I
certainly don't follow his career.
I really need to get this done tod,
so, uh,
I promise I won't take
up much of your time.
I' given enough time to my ex-husband,
Mr. Merrick.
I see. The, uh...
The Bureau can take its
toll on your family.
I understand that.
My ex-wife is a...
an agent and, um...
let's just say I
know how you feel.
Promise me that he
won't find out we spoke?
Oh, it's totally confidential.
Do you mind if I ask why?
To be perfectly honest,
he scares me.
Information.
Hi, I need the number for
a Sundown Hotel please.
- What state?
- Uh, all of them, please.
- Got one in Pierre, South Dakota.
- Okay.
Another in Sutton,
West Virginia
and one more in Gila,
New Mexico.
- What can I do you for?
- A batch of them sunflowers, please.
You don't mind me saying, you do
not sound like you hail from Kansas.
You've got a sharp ear.
I hail from what we call the,
uh, Yellowhammer State.
What brings you to Tribune?
Sir?
Romance.
Thank you so much.
Somebody's going to get hurt.
Feds going to be swinging
bigger bats than these.
We gotta have ours.
Look, man, that's all we need
is your car, your truck,
and some guts, man.
We don't need all of this.
- Maybe we should think about it.
- I said no!
What's going to happen, man,
when the bullets start flying, huh?
Can you guarantee me that my
family ain't going to get hurt?
Johnny Law is going to be strapped up.
I'm going in hot.
I don't think you heard me,
little man.
No, I don't think
you heard me, bro.
I'm not going in naked.
I know we said we'd
ride with you on this,
but I'm not going in there
without some of these.
You want to punk out, man?
Then punk out,
'cause I can do this myself.
Ain't nobody punking out.
And no guns.
But you'd better be right about this
'cause if bullets do start flying,
the only blood being
spilled is going to be ours.
Feel me?
I feel you.
Agent Kellerman.
- Agent Kellerman!
- Yes.
That name you wanted me to track,
Kelli Foster.
She booked a flight to New Mexico,
just landed.
You got someone on it?
No, but we got an ID
on her rental car.
- Should I update Mr. Kim?
- No, I'll take care of this myself.
Got a tip from a waitress
who thinks she saw Burrows
and his son outside St.
David, Arizona.
Get a road team out
there to confirm.
Once they got a bead on Burrows,
notify me immediately.
Everybody out!
Let's go, come on!
Yeah?
Sara Tancredi just booked a
one-way ticket across the country.
- To where?
- New Mexico.
Of course.
Any luck breaking that code?
- Uh... this helps.
- Good.
Wheeler!
Sir.
Every combination
that has NM in it.
I want you to check it to see
if it contains the name of
a location in New Mexico.
And I want it done now.
Yeah, right now.
So, how well do you know Alex?
He knows me better
than I know him.
He's a closed book, all right.
But he wasn't always like that.
In the first few years of our marriage,
he was actually...romantic.
Hmm.
And then, one day,
out of nowhere...
Out of nowhere what?
Everything changed.
He became obsessed with getting out.
Out of the marriage?
Getting out of the marriage,
getting me out of the house,
out of his life.
He left me.
He left the both of us.
You said you were scared of him.
Why is that?
He started acting strange.
Started spending all of his
time in the backyard gardening,
of all things.
I mean, the man was a neat freak.
He'd throw away a pair of
shoes if they even got scuffed.
But he'd be out there
all covered in dirt
and surrounded by these huge
bags of fertilizer and lye.
We'd just put this new sod in
and he just tore it all up
and planted a flower bed.
And I went out back once to talk
to him and he screamed at me
and said not to come
near the garden.
Said that it was his.
I'm sorry. If you, uh...
if you want to take a break...
All I wanted was an explanation
why things ended so suddenly.
And all Alex could say was
"Sometimes things happen that
are just out of your control."
Excuse me.
So the picture in your
daughter's bedroom--
the exact location where it was
taken was a merry-go-round, right?
Yeah.
So, all you have to do is
wait by the merry-go-round.
Right where Benjamin's
expecting you.
Is that necessary?
- I mean, Benjamin is not...
- It's precautionary.
Look, I do this,
you leave me and my child alone.
You have my word.
- Is my wife there?
- Yeah, she's here.
Well, let's go get her.
In 15 seconds,
a black Jeep is going to pull up
by the parking lot's entrance.
Run to it.
Chris?
- Go.
- I can't.
- They're going to take Dede.
- Look, no, they won't.
Is that guy talking to her?
Get a read on him.
Look, it's taken care of. Go!
Go!
She's running!
Go, go, go, go, go, move, move!
Get in!
Hold on!
It's a 2007 black Jeep.
License plates have been removed.
We're in pursuit headed... No!
Move the truck. Move the truck!
I said move it!
- Where is my child?
- Here.
- Dede?
- Hey, it's me, baby.
Look, I just want to tell you that
everything is going to be okay.
We're going to be a family again.
I promise you that.
- Where is Dede?
- He said that you had her!
Whoa, whoa. Easy, baby. Easy.
Darius is picking her up
from school right now.
Dede Franklin, Dawson Elementary--
I want her pulled from school now!
What the hell is going on, man?
They say she's
taking a test, man,
but I think they're stalling.
What about, um...
What about Oscar Shales?
Oscar Shales?
Why is he important?
Well, he's, uh...
he's the only fugitive to ever
successfully elude your, uh...
your ex-husband.
Alex was consumed
with finding him.
After what Shales did to all of
his victims, who could blame him?
It was all he worked on,
all he did for a year.
But I don't think that it was
the stress of chasing Shales
that caused Alex to start
behaving erratically.
Why is that?
Because Alex changed
after the trail went cold.
I remember it like
it was yesterday.
He just walked into the kitchen
after 12 years of marriage
and says that he wanted me
out of the house immediately.
I'll never forget the date.
It was June 15.
I think I have
everything I need.
But you didn't even ask about
social history or education.
That's standard
in these checks.
That's been handled.
I have to get these reports filed with,
uh, Strategic Operations ASAP.
You're with
Strategic Operations?
They handle these checks.
Not since the 9/11 realignment,
Mr. Merrick.
The Chief Information
Officer does them now.
They handled Alex's last check.
When an agent reaches a level
as high as your ex-husband's,
S.O. takes over. Again.
Bureaucracies. Thank
you for the coffee.
Look, just get
her out of there.
They're here.
- No! See, we got to go!
- No, don't worry about it.
Just get the car started,
all right? Go!
- Daddy!
- Hey, baby! You ready to go?
- Where are we going?
- Disneyland.
You can't take her.
Mr. Franklin, please.
Come on, let's go!
Go, baby. Go, baby.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Franklin has the child!
Repeat, Franklin has the child!
Evening, Mrs. Hollander.
Don't you look lovely this evening.
You should have told
me what you were!
My God,
I let you near my children!
Don't think I won't remember
what your front steps look like.
Come on, get away from the road.
You want to get caught?
I, uh...
I saw you checking out those
girls back at the diner.
- What?
- Come on. Fess up.
No. I was just making sure that
they weren't staring at us.
With what? Their asses?
Beautiful girls in Panama.
They love Americans.
Cool.
So, uh,
how long have you known about girls?
Long enough.
Since when?
- Thirteen.
- Thirteen? With who?
Donna Anselmi.
She was the kid next door.
She was about...
She's four years older than me.
Your mom was paying
her for French lessons.
Well, she earned the money.
Come on. Away from the road.
You're still way too close.
Let's go.
You want to learn
some tricks, Gracey?
- Like what?
- Yeah.
I let you into my life.
Twenty seven!
Evening, Mrs. Hollander.
How are you feeling,
little Teddy?
Six.
Tomorrow.
Pam, I really can't
talk right now.
Maybe I should call back.
Who is this?
I think you already know.
If you've done
anything to Pam...
or my boy...
We both know your
family's fine.
Although, Pam did seem a little
upset about you leaving.
But then you had to,
didn't you?
'Cause you couldn't
let her find out.
- Find out about what?
- Oscar Shales.
You remember?
The one that got away.
Except he didn't get too far.
Did he?
Uh... you're
slipping, Scofield.
Maybe. Let's hypothesize
for a moment.
Let's pretend I was the
one who caught Shales.
I don't think I could of just handed
that psychopath over to the courts,
not after he'd eluded
me for so long.
Made me look bad.
You've been out in the
sun way too long, boy.
You feds make a nice living,
but not so nice you go around
tearing up expensive sod.
Not unless you had to
do a little digging,
not unless you wanted to hide
something... or someone.
That's what all the lye was for.
Wasn't it?
See, because there
are two kinds of lye.
Small amounts, the first kind
can be a garderner's best friend.
And large bags,
the other kind decomposes bodies.
Ah, you should write
mystery novels.
Now, I don't know about you,
but if I buried someone
in my own backyard,
I'd think about
it all the time.
I'd think...
I'd think maybe I should move that body.
But then I remember,
DNA leeches into soil.
So even when the body was gone,
the proof of what I'd done
would still be there.
I can imagine how it feels.
The pressure...
the constant fear.
It's more than a man can bear.
I'm going to give you a chance.
Back off.
Let me and my family disappear.
And in return,
I'll keep your little secret.
- How does that sound?
- Like a dead man talking.
I know it's not how you
wanted this to play out.
But sometimes things
happen that are just
out of your control.
This is one of those times.
- Take care of yourself.
- I'll see you soon, Michael.
Oh, and, Michael,
it just may be sooner
than you think.
Did you have a nice nap?
Visions of 12 year olds
dancing in your head?
You're trespassin'.
Nobody lives here
anymore, Goldilocks.
Seems the owner hit the bricks
as soon as she heard a certain
someone had reentered society.
Left in a hurry, too,
even left some stuff behind.
So this is where Theodore
practiced Pervert Knows Best.
This... is where he
had his family supper.
And that I believe
is where you and Ms.
Hollander expressed your love.
Tell me, little Teddy,
did you make her wear Dr. Denton's
and hold a lunch box to
help you get all worked up?
Bradley, I couldn't
possibly expect a grown man
who still lives with his momma
to understand the
machinations of love.
You want to know
how we found you?
52 mash notes, sent by you,
to this address.
All of them beggin' Ms. Hollander
to take your white-trash ass back.
And every one of them
boomeranged to Fox River
marked "return to sender."
Oh, the guards had a real laugh
readin' 'em, didn't we, Geary?
Oh, damn right we did.
That is one mangy lookin'
paw you got there, slick.
What happened,
a Boy Scout fought back? Geary.
Now you're going to tell me where
you stashed Westmoreland's money,
or I'm going to pluck you like
a chicken, stitch by stitch.
Fine, you want to know
where the money is?
I did spend a whole bunch of
it last night on your momma.
Wrong answer.
Come here, baby.
How are you?
- Hm? You good?
- Yeah.
She's okay.
- Baby.
- Yeah.
What do we do now?
What are we going to do?
Get a ticket on the train.
Come on.
Just wait here til
the train comes.
Two Caucasian males on foot,
fleeing the Willcox station.
LJ!
Don't move.
Please. Please.
He's got nothing to do with this.
Face down.
Both of you face down!
- Please.
-  Now!
Cuff 'em.
LJ, I'm sorry.
Suspect in custody.
Possible ID: Lincoln Burrows.
I'm sorry. LJ, I'm sorry.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net