Previously on Prison Break
They refer to it as Scylla.
It's like the company's black book.
- What's that?
- Wireless hard drive that swallows up
any electronic data
within ten feet of it.
And the information
embedded in Scylla?
If we can get close enough...
it's ours.
If Scylla was like a pizza,
all we got is a slice.
So Scylla isn't one card,
it's six.
They killed my boy.
I need to find out who did it.
Rise and shine, bitch!
Breakfast.
Hello?
Cole Pfeiffer, Gregory White here.
I'll see you at Gate
first thing tomorrow.
And I will personally
hand you...
your bonus check.
Sara Tancredi's somewhere
safe, isn't she, Bruce?
So tell me, where is Sara?
Los Angeles?
Good job.
It wasn't a meeting between two
Scylla cardholders, Agent Self.
It was a meeting between
all six cardholders.
So now we know who has the other five cards.
Hey. You got anything
off the video?
Ah, it's a camera
phone 50 feet away.
So, it's pretty grainy.
Still printing.
You ever been on
one of those?
Yeah.
I was still drinking at the time,
so I don't remember much.
Told I was a lot of fun.
You?
No.
Not a lot of yachts
where I'm from.
I always kind of wanted
to live on one.
I thought it'd be nice to have
the ocean as my front yard.
The ocean is your front yard.
What's wrong with the
SS Minnow back there?
Nothing.
You really want to drop
that thing in the water someday
and sail off to parts unknown?
Yeah, why not?
As long as it's you and me.
I like the sound of that.
Yo, Papi.
We got something.
One day.
What's up?
Uh, we got a,
we got a license plate.
It's a printout from
the camera phone.
The numbers
are fuzzy, though.
The whole damn thing's fuzzy.
Forget the numbers.
What's that next to the plate?
Looks like a sticker.
- DMV?
- That's a flag.
It's a diplomatic plate.
The Six Ps, guys.
When I supervised 32 COs
back at Fox River...
it was the Six Ps made it happen.
Can you blow it up?
I need to see more detail.
I'm already on it.
Prior, Planning, Prevents,
Piss-Poor, Performance.
How about you quit shaking your ass
and say what's on your mind?
The second step.
Deciphering the cards, the break-in.
We need to plan.
Agent Self will provide
that information.
You worked with Whistler.
Didn't he say anything
about a location?
Wasn't that in his bird book?
Which T-Bag has.
If he made it out of Sona alive.
Finding where the break-in
is doesn't mean anything
if we don't have the cards.
Here's your flag.
- Algeria?
- Turkey.
Find out where the
Turkish Consul is in town.
You know what?
Get with the program.
You're up.
The guy's name is Erol Tabak.
Consulate is downtown.
Yeah but we can't get
into the consulate.
We can follow him from there.
Michael.
I'm gonna stay back
and work on the video.
Okay.
- One day.
Cole Pfeiffer, how are ya?
Cole.
Pfeiffer.
P-f-e-i-f-e...
Damn it!
Cole Pfeiffer,
how are ya?
No.
Call me Cole, please.
P-f-e-i-f... e...
Damn!
Breaking down...
the captivity of negativity.
That's what we're doing here.
That's what we're
doing here at Gate.
And I would encourage all of you to...
Huh.
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
...f-e-r.
P-f-e-i-f...
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
What do diplomats usually do?
Not a whole lot, but they
park anywhere they want.
Put this on the dash.
Can we get any closer?
That's our guy.
Yeah?
We're copying.
He's got the card on him.
Hell, yes.
That's his wife?
Sign me up.
You lost it.
How?
Dude, I don't know what to tell you
other than you lost it. It's gone man.
We lost it.
What?!
How did we lose him?
We're right next to him.
He's not the cardholder.
She is.
We gotta get out of here
now before we get made.
Come on, go! Go!
Transcript: YDY.com/BBS
Edits: SubScene.com [Team Subscene]
Prison Break S04E04:
Eagles and Angels
Major Editing: Shocker
Minor Editing, Re-Check: VeRdiKT
Last Sync: TheSurferGuy
You know what we've
got in common, right?
What?
We both live in the real world as
opposed to these other knuckleheads.
So that whole prior planning
thing you were talking about,
if you got something
on your mind
and no one else is interested,
you just run it by me, okay?
And we'll just leave it at that.
All right?
Hello?
Sara.
Hey, it's Don Self.
Listen, um,
I have some bad news.
Bruce Bennett was found dead
in his apartment this morning.
I'm sorry.
Lisa, come in.
This will be quick.
I know you're on a schedule.
The value of the kip
is at ten right now.
I'll let you know as
soon as it reaches 15.
At that point, you'll
have to leave immediately.
I have my bags with me.
I could go now.
Don't you have that event tonight?
Yes.
But I--
It's important to keep up appearances.
Not arouse suspicion.
Fine.
I have no doubt in your
leadership abilities, Lisa, but--
Good. Nor do I.
So I won't keep you any longer.
Please...
be safe.
There she is.
All right, do what you gotta do.
Be next to her for two minutes
so the device can copy the card.
I'll get it.
Take a seat.
See the three suits?
Forming a triangle around her?
Those are private contractors.
The Company would only do that
for the inner circle.
We're not getting
anywhere near that lady.
- Not today.
- Great.
What's wrong?
Hey, Teddy.
Well, if it ain't the Brothers Grim.
Easy, Linc! Remember,
we need him.
Now what are you
doing in Los Angeles?
I was thinking about maybe
getting me a career in pictures.
If anyone's got a right
to be pissed, it's me.
You put me out to
pasture back in Panama.
Left me for dead.
Which makes it the third time,
I believe. So, congratulations!
- You got yourself a turkey.
- Where's the bird book?
Bird book?
Where's the book?!
Ooh, look who's looking, pretty.
Look who's looking.
I don't think the two of you are
supposed to be carousing around
the Angel City any more than I am.
You don't know what you've
gotten yourself into, Teddy.
But you don't want to find out,
and you're gonna tell us
where that bird book is.
You're gonna let me go right now,
or all of us are
going down together.
Your choice.
Linc, come on.
WYATT: Tancredi. T-A-N...
C-R-E-D-I.
Make it a buckshot across the grid.
35-mile radius.
If she or any of those
other names come up, call me.
FEMALE VOICE: Confirmed.
Where are you?
Los Angeles.
Trailing Dr. Sara Tancredi.
I ask for the knights,
you're chasing a pawn.
She's irrelevant.
Not to Scofield.
If anyone knows what rock
he's hiding under, it's her.
What about Gretchen?
I'm having her softened up,
but I question the merit
of keeping her alive.
I don't think you should allow--
She must know something.
She lives until she talks.
Now, I have something else
I need you to do for me.
It seems a former employee...
is looking into Scylla.
T-Bag's in town?
Yeah, but we lost him.
He could be anywhere by now.
It's not where he is.
It's what he's doing.
He blew this whole
thing for all of us.
- Where's Sara?
- The boat.
Of course it's my fault
that he's dead.
- That's not true.
- We both know it is.
I shouldn't have called him.
I knew that. I should never
have reached out to him.
I shouldn't have
involved him in any--
Bennett chose to help you.
The Company killed him...
not you.
Listen to me, Sara. This is...
This is not your fault.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Hi. Can I help you?
With that smile
you already have.
I'm Cole Pfeiffer.
Mr. Pfeiffer, uh,
welcome to Los Angeles.
No, please! Call me Cole.
Uh, Mr. White is looking forward
to meeting with you,
uh, Cole, but he's just
running a few minutes late.
Precisely how few minutes
are we talking about?
Oh, it shouldn't take long.
You can have a seat
right over there.
Oh. Ooh, I almost forgot.
You already have a message.
I do?
Mm-hmm. Mr. Xing called.
Twice.
I guess your reputation
precedes you.
I guess so.
Don Self.
When did they find the body?
This morning.
They're saying it was a suicide,
but you and I know better.
So I need to ask you
something very important, okay?
Did Bruce Bennet
know where you are now?
I don't know.
Because if he did,
there's a damn good chance
that the Company
does now too. Okay?
So you need to work double time.
Get some eyes in the back
of your head, you understand?
Look, I appreciate the
motivational speech,
but how about you figure out
where we have to break-in
so we can decode those cards?
I've, I've got...
other guys doing
some digging, okay?
Actually, you might have two.
Well, what are you...
what are you talking about?
His name is Theodore Bagwell.
He was with us in Panama,
and now he's here in Los Angeles,
and he has a book that used to belong
to Whistler, and Mahone thinks...
Mahone thinks this book
has a plan for the break-in.
You've got to be kidding me.
I wish I were.
You've reached Jasper Potts.
Leave a message.
Hey, it's me. Listen,
I need that information
we talked about, like yesterday,
you understand?
Call me back. Call... me... back,
as soon as possible.
Lisa Tabak.
Wife of the Turkish Consul.
Married four years,
children... none.
Listed as the logistician in
the executive profile for SENSA,
a privately funded think tank
with offices in D.C,
New York, Chicago
and Los Angeles.
Yeah, and the only thing I want to
know about this chick is her schedule.
What she's doing,
where she's going.
We might not have that kind of time.
This morning, when she
first got out of the car,
she had a suitcase.
Well, let's check the airlines, match
her name against any departing flights.
Maybe she's already gone.
I don't think so.
If she's going anywhere today,
it's gonna be on the red eye.
According to this press release,
Lisa Tabak is being honored
at some charity shindig Downtown.
Well, that's great.
That's where we'll get her.
What's the benefit for?
She's the top donor of an
organization called Eagles and Angels.
Eagles and Angels?
You've heard of it?
When a police officer dies
in the line of duty,
he's an Eagle.
The ones he leaves behind are Angels.
That's a benefit for the
Association of Law Enforcement.
If you're gonna get near her,
it's gonna be with about
half the cops in L.A.
Jasper, where the hell you been?
- Thinking.
- Thinking?
Come on, the only thing
you should be thinking about
is what I asked you to get for me.
Did you find the location?
Yes, yes, and don't
say anything else, okay?
I heard clicks yesterday on my phone.
All right, settle down, all right?
I'm coming to you.
It doesn't matter, you know,
cause you're never gonna
be able to get in, not
where they're keeping it.
I should have never
helped you out. I--
Just relax, okay?
I'm coming to you right now.
Think they're strong enough?
Together they should be.
There's everything on the list.
You sure we have to steal them?
It's the one thing we need that
we can't get at a store,
buddy, so yes,
we got to steal them.
We'll get everything else
and meet you there.
All right.
Look, um,
you gonna be okay?
Yeah. I just need time.
All right.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Okay.
I am so sorry I'm not
going to be around next week
to see you in action, Cole.
But you'll be in good
hands with Andy here.
I have to catch a
flight to San Francisco,
but I just wanted to
say how thrilled we are
to have you here,
and hopefully, some of the rest
of the sales force can
learn a thing or two.
Uh, we'll settle up that check
when I get back, all right?
Uh, remember,
don't call it Frisco.
They hate that up there.
True.
Well, why don't I show
you to your office, Cole?
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't see anywhere
in your paperwork
that you were...
handicapped.
Otherwise, I would have made
the necessary adjustments
to your work space.
Andy, I like to think of myself as...
handicapable.
- Right!
- Yeah.
Well, here you are.
Right, right.
So this is where I'm
gonna be doing my, uh...
my work,
right here in this, uh...
...office.
That's right.
So, I'd better be rolling my sleeves, then.
You know, Cole,
I-I got to tell you.
I'm still a little amazed at somebody
I've never even seen at a convention
or seminar just falls from the sky
and shatters all of our sales records.
When you believe in Gate like I do,
it ain't that hard to sell.
There you go.
Well.
And here's your corner
office as requested.
Welcome to the team.
All rightly, then.
Thank you.
One...
22...
...B.
Oh.
Hello, Sara.
Hey, Sara,
where you going?
What can I get you?
Club soda, please.
How many years?
Sorry?
In the program.
How many years
have you been sober?
About three years
and three months.
Good for you.
Yeah, it doesn't feel good today.
But I'll take the high five
for cracking the big question.
Which is?
Is life a tragedy,
or is there...
...hope?
You tell me.
Double bourbon, neat.
Just pour it.
Cheers, honey!
Over here.
Eagles and Angels,
with contributions from the Company.
This thing's supposed
to start in five minutes.
- Excuse me, sorry.
- No problem.
Where do you work out of?
That's one of my guys up there.
I'm sorry, I just--
Oh, sure, sure.
Of course.
Okay, I've known
him my whole life.
He was a very close
person to my family.
It's always the good ones.
You ain't gonna drink that?
Honey, the Good Shepard
is here to ease your pain.
Ronald Winston Shepard...
you can call me Shep.
Shep, I really don't feel
like talking right now.
You've been talking to her.
Leave her alone, okay?
Pardon me.
Go on.
When I was 13,
I had to go see Annie, the musical,
but my mom had passed away earlier that
year and my dad had agreed to take me in.
I was all ready in my new dress,
and, uh, and I knew
every word of this thing.
And my dad called from work, and
he said he wasn't going to make it.
That wasn't the first time.
And I remember feeling
like I was floating...
like I was the only person
in the whole world.
And Bruce came.
He showed up to take me in, uh...
And after,
he took me home, and he said
that if I ever needed him,
he'd be there for me.
And a month ago,
I needed him, and I called him.
And he died for it.
Hey!
Just a sec.
What would he want you to do?
Let me do you a favor.
A settle-up here.
Uh, before we sit down to eat,
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the 15th Annual Eagles
and Angels Benefit.
We all know why we're here tonight,
so I'd like to begin
with a moment of silence
to renew our dedication to the law
and to honor those
whose lives were cut short
by their fearless pursuit of justice.
They will truly be missed.
Thank you!
Enjoy your dinner.
I've been made, guys.
Just get the card copy.
Here we go.
We're copying!
Hi, my condolences.
Yes?
The kip's at 15.
I understand.
I'm very sorry, but I'm
going to have to leave.
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
What's she doing?
She's leaving.
I'm... so sorry.
No, no, not again.
Yeah?
I've been made.
Meet me out back.
Go.
Hey!
Lincoln Burrows.
I don't know who
you think I am.
I know who you are.
Now put the gun, slowly.
Three. Copy?
Move.
Move it.
Let's get the device.
That's far enough.
Why don't you just
call one of the cops?
We work for the Company,
Burrows. We don't need cops.
Got any last words?
Yeah?
We got a problem. I just
killed one of the guards.
Let's go now!
No. We don't have it yet.
Do what you got to do.
We got to get rid of the body.
Let them find him.
What?
Wait for Mahone.
Gretchen.
How's my girl?
It seems your friend Whistler wasn't
the only one looking into Scylla.
You know anything about that?
No!
No.
You never know anything, do you?
You have nothing to
do with any of this.
Scofield, Burrows...
You don't know who--
No.
You can't keep lying to me.
No!
I don't know!
You look so...
...damn easy.
I can make this a lot harder.
Yes.
A credit card belonging to Bruce Bennett
was just used at a bar in San Pedro.
Thank you. It's lovely.
Excuse me.
Uh, we have a DOA outside,
I believe it's one of your men.
You need to come with me.
Excuse me?
No one's leaving here
until you make an ID.
Please.
Mathers.
Stay with Mrs. Tabak.
Uh, what happened?
I have a plane to catch.
I understand.
We'll make this fast.
Officer Mathers,
he'll wait with you.
Please. Stay with her.
If you could just wait
with me, ma'am.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Should only take a few minutes.
This is a nice memorial.
I very much respect the
sacrifices you men make.
There's a lot of bad people out there.
Officer Mathers, you, um...
you have something.
Your, your nose is bleeding.
One day...
Excuse me.
I'm looking for this woman.
Sara Tancredi?
- Here, take that.
- Thank you.
You okay?
Here we go.
Here we go!
Hell, yes.
It's nothing.
Travel safely.
Mrs. Tabak, we've got to leave.
Ma'am, now.
I'm telling you,
I haven't seen her.
You're sure?
Oh, look out, fellas!
It's the pigs! Run!
Shut up, wiseass.
You're sure you got
the whole thing?
A hundred percent.
Where's Sara?
It's not my turn to watch her.
What the hell are we gonna do?
Someone must've seen us.
SELF: Don't worry, it's handled.
PAD: Politically motivated?
Possibly an Armenian.
Tip came in to LAPD.
The assailant thought the
consul was at the event.
Lisa's bodyguard got in the way.
Did Lisa make her flight?
Yes, General.
What do you got?
I had a guy.
I did. I had a guy.
He, uh, was an informant.
Actually, he used to work for the
Company for about 11 years until
he turned against them
and decided to help me.
He said he had the
location we needed.
But I, uh...
found him dead in
his apartment today.
I'm sorry.
First Bennett,
now your guy, huh?
Yup.
They're closing in on us.
There's no doubt about it,
and now, I'm, uh...
empty-handed.
And now I have no idea
where we need to break into.
We keep moving forward, Agent Self.
Nothing changes.
- No matter what.
- Right.
Okay.
Regardless of what happens, I, uh,
I like your style, Scofield.
You need anything else, Mr. Cole?
I'm all right, little lady.
What was your plan,
Mr. Whistler?
What was your plan?
Shan Xing.
You're wasting my mail, now.
Cole Pfeiffer did not
arrive for our meeting.
So you don't have Scylla?
Next time, Shan Xing.
I'll be in Los Angeles
if anyone needs me.
Number two down,
on to number three.
We manage to get anything
off Lisa Tabak's phone?
I don't know.
I didn't pick up anything but the card.
I want to thank you for
what you did back there.
I need you to do
something for me.
Yeah, doesn't everybody.
I'm looking for the man
who killed my son.
What do you need?
Here's the police report.
I need you to get into
the FBI database...
and find a profile.
This man is a professional assassin.
He's African-American,
six foot, four.
About 220 pounds.
That's for your eyes only.
Hey.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Well, I was worried.
Where are you?
Let me come get you.
No, it's okay.
I'm almost home.
Um, listen...
You're what's keeping
me going right now.
And you're all I have left,
and that scares me.
I just want to be together.
I know the circumstances are
a little less than ideal, but...
We are together.
You're here, I'm here.
It's not "one day"
anymore, it's, um...
it's today.
Well, why don't you come back and
uh, we'll make some dinner, and...
maybe find a little
time for ourselves.
Okay, I'll be right there.
www.tvsubtitles.net