Previously on Prison Break:
Hey, yo, we're headed out man.
Good luck.
I hope you find
the girl, buddy.
Baby, what the
hell is going on?
Yeah, well Hector says that you
can serve your full sentence.
What are you doing here,
where's Maricruz?
She's with me now.
What's this I hear about
you coming home soon?
You're not getting your
daughter's hopes up are you?
You sitting down?
Your man is coming home this week.
We can make it to the
courthouse on foot from here.
You don't understand,
everything is in that car.
I've been clean
for 18 months now.
I want to help people get from
where I've been to where I am.
You were right. I should never
have gotten you involved in this.
I just need to know what
Michael Scofield wanted from you
in exchange for the green card.
Caroline, I've been
doing this for 15 years
and it's never been about anything
other than you, your family
and, most importantly,
this country.
Now, I need to know who
I'm working for here.
You are working for me.
Are you aware of any arrangement
Officer Bellick had with any inmate
regarding Prison Industries?
Yeah, he sold it
to John Abruzzi.
Officer Brad Bellick, you're terminated,
effective immediately.
They just announced
the rewards on the TV.
- How much?
- $100,000 a piece.
The money is just
outside of Tooele, Utah.
Truck!
Get men in all the
area hospitals.
Wherever they are,
one of them is bleeding good.
- We got to move.
- I can't.
You put in all that work,
break out of prison,
only to end up dead at
the bottom of a ditch.
Kind of sad really.
So which one of them was it?
We've got a blanket
on all the hospitals.
Free clinics?
If they've got Band-Aids and Bactine,
we've got a body in there.
The brothers come
in for medical,
they're getting it in a van
on the way back to Fox River.
Anything break on
the other six?
Eyes and ears on the families.
So far, no hits.
Maybe just laying low.
What's the hardest thing in
the world for a con to do?
Nothing?
Few things in life
are certain, Ms....?
Lang.
Death, taxes and the fact
that a man on the run
will make a mistake sometime
in the first 72 hours.
Needing distance,
he'll steal a car.
Needing money,
he'll rob a store.
Needing help,
he'll trust someone that he shouldn't.
And when he does...
he will leave behind the crumbs
that will take us right to him.
I need your help.
- Michael, what are you doing?
- Cayenne pepper.
What?
- In your kitchen, do you have any?
- Um... yeah, maybe.
I'm gonna need some
rubbing alcohol,
some towels and pain killers,
whatever you got.
- Some booze.
- Please!
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
It's fine, man,
let's just keep moving.
We keep moving and that
leg keeps bleeding.
The leg keeps bleeding and we're
not getting out of Illinois.
This is going to hurt.
That's good, that's good,
that's good.
- This will seal the capillaries.
- Michael, you should not have come here.
- The police have been here asking questions.
- We didn't have a choice.
Listen, you know I'm thankful
for the help with the green card,
but I just don't want
to get involved.
I know, I know it wasn't part
of our deal, I know, Inow.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But there was nowhere else to go.
When I saw you on the news,
I was worried.
I just hoped you crossed
the border by now.
So did I.
Keep giving him these.
See if you can find
him some clean clothes.
Okay.
I got to go back
and get our car.
Forget the car.
We can get another.
I don't need a car,
I need that car.
Why?
Because in that car is
everything we need to disappear.
- What have you got?
- Here we go boss,
one of the blues hauled in a
vagrant a couple hours ago.
Seems the man was in
possession of an item or two
that didn't exactly
belong to him.
Looks like we got
our first mistake.
Hey, you got any of
that oriental jerky?
Excuse me?
Teriyaki flavor.
No.
You got any in the back?
Uh, let me check.
And, give me a bottle of that Early
Times while you're back there, junior.
Feel free to earn
your paycheck today.
Watch the store,
I'll be right back.
How goes it, Roy?
To be honest, Roy, I could've done
without the knee to the junk.
You bit me, Brad.
Like a little girl, you bite me.
- Well, you had it coming.
- Yeah, probably did.
You know it's crazy,
us taking it out on each other
for how things turned out.
You want someone to blame,
how about those convicts staring up
at us from the papers every morning.
They took my job,
my pension, my dignity.
When they went over that wall, they
took all of it right along with them.
Everything I worked
for my whole life.
See that reward they got?
Those ass-hats are worth more
dead than you and I are alive.
- Not for long.
- What do you mean?
I mean somebody's going to get
that money, might as well be me.
You know a job like that might
go a little smoother with
an extra pair of hands.
You really think I'm going to
split that reward with you?
I'm just saying, you run into those
brothers, two of them, one of you.
You might find yourself
wishing for a good wingman.
Just get it done, Mike.
- How are you doing?
- May I help you?
Yeah, I hope so, Chuck.
I think you may
have towed my car.
- What did it look like?
The car you stole the backpack from.
What did it look like?
- I don't know, man, maybe it was gray.
- It's a gray Accord.
License number?
Look, man, that's all I know.
I wasn't after the car.
Thought the bag had
some clothes in it.
You remember where
the car was parked?
- Where'd you park it?
- Corner of Hancock and 15th.
I don't know,
maybe around 15th somewhere,
but it ain't going
to be there anymore.
What do you mean?
That's the reason I didn't
get to grab anything else.
- Tow truck rolls up.
- Already on it.
Okay. It's going to be
60 bucks for the tow,
and 24 for the overnight.
All right,
be right back with your vehicle.
Shouldn't take
but a few minutes.
- Hello?
- Petey, it's Sucre.
- As in, Fernando Sucre?
- Is there another one?
Man, I hope not. But my boy Sucre would
not be calling me on the telephone,
thereby making me an accessory
to his dumb-ass escape, man.
I'm sorry, bro, I just...
I just...
I just need you to get
a hold of Maricruz.
I can't call her cell because the
Feds will be all over the place...
Homie, listen, man,
you have got to forget about that girl.
If I could forget
about her, pendejo,
I'd still be at Fox River,
sitting in cell 40 on your old bunk.
Yeah, well, I hope you're
holding on to something tight
'cause I'm about to break
it down for you, brother.
She's getting married
to Hector on Saturday.
- What day is today?
- Thursday, bro. Sorry, man.
All right, you got to get
her to your place tonight.
I got one last shot to make
her change her mind, dude.
Just find a way to
get her there, okay?
Wait... Sucre, hang on, man.
About the, uh...
about the broken window.
Yeah, we got a disclaimer
posted right there on the wall,
says we're not responsible...
Yeah, I don't... I don't care
about the broken window, Chuck.
- I had a backpack inside.
- Not when we got it.
I got some paperwork
for you to fill out.
You look familiar.
Yeah, you... you were the attending
when I first started here.
Sure.
Um, would one of you mind
calling me a cab, please?
I don't think so.
Look, Dr. Tancredi, I...
I just want to say good luck.
- Sara Tancredi?
- I'm sorry.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Please place your
hands behind your back.
If you have any questions,
I'm happy to come down to...
Ms. Tancredi,
out of respect for your father,
- I'm going to ask you again.
- My father?
I'm sure he'd prefer that
this went without incident.
You have the right to speak to an
attorney before you speak to the police.
Anything you say may be used
against you in a court of law.
And to have an attorney present during
questioning now or in the future.
Caroline, they're
taking her in.
Of course.
I'll keep an eye on her.
All you got to do is sign
here at the bottom...
and be on your way.
Excuse me, please.
Brewster's Towing.
This is Agent Mahone with the FBI.
Who am I speaking with?
Chuck.
Okay, Chuck, I want to alert
you to a possible situation.
Are you listening to me, Chuck?
An individual may be coming
there to inquire about a vehicle.
A gray Accord,
probably with a busted rear window.
Has anyone come by looking for a
vehicle that matches that description?
Yes, sir.
When?
Uh...
Chuck.
Will you tell me
when he was there?
Right now.
Scofield's there.
Chuck, stall him.
We've got people on the way--
do not let him leave.
- Do not let him leave.
- It's my supervisor, he...
I just got to get clearance
before I can release the car.
Chuck, you there? Hey, Chuck.
Okay, come on, come on,
Chuck, you still with me?
Yeah, that vehicle might not
be here when you get here.
- You need to send somebody now.
- Do not let him leave!
Oh, he got the keys.
- Where the hell are those units?!
- Still six or seven minutes out, sir.
We got chatter; it's Franklin.
He's at a payphone Downtown.
Mistake number two.
Look, I know. I know, baby,
just let me explain, all right?
Were you ever even
in the military?
I served my country,
and my country served me up. All right?
Look, I wish I could lay this all
out for you right here, right now.
But just know, baby,
I am sorry, and I love you,
and when the time comes,
I will explain everything.
Give me one good reason why I
shouldn't turn you in right now.
You know what?
I'll give you three.
Me, you,
and that beautiful little girl of ours.
I got a plan. I got a plan that
is going to get us some money,
where you and I and our baby--
nobody can ever find
us or bother us again.
You got to trust me.
That's all I need is the opportunity
for you to hear me out. All right?
All right.
All right, listen. Has anybody
tried to contact you about me?
- No.
- Okay.
Okay, that's good, that's good.
Listen.
In the Rainbow Room...
Restaurant, New York City.
Do you remember that beautiful
spot where we took that picture?
The one by the window?
Mm-hmm.
I am going a be waiting in
that spot one week from now.
And that's all that I
want in this whole world
is for my two girls to
be waiting there for me.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Look, I got to go.
Baby, I just want to know,
are you going to be there?
I don't know.
But you know me.
- Do I?
- Yes!
Good-bye, Miles.
I'll alert the field
office in Manhattan,
have them send Franklin's picture to
every employee at the Rainbow Room.
Then go have a chat with
his wife, woman-to-woman.
Ask her why she never once
visited her husband at Fox River.
Pretend you don't know the answer.
That relationship is fragile.
We keep tapping on cracks,
and she's going to break.
Yes, sir,
I appreciate the assignment. I...
Lang, I don't need gratitude.
I need leads, answers, progress.
Anybody that can't deliver
that just don't even unpack.
- Clear?
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Wheeler.
- Stand by.
Stay on Scofield. I want the
license plate number on that Accord
and I want you to get
it out on the wire.
- Yeah.
- Now.
I'll call you back.
What's going on?
Apparently, I wasn't the only
one looking for this car.
Great! Let's get out of here.
I'm sorry I had to
involve you in this.
I mean,
any more than I already have.
Good luck.
To you, too.
So, um...
I'll see you.
Yeah, I hope so.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
We're heading west,
toward the money, toward LJ.
We just got one
more stop to make.
What for?
You trust me?
Of course I trust you, Brad.
It's just that if anybody
finds out about this, I...
They won't.
Let me handle this.
Humpty Dumpty
climbed up a wall.
Humpty Dumpty had a great fall.
Look... I already told the feds
I don't know anything, okay?
Those suits with pedicures and
penny loafers. Why would you?
They have rules to follow,
codes of conduct.
They got jobs to protect.
Now me, on the other hand.
Come on, Boss. I swear.
Those guys didn't let
me in on any plans.
Then you're telling me in all
your little powwows in the yard,
they never once mentioned
what they were going to do
- once they went over that wall?
- That's right.
Now... I may not work
here anymore, Big-uns,
but I still got influence
with people who do,
people who will do whatever I ask
them to to whoever I ask them to.
And a...
curvy man like yourself,
well, let's just say there's
some filthy individuals
who might enjoy a cellie
with womanly attributes.
Now, you're going to tell
me everything you know
about where those
convicts are headed,
or I'm going to throw your
fat ass to the wolves.
Okay, thanks.
Mistake number three:
someone reported seeing a man
matching Fernando Sucre's
description stealing a car.
- Where?
- Defiance, Ohio.
Someone's going down today.
I know, mami, I know.
- Sara... I paid your bail.
- You took your time.
I'm the governor.
I do have things that...
Go to hell, Dad.
You keep this up,
this may be the only place
I'll be able to see you.
Do you even want to
hear my side of things?
Not particularly, Sara, no.
Especially when I have no
idea whose "side" you're on.
But I do know this.
Somebody is going to go down because
of what happened at Fox River.
And it would be in both of our best
interests if that someone was not you.
And to ensure this,
certain steps need to be taken.
One: you should go to a
daily recovery meeting.
Two: you need to go before a
judge and plead not guilty,
- and three,
- Dad, I don't...
You need to tell the D.O.C.
everything you know about how
that prison was being run.
And that Warden Pope,
how he was granting favors to Scofield
because Scofield helped him
with his personal projects,
thereby exposing him to
certain restricted areas
where he may have been able to
obtain a key to the infirmary.
I can't do that.
Oh, yes you can, Sara.
You can do that and you will.
I did it, Dad.
I left the door open,
me and no one else.
That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
- That's not true.
Sara... just do
what you're told,
otherwise there will
be consequences...
that will affect us all.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
Yes, sir.
Good.
In one week...
I will be appointed the new Vice
President of the United States.
There will be a ceremony,
you will be invited,
but you will not attend.
Good-bye, Sara.
- Let's put some music on.
- Don't.
I forgot. No radio.
Man, it's quiet out here. Inside,
there was always noise, you know?
Someone yelling, guards making rounds.
I got used to it.
You're right.
We should go back.
The tats... they weren't just
for getting out, were they?
Breaking out was
just the beginning.
Now, it gets a little
more interesting.
Mm-hmm, 'cause me being strapped to the
electric chair wasn't
interesting enough.
All I'm saying is inside,
we had the element of surprise.
No one knew what
we were planning.
There's something about this guy--
the one in the elevator.
It's like...
it's like he knows
where we're going,
what we're thinking.
If that's true,
it's just a matter of time before he
finds out about the money in Utah,
Bolshoi Booze,
our way into Mexico.
Everything.
- Are you ready for this?
- Make the call.
Please leave a message.
Hey, it's me. I've got Linc.
We're on our way there.
If for some reason you can't make it,
call me back at 9-1-7-4-5...
We just got this
from surveillance.
You remember that voicemail Scofield
prepaid for when he went off to prison?
Yeah.
Someone just left
a message on it.
- Who?
- Scofield.
Something... something
about a meeting,
it sounded like he was
waiting for someone else
to check the message
and then call him back.
This prefix,
that's a cell phone number.
As long as it's turned on...
We can track
exactly where he is.
Don't do anything stupid.
Is there a problem, officer?
You know why I pulled
you over today, sir?
Speeding?
Let me see your license
and registration please?
The thing is, I, uh...
I lost my wallet.
Well, I guess your registration
will have to do just fine then.
So... this is your car,
Mrs. Miller?
Mrs. Miller's my wife.
I'm Mr. Miller.
Well... your tags are expired.
I'll be right back.
Did he sing?
Like a fat, sweaty bird.
Hey, sweet pea.
- Daddy?
- Hey, come here.
Oh, look at you. You're so big.
Hey, why don't you do me a
favor and grab a piece of chalk
and draw Daddy a picture
on the ground, okay?
So, how're you feeling, huh?
You keeping your appetite up?
Sorta. I guess.
That's good. That's real good.
Oh, God, it's so good to see you,
baby girl.
Do you understand what Daddy
is going through right now?
Sorta.
But the kids at school
have been sayin' stuff.
Okay, what have
they been saying?
They're saying you're on TV
because you're a bad man.
And what do you think?
I think if I were someplace
and they wouldn't let
me leave to see you,
I wouldn't do what
they said, either.
Well, you know what?
We are gonna be together real soon.
I promise you.
But Daddy needs you
to do him a favor.
I need you to get a
message to Mommy, okay?
Okay.
Now I need you to tell her if
she understood what I told her
and if she is willing
to trust Daddy...
that she needs to turn on the
porch light at 7:00, okay?
Can you remember that?
That's a good girl.
Dede, stay away from
the gate, honey.
Daddy gotta get going,
okay sweet pea?
- I love you, Daddy.
- I love you, too, baby.
There.
It's not much further now.
Okay, they moved off the Interstate,
heading North on Route 38.
Talk to me.
Where?
There's a patrolman who thinks
he's has Fernando Sucre
pulled over outside of
Latrobe, Pennsylvania.
Get in touch with
the local dispatch.
Make it clear that we want this
man in custody, not in a body bag.
Dead men can't tell us where their
friends are. Yeah, you got it.
It's gotta be,
it looks just like him.
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
I will.
Mr. Miller...
I'm gonna have to ask you to place
your arms outside the vehicle please.
Mr. Miller,
I need to see some hands.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Now.
This is the one.
Do you see him?
Nope. Maybe he didn't
get your message.
They've stopped.
Couple miles up ahead. There's...
There's nothing up
there. What...?
What are they waiting on?
Or who?
All right, that's good,
that's good, that's good.
Oh, come on.
Come on!
Go red.
Now, go red!
Just one more thing.
Do you trust me?
Of course.
How do you throw the
hunter off the scent?
Get rid of the prey.
Remember,
once I hit scan, we'll have about
30 seconds before it reaches 103.7.
And then she blows?
- That's right. Ready?
- Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Something's wrong.
What happened?
I don't know.
But we're going to need the explosion.
He's here.
The radio must have jammed.
We're going to have to
set it off manually.
The car could blow
any second, Michael.
Well, the feds are going to
be here in about two minutes.
If it doesn't look like we're dead,
we will be.
Rock, paper, scissors?
- Linc?
- It's my turn.
Better pray for reception.
How many stations
between 102.1 and 103.7?
Way out here?
Just one, probably.
Oh!
Where's Maricruz?
- Hey. Hey, look, man...
- No, no, no, Petey. You look.
I haven't slept in 72 hours,
I've seen a man's
hand get chopped off,
I've been...
I've been shot at, dug up a grave,
stolen a car,
jumped on a fricking a train,
so please,
just tell me where she is.
Hey, Fernando, slow down, man.
I was trying to tell you,
but you hung up the phone, man.
The wedding-- it's in Vegas.
The city?
Yeah, and they left
a few hours ago.
Wait, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on, hey,
come on. Fernando!
It's pristine, man.
It's just...
Gonna be back to you in one piece,
I promise.
Can we go back to the
part where I said no?
- I wish I had another choice.
- You do have a choice. Come on, man.
It's a 1952 Ural motorbike, bro.
If you so much as scratch it...
No scratches... I promise.
She's the love of my life, bro.
I got to do something.
- You look like hell.
- I've been through hell, papi.
Now I just got to get to Vegas.
Um, hi, I'm Sara, and I, uh...
Um...
over the years,
I've worked with...
more than a few people who had a
history of addiction, and, uh...
I would tell 'em that I could understand
what they were going through
because I...
used to be just like them.
I used to be an addict, too.
And I think, uh...
I think that what's becoming
clear to me is that...
the reason I
understood them is...
because I am like them.
Um...
I never used to be an addict.
I, uh...
Hi, my name is Sara,
and I'm an addict.
Hi, Sara.
Hi, my name's Lance,
and I'm an addict.
Hi, Lance.
I guess a lot of what Sara
just said resonates with me
in what I'm going through.
Put in all that work,
break out of prison,
only to end up dead at
the bottom of a ditch.
Kind of sad really.
So, which one of them was it?
- Shales.
- Shales?
Scofield. Might be Scofield.
You're probably going to find
his brother in there, too.
Oscar Shales is this guy
Mahone tracked for a while.
Nasty little bottom feeder.
You know the type.
- He's still in the wind.
- Can't get 'em all, right?
We should have a pretty
clear path to Utah now.
They'll turn their
attention to the other guys,
which means we'll be off
their radar for a while.
They're going to get the lab
results back from the accident, man.
- We'll be in Mexico by that time.
- Provided the transport comes through.
Oh, come on, baby.
In the Rainbow Room.
Do you remember that beautiful
spot where we took that picture,
the one by the window?
I am going to be waiting in
that spot one week from now.
- She sleeping okay?
- Yeah. Like a baby.
Good.
So, you said you had some information
you wanted to tell me about
your husband?
Looks like I owe
you another one.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
Well, uh, once we get to Mexico,
I'll send you $10,000,
like I promised.
Plus another three for the car.
Are you meeting up with her,
the doctor?
Sara?
I, uh... I don't know.
We should get moving.
Next town is a few miles away.
Yeah, that's fine.
I can catch a bus from there.
Thanks again, Nika.
I knew the little whore
would take us right to 'em.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net