1
00:00:01,350 --> 00:00:03,510
los angeles california

2
00:00:03,600 --> 00:00:05,540
They ran the projection you asked for, General.

3
00:00:18,640 --> 00:00:19,240
You're clear.

4
00:00:19,540 --> 00:00:20,250
Go ahead.

5
00:00:20,250 --> 00:00:22,080
There's been a complication.(Chicago Illinois)

6
00:00:22,080 --> 00:00:24,050
Burrows and Scofield have been transferred to...

7
00:00:24,050 --> 00:00:26,060
I read the newspapers.

8
00:00:26,160 --> 00:00:28,720
You don't have to tell me what's in the headlines.

9
00:00:29,250 --> 00:00:32,590
The exact penitentiary where they're being held is undisclosed.

10
00:00:32,650 --> 00:00:34,700
But you can guarantee it'll be Federal.

11
00:00:35,620 --> 00:00:36,600
Supermax.

12
00:00:36,600 --> 00:00:38,060
No more updates.

13
00:00:38,400 --> 00:00:39,570
Call me when they're dead.

14
00:00:41,970 --> 00:00:43,360
SELF: Welcome to Los Angeles.

15
00:00:43,840 --> 00:00:46,610
As it turns out, men who have escaped not one, 

16
00:00:46,710 --> 00:00:50,070
but two penitentiaries, are considered a bit of a flight risk.

17
00:00:50,070 --> 00:00:53,360
So we need to know where you are and what you're doing at all times.

18
00:00:53,360 --> 00:00:55,420
Theses are GPS ankle monitors.

19
00:00:55,420 --> 00:00:57,350
Now step up, take one and put it on.

20
00:00:58,100 --> 00:00:59,150
I ain't wearing that.

21
00:00:59,760 --> 00:01:04,710
Let's make this clear: I'm your ally, but more importantly, I'm your boss.

22
00:01:04,710 --> 00:01:07,910
Which means if this fails-- it's my ass on the line as much,

23
00:01:07,910 --> 00:01:10,310
 if not more, than yours, so from this point on, 

24
00:01:10,310 --> 00:01:12,760
if I ask you to do something, you do it.

25
00:01:12,910 --> 00:01:15,290
If I ask you to say something, you say it.

26
00:01:15,290 --> 00:01:18,230
And if I ask you to put on a monitor-- you put on a monitor.

27
00:01:38,930 --> 00:01:41,060
SELF: As far as the general public is concerned,

28
00:01:41,060 --> 00:01:44,850
 you're being contained in a supermax facility somewhere in the United States.

29
00:01:44,850 --> 00:01:49,030
So to avoid any messy explanations and stay off the Company's radar

30
00:01:49,030 --> 00:01:51,690
-- you need to keep your heads down and your ears open.

31
00:01:53,480 --> 00:01:55,870
We've provided cell phones, clothing, and toiletries--

32
00:01:55,870 --> 00:01:58,090
 all the basic necessities to get you up and running.

33
00:01:58,510 --> 00:02:01,400
Hey, uh, you-you patted these guys down before you let them in, right?

34
00:02:01,400 --> 00:02:02,690
'Cause I can't be getting shanked or shivved.

35
00:02:02,690 --> 00:02:03,700
Who's this?

36
00:02:04,490 --> 00:02:05,760
This is Roland Glenn.

37
00:02:05,760 --> 00:02:06,900
He'll be assisting you.

38
00:02:06,900 --> 00:02:08,090
We've already got our team.

39
00:02:08,090 --> 00:02:11,500
No, Scofield, see, this is my team, And Roland's working off 

40
00:02:11,500 --> 00:02:12,950
a sentence just like the rest of you.

41
00:02:13,380 --> 00:02:15,870
In fact, with the amount of security that's gonna be around Scylla,

42
00:02:15,870 --> 00:02:17,990
 Roland's expertise will be a necessity.

43
00:02:17,990 --> 00:02:21,260
So, if no more questions, let's get to work on finding Scylla.

44
00:02:21,260 --> 00:02:22,560
What about that second step?

45
00:02:22,560 --> 00:02:23,570
What about the break-in?

46
00:02:23,570 --> 00:02:25,380
You let me worry about step two, okay?

47
00:02:25,380 --> 00:02:26,970
You just worry about finding Scylla.

48
00:02:26,970 --> 00:02:28,500
I've got an idea where to start.

49
00:02:29,900 --> 00:02:31,190
That's excellent, Alexander.

50
00:02:31,190 --> 00:02:32,980
See, there's a man who's thinking.

51
00:02:33,350 --> 00:02:35,930
All right, let's let these men get to work.

52
00:02:36,590 --> 00:02:37,380
Good luck.

53
00:02:37,910 --> 00:02:38,680
To all of us.

54
00:02:41,310 --> 00:02:43,980
Yeah, since I was here first I think I'll just go ahead 

55
00:02:43,980 --> 00:02:45,850
and grab that S.S.bedroom, if that's cool.

56
00:02:47,180 --> 00:02:47,770
Sara...

57
00:02:47,850 --> 00:02:48,660
Yeah?

58
00:02:48,660 --> 00:02:49,700
you take the bunk.

59
00:02:53,660 --> 00:02:57,230
You know, when this is, when this is all done-- you and me, we're gonna settle up.

60
00:03:04,260 --> 00:03:07,330
All right, obviously, there's a lot of history in this room.

61
00:03:07,800 --> 00:03:08,600
That's a given.

62
00:03:09,010 --> 00:03:11,910
But it we're gonna pull this off, it's gonna take all of us.

63
00:03:11,910 --> 00:03:13,320
We got to work together.

64
00:03:13,320 --> 00:03:15,800
So if anyone has a problem, get it out now.

65
00:03:16,280 --> 00:03:17,950
You want to clear the air with someone...

66
00:03:19,220 --> 00:03:20,180
now's the time.

67
00:03:29,610 --> 00:03:30,190
All right.

68
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:31,320
Let's get to work.

69
00:03:32,290 --> 00:03:36,410
Whistler's assignment was to drop off this, this, this data card-

70
00:03:36,410 --> 00:03:38,460
- th-this 'Scylla' to a Company Executive.

71
00:03:38,460 --> 00:03:40,570
Someone he referred to as "The Cardholder.

72
00:03:40,570 --> 00:03:43,550
" And his job was to-to protect it.To...

73
00:03:44,000 --> 00:03:44,970
keep it safe.

74
00:03:45,410 --> 00:03:49,930
Now, I didn't see who he was, but I got a look at his driver.

75
00:03:49,930 --> 00:03:50,750
His driver?

76
00:03:51,260 --> 00:03:55,100
You want to sketch this guy's face and match it up to 10 million people in Los Angeles?

77
00:03:55,100 --> 00:03:56,210
Well, that's just great.

78
00:03:56,210 --> 00:03:58,150
I saw more than just the guy's face.

79
00:03:58,740 --> 00:04:00,770
All the drivers were hanging around, talking shop, 

80
00:04:00,770 --> 00:04:02,380
but this guy, he was standing by himself.

81
00:04:02,380 --> 00:04:06,290
Legs apart, hands behind his back, at rest-- he's former military.

82
00:04:06,290 --> 00:04:08,830
His car rides a little lower than the rest of 'em.

83
00:04:09,410 --> 00:04:11,660
Probably signifies private security.

84
00:04:11,660 --> 00:04:13,800
Weighed down by bulletproof siding.

85
00:04:13,800 --> 00:04:16,750
His suit, his suit-- you don't buy a suit like that 

86
00:04:16,750 --> 00:04:19,820
on a cop's salary or pulling weekend gigs as a driver.

87
00:04:19,820 --> 00:04:21,220
That means he's full-time.

88
00:04:21,220 --> 00:04:22,280
He's highly paid.

89
00:04:23,080 --> 00:04:26,490
You ask our friend Mr.Self to run tax records 

90
00:04:26,490 --> 00:04:29,660
on the 45- to 55-year-old white males in Los Angeles 

91
00:04:29,660 --> 00:04:34,010
drawing a military pension, and taking six figures from a private security company, 

92
00:04:34,660 --> 00:04:37,930
and you narrow your field from 10 million till about 50.

93
00:04:37,930 --> 00:04:39,750
And then I can pick the guy out from there.

94
00:04:43,020 --> 00:04:44,810
Find the driver, you find the Cardholder.

95
00:04:47,730 --> 00:04:52,240
Mexican desert
60 miles south of us border

96
00:05:04,900 --> 00:05:06,930
We haven't ate or drank anything for days.

97
00:05:08,730 --> 00:05:10,440
Oh, I don't want to die out here.

98
00:05:10,440 --> 00:05:11,760
We ain't gonna die, Sancho.

99
00:05:12,200 --> 00:05:15,160
Hey.Hey, hey, we ain't gonna die.

100
00:05:15,160 --> 00:05:15,940
Okay.

101
00:05:16,040 --> 00:05:18,400
We just gotta find what's called a compass cactus.

102
00:05:18,680 --> 00:05:20,940
Due to the fact it always leans toward the south.

103
00:05:20,940 --> 00:05:23,550
Inside there's delicious fruit which'll fill our bellies.

104
00:05:23,550 --> 00:05:27,740
Plus, we find out which way is south, we're gonna find out which way is north.

105
00:05:27,740 --> 00:05:28,390
緾omprende?

106
00:05:32,490 --> 00:05:32,990
Tell you what.

107
00:05:34,520 --> 00:05:36,860
Why don't we, uh, rest here for a while, huh?

108
00:05:36,860 --> 00:05:38,420
Travel at night when it's cooler.

109
00:05:40,070 --> 00:05:41,010
Si.That sounds good.

110
00:05:44,390 --> 00:05:45,590
What are we gonna do when we get there?

111
00:05:46,930 --> 00:05:47,900
To San Diego.

112
00:05:48,790 --> 00:05:51,810
You mean after Michael pays for the vile he's transgressed upon me?

113
00:05:56,740 --> 00:05:58,740
I'm still trying to figure that out.

114
00:07:04,710 --> 00:07:05,540
Nice to work with Homeland.

115
00:07:06,950 --> 00:07:09,400
The FBI would take days to gather this intel.

116
00:07:09,400 --> 00:07:11,430
Well, the FBI should'a hired me 'cause I could've gotten

117
00:07:11,430 --> 00:07:13,570
 whatever info you wanted in 25 minutes tops.

118
00:07:14,020 --> 00:07:14,960
You some kind of hacker?

119
00:07:14,960 --> 00:07:17,400
I design silicon lithography for personal gain.

120
00:07:17,400 --> 00:07:18,820
He's an identity thief.

121
00:07:19,100 --> 00:07:19,920
He's a douche.

122
00:07:20,230 --> 00:07:23,080
Hey, why don't you sit in the corner and we'll get you when we need you.

123
00:07:24,700 --> 00:07:25,350
This is him.

124
00:07:26,000 --> 00:07:26,960
That's the driver.

125
00:07:29,220 --> 00:07:29,820
SUCRE: Now what?

126
00:07:29,820 --> 00:07:34,420
Well, he takes us to the Cardholder, and the Cardholder takes us to Scylla.

127
00:07:42,150 --> 00:07:44,430
- You could have left me there,
- in jail.

128
00:07:44,430 --> 00:07:45,690
Could have or should have?

129
00:07:46,430 --> 00:07:47,310
Maybe both.

130
00:07:47,710 --> 00:07:49,090
Are you thanking me, Alex?

131
00:07:49,090 --> 00:07:49,800
I don't know.

132
00:07:49,800 --> 00:07:50,640
Don't bother.

133
00:07:50,640 --> 00:07:52,330
You're here because we needed you.

134
00:07:52,330 --> 00:07:53,700
Not because we wanted you.

135
00:07:53,950 --> 00:07:54,650
That's him.

136
00:07:55,830 --> 00:07:56,580
That's the guy.

137
00:08:06,980 --> 00:08:07,540
MICHAEL: Whoa, whoa.

138
00:08:07,540 --> 00:08:09,940
What's that, private security?

139
00:08:13,630 --> 00:08:14,880
MICHAEL: It's like a fortress.

140
00:08:17,670 --> 00:08:18,640
MICHAEL: Slow down.

141
00:08:18,640 --> 00:08:19,310
Slow down.

142
00:08:19,310 --> 00:08:21,980
This thing we gotta get, it's in there?

143
00:08:24,600 --> 00:08:28,450
Motion sensors, alarm systems, armed guards.

144
00:08:30,800 --> 00:08:33,290
In and out of that place without anybody knowing.

145
00:08:35,020 --> 00:08:36,850
You better have one hell of a plan, Michael.

146
00:08:39,140 --> 00:08:41,560
So, basically, there's no freaking way to break in to the place.

147
00:08:41,560 --> 00:08:42,490
Not quickly.

148
00:08:42,490 --> 00:08:43,700
Not without being seen.

149
00:08:43,700 --> 00:08:46,480
What about the neighbors, uh, somewhere we can be staged from,

150
00:08:46,480 --> 00:08:48,030
 you know, go under and up?

151
00:08:48,520 --> 00:08:50,750
Closest neighbor is here, across the street.

152
00:08:52,160 --> 00:08:53,580
And even that would take weeks.

153
00:08:54,050 --> 00:08:58,140
The government's story about us being held in a supermax will only last so long.

154
00:08:58,140 --> 00:08:58,880
What does that mean?

155
00:08:59,240 --> 00:09:01,650
I mean, then what if somebody finds out we're not.

156
00:09:01,650 --> 00:09:03,270
What if we don't have to be in the house?

157
00:09:03,270 --> 00:09:07,090
If the card-- this Scylla-- is so important maybe the guy is carrying it on him.

158
00:09:07,090 --> 00:09:09,970
Well, according to public records, the owner of the estate's name is Stuart Tuxhorn, 

159
00:09:09,970 --> 00:09:13,650
and he's a CEO of a company called Spectroleum.

160
00:09:13,650 --> 00:09:16,360
Heavy hitter like that's gonna have security 24-7.

161
00:09:16,360 --> 00:09:18,690
And we gotta get this thing without anyone knowing it's gone, right?

162
00:09:18,690 --> 00:09:21,040
So even if he's got it on him, how do we get it off him?

163
00:09:21,040 --> 00:09:22,290
You don't steal the card.

164
00:09:22,560 --> 00:09:23,340
You copy it.

165
00:09:29,500 --> 00:09:31,650
Oh, now you're interested in what I gotta say, right?

166
00:09:33,820 --> 00:09:35,370
Copying it will make it harder.

167
00:09:35,520 --> 00:09:38,310
Not only do you have to steal it, you have to return it, genius.

168
00:09:38,680 --> 00:09:41,790
Only if you don't got me, hombre.

169
00:09:43,360 --> 00:09:44,050
What's that?

170
00:09:44,750 --> 00:09:46,240
This is the reason I got busted.

171
00:09:46,240 --> 00:09:47,830
Oh, you stole the cell phone?

172
00:09:47,830 --> 00:09:49,880
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, I'm lookin' at federal time 

173
00:09:49,880 --> 00:09:51,290
'cause I stole a cell phone-- seriously?

174
00:09:51,290 --> 00:09:53,060
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.

175
00:09:53,060 --> 00:09:56,070
I invented this so that I don't have to steal.

176
00:09:57,160 --> 00:10:00,340
It looks like a cell phone but it's really like a digital black hole.

177
00:10:00,530 --> 00:10:04,240
Wireless hard drive that swallows up any electronic data within ten feet of it.

178
00:10:04,240 --> 00:10:05,110
SUCRE: Like what?

179
00:10:05,110 --> 00:10:08,600
Like the account info of anyone at Starbucks with a latte and a laptop.

180
00:10:09,440 --> 00:10:11,980
Like the PIN number of any credit card used at a gas pump.

181
00:10:12,400 --> 00:10:14,120
I can walk out of here and get the identities 

182
00:10:14,120 --> 00:10:16,980
and financial statements of ten people in ten minutes, on a slow day, 

183
00:10:16,980 --> 00:10:18,760
with one hand on my junk.

184
00:10:20,180 --> 00:10:22,030
And the information embedded in Scylla?

185
00:10:22,420 --> 00:10:23,990
If we can get close enough...

186
00:10:25,920 --> 00:10:26,850
it's ours.

187
00:10:26,920 --> 00:10:29,850
【XTM 字幕组】
http://cnX264.com 荣誉出品

188
00:10:30,920 --> 00:10:35,850
《Prison Break》S04 E02

189
00:10:36,920 --> 00:10:41,850
sync：虾米  四环边上

190
00:10:42,040 --> 00:10:43,090
Is this number...

191
00:10:44,460 --> 00:10:45,770
acceptable to you?

192
00:10:49,780 --> 00:10:51,280
10,000 people?

193
00:11:01,880 --> 00:11:02,940
- Yes.
- Good.

194
00:11:03,660 --> 00:11:07,080
Now that you're on board, we can issue the op-order today.

195
00:11:17,020 --> 00:11:17,780
He's on his way.

196
00:11:19,620 --> 00:11:20,230
All right, hold on.

197
00:11:23,570 --> 00:11:24,520
MICHAEL: Sara, it's me.

198
00:11:25,010 --> 00:11:25,750
Everybody's on.

199
00:11:28,030 --> 00:11:29,390
Now, while I'm monitoring the device, 

200
00:11:29,390 --> 00:11:31,740
I'm not gonna be able to see exactly what data's being copied.

201
00:11:31,740 --> 00:11:34,380
But, like downloading quality porn from the Internet, 

202
00:11:34,380 --> 00:11:37,100
progress bar's gonna tell me when it's time to rock and roll.

203
00:11:37,100 --> 00:11:38,760
How long do they need to stay in range?

204
00:11:39,150 --> 00:11:41,740
Encrypted data like this is gonna take at least two minutes.

205
00:11:42,140 --> 00:11:43,060
Here he comes.

206
00:11:43,520 --> 00:11:44,620
Sucre, you're on.

207
00:11:57,420 --> 00:11:58,120
Good luck.

208
00:12:02,540 --> 00:12:03,160
Easy.

209
00:12:05,970 --> 00:12:07,530
Sir, would you mind stepping away from the vehicle?

210
00:12:09,040 --> 00:12:09,980
Talk to me, Roland.

211
00:12:10,530 --> 00:12:11,470
I got nothing, man.

212
00:12:11,990 --> 00:12:14,740
Last time I had this little action, I was dry humping my way through fifth grade.

213
00:12:14,740 --> 00:12:15,540
Calm down.

214
00:12:17,130 --> 00:12:17,810
Sir...

215
00:12:19,030 --> 00:12:19,720
Sir...

216
00:12:20,270 --> 00:12:21,440
Step away from the vehicle!

217
00:12:22,020 --> 00:12:24,540
Okay, bro, just relax-- we don't have to get all excited.

218
00:12:24,540 --> 00:12:25,760
You speak English now.

219
00:12:26,210 --> 00:12:27,510
Only a little, but, uh...

220
00:12:28,720 --> 00:12:29,590
How about now?

221
00:12:30,110 --> 00:12:30,750
ROLAND: Nada.

222
00:12:30,750 --> 00:12:32,170
Try to get closer to them.

223
00:12:32,170 --> 00:12:34,370
If he was any closer, he'd be in the car.

224
00:12:35,990 --> 00:12:37,760
I get your little act, Pedro.

225
00:12:37,920 --> 00:12:41,560
Hit the brakes, let the rich guy pay for damage you don't intend to fix.

226
00:12:44,060 --> 00:12:47,870
Just give the man some money so we can leave.

227
00:12:53,090 --> 00:12:54,070
Congratulations.

228
00:13:02,180 --> 00:13:03,890
He was there-- I think Tuxhorn was in the car.

229
00:13:03,890 --> 00:13:05,210
So did we get it or not?

230
00:13:05,610 --> 00:13:06,290
Nope.

231
00:13:06,660 --> 00:13:07,350
Nothing.

232
00:13:20,120 --> 00:13:20,850
Can I help you?

233
00:13:24,150 --> 00:13:25,320
JASPER: So how did you find me?

234
00:13:25,780 --> 00:13:26,810
I never lost you.

235
00:13:27,370 --> 00:13:30,600
The, uh, the new nose threw me a bit, but...

236
00:13:30,600 --> 00:13:31,600
What do you want, Don?

237
00:13:31,790 --> 00:13:33,010
I got customers.

238
00:13:33,690 --> 00:13:36,090
Look, back in the days, when you worked with the Company...

239
00:13:36,090 --> 00:13:37,350
Well, for the Company.

240
00:13:37,350 --> 00:13:39,460
I did economic forecasts of their operations.

241
00:13:39,460 --> 00:13:40,600
I mean, I wasn't one of the guys...

242
00:13:40,600 --> 00:13:41,670
But you had access.

243
00:13:41,670 --> 00:13:43,910
Come on-- the last time I helped you, the only thing

244
00:13:43,910 --> 00:13:47,090
 I got out of it was plastic surgery and a $100,000 pay cut.

245
00:13:47,090 --> 00:13:49,620
You know, so either you buy one of these exceptional family cars, 

246
00:13:49,620 --> 00:13:52,260
with above average gas mileage, or you leave me the hell alone.

247
00:13:53,010 --> 00:13:54,040
I know about Scylla.

248
00:13:56,360 --> 00:13:57,460
And I'm going after it.

249
00:13:59,770 --> 00:14:00,970
You know, I knew you were crazy.

250
00:14:00,970 --> 00:14:02,400
I didn't know you were stupid, too.

251
00:14:02,400 --> 00:14:05,130
Well, let's just say I was able to get my hands on it.

252
00:14:05,130 --> 00:14:07,410
It's my understanding that Scylla could only be used 

253
00:14:07,410 --> 00:14:10,870
if it's plugged into a decoder box that's hidden in one of the Company facilities.

254
00:14:10,870 --> 00:14:11,560
Am I right?

255
00:14:11,560 --> 00:14:13,990
You know, I wish I could help, but I can't.

256
00:14:13,990 --> 00:14:15,770
No, you are helping, Jasper.

257
00:14:15,770 --> 00:14:18,470
Just a matter of whether you do it before or after

258
00:14:18,470 --> 00:14:20,870
 I shame you in front of your coworkers here.

259
00:14:26,000 --> 00:14:28,060
Tell me where the Company keeps the box, Jasper.

260
00:14:28,060 --> 00:14:29,230
Could be anywhere; I don't know.

261
00:14:29,230 --> 00:14:30,200
Somebody does.

262
00:14:30,540 --> 00:14:31,200
Right?

263
00:14:31,710 --> 00:14:33,550
Somebody that you might have access to.

264
00:14:33,550 --> 00:14:37,030
You know, if you go down this road, your government job won't protect you.

265
00:14:37,030 --> 00:14:38,570
Then I better not get caught, right?

266
00:14:40,130 --> 00:14:43,770
T-BAG: If I don't find something to eat soon, I don't know what I'm gonna do.

267
00:14:44,440 --> 00:14:45,840
SANCHO: We're not gonna make it.

268
00:14:46,520 --> 00:14:49,430
T-BAG: No, we got to, we got to just keep talking, Sancho.

269
00:14:49,800 --> 00:14:51,680
Keep our brains focused on something other than 

270
00:14:51,950 --> 00:14:54,520
our empty bellies and our dry mouths, okay?

271
00:14:54,520 --> 00:14:55,340
Come on.

272
00:14:55,340 --> 00:14:58,620
Let's start with, uh, your-your favorite color.

273
00:15:05,720 --> 00:15:06,460
Hell you doing?

274
00:15:07,750 --> 00:15:08,750
I'm hungry, Teddy.

275
00:15:08,750 --> 00:15:10,470
Why should the both of us die out here 

276
00:15:10,470 --> 00:15:13,080
when one of us could help the other one survive?

277
00:15:13,080 --> 00:15:15,200
You don't want to do this.Please.

278
00:15:15,200 --> 00:15:16,280
I'll make it quick.

279
00:15:16,740 --> 00:15:17,350
I promise!

280
00:15:21,590 --> 00:15:22,260
Sancho.

281
00:15:29,320 --> 00:15:30,190
Sancho!

282
00:15:31,470 --> 00:15:33,240
Why'd you have to go and do something so...

283
00:16:11,850 --> 00:16:13,470
MICHAEL: So Tuxhorn doesn't keep the card on him.

284
00:16:13,720 --> 00:16:14,930
It must be in there.

285
00:16:18,070 --> 00:16:21,750
Look, there's no way we're getting in that house without being seen.

286
00:16:21,750 --> 00:16:22,570
I know.

287
00:16:23,000 --> 00:16:24,780
Well, if the card's in there, how we gonna copy it?

288
00:16:25,080 --> 00:16:25,680
We're not.

289
00:16:26,750 --> 00:16:28,200
She's gonna do it for us.

290
00:16:40,000 --> 00:16:40,580
Hey.

291
00:16:41,290 --> 00:16:41,800
Hey.

292
00:16:44,280 --> 00:16:45,080
What you reading?

293
00:16:46,590 --> 00:16:48,220
"There is no fighting her.

294
00:16:48,670 --> 00:16:50,090
"No power can fight her.

295
00:16:50,090 --> 00:16:51,710
All that avails is flight.

296
00:16:53,190 --> 00:16:54,360
" That's Homer.

297
00:16:55,120 --> 00:16:56,290
That's from The Odyssey.

298
00:16:56,290 --> 00:16:57,790
Is this from my father's folder?

299
00:16:57,790 --> 00:16:58,420
Yeah.

300
00:16:58,420 --> 00:17:01,000
And it explains why Scylla sounded so familiar.

301
00:17:01,370 --> 00:17:03,780
If I'm not mistaken, it's from that chapter in the book

302
00:17:03,780 --> 00:17:09,100
 where Odysseus is told he has to confront a monster known as Scylla.

303
00:17:09,490 --> 00:17:10,830
Wonder why he wrote this down.

304
00:17:11,390 --> 00:17:17,360
I could be wrong, but I believe Odysseus is told that in order to continue on his path, 

305
00:17:17,360 --> 00:17:21,010
to pass Scylla, it'll require the sacrifice of six of his men.

306
00:17:21,880 --> 00:17:24,490
His only other alternative is to abandon his path.

307
00:17:24,490 --> 00:17:27,730
And he chooses to make the sacrifice.

308
00:17:28,940 --> 00:17:30,340
Well, that's a hell of a choice.

309
00:17:34,050 --> 00:17:35,930
One I'm not sure I'm comfortable making.

310
00:17:40,490 --> 00:17:45,670
Sara, um, about tomorrow-- the plan, the housekeeper...

311
00:17:47,610 --> 00:17:48,600
If you're not up to it...

312
00:17:48,600 --> 00:17:49,530
No, no, I am.

313
00:17:56,320 --> 00:17:59,750
Chicago Illinois

314
00:18:01,880 --> 00:18:06,760
WYATT: Tell me, is Claudia Mauricio a good roommate?

315
00:18:15,350 --> 00:18:16,060
A good person?

316
00:18:20,330 --> 00:18:22,180
I hope she feels the same about you.

317
00:18:28,590 --> 00:18:30,920
Oh, Shelby, you wouldn't believe the traffic on the...

318
00:18:33,180 --> 00:18:35,770
You'll want to be quiet now, Claudia.

319
00:18:36,550 --> 00:18:41,660
There are levels of clearance at the Department of Corrections that are simply not available, 

320
00:18:41,660 --> 00:18:44,010
even for friends as connected as mine.

321
00:18:45,330 --> 00:18:51,730
So, listen carefully, if you even remotely value your friend's life.

322
00:18:53,530 --> 00:18:57,960
You're going to use your security code to access the records for prisoner transfers 

323
00:18:58,310 --> 00:19:02,960
and tell me where they sent Michael Scofield and lincon

324
00:19:33,190 --> 00:19:33,990
Can I take that for you?

325
00:19:34,150 --> 00:19:34,710
Thanks.

326
00:19:34,870 --> 00:19:35,570
Sure.

327
00:19:39,610 --> 00:19:40,480
That's a great bag.

328
00:19:40,680 --> 00:19:41,710
Can I ask you where you got it?

329
00:19:41,820 --> 00:19:45,440
- It was a gift from my boss, so I don't really know
- sorry.

330
00:19:45,560 --> 00:19:46,120
Sure.

331
00:19:46,600 --> 00:19:47,880
Thanks.

332
00:19:48,410 --> 00:19:49,060
I, uh...

333
00:19:49,160 --> 00:19:50,470
I can never find a good bag.

334
00:19:50,610 --> 00:19:54,220
I'm a teacher, and I have books and grading materials and...

335
00:19:54,440 --> 00:19:58,480
I should probably go ahead and just invest in a wagon one of these days.

336
00:19:58,930 --> 00:20:00,160
Yeah, that's why I love this bag.

337
00:20:00,270 --> 00:20:01,570
It has so many pockets.

338
00:20:03,110 --> 00:20:04,580
Do you mind if I take a look?

339
00:20:04,890 --> 00:20:05,950
Oh, no.

340
00:20:06,170 --> 00:20:07,240
Thanks.

341
00:20:27,140 --> 00:20:28,880
Ah, thank God, thank God.

342
00:20:32,160 --> 00:20:33,300
You all right, mister?

343
00:20:33,430 --> 00:20:36,870
Yeah, my damn truck blew a gasket a few miles back.

344
00:20:37,030 --> 00:20:38,610
I've been, uh, hoofing it ever since.

345
00:20:38,900 --> 00:20:39,980
Where you headed?

346
00:20:40,710 --> 00:20:41,910
San Diego.

347
00:20:43,150 --> 00:20:45,090
Hell, we can give you a ride, if you'd like.

348
00:20:46,240 --> 00:20:47,430
Hey, what's wrong, man?

349
00:20:47,560 --> 00:20:48,840
Eat some bad Mexican?

350
00:20:50,490 --> 00:20:51,710
Something like that.

351
00:20:58,420 --> 00:20:59,960
LINCOLN: Same as yesterday, right on schedule.

352
00:21:07,150 --> 00:21:08,690
I hope to hell she's still got that thing in her purse.

353
00:21:15,900 --> 00:21:16,990
Tuxhorn residence.

354
00:21:17,110 --> 00:21:18,690
Hello, I'm from the alarm company.

355
00:21:18,810 --> 00:21:22,770
We've been receiving some, uh, strange signals from your property.

356
00:21:22,870 --> 00:21:24,370
We'd like you to check the windows, please.

357
00:21:24,490 --> 00:21:26,720
Make sure all the contacts are still active.

358
00:21:27,110 --> 00:21:28,330
All the windows?

359
00:21:28,660 --> 00:21:29,690
Yes, ma'am.

360
00:21:29,810 --> 00:21:31,490
Every room in the house.

361
00:21:33,000 --> 00:21:34,280
Okay, hold on.

362
00:21:40,040 --> 00:21:41,300
Does she still have the bag?

363
00:21:41,460 --> 00:21:42,170
Yeah.

364
00:21:48,180 --> 00:21:49,190
She's got it.

365
00:21:49,470 --> 00:21:51,620
I'm picking up all kinds of gak from the house, man.

366
00:21:51,710 --> 00:21:54,370
Small stuff, maybe a digital camera, an MP3 player.

367
00:21:54,480 --> 00:21:56,300
Nothing of the size of what we're looking for, though.

368
00:21:56,660 --> 00:21:57,490
Keep her moving.

369
00:21:57,590 --> 00:21:58,670
So far, so good, ma'am.

370
00:21:58,790 --> 00:22:00,320
Uh, please move on to the next room.

371
00:22:04,580 --> 00:22:05,650
How we doing?

372
00:22:06,690 --> 00:22:07,830
Still don't got it.

373
00:22:11,590 --> 00:22:13,400
If the card's in there, it'd be in some kind of...

374
00:22:13,510 --> 00:22:14,370
a safe.

375
00:22:14,560 --> 00:22:15,370
Office.

376
00:22:15,620 --> 00:22:18,520
Ma'am, our system is showing that the malfunction is coming from a room 

377
00:22:18,640 --> 00:22:21,780
that's designated as, uh, an office or a den.

378
00:22:21,900 --> 00:22:23,000
You mean the library?

379
00:22:23,130 --> 00:22:24,690
Mister doesn't like me going in there.

380
00:22:24,830 --> 00:22:26,640
Well, I think he'd like it even less if you went home 

381
00:22:26,730 --> 00:22:29,350
without properly setting the alarm first, don't you think?

382
00:22:30,660 --> 00:22:31,920
All right, I'll check.

383
00:22:37,850 --> 00:22:38,790
We got something.

384
00:22:38,930 --> 00:22:39,700
The card?

385
00:22:40,330 --> 00:22:40,840
Oh, yeah.

386
00:22:41,010 --> 00:22:42,550
File's so big it can't be anything else.

387
00:22:42,660 --> 00:22:44,960
Now you just gotta keep her there for two minutes while it finishes the burn.

388
00:22:45,130 --> 00:22:46,530
Stall her, we need two minutes.

389
00:22:46,640 --> 00:22:48,280
Ma'am, I think we found the source of our problem-- 

390
00:22:48,420 --> 00:22:51,460
if you could just stay at that particular window and hold it closed 

391
00:22:51,590 --> 00:22:53,670
while we reset the system, that should do it.

392
00:23:04,320 --> 00:23:05,520
Talk to me, Roland.

393
00:23:05,670 --> 00:23:07,320
It's almost there, almost, almost.

394
00:23:07,420 --> 00:23:09,330
Come on, come on, come on, come on.

395
00:23:13,370 --> 00:23:14,880
Come on.

396
00:23:19,820 --> 00:23:21,070
Come on.

397
00:23:22,580 --> 00:23:23,110
Got it.

398
00:23:23,690 --> 00:23:24,260
Got it.

399
00:23:24,510 --> 00:23:26,490
All right, ma'am, thank you so much for your help.

400
00:23:32,440 --> 00:23:33,870
All we need to do now, man, is just...

401
00:23:36,100 --> 00:23:38,740
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, she's heading back inside.

402
00:23:39,030 --> 00:23:39,700
What for?

403
00:23:39,840 --> 00:23:40,720
I don't know.

404
00:23:44,580 --> 00:23:45,380
Oh, no.

405
00:23:46,460 --> 00:23:47,330
No, we're good.

406
00:23:48,340 --> 00:23:49,410
LINCOLN: She's out.

407
00:24:05,440 --> 00:24:05,990
Hey!

408
00:24:06,600 --> 00:24:07,730
Hey, stop it!

409
00:24:08,430 --> 00:24:09,370
Wait here.

410
00:24:17,440 --> 00:24:19,380
I actually had to slow down not to catch you.

411
00:24:19,480 --> 00:24:20,640
I think I pulled a groin.

412
00:24:23,570 --> 00:24:24,600
It's not in the bag.

413
00:24:27,800 --> 00:24:28,380
It's not here.

414
00:24:28,600 --> 00:24:29,440
How could it not be in here?

415
00:24:29,520 --> 00:24:31,490
The device, it's not here-- give me it.

416
00:24:34,160 --> 00:24:35,450
Son of a bitch.

417
00:24:40,460 --> 00:24:41,670
Twenty-Six...

418
00:24:42,530 --> 00:24:43,760
Twentyseven...

419
00:25:09,490 --> 00:25:10,160
FEMALE VOICE: Go ahead.

420
00:25:10,810 --> 00:25:15,610
Before Burrows and Scofield were allegedlly transferred to Arlington
someone posted their bail.

421
00:25:16,540 --> 00:25:17,640
I need to know who.

422
00:25:17,910 --> 00:25:21,020
I'm showing a Bruce Bennett, former aid to Governor Frank Tancredi.

423
00:25:37,850 --> 00:25:39,000
You think it fell out?

424
00:25:39,110 --> 00:25:40,250
We looked everywhere.

425
00:25:40,640 --> 00:25:42,070
You think we got the thing copied?

426
00:25:42,190 --> 00:25:46,110
Like I said, I can't read the content without downloading the device, but...

427
00:25:46,680 --> 00:25:49,970
unless this Tuxhorn's got, like, a 50,000-hour Tivo, then, yeah, I think we got it.

428
00:25:50,070 --> 00:25:51,680
Doesn't matter if we got it if we can't find it.

429
00:25:51,770 --> 00:25:52,700
Where the hell is it?

430
00:25:54,370 --> 00:25:55,830
It's still inside the house.

431
00:25:57,240 --> 00:25:58,660
That's why the maid went back inside.

432
00:25:58,780 --> 00:26:02,090
She must have found it, assumed it belonged to her boss, and then she left it behind.

433
00:26:02,270 --> 00:26:04,030
Well, then guess what, fellas, it's game over.

434
00:26:04,180 --> 00:26:06,440
You know how many months it took me to make that thing, Michael?

435
00:26:06,570 --> 00:26:08,660
What, you just think I can whip up another one in a couple seconds?

436
00:26:08,730 --> 00:26:10,140
Losing it is not the problem.

437
00:26:10,280 --> 00:26:12,410
If they find it, that's the problem.

438
00:26:13,280 --> 00:26:16,200
LINCOLN: If they find out someone was after that card, we're done.

439
00:26:16,640 --> 00:26:17,370
BELLICK: What do you mean, done?

440
00:26:17,450 --> 00:26:19,060
What does that mean?
Does that mean we're gonna go back to prison?

441
00:26:19,160 --> 00:26:20,320
Are they gonna kill us?

442
00:26:20,420 --> 00:26:21,680
- What the hell does that mean?
- All right 

443
00:26:24,310 --> 00:26:26,000
It means we go into and get it

444
00:26:33,490 --> 00:26:36,020
Maybe if we had a few days, we could figure out a way to pull this off, 

445
00:26:36,130 --> 00:26:37,920
but I gather we don't have that kind of time.

446
00:26:38,080 --> 00:26:39,090
Yeah, you gather right.

447
00:26:39,190 --> 00:26:41,090
Look, if you want us to get that device out of there, 

448
00:26:41,230 --> 00:26:43,140
you gotta throw us a bone, give us some extra help.

449
00:26:43,310 --> 00:26:46,170
What you're asking for requires involving additional people, 

450
00:26:46,290 --> 00:26:49,000
which, given the covert nature of this operation, I cannot do.

451
00:26:49,110 --> 00:26:50,230
Then you're asking for the impossible.

452
00:26:50,320 --> 00:26:52,380
No, what I'm asking for is competence, okay?

453
00:26:52,480 --> 00:26:55,240
I'm not the one who put the entire mission in the hands of a damn maid.

454
00:26:58,780 --> 00:27:02,980
Look, if the Company finds that copy of Scylla before we do, that's it, Michael, 

455
00:27:03,130 --> 00:27:03,950
that's ball game.

456
00:27:04,060 --> 00:27:07,030
They're gonna find out who was behind it, and they're going to ghost us.

457
00:27:07,130 --> 00:27:08,280
All of us.

458
00:27:09,130 --> 00:27:10,190
Are you okay?

459
00:27:11,630 --> 00:27:12,640
Yeah.

460
00:27:14,720 --> 00:27:15,680
I'm fine.

461
00:27:17,140 --> 00:27:20,310
Look, I didn't choose you to do this because I had you in custody.

462
00:27:20,430 --> 00:27:23,080
I chose you to do this because I believed you could pull it off.

463
00:27:23,640 --> 00:27:27,000
Yeah, well, a lot of people have believed in me in the last few months, Agent Self.

464
00:27:27,820 --> 00:27:29,640
Not all of them are alive today.

465
00:27:32,610 --> 00:27:34,550
Can you get me back the device or not?

466
00:27:39,970 --> 00:27:41,130
All right, this is what we got.

467
00:27:41,230 --> 00:27:43,890
The housekeeper saw the device as she was leaving the house.

468
00:27:44,010 --> 00:27:46,730
Then she disappears back inside for 15 seconds.

469
00:27:46,860 --> 00:27:48,830
So, we know, wherever it is, it's somewhere close to the door.

470
00:27:48,960 --> 00:27:51,570
So, 15 seconds, that's all we have to buy ourselves.

471
00:27:52,370 --> 00:27:55,070
Listen, I'm not sure how close we're gonna get to this house, 

472
00:27:55,180 --> 00:27:57,720
let alone inside of it, but let's say that we do.

473
00:27:57,860 --> 00:28:00,190
The alarm they got installed in this house is triggered 1.

474
00:28:00,340 --> 00:28:03,430
2 seconds after broken contact in any door or window.

475
00:28:03,550 --> 00:28:07,780
Which would immediately send the private security guards with their 47 guns rushing into the property.

476
00:28:07,930 --> 00:28:11,200
And after 30 seconds, the alarm company will dispatch vehicles to the property.

477
00:28:11,320 --> 00:28:12,990
Three to four, depending on availability.

478
00:28:13,250 --> 00:28:14,760
After confirmation of a break-in, 

479
00:28:14,890 --> 00:28:18,530
they'll dispatch additional vehicles to seal off any and all exits from the property.

480
00:28:18,650 --> 00:28:19,830
SUCRE: I don't know about this, Michael.

481
00:28:19,910 --> 00:28:22,730
It's getting pretty clear why they hired a bunch of cons to do this job.

482
00:28:22,870 --> 00:28:24,570
It's not because they wanted it off the books.

483
00:28:24,690 --> 00:28:26,170
It's because we're expendable.

484
00:28:26,290 --> 00:28:29,210
Who's gonna care if a bunch of crooks wind up dead?

485
00:28:29,400 --> 00:28:30,570
It's suicide.

486
00:28:30,740 --> 00:28:32,250
SARA: I'm gonna keep looking and see what I can find.

487
00:28:37,960 --> 00:28:39,570
That quote from The Odyssey.

488
00:28:39,910 --> 00:28:40,700
What about it?

489
00:28:41,540 --> 00:28:43,210
I can't shake that line.

490
00:28:44,470 --> 00:28:46,200
"All that avails is flight.

491
00:28:47,790 --> 00:28:49,760
" What if flight is our only option, Linc?

492
00:28:52,360 --> 00:28:55,830
What if our father-- after everything he discovered about the Company-- what...

493
00:28:57,760 --> 00:28:59,530
what if that's what he finally realized?

494
00:28:59,780 --> 00:29:03,890
You know, uh, the one thing I remember most about Dad was the back of his head.

495
00:29:04,010 --> 00:29:05,650
Always walking out the front door.

496
00:29:06,160 --> 00:29:07,770
Always running from something.

497
00:29:08,480 --> 00:29:10,220
Mom, us, himself.

498
00:29:11,730 --> 00:29:16,290
But the one thing he never ran away from was his belief that the Company needed to be taken down.

499
00:29:16,620 --> 00:29:18,380
And we got an opportunity to do that.

500
00:29:18,490 --> 00:29:20,820
Then this is our fight, not theirs.

501
00:29:21,300 --> 00:29:22,020
Man, this...

502
00:29:22,120 --> 00:29:23,650
this ain't Fox River.

503
00:29:24,430 --> 00:29:26,190
These guys chose to be here.

504
00:29:26,910 --> 00:29:28,600
Remember that.

505
00:29:29,240 --> 00:29:30,510
They got a choice.

506
00:31:11,490 --> 00:31:12,590
Almost

507
00:31:12,730 --> 00:31:13,710
Ready?

508
00:31:17,440 --> 00:31:18,340
Go.

509
00:31:48,690 --> 00:31:49,710
let's go.

510
00:31:54,710 --> 00:31:55,760
Where's it coming from?

511
00:31:55,910 --> 00:31:57,180
It's across the street.

512
00:32:02,790 --> 00:32:03,550
Come on.

513
00:32:16,940 --> 00:32:17,900
Go.

514
00:32:29,240 --> 00:32:30,670
Just something across the street.

515
00:32:31,430 --> 00:32:32,960
We got a team checking it out now.

516
00:32:33,310 --> 00:32:34,530
You can go back inside, sir.

517
00:32:46,990 --> 00:32:48,270
Must be out of town.

518
00:32:56,740 --> 00:32:58,830
BOY: Daddy, is everything okay?

519
00:33:09,060 --> 00:33:10,200
Alex...

520
00:33:11,580 --> 00:33:12,480
Thanks, Jim.

521
00:33:13,610 --> 00:33:14,830
Alex!

522
00:33:15,330 --> 00:33:16,480
Let's go.

523
00:33:48,390 --> 00:33:49,500
Go!

524
00:33:59,760 --> 00:34:00,960
Don't turn around, 

525
00:34:01,590 --> 00:34:07,150
unless you'd like to experience a great deal of pain over an even greater length of time.

526
00:34:08,220 --> 00:34:10,610
You-you know, just-just take whatever you want here.

527
00:34:10,780 --> 00:34:15,360
The only thing I want from you, Bruce, is the answer to a simple question:

528
00:34:16,000 --> 00:34:18,730
 Where are Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows?

529
00:34:18,880 --> 00:34:20,830
I only know what-what I read in the papers and...

530
00:34:20,960 --> 00:34:26,030
Three days ago, there were 105 inmates in the supermax wing of the U.S.

531
00:34:26,130 --> 00:34:31,110
penitentiary in Livingston, Texas, where the brothers were allegedly sent.

532
00:34:31,740 --> 00:34:37,480
There are still 105 inmates there, and no one has been released during that time.

533
00:34:37,890 --> 00:34:41,330
Someone is playing a shell game, Bruce.

534
00:34:41,790 --> 00:34:43,730
I'm just trying to find out who.

535
00:34:45,060 --> 00:34:47,520
I have no criminal jurisdiction over...

536
00:34:47,610 --> 00:34:49,030
I know you bailed them out.

537
00:34:50,160 --> 00:34:52,930
I know you've been in contact with Sara Tancredi.

538
00:34:53,020 --> 00:34:56,580
I swear to you, I-I have no idea where they are.

539
00:34:59,400 --> 00:35:01,010
I guess we'll see about that.

540
00:35:07,600 --> 00:35:08,810
Good luck, Teddy.

541
00:35:09,630 --> 00:35:12,190
Who needs luck when you got friends like you fellas, huh?

542
00:35:14,600 --> 00:35:17,840
Hey, you mind if I take this old newspaper of yours with me?

543
00:35:17,930 --> 00:35:18,660
No problem.

544
00:35:18,760 --> 00:35:20,060
Sorry to hear about your friend, dude.

545
00:35:21,370 --> 00:35:22,780
It's all right.

546
00:35:24,100 --> 00:35:25,780
He had a full life.

547
00:35:27,300 --> 00:35:28,030
Later, Teddy.

548
00:35:43,920 --> 00:35:45,030
There you go.

549
00:36:03,300 --> 00:36:08,640
Thirty-six, twenty-four, thirty-six.

550
00:36:28,490 --> 00:36:29,570
Huh.

551
00:36:53,160 --> 00:36:54,080
ROLAND: Did you get it?

552
00:36:54,820 --> 00:36:56,460
Let's make sure we got what we wanted.

553
00:36:59,380 --> 00:37:00,030
Linc.

554
00:37:00,480 --> 00:37:01,380
Yeah.

555
00:37:01,770 --> 00:37:03,200
Don't let that thing out of your sight.

556
00:37:03,790 --> 00:37:04,690
All right.

557
00:37:06,420 --> 00:37:07,540
We're halfway there.

558
00:37:07,760 --> 00:37:11,110
- All we got to do is that little B and E, and
- we're out of here.

559
00:37:11,200 --> 00:37:14,100
Reminds me, I need to get ahold of Self, see when we can get started.

560
00:37:14,230 --> 00:37:16,140
So what are you gonna do when all this is over?

561
00:37:19,060 --> 00:37:20,390
MICHAEL: That's a good question.

562
00:37:23,970 --> 00:37:27,130
Brother, whatever this Scylla thing is, it is a monster of a code.

563
00:37:46,540 --> 00:37:53,420
Sara, I was gonna come down here and ask if you wanted to talk some more about what happened in Panama,

564
00:37:53,470 --> 00:37:57,530
 but, um, I think I already know what you're gonna say.

565
00:37:58,190 --> 00:37:59,270
How's that?

566
00:37:59,590 --> 00:38:01,090
Because you're a little like me.

567
00:38:02,500 --> 00:38:05,880
Because you're gonna say you're fine, that you can handle it.

568
00:38:07,560 --> 00:38:10,850
So, um, I'll just leave it at this.

569
00:38:11,730 --> 00:38:12,700
I'm here.

570
00:38:14,240 --> 00:38:17,490
Whenever you want to talk, I'm here.

571
00:38:19,240 --> 00:38:20,350
Thank you.

572
00:38:26,240 --> 00:38:31,480
You know that the only thing that kept me alive when I was being held was the thought of being with you.

573
00:38:34,650 --> 00:38:37,580
But I also knew that if anything happened to me, you were gonna blame yourself, 

574
00:38:37,660 --> 00:38:40,560
and you would spend the rest of your life punishing yourself for it, and...

575
00:38:41,430 --> 00:38:44,230
I can't bear the thought of that.

576
00:38:48,510 --> 00:38:51,150
So can we make a deal right now that we're even, 

577
00:38:51,610 --> 00:38:57,700
and just wipe the slate clean and no guilt and no responsibility?

578
00:38:58,040 --> 00:39:01,340
If we're gonna be together, I don't want it to be out of a sense of obligation.

579
00:39:02,000 --> 00:39:06,800
Or-or even that we should be, because of what we've been through.

580
00:39:06,960 --> 00:39:08,080
I-I...

581
00:39:08,600 --> 00:39:10,190
I just want to start over.

582
00:39:11,680 --> 00:39:12,840
Start over.

583
00:39:14,440 --> 00:39:15,430
Okay.

584
00:39:15,720 --> 00:39:19,730
But, uh, does that mean I have to divorce my wife?

585
00:39:22,550 --> 00:39:24,610
Because you're still married to a Russian stripper.

586
00:39:24,780 --> 00:39:30,090
Well, "A": I've been a little busy, and "B": I'm pretty sure she was Czech.

587
00:39:30,190 --> 00:39:31,470
LINCOLN: Hey, Michael.

588
00:39:32,980 --> 00:39:34,070
What's wrong?

589
00:39:34,670 --> 00:39:36,340
Whatever it is, it ain't it.

590
00:39:36,450 --> 00:39:37,310
I don't understand.

591
00:39:37,430 --> 00:39:38,700
I thought you said we copied the card.

592
00:39:38,870 --> 00:39:39,710
No, we did.

593
00:39:40,020 --> 00:39:41,600
But according to the encryption code...

594
00:39:42,540 --> 00:39:43,690
Okay, how do I make this clear?

595
00:39:43,790 --> 00:39:47,790
If-If Scylla was like a pizza, all we got's a slice.

596
00:39:48,360 --> 00:39:49,770
So where's the rest of the data?

597
00:39:49,890 --> 00:39:50,530
I don't know.

598
00:39:50,630 --> 00:39:51,920
I don't know.I mean...

599
00:39:52,570 --> 00:39:54,370
I mean, I don't know how we didn't see this coming.

600
00:39:54,460 --> 00:39:56,020
I mean, it-it makes perfect sense.

601
00:39:56,100 --> 00:39:57,570
It's like the nuclear launch codes.

602
00:39:57,660 --> 00:39:59,990
You don't give all that information to just one person.

603
00:40:00,190 --> 00:40:01,250
How many do you give it to?

604
00:40:01,350 --> 00:40:03,400
Okay, that quote your father held onto-- 

605
00:40:03,510 --> 00:40:08,970
in The Odyssey, Scylla is a six-headed monster that requires a sacrifice of six soldiers in order to pass.

606
00:40:09,440 --> 00:40:13,500
So Scylla isn't one card, it's six.

607
00:40:21,590 --> 00:40:22,220
BELLICK: What does that mean?

608
00:40:22,270 --> 00:40:24,180
How we gonna find five more of these things?

609
00:40:24,240 --> 00:40:24,950
Michael!

610
00:40:25,070 --> 00:40:25,840
Michael!

611
00:40:34,500 --> 00:40:35,380
I'm busy.

612
00:40:35,800 --> 00:40:37,430
I don't care what she looks like.

613
00:40:37,710 --> 00:40:40,950
Three tablespoons of water, one of honey.

614
00:40:41,260 --> 00:40:42,320
Nothing more.

615
00:40:44,700 --> 00:40:49,650
If she knows something about anything that's going on, I'm going to find it.

616
00:40:54,840 --> 00:40:56,250
Rise and shine, bitch.

617
00:40:57,180 --> 00:40:58,340
Breakfast.

618
00:41:35,600 --> 00:41:36,510
LINCOLN: Michael?

619
00:41:39,850 --> 00:41:40,720
You all right?

620
00:41:41,470 --> 00:41:43,100
Yeah, I'm fine.

621
00:41:44,050 --> 00:41:46,620
LINCOLN: All this security makes you wonder what the Company's hiding.

622
00:41:47,830 --> 00:41:51,710
Only way to know for sure is to find those five other cards, see for ourselves.

623
00:41:52,200 --> 00:41:53,390
Think we'll have enough time?

624
00:41:54,160 --> 00:41:55,100
Yeah.

625
00:41:56,070 --> 00:41:57,270
We'll, uh...

626
00:41:58,430 --> 00:42:00,010
We'll be fine.

627
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


628
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


਍਍㤹㤹਍〰〺㨰ⰰ〵‰ⴭ‾〰〺㨰ⰲ〰਍昼湯⁴潣潬㵲⌢晦晦〰•楳敺ㄽ㸴睷⹷癴畳瑢瑩敬⹳敮㱴是湯㹴਍