You know,
someday, weeks will go by,
maybe even years, it won't
even cross our minds.
We'll come home,
and we'll talk about work.
And what we want
for dinner...
movies.
Nursery schools.
It's going to be great.
Yeah. Yeah, all we got to do
is survive.
We will.
I promise.
What happened?
Nothing. The detonator
must have failed.
Distract them.
We'll be there in five minutes.
No, we don't have
five seconds, Michael.
Then you'll have
to trigger it manually.
How much time
is that gonna give me?
Out. Now.
Alex?
Alex?!
It's wiped clean.
That's not possible.
- Really?
Well, then where is it?
Where's the data?
It was intact
when I took it.
I'll tell you what,
If it doesn't boot up
in ten seconds,
I'm gonna
splatter your skull
all over these walls.
I came to you. I want this over.
Why would I jeopardize that?
I don't believe that Michael
just let you have it.
He didn't-- he left me alone
in a room, and I took it.
And that wasn't the least bit
suspicious to you?
Maybe. I...
I don't know.
Or you're lying.
Kill the junkie.
Oh! You pathetic slug.
Sara was the only
leverage we had.
Scofield's donned
many a chapeaux,
but human fly?
I should anticipate him
scaling the building?
Move on Panama.
Proffer your nine.
Men in my employ, Bagwell...
anticipate.
They cover their bases.
They refuse to fail--
which you seem to do
with unyielding consistency.
That's got to be Sara's phone.
I should answer it.
What do you got
to lose, General?
Yello?
Who the hell is this?
Is this Fernando Sucre?
Oh, thank you, God.
Bagwell?
Yeah.
And we're on the same team,
brother, same team.
Our boys are
in a hell of a pickle.
Where's Michael?
Uh, his mother snatched
him and Tancredi.
Linc, too-- and I personally
took a nasty beat-down.
Where does she have them?
I got an idea,
but I can't say on the phone.
I'm running scared, amigo.
Okay, cool it. You know what?
Um, we got somebody
who can help us out,
but I need to get ahold
of Michael.
We should, uh, we should get
together and pool our resources.
The park on 72nd Avenue,
uh, in an hour?
Okay, I'll be there.
Excellent, perfecto.
He's got someone
who can help on his cause,
I'm certain can
draw out Scofield.
You're certain of nothing.
Yet I do have
a sit-down with Scofield's
friend in an hour.
You got no better hand, General.
Your breathing is short.
Does it hurt to inhale?
I'm fine.
- Hell, you've collapsed your lung.
No hospital.
Hospital means jail.
Come on, Michael come on!
Can you treat him?
- I don't know.
I need a better look
before I can try.
Christina?
Buried.
You are a sight
for sore eyes, my friend.
Can the reunion.
Where can I find
Michael and Lincoln?
Admittedly, they're
in dire straits.
Are you deaf?
Unlikely, amigo--  I just heard
the dime drop on your sorry ass.
And from the bench
over my left shoulder,
the gentlemen
in the Wayfarers?
Just like in Fox River,
you never thought things through.
Now, are you gonna
name the friend
who said he'd show up
and help out the brothers?
No.
You're gonna hand Sara's phone,
or I'll break your face.
Accuse me of being deaf, but you're the
one that's going blind, Puerto Rican.
The man's a Company operative
trained assassin.
What's up, Jethro?
We're a long way from Fox
River, T-Bag. Let's go.
Yeah, I got Tancredi's phone.
Paging Dr. Bender.
Do you know if he's diabetic?
On some medication
he may have missed?
I have no idea.
Any chance he's faking it?
No. His pupils are dilated.
He needs a head CT stat,
EKG and a chest X-ray.
He may have bled into his
brain or had a heart attack.
Franco.
It wasn't just Scofield
and Burrows; this is the team
that Self had at the warehouse.
Former federal agent.
Yeah, Self was into
something nasty.
Agent Self, can you hear me?
Agent Franco, we have to move him.
Where are Scofield
and Burrows?
We're going now.
His finger moved.
He can hear me.
Agent Self,
can you help us?
He's not going anywhere.
Michael,
what's the plan?
Who do we trust?
No one.
We're out of options.
Destroy Scylla.
Is that it?
Is that where we're at?
What if the General
decides to retaliate?
He will even if we
give it to him.
We can crush it, incinerate it,
throw it in the ocean.
All three sound good.
Alex?
All right.
Then it's decided.
Hello.
Hello, Michael.
You're a tough man
to get ahold of.
Kellerman!
I heard you were dead.
Those rumors
were greatly exaggerated.
No, I was, um... freed
by a group working
against the Company.
The same group
founded by your father.
I'm working with them.
Could've used
a hand, Paul.
Do you have Scylla?
What do you think?
I think you do.
Michael, there is a
UN attaché, who will be in Miami
today at 5:00
to receive Scylla from you.
Why should I trust a word
coming out of your mouth?
I assume you know that
what you have can--
and this is no exaggeration--
change the world
for the better.
All you have to do
is deliver it.
And you don't need to trust me;
just trust the people that work
at the United Nations.
The phone died.
He's not getting
any better.
- All right, come on.
Let's get him up.
I got to get some supplies.
Yeah.
Okay.
That was Kellerman.
This Alabama trailer trash
has been making good.
He hooked up with
General Krantz.
What's it to you, rughead?
Well, where is the General now?
Same place as your daddy.
Location unknown.
Do you remember that day
we were in the chow line,
Fox River,
you made that offhanded comment
to me?
I believe it had a racial bent
to it.
Yeah.
Do you remember your broken jaw?
Now, just imagine what I can do
to you right now
with something real on the line.
Such as?
We need the General's location.
What's in it for me?
If we take Scylla to the place
it's supposed to be,
there'll be an immunity list.
You could be on it.
- No.
Where I'm sitting, albeit
momentarily compromised,
you're backing the wrong horse.
Scofield cannot pull this out.
You help me get him to the
General and we are set for life!
Man, I don't have
time for this, man.
Time? It's time you backed a
winner for once, my chocolate
friend!
Ow!
Sit down!
Now where is the General?
Where... is... the General?
No word from Agent Frost
or Bagwell.
That slippery little rat.
If he's AWOL, I'll
skin him alive.
No way he got over on Frost.
He's... he's captured...
or dead.
So we're exposed here.
Is this the end?
Whimpering?
There's no shame in retreating
to regroup, sir.
That, son, is a tremendous load.
Yeah?
Lincoln Burrows' phone
pinged a cell tower downtown.
We have his location.
Then what are you doing here?
You holding up?
You're going to give
Scylla to Kellerman?
I don't know.
Do you trust him?
No.
The thought of walking free
from this
sounds pretty good right now.
I mean, that-that was the goal.
5:00, Declan Plaza.
It's right across town.
If you have to leave, Michael,
you should.
I'm not leaving
you, Linc.
You're my brother.
Not according to Christina.
Don't let her mess
with your head.
Well, maybe it's true.
I keep... I keep playing things
over in my head
from-from our childhood...
Doesn't matter what she said.
It doesn't change anything.
You're stuck with me
whether you like it or not.
The doc said
the CT scanner is free.
We got to take him now.
No, he stays till he talks.
He's worse than he was
ten minutes ago.
He won't be talking
anytime soon.
Yeah, but you can write,
can't you, Don?
So you give me
what I need,
and you'll get top-notch
care and a pension.
Or you can waste away
in front of us
until you have the brain
capacity of a peanut.
Your choice.
All right, all right,
all right, all right,
all right, come on.
Excuse me, um...
May I speak to you
for a second?
Paging Dr. Stateman.
Dr. Stateman, please.
Alex was arrested.
Federal agents.
We need to get him.
If we give Scylla to Kellerman,
Alex gets exonerated.
He's fine.
We need to get the fluid out.
It should ease the pressure
and help him breathe.
Can you hold that?
That won't last long,
but we can go.
Mind if I drive?
In two minutes, your eyeballs
are gonna pop out of your head.
Now, that's worse than death.
I can't betray.
My destiny is to be...
a respected gentleman.
Where's the General,
you son of a bitch?!
Battered and bruised.
Staring death in the face.
Surprising that you still need
more assurance that you've come
to the end of the line.
We don't have Scylla.
Michael...
your brother is dying.
It's fascinating...
watching the blood
drain from his face.
Do you suppose
that he would like to see
that happen to his girlfriend?
Sofia...
You give me Scylla or he can
sit there and watch
as Sofia's throat is slit.
The gun that killed
Naveen Banerjee.
We pulled Lincoln Burrows'
thumbprint off the stock.
We got video of you
outside the crime scene
with Burrows.
Isn't that a coincidence?
Lincoln didn't kill Banerjee.
He was set up.
By whom?
It was the Company.
The Company-- you know
what I'm talking about?
They've developed a device
that's called Scylla.
If you want to see
the light of day again
as a free man, you'll give us
Scofield and Burrows...
- You're missing what's
right in front of your face!
The brothers
didn't kill anybody.
You say you're here
'cause you want
to do the right thing?
Then listen to me.
Listen to what I'm telling you.
Scofield and Burrows.
Where are they?
Sofia...
Granted, it is
a dreadful decision.
You have me.
I don't really care
about you, Lincoln.
I just want my property.
All right.
Let's say I do know where it is.
Why should I tell you?
You're just gonna
kill us anyway.
True, you and your brother
are walking dead,
but if I get Scylla
within the next half hour,
I'll release Sofia.
And what about Sara?
We're negotiating
for Sofia right now.
I want you to let her go.
And I want a decision, Michael.
Let her go!
All right.
Don't move.
Let Sofia go.
Now.
Make the call.
Stand down.
Just let her walk.
Yes, immediately!
All right.
And this is where
we say good-bye.
Michael, no.
Kill him.
No. We leave.
Listen to her, Michael.
Kill him.
I'm just an old man
who's lost everything.
You win, Michael.
And you, Lincoln.
You win, Michael!
You both win.
Because it's all
just a game, isn't it?
When you get to be
as old as I am, Michael,
should you survive so long,
you, too, will see that's
exactly what it all is-- a game.
Kill him.
Listen to me, huh,
just listen to me.
I didn't risk everything
to come down here for revenge.
I'm here to clear my name.
Do you have Scylla?
Yes.
Then let's go.
Come on, General.
Never thought I'd be
so happy to see you.
Tell me something.
- Yeah?
Are you sure we can
trust Kellerman?
You know, the only
thing I'm sure of
is that he's our last option.
Gentlemen, we gotta leave.
Wait for me!
Michael?
Freeze! I'll shoot!
Go! Go!
Michael, go.
He's not going to make it
much longer without a hospital.
No.
Not till this is done.
Hey, Linc,
I need your phone.
Here.
Dial Kellerman's number.
Don't tell me
you're getting cold feet.
Just dial it, please.
It's voice mail.
And you'd better come through
for us in the end.
Yeah, he will.
Yeah, well...
We know him a little bit
better than you do.
Be sure to turn
the phone off.
That's how Krantz
found us before.
And somebody already has.
Yo, hey, hey, get out, get out!
Get out! Get out!
Just make the call.
Get Scofield or Burrows
or whoever they're
in business with.
Get them on the phone.
This is your last chance
before we take the deal
to Mahone.
If Mahone was talking,
you guys wouldn't be here.
What kind of man are you?
I mean, you got your woman
and your baby up north.
Don't you want
to look out for them?
to get their back?
Why the hell you gonna
give all that up
for two guys
you did time with?
Unless something went down
at Fox River that we
don't know about.
- Are you guys blind?!
Don't you see, they're trying
to do something
that's bigger than all this.
Then you're dumber
than you look.
Are you going to make
the call or not?
Last chance.
No.
Drop it!
Where do you think you're going?
Turn around...
slowly.
Drop the gun.
Do it now.
Michael, when you were eight years old...
- Save it.
I don't care.
Drop the gun.
Put Scylla
on the ground,
and I'll let you walk
out of here.
If you don't...
I'll kill you.
You can't kill
your mother, Michael.
You were never my mother.
And I'm no longer your son.
Fine.
Then pull the trigger.
Don't tempt me.
Pull the trigger,
Michael.
Do it for Lincoln.
Drop the gun!
You can't do it, can you?
Oh... dear.
Misfire.
You were born a Scofield...
but you'll die
a Burrows.
Okay?
I have to get Lincoln
to the hospital.
I'll get this to Kellerman.
It's all on you again.
Thank you.
Ooh... sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
Nice and easy.
You're coming with us.
Let's go.
- Nice and easy. Stay calm.
Sorry about all of that.
I had to make sure
you weren't followed.
Solomon Okella
from United Nations--
he's the man
to get that thing done.
Lincoln.
Sara.
Mahone, Sucre.
Exonerated-- all of them.
I'm telling you,
it's okay.
It's okay.
Something's wrong.
There's a piece missing.
What the hell are you doing?
How is someone from the UN
supposed to get us
exonerated here?
You are wasting time,
and we are all in danger.
What is going on here, Paul?
Need to know exactly
who his contacts are
in the U.S. Government.
I've been telling everybody
what a genius you are.
Don't get stupid on me now.
I'm not waiting.
He either has it or he doesn't.
Michael...
if you have it,
please give it to me,
and we can be done
with all of this finally.
And if you don't,
fine... but just tell me,
so we can hurry up
and run for our lives.
I don't want
to run anymore.
Neither do I.
I'll make the call.
You did it.
It's over.
Hands up!
Jonathan Krantz?
General Jonathan Krantz.
Put your hands
behind your back.
Sir.
Okay, we got everything
we need. We're done here.
And this is it?
There will be some follow-up
interviews, but...
this is it.
Sign it,
and you're free to go.
Can I keep the pen?
Sure.
Alex?
Pam's been located.
She's safe.
Mr. Burrows,
Sofia and LJ are
safe, as well.
Police station in Panama.
Now, last bit
of business, um,
Bagwell, T-Bag...
claims he helped find Scylla.
He was helpful
here in Miami.
He wants
exoneration, as well.
I can make that happen.
I'll leave it up to you.
"And be kind to one another,
tenderhearted,
forgiving each other, just
as God in Christ forgave you."
Ephesians 4:32.
Let's forgive each other,
Lincoln, Michael.
In God's name,
'cause there's too much pain.
There's too much hate
in our hearts.
We took a vote.
You're in luck.
Oh, lucky day.
What we voted on
was whether or not
you took a stick of gum
on the van ride back
to prison.
You rot in hell,
both of you!
I want you to know,
I'm totally going to
be a hands-on dad.
Okay.
Like, if the baby needs a bottle
in the middle of the night,
I will totally keep
your side of the bed warm
until you get back.
Thank you.
When do they start walking?
Uh... a year?
We'd better get
some baby books,
because I plan
on being the most
overinformed dad in Chicago.
No kidding.
I'm happy right now.
So am I.
Oh.
Thanks.
I love you.
I love you, too.
When do you leave?
Eight o'clock.
I'm going to miss you.
I'll be back soon.
Did LJ make any decision?
I made it for him.
I told him
to take his finals.
Next year.
Yeah.
Always next year.
All right, sweetheart.
Love you.
Mmm. Love you, too.
Get home safe.
I will.
Hi.
Daddy's going to come
back in two days, okay?
It's been a pleasure
meeting you,
Congressman
Kellerman.
And meeting you,
as well.
You fight those bastards
in Washington.
Don't let them
give you any guff.
You watch me.
I'm not gonna.
Anne, thank you
for your support.
It's all right.
Thank you.
Remember me, Paul?
I'm Danny Hale's widow.
Remember Danny?
Of course, Allison.
Danny was a true
American hero.
Okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
...the captivity
of negativity...
What's that?
It's just this book I got.
I don't ever want
to see this book again.
You hear?
Yes, sir.
Those right there.
Right. Thank you so much.
Michael, we got to go.
Here.
Oh, you're so tough.
¿Quanto cuesta? ¿Tres?
Here you go.
Muchas gracias.
Come on. Let's go
see your daddy.
Give me your hand.
Thank you
very much, sir.
You want to do a skip?
All right, I'll skip.
# Skip down! #
Then on three,
biggest jump you got.
One, two, three!
Not two! On three!
Buddy.
Ooh!
Oh, my goodness.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net