Previously on Prison Break:
The ranch is gone, Michael.
We gotta do something, and it's
not going to involve hurting anyone.
I got an idea.
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
Is your electricity out?
Those cons are in
one of these towns
and couldn't have gone further
than 64 miles in any direction.
I want everything you've
got in that perimeter.
Well, to be honest, uh...
I was expecting to
brief the president.
You report to me now.
Frankly, the biggest
issue we have to address,
are the charges
facing your daughter.
Good to meet you, sir.
Sara, do you remember that guy that
I met with you in your apartment?
I want you to stay
away from him.
- What are you talking about?
- I found out some other things too.
- Where is that?
- It's Holland.
It's beautiful.
And that's for the car.
We'll meet you right
back here in an hour.
Put your hands behind your
head and drop to your knees.
Oh, God.
Don't say a word,
you little whore
or I'm gonna cut
your throat out.
Ah! Oh, please!
You try that again,
I'll pry those vocal chords
right out of your throat.
She's coming up.
What's she doing?
She's coming up here.
Stay there. Stay there.
Mom, you home?
Stay quiet.
Mom?
It's okay. It's okay.
Back away and put
your hands up.
Just go easy.
Go nothing. She ain't the
one carrying the cards here.
Back away and put
your hands up.
I put my hand up,
I'll take her jugular with it.
I don't want anyone to do
anything stupid, okay?
Let's be civil here.
Stop. Relax. You can go.
Guy at the garden center said
Burrows was strong as a gorilla.
It was 1:00 p.m.
when they tangled it up.
The guy ID'd both of them--
Scofield, Burrows.
No doubt about it in his mind.
Of course,
given that was 1:00 p.m.,
those two could be 300
miles from here by now.
You have a half a
dozen picks, shovels
and power tools missing
from that store.
They're here and
they're digging.
Five million dollars buried somewhere
beneath the streets of Tooele.
You really believe that?
They believe that,
and that's the important thing.
They could be anywhere now.
We don't have the units
to go door-to-door.
We won't need them.
He's going to tell
us where to look.
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Sycnhro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
ww.forom.com
It's so funny:
I was just about to text you.
- Today's your lucky day.
- Is it?
Yeah, my Aunt Maxine finally
gave me her famous chocolate
chip cookie recipe and
if you're free tonight,
I'd love for you to be my guinea pig.
Uh... I can't. Not tonight.
Come on. You sound just like Daniel.
Not tonight. Not tonight.
You know what? If you don't mind,
I've actually gotta go.
Are you okay?
I mean, your cart's empty.
- I'm good. Just gotta go.
- Sara.
This is going wrong in
every possible way.
This is stupid, man.
We can not do this.
Hat's over the wall now.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
I mean we committed.
It's time to go get the hat.
We don't have a choice.
Yeah, we do. We can walk right
up out of here right now, man.
And then what?
We are already in the house.
Those women are bound.
We have already committed this crime.
We leave,
it ain't gonna change any of that.
Why couldn't there
just be a silo
in the middle of a field
with no one around?
We'll figure it out.
We can get the money another way.
Yeah, maybe I can
rob another bank.
You know what Charles
once said to me?
He said there's no such
thing as an ex-con.
Because I used to think
there was a way we could
wipe the slate clean,
make up for everything
we've done.
The hat's over the wall, Linc.
For everyone.
"Sorry" isn't going to mean
anything to you right now,
but I want to say it anyway.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
One or two hours tops
and we'll be out of here,
and you have my word,
no one will harm you.
Keep your eyes open, okay?
Nothing happens to them.
Nothing.
- The doctor is suspicious.
- She should be.
She was on the line with the
governor when you walked up.
You were listening.
Both lines are tapped.
We're not rookies.
Did her father tell
her what you know?
Not over the phone. But he knows
who you are, and so does she.
Seeing how she was supposed
to lead you to Scofield
and eventually to Burrows,
it looks like we're back to square one.
Not necessarily.
There are other people they care about.
The kid. L.J.
- In terms of the governor...
- Burrows' kid, Paul.
Focus.
Governor Tancredi's office.
Please hold.
Hold, please.
- Hey, is, is my father in?
- Just a second.
- Hey, Bruce.
- Oh, hi, Sara.
I'm trying to get a hold of Dad.
I need to reach him on his cell.
He actually just landed.
Should be home soon.
I don't know if he's going to be
in much of a mood to talk, though.
Why?
Your father got a call
from the White House.
They withdrew his nomination.
What? I talked to him two hours ago.
He didn't say anything about that.
It just happened.
According to them, his confirmation
was going to be a problem.
We had the votes, right?
- Super majority.
- Okay. So...
President Reynolds pulled
the plug on a sure thing
in order to start
over from scratch?
How often does something like
that happen in politics?
Never.
Since when did we become kidnappers?
It ain't right.
Well, we can buy a
conscience tomorrow.
Yeah, well, yeah. Closing your
eyes ain't gonna make it go away.
I'll take five minutes of
a situation I can control
over 50 years of
one I can't any day.
Hey, Mr. Hundred Dollar Bill.
Uh, what's it like being with
the African persuasion anyhow?
- You shut the hell up.
- Oh, hit me a nerve.
Why don't you get down in
that hole and dig, man?
Oh, yeah.
How about you backin' up, dark fella?
You're a long way away from home,
trailer park.
I can put you in that hole,
and nobody would ever hear you scream.
Knock it off.
We have security expert
Marc Bruni with us
who will explain how
other prisons are ensuring
that they are not victimized
by the next Fox River Eight.
Should be the Fox River Seven
now that Abruzzi's
taken his dirt nap.
God rest the man's soul,
of course.
Speaking of numbers,
we're short one.
Kid's taken a long time
to fill that gas tank up.
Leaned on him in every way
I can think of. He's, uh...
He's not talking.
Are you Catholic?
Not much good in it.
Lot of guilt.
But the one good
thing is confession.
Whatever you got eating at you,
you just...
give it up.
Feels good, I have to say.
Guess it's letting it out.
Letting another
human being hear it.
I ain't got nothin'
to say to you, man.
What if I told you something?
A secret nobody else knew.
Oscar Shales...
Guy I was chasing
a few years back.
Smart as hell. I...
kept just missing him.
It became kind of a game,
like, uh, chess.
Would've almost been fun
if it weren't for the fact
that he was killing
people all along the way.
Bodies kept stacking up,
and I started to feel that
it was because of me.
Because I couldn't do my job.
Because I wasn't smart enough.
Never did catch him,
but I did lose him.
I saw things when I would
drive at night: bodies...
nightmares to the point
that I couldn't sleep.
It... was a complete
break from reality.
That's what these
little guys are for.
To keep me in the game.
So now you know.
Now it's off my chest.
Ought to try it sometime.
Like I said before...
- I ain't gonna tell you nothin'.
- You know where those guys are.
If you're looking for a rat,
you got the wrong guy, man.
Nah, I'm just trying to
spare you some guilt.
Bagwell was free less than 24 hours
before he killed his first victim.
If you don't tell
me where he is now,
he's gonna kill again,
and that blood is gonna be on your
conscience and nobody else's.
Confession might not be
such a bad thing, huh?
He just arrived, LJ.
That's impossible.
I don't have a meeting
scheduled with my lawyer.
He's a court-appointed
public defender in Illinois.
I doubt he would come to
Arizona without calling me.
Let's go.
Yeah.
We're all set in Arizona
with the Burrows kid.
Good.
The kid's as good as gone.
What'd you say the name
of that lawyer was?
Didn't give it to me.
Gave it to the warden.
Then I want to talk
to the warden.
- Hey, you hear me?
- After.
Hello, LJ.
What do you want?
They didn't tell
you why I came here?
No.
I'm an ADA here
in Mohave County.
I'm here to serve
you with these.
- What are those?
- Your release papers.
- Hey, Matt.
- Ms. Tancredi.
- Is my dad in?
- In his study.
Hey, Dad?
Help!
I need my pill.
Please, I need my pill.
- What?
- I need my pills.
Forget it.
No, you don't understand; I need them.
They're for my baby.
They're Metformin to prevent
a miscarriage. Please.
They're in the drawer in the kitchen.
That one right there.
- How many?
- Two.
And water. Please.
You know I got to
put the gag back on.
Wait, before you do,
I just have one more question.
You seem like a really good guy.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not a good guy.
Do you really think
they'll help keep predators
like Theodore Bagwell
safely behind bars?
Picture makes me look
like a sociopath.
I'm not joking with you, trailer park.
Now, get in here and dig!
I am incapable,
thanks to all y'all.
You just remember:
my X marked the spot! You remember that.
We got a bigger issue. The kid.
How long's it been since he left?
An hour and a half, maybe.
Hour and a half to fill a tank of gas?
That ain't right.
There has been a
breaking development
in the double homicide
prosecution of Lincoln Burrows Jr.
Due to the sudden disappearance
of crucial blood and...
Hey, Linc,
I didn't know you had a boy.
...the Cook County
District Attorney's Office
had no choice but to drop all
charges against the 16-year-old.
Burrows is scheduled to be released
from the Klipton Detention Center
in Kingman, Arizona, where he's
currently being held, tomorrow morning.
Keys to the car--
where are they?
- Just hold on.
- You okay?
You can't do this. Linc.
We're five minutes
away in there.
We've been five
minutes for four hours.
Just give me some time.
Be patient.
You think I give a
damn about the money?
I'm doing what's necessary!
You're afraid to fail--
you're afraid this big plan of
yours ain't gonna work out.
You want to get caught proving you
can pull this thing off, be my guest.
LJ's out there;
I'm gonna get him.
We have come 1,500 miles
across the country.
We have made it this far.
Then I guess this is
where we part ways.
Any word of how the
interrogation's going?
Nah, the kid's
still stonewalling,
but we've got
confirmation on Patoshik;
his prints were all over
that old lady's house.
So he leaves the cash
and the jewelry.
The only thing he steals is
a ten-dollar oil painting.
What the hell's
wrong with that?
Is there something
I can help you with?
What? No.
You know, it'd be a little easier if
you use the cart for all that stuff.
I'm just, uh, I wanted to...
see if it'd all fit in the bag.
What happened to
your knee there?
Motorcycle accident.
So, uh...
you don't move around too well,
then, do you?
Not very.
- That's good.
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
You can still come with me.
No, I can...
I can do this.
- And if you can't?
- Then we still meet up
exactly where we planned.
Bolshee Booze.
- Bolshoi.
- LJ's going to be with me.
- You remember how to get there?
- How can I forget?
- Thursday night, 6:00.
It's our last shot.
If we're, uh... Um...
If we do this right,
we're gone forever.
Lot of ground to
cover in three days.
Lot of ground.
Yeah. All right.
Take care.
They'll be gunning for you.
They'll get you any
way they can, so...
Yep.
Tell LJ...
tell him I said
there'll be a surfboard
with his name on it.
Nice.
- Bolshoi Booze.
- Three days.
Keep your head down.
Ms. Tancredi...
Hi. Um...
I just wanted to let
you know that the ME--
she's finished her preliminary
examination of the body.
She found no signs
of foul play.
I know it's a shock, but we've
also spoken to the detail guard
stationed outside and he didn't
see anyone other than your father
enter or exit the mansion since
he came back from Washington.
My father is not
a suicidal man.
Look, is there any extended
family I should call?
I'm an only child.
My mother passed away.
- Could I have a moment, please?
- Yeah.
That's a hell of
a good deal, son.
We're talking no additional time
on your sentence for the escape.
You want it in writing,
I'll put it in writing.
We will put you up
at Club Fed and
you'll spend your days playing
racquetball with stockbrokers
and lawyers.
Four years from now you'll
be out on the street,
22 years old with a clean slate
and your whole
life ahead of you,
and no blood on
your hands. Okay?
There's a woman in the house.
If you guys show up...
it's just going to turn
her into a hostage.
T-Bag-- he ain't
coming out alive.
And he's going to
take her with him.
- Let me worry about that.
- Uh-uh. No, hell, no.
The only way that that
woman comes out free
is if someone shows up on
that porch that they trust.
- Being you?
- Being me.
I'll take it then.
You like it?
You like jerk...
you like jerky?
You like jerky.
What were you in for?
I don't want to talk, lady.
I'm a prisoner in my own house.
Least you could offer me
is a little conversation.
All right.
Just let me know when I hit it.
Murder?
Rape?
Kidnapping?
Sexual abuse?
- Child sexual abuse?
- Aggravated robbery.
- How long were you doing?
- Five years.
How much longer did
you have left to serve?
18 months.
Why on earth would you
break out of prison with...?
What's her name?
It doesn't matter.
So what,
she was running away with another man?
Look, maybe you should have
let her go rather instead of...
She's having my baby.
- How far along is she?
- I don't want to talk about it.
I'm two months. I just had my first
trimester sonogram on Tuesday.
- 10-5 Dispatch to all units.
- Has she shown you pictures of...?
Transporting David Apolskis
in FBI custody. Stand by.
Yo, this is going to take all day.
We need more manpower.
Standing around jabbering ain't gonna
get the dirt out of that ground.
Son of a bitch. Now what?
- We got to roll.
- Why?
They got Tweener.
It was on the radio.
Nice knowing y'all.
They say anything
about where we are?
I'm not hanging
around to find out.
Well, maybe you should.
Maybe you should.
Maybe we all should.
Let's go over this again.
None of them are armed?
With guns-- no.
Bagwell had a
screwdriver or something.
Do we really need this, man?
Yeah.
In case you decide to do something
stupid like tip them off.
You know it's out
there. Holland.
I'm going to live
in a windmill.
All we need is a raft.
I'm going to build it.
It all starts with this...
No, this stick.
Charles Westmoreland,
God bless you and your
wrinkled old sack.
It's all here.
I owe you a profound
thanks, pretty.
A couple days from now,
I'm going to be walking
down the streets of Bangkok
with a million US in my pocket.
That's about 40 million
Baht in the local currency.
Man, what the hell is up
with you and Thailand, huh?
Black market surgery,
anonymous transplant donors,
"he"s dressed like "she"s--
what's there not to like?
Are you really going to
try to replace that hand?
Body ain't takin' to this one.
- Unbelievable.
- All right, let's move.
You know,
that hand ain't gonna be white.
- What?
- The new one.
Even if you get down there,
it ain't gonna be white.
Hey, Johnny KKK over here is
going to have an Asian hand.
No mistakes.
Let's get them clean.
I need to know if
I can trust you.
- We had a deal, remember?
- Now walk.
Scott... I don't got much time,
all right.
I had to tell you something.
What you did for me that
day at the motel...
...ain't nobody in my life has
been to bat for me like that.
And I lied to you.
My name isn't Scott.
My name is Dave. Dave Apolskis.
I wanted you to know.
Because I'm gonna
be writing you.
And I sure as hell hope
that you write back.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
Contractor. We got some
electrical issues.
No. No, you can't help me.
Excuse me. Is there a problem?
Ms. Owens is not home.
Yeah, well,
I'm supposed to drive her to the club...
She already went to the club.
Yeah, um, she came out,
said she was going to the club.
She got into her car and left.
I don't know what
else to tell you.
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
He's gone.
We got to get out of here.
'Cause once he gets to the club,
he's going to find out she's not there.
Then he's going to be back.
Know what? You were right.
It does feel good to get
stuff off your chest.
I'm sorry I had to play
you like that, bro.
Yo, what's up?
Come on. It's going to be a long drive.
Stretch your legs.
All right.
Kellerman.
I thought you were going to deal
with the LJ Burrows situation.
Oh, I did.
Then why is he being released
from custody tomorrow?
In and of himself,
the kid is useless to us.
His only value is in who
comes looking for him.
More importantly, though,
Governor Tancredi...
not part of our plan.
Last time I checked, you left no
shortage of bodies in your wake.
No, I did what I
had to do to get
Caroline where she is.
Now that she's there,
let's not draw any more
attention than we have to.
You think getting to the
top is the hard part?
She's a hundred
times more visible,
has a hundred
times more enemies.
Anyone who knows anything
has got to be dealt with.
If someone is a liability,
they go.
Tancredi was becoming
a liability.
So was his daughter.
Wait. What? Sara?
Goodbye, Paul.
You walk out that door
with those guys right now,
and it's only a matter of
time before you get caught.
You realize that, don't you?
You're not just gonna be
dealing with escape charges,
but assault,
unlawful imprisonment, kidnapping...
I don't need to hear
this right now.
Oh, no, you do.
How much longer do you really think
you can stay ahead of the cops?
Look, if you turn yourself in,
I will testify at the sentencing.
I will say that you cooperated.
That can make a huge difference.
- Shut up.
- Be smart.
You have a baby on the way.
Do you want to be around for
its second birthday or its 22nd?
Shut up.
If you didn't want to
hear what I had to say,
if you didn't want to hear what
a big mistake you're making,
you would've put that
gag back on me...
Fernando!
Time to go.
You can still do the
right thing, Fernando.
Look-a-here, look-a-here.
Look-a-here.
Pocket change.
In case you want to tip the
valet when you're at the Ritz.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about,
boy. Where's Sucre?
- Right here.
- What are you doing?
Drop the bag.
No one's going anywhere.
Hey, yo.
Just so you know, man,
I'm not gonna roll on those guys.
It ain't gonna happen, so...
if that's what this is about...
We were talking about
confession earlier. And, uh...
I think I owe you an apology
because I lied to you...
...about Oscar Shales.
Smart-ass just kept pushing it,
and I...
I snapped.
Right there.
That's where I put
the bullet in him.
I don't care about
none of this.
Mistake about that is forensics
will tell the whole tale.
Powder burns.
The gun was right against his head.
Sir... I think we
should go back to...
See, that's what's good
about confession, you know,
'cause you say something,
you get it off your chest and...
it just goes out there
into the whole world.
And I'm so sorry about this, kid,
because I really hope you understand.
Yo, yo...
I got nothing against you, kid.
What are you doing, man?
What they do.
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Sycnhro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
ww.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net