Previously on Prison Break:
Let me get this straight.
The brothers come back to a city
that's 15 miles from the prison they
escaped from-- why would they do that?
Maybe it's because the president
is in Chicago to make a speech,
- and they're up to something.
- Legally speaking, this tape is useless.
- So we blackmail her.
- In exchange for what?
A presidential pardon.
Now, are we gonna keep crying about
money you've already got coming to you?
Or do you want to
make some more?
- I'm listening.
- Ever been to Mexico?
When's the meal coming around?
I'm starved.
Freshen me up when you
get a chance, darlin'.
Fernando!
Tia! Tia, ella es Maricruz.
I'll check this
bag for you, sir.
Oh, no. That's coming with me--
give it back.
Sir, I know that bag is
way over the weight limit.
Sir, your bag will be safe.
They're watching you.
But from where?
There.
President Reynolds ruined your life;
she ruined my life.
You want to take
that bitch down?
You just found your inside man,
but it's got to be right now.
Have either of these
men checked in?
Yeah. Room 10-06.
Later today,
you'll get a package in your cell.
It's gonna be from me--
I need you to use it. Okay?
Open on four!
I need a hand in here!
I need a medic in B-4!
Let me die.
No.
Shh!
Let me die.
A large crowd is gathering
along Beaumont Avenue
here in downtown Chicago,
anticipating the arrival of
President Caroline Reynolds,
who continues her speaking
tour today with an appearance
at the Grand Carlisle Hotel.
Inner Circle approaching the
south perimeter. Marker One.
Marker Two.
Marker Three.
Okay.
- I think you'd better go.
- You sure?
Yeah. Thank you for your help,
but, uh,
there's nothing more
you can do for us.
It doesn't feel right,
just leaving.
I don't think you want any part of this.
Thank you.
- It's ten minutes away, right?
- At least.
Listen, if this doesn't work,
we're gonna need a way out--
- for good.
- Well, that's on you.
Yeah. What about Derek?
- Derek Sweeney?
- Yeah.
- You think he'll be up for this?
All right.
This is your neck of the woods.
You want to meet at the park?
Uh... how's Third and Racine?
Third and Racine? Uh...
3:15, the corner. I'll be there.
If anything happens...
...I love you both.
Shh!
Key!
Go! Go!
Sit down.
When were they here,
five minutes, ten minutes?
They were never here.
No, no, no, they were here. I know
they were here. Where did they go?
- I don't know.
- No, you do know.
He decided it was for the best,
and I couldn't take this anymore.
- It's over just like that, huh?
- Yeah.
It's over like the time
you flew to New Mexico
on dead woman's ID
to meet up with him?
Or it's over like the
time that you met up
and got back together at the
train station in Evansville?
Or maybe like the day, today, when you
checked into this hotel here two
hours ago?
Which one is it like,
like that?
No plans to meet,
no phone calls?
- I'm telling you the truth.
- He's not going to call you?!
Don't lie to me.
You don't want to do that.
Excuse me. Can you tell me what
the sign means over there?
I'm just wondering.
No hablo granjero.
Hey!
Hey, hombre! ¿Que haces?
I need a phone.
Listen to me, man,
it needs to be today.
Hey, look, my family is in trouble,
all right?
There's a man out there who's
trying to hurt my family.
Your family is fine.
There's nobody after your family.
No, look at me, man.
Look, I'm not crazy, okay?
I know the rules.
I wouldn't be asking you
if it wasn't an emergency.
Please, just let
me use that phone.
Please.
Agent Lang.
Yeah, yeah,
I need to speak to Mahone, please.
Can I have him return?
Listen, this is Benjamin
Miles Franklin,
and I need to speak
to Mahone right away.
-It's Franklin for Mahone.
- I'll take it.
Mr. Franklin? This is Agent Wheeler.
I don't believe we've met before.
- I need to speak to Mahone.
- Something I can help you with?
Listen...
I want to leave a
message for him.
You tell him...
you tell him that I'll do
what he wants me to do, okay?
I just need a little bit more time.
I'll do it.
Just don't hurt them.
You hear me?
Don't hurt them.
What's up?
Excuse me.
What the-- Are you crazy, man?
What the hell are you doing here, man?
Keep your voice down.
Keep it down.
How you been?
You all right?
- It's good to see you, man.
- You, too, brother. You, too.
Look, if some of the guys knew you were
here, they might not be too cool...
Well, I ain't hanging around;
I need a favor.
- You owe me.
- I do. You know I do.
Look, it's just... Look,
it's just your situation right now.
I mean, I just had a kid,
a baby boy, and I promised Marie...
I didn't come here
to cause trouble.
I'm short on friends;
I need to hook me up.
You're the only one who can do
it without the green up front.
I'm serious about this, man.
Here. I need it.
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
- By when?
- ASAP.
Tomorrow? The next day?
Now.
All right, Linc. Come with me.
We have the tape.
Didn't see him go down.
Any press?
We got him down pretty quick,
but you never know.
- Somebody may have gotten a shot.
- Check around.
Confiscate cameras
if you need to.
Put out a statement before
rumors get started.
And get everyone
out of here. Now.
We're still waiting for the
response from Counter...
You and I both know that this situation
requires us to abandon protocol.
I don't know what you need to tell them,
but I need your men to leave.
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
Where's your brother?
- I need to see the president.
- Really?
And you think that's
a possibility?
She'll want to hear
what I have to say.
Oh, I highly doubt that.
The only person you
get to talk to...
...is me.
And the only way you're going
to live through the next hour
is if you tell me where
to find your brother.
Okay.
- He's in a safe place.
- Be more specific.
Specifically...
a place you will
never find him.
I had the honor...
to attend this country's most
prestigious military academy...
whose mission it is "To ensure
the greatness of this country,
its future leadership,
encouraging patriotism,
building a strong
world foundation
and providing the
service of men,
committed to the
values of honor,
freedom and country."
But, first and foremost,
they taught you this.
How do you say
"cherries" again?
Cereza.
Looks like you have
to get more cerezas.
Baby, I just got you 100 pistachios,
with the right amount of salt, too.
Well, it's the combination.
I need both.
Why am I a sucker for you, huh?
What? What's she saying?
That looks like T-Bag.
- What?
- Shh.
She said he was trying to
steal luggage from the airport,
but he's got $5 million.
Why would he...?
Unless he doesn't have it.
Unless he lost it there.
- Stop it, Fernando.
- What?
Do you really believe that
that money is at the airport?
Hey, forget it.
Look at what we have together.
Do you really want
to risk that?
We have everything
that we need.
- Except your cerezas.
- Right.
- I'll be right back.
- Fernando...
I'll be right back.
You got to know it's not real hard
for me to recognize a junkie.
I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm saying
you don't look so good.
- I'm fine.
- Yeah.
You mind me asking
what you're taking?
- Here. You want one?
- No, that's okay.
Here. Save it for later.
Varatril.
That's a hardcore tranquilizer, man.
You take these every day?
20 milligrams.
You must feel like you're
walking underwater.
I do.
It's very quiet down here.
That's where you started, right?
Peace and quiet.
That's not why you do it anymore,
though, is it?
Now it's the headaches, right?
Ann you probably don't sleep.
And you know you're going
to destroy yourself, right?
I haven't ruled that
out as a possibility.
I hope we hear from
your boyfriend.
There's one difference
between me and agent Mahone.
He doesn't know value
of a pair of hands...
he just keeps beating and
beating around that bush.
But if you don't give up Burrows,
I don't care.
One down, one to go.
I need to talk to
Scofield. Alone.
Madam President...
could I...
have a word?
It wouldn't be prudent for me to
leave you alone with Mr. Scofield.
My men are right outside this door.
I have a right to privacy.
Your rights aren't
my first concern.
Do I need to remind you
who you are talking to?
Step outside,
and close the door behind you.
The things you do
for your brother.
It's impressive.
I could say the same for you.
But I won't.
Bear in mind,
your opinion means little to me.
This tape.
You have it with you?
No. But I can arrange
for you to hear it.
You don't make arrangements for me,
Mr. Scofield.
I have people for that.
I'm not exactly sure
what is on this tape,
but I doubt it's of
any interest to me.
It's a recorded conversation
between you and your brother.
Well, out of millions
of conversations
that I had with my brother
during his lifetime...
I'll narrow it down for you.
It was recorded sometime
after his death.
And this
particular conversation...
you might want to
keep in the family.
And where is it?
20 different copies in
20 different locations.
I can call my brother right now.
He can play it for you.
Not on the phone.
Have him bring it here.
These are the terms.
You can hear it over the phone,
or you can hear it on the news.
It's up to you.
- I know it's why I started.
- Started what?
Using. Same reason as you.
Why, because you had to stay
up all night during residency?
Because the bass player dumped you
in front of the whole sorority?
Yeah, you and I got
a lot in common.
I've seen people die, too.
I'm assuming you
didn't make them die.
You need help.
Not what I'm looking for.
For your sake, I hope your
boyfriend calls back real soon.
¿Tia?
Maricruz?
Where the hell is everybody?
Mami.
Hey... lookie here,
good ol' Sucre.
What did you do to them?
Where are they? Maricruz!
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
keep your cap on.
They're out picking apples
for the Snuffleupagus.
- If you ever...
- Calm down!
They're going to walk back
in here any minute...
which means trouble.
Now, unless you want to see
me try out the new T-20Z
on your bella
muchacha, Mari-poon.
...I think you'd
better come with me.
Yeah?
- Lincoln Burrows?
- Caroline Reynolds.
I understand you have
something for me.
- You still there?
- Oh, I'm here.
It's good to
finally talk to you.
Wish I had the chance one of those
242 nights I spent on death row.
Please just play the tape.
It's awful, I know.
But the choice was clear. You needed
to be far away from all of this.
I am.
I'm the Isle of Terrence,
far off to sea.
Look, I'm still here for you.
Now, listen to me,
don't dwell on the negative.
Some people deserve
to dwell, Caroline.
You know I'm only
a phone call away.
And 3,000 miles.
Do you...
Do you know how
cold it is here?
We talked about this, Terrence.
You knew that you would be lonely,
but it's only temporary.
His appeals process
has started already.
This is gonna fly by
quicker than your 20s.
And soon the world will
forget all about him
and they'll forget about you, too.
I promise.
But...
it's killing me
not being able to see you,
sweet Caroline.
I want to see you, too.
But that can't happen right now.
This house is so big.
I just think of you...
lying in bed...
I know. Me, too.
Your warmth... your touch.
Was it quick when
he killed himself?
It was a lot quicker
than how my father died.
They shot him in the back.
He died in my arms.
I just want to know
what happened.
Your brother apologized.
He said he was sorry,
and then he blew his brains
out all over the wall.
It was quick.
And it was his decision.
And now it's time for
you to make yours.
Nah, nah, nah, man.
I can't do it. I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You don't get it, do you?
You can't stop this guy.
Not without your cooperation,
I can't, but if you talk to me,
if you tell me what's going on,
I can take care of you, okay?
You've got to trust me, Mr.
Franklin. I can help you.
- C-Note, right?
- Yeah. Whatever, man.
All I need you to do is tell me
exactly what Agent Mahone told you.
If you give me Mahone,
I'll give you your life back.
God's been smiling down on me,
I can tell you that.
First, I caught up to
Haywire up in Algoma.
He did a swan dive off a grain elevator
before they could put him away,
but I still get the reward.
Wait, wait, wait. He's dead?
Yep, like a gnat
on a Peterbilt.
Hope you don't take
the same route, Sucre.
Oh, hell no,
I got plenty reasons to live.
I hope a few of them
are in Fox River.
Or maybe, if you play nice,
I'll throw your Maricruz a couple bills
after I turn you in.
How much are you
getting for this?
A hundred grand.
I bet you never thought your
ass'd be worth all that.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
What if I know where you can
get five million dollars?
You heard me.
Where is it?
I could take you there,
if you didt have to take me back
to the States and turn me back in.
Where is it?
T-Bag's in town.
I made my commitment
a long time ago.
I agreed to put my
country ahead of myself,
like a mother does for a child.
And I thought that what I was doing
was noble and that I would be rewarded.
You were wrong.
Don't you see that I'm
a pawn in this, too?
The power that has taken over
this country is like a cancer,
and it will stop at nothing.
- It is out of my control.
- So is this.
- Tell me what you want from me.
- Uncuff me.
- I don't have the keys.
- You'll get them.
Second, I want you to arrange
for me to walk away, alone.
- No surveillance.
- Okay.
And finally, I want a presidential
pardon for me and my brother,
fully exonerating us
of all our crimes.
And I want it today.
I can't just hand out
pardons to anyone I choose.
- There is a process, rules.
- This is no exception.
A document will be delivered for
your approval just like any pardon.
You'll sign it and then file
it with the attorney general
who'll submit to the
presidential record.
Fine. I will sign whatever
you need me to sign.
That's very kind,
but we both know that's not enough.
What do you want from me?
I will unlock you myself,
walk you out of here.
What, you want me to
drive you to the airport?
I guess I'm not as
trusting as I used to be,
especially with paperwork.
It's so easy to lose.
No, I want you to go out
there in front of everyone
and announce our full
pardon on live TV.
You're insane.
That is not the way things are done.
This is not a vacuum--
people will ask questions.
Pardon! On stage. Now.
And how do I know that you won't
release the tape an hour later?
You don't.
You'll just have to
take my word for it.
- Well, I need more than that.
- Well, you're not going to get it.
Caroline...
it's time.
Make your choice.
Adams, I need you to
uncuff the detainee
and bring him here
to be released.
What are you doing?
I am going to make an announcement
pardoning Mr. Scofield and his brother,
and he will walk away unharmed.
Are you out of your mind?
He has brought some
indisputable evidence to light.
We could end this
all right now.
And you're gonna let them walk?
I am the commander in chief,
and you are a corporate lackey.
I am making the calls now;
you have no authority.
My men will see to it that Mr.
Scofield walks away
without the interference
of you and your pit bulls.
- You alone?
- Yeah.
- How'd you do?
- Three tickets, one cabin, one way.
Nice.
- I owe you.
- No, we're even.
These are few you.
- Nice.
- And this.
What's this?
Eddie, when he broke out,
bet me a hundred bucks
you'd be caught in a week.
I said, "No way.
Not the Linc I know."
Figured I'd split it with you.
- So this is it, huh?
- Yeah.
Good luck.
- You take care.
- You, too.
All right. You be safe.
Your neck of the woods.
- Yeah, how's Third and Racine?
- I'll be there.
I don't want to do this,
I really don't.
What are you talking about?
But you can't say that I
didn't give you a choice,
but you, you know,
you never take the easy way, you...
And I noticed that
about you, you...
I didn't expect it
to be any different,
but I have a job to do,
a job that I'm being made to do.
Pick it up, Sara.
Sara, pick it up.
Pick up the phone! Wait, wait!
Don't move.
Just, uh... don't, don't move.
Okay, I need the phone.
Give me the phone.
Stay right where
you are, please.
You don't really
want to do this.
You don't know the first
thing about what I want.
- Get my message?
- Yeah.
- I got her.
- She's on her way out.
Follow her;
she'll take you right to Scofield.
Sir... we need to talk.
In just a few minutes,
the president
is going to announce a pardon
for Burrows and Scofield.
As you're well aware,
this is quite a departure.
She's always been
willing to play ball,
but I think we need to
take some sort of action.
Sir...
I hate to disturb you, but
I'm not sure you realize the
gravity of what she's about to do.
- Michael.
- Sara, it worked.
The pardon?
She's announcing it any minute.
Oh, my God.
Oh... oh, my God.
Michael, that's amazing.
Just get here, okay?
I'm on, uh...
Highland. It's a warehouse.
It runs right down to the water.
Uh, yeah, yeah, I'm on my way.
We did it.
Yeah?
What happened to
your face, man?
If you want to take the ride...
...you got to buy the ticket.
Yeah, right.
Well, uh, Derek hooked us up with
a cabin on one of those freighters.
South America via
the Great Lakes.
We're not going to need that,
but, uh, this is appreciated.
One more time, bro.
We did it?
It's done.
We're done.
I wish I could have seen
the look on her face.
No, you don't.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Unbelievable.
- She's going to do it.
- Unbelievable.
The president is now taking the stage
here at the Grand Carlisle Hotel.
The two-hour delay
in her appearance
due to an investigation characterized
by Press Secretary Ryan Berg
as "an overzealous fan."
- You are not going to do this.
- I'm afraid I am.
There are some developments
you need to be aware of.
I have made my decision.
And I would appreciate you
not second-guessing me.
I don't think you understand.
We know your secrets, too.
And we can reveal
them just as easily.
You need to ask yourself who you
fear more, Michael Scofield or us?
You got 30 seconds.
I won't keep you.
The world is waiting.
Ten seconds.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
Nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Thank you for waiting so
patiently all afternoon.
If it were not for the support of this
great state, my home state
of Illinois...
Thank you.
I would not be here today.
Which is why I
have chosen today
to make this very
important announcement.
A situation has
recently come to light,
and I feel that I
must take action.
It is my job as president
of this great country
to make rational decisions
when I am given facts.
Decisions that are best not for me,
but for the people.
And so,
after much consideration,
I regret to inform
you that I have been diagnosed with
a highly malignant form of cancer.
And because of that reason,
I am no longer fit to serve
as your commander in chief.
In the best interest of this country,
effective immediately,
I am stepping down as
president of the United States.
If she ain't the president,
the tape's useless.
She can't pardon anyone.
We got nothing.
There's only one
thing we can do.
We got to disappear...
forever.
Subs by Travis and Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net