Kaniel Outis. He's
been working with ISIL.
You know that's not Michael.
We're gonna need you.
I can rest when I'm dead.
That's what I'm worried about.
I'm not leaving Michael.
We can't risk all of
it for just one man.
ISIL has broken through the checkpoint.
Sana'a is falling.
We work together or we both die.
You have my word.
It's Abu Ramal that Poseidon wants free.
Poseidon sent you?
Enough!
Who the hell is this guy?
- He's my brother.
- Back at the prison...
I had to deny who you
were. They were filming me,
and they can't know.
Abu Ramal has been martyred.
The entire army of ISIL
just declared war on us.
Behold the villain.
Hi.
Hey. I, uh, I ran into
town to get some coffee.
- Do you want anything?
- No. I'm good.
Thanks, honey. I'm almost done here.
I will see you at the lake
in a little while, okay?
Okay. I'll see you back at the house.
The hubby?
Uh, what did you learn from Kellerman?
There's no easy way to
deliver this news, darling.
It's a heartbreaker.
Doesn't get any better.
He's rotten all the way to the core.
You've been sleeping
with the enemy, baby.
I don't understand.
I followed them two monkeys
from Kellerman's house
right after they put a bullet in him.
Needless to say he wasn't our guy.
He did say some pretty alarming things
about your boy, Poseidon,
the world shaker.
Didn't give me enough
to put all the pieces together.
Back up, back up, back
up. What did they say?
Jacob? His words?
I couldn't get close enough
to hear much, but what I did...
what I did hear was
your name and Michael's.
Yes, they seemed pretty cozy,
- the three of them.
- Oh, my God.
It's a nasty bag of conspir...
Where are you going?!
To my son!
Stay down. Stay down.
It's another artillery strike.
But they sure as hell are used to it.
Go, go!
_
Allahu Akbar. Allahu Akbar.
Allahu Akbar.
_
ISIL just offered
ten million for our heads!
Wait. Wait. Stay here.
We got to get off these
streets or we're dead.
Ten million rial?
You give up your mother
for cash like that.
It's about what I paid
for Freddie Mercury's ashes.
Freddie Mercury now, really?
It's better than talking
about 500,000 people
looking to kill us.
Come on.
Found a place to figure out next steps.
Let's go.
This is the part you
tell me what's going on,
the whole thing.
No. Th-There's no time.
Country's about to fall.
You'll get your answers, I promise.
Right now our window is closing.
We need to...
We need to pivot to
the next contingency.
- Train station.
- Get up to the north.
Exit the country that way.
Things have changed in the four years
you've been locked
up in Ogygia, Michael.
Your plan's redundant.
ISIL control the north, roads,
checkpoints, train stations.
Even if we make it across
the city, it's suicide.
No. You're wrong. It's a shell game.
You go where they never expect you.
Wait. You came all the way
to Yemen looking for him.
You think he was lost or something?
Come on.
You want to live?
The airport's the only option.
The airport's known as the main
artery to the outside world.
It's the first thing
ISIL will shut down.
Planes were flying an
hour ago. You got a phone?
No, but he does.
Burned it up jacking
off to Queen, though.
Guilty as charged.
C-Note's organizing a passage
on the flight as we speak.
No, I'm telling you,
my plan will work.
Once... once you leave
the northern part of Sana'a...
Enough. We shouldn't even
be talking about this.
Get off me!
How are you alive?!
In Yemen?!
What happened to you, Michael?!
Now, I'm not moving another
inch until you tell me
what the hell is really going on here.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
Michael Scofield had to die.
I had to fake my death.
Go away.
It was part of the deal I made.
If I went to work for
a deep-cover operative
named Poseidon...
we would all go free.
We were free.
We were exonerated.
No. That's what we thought...
but we were wrong.
A few weeks before I married Sara...
I was approached by Poseidon.
You think I'm showing?
I'm not used to that yet.
I got to... I got to tell Michael.
Here you go. Burgers will
- be just a second.
- Hello?
Yes, this is Michael.
Poseidon told me Kellerman didn't have
the authority or jurisdiction
to exonerate our crimes.
He used that as a legal fulcrum.
Told me he could put
us all away for life
within the mandate of the law unless...
unless I went to work for him.
What the hell can they be talking about
at a time like this?
I don't know...
but big brother's hearing
things I want to hear.
We cannot stay.
We must go now.
Maybe we don't.
What the hell are you talking about?
Maybe all this running
is just delaying the inevitable.
Die alone here. Die alone at home.
God, you need a girlfriend, man.
Those voices are heading our
way. They're almost on us.
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?
A psychopath.
A frustrated policy wonk in the CIA
who felt he could do
better than his superiors.
So, he created a cell within
the CIA called 21-Void,
implementing his own
intelligence operations.
And he needed my help
breaking out people
imprisoned all over the world.
Terrorists,
political dissidents...
rogue agents...
and if I did it, you
and Sara, you'd go free.
Your record's expunged,
but... there was a rub.
I wasn't allowed to have
contact with any of you,
including my son.
Michael.
So, Michael Scofield was dead and...
over the years I assumed many names.
Kaniel Outis... the most recent.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you reach out to me?
I didn't have a choice.
Poseidon made that... very clear.
How?
At first, I said no.
I wouldn't do it.
Then within weeks, Sara
was incarcerated, beaten.
And so I gave in.
Everything I did, I did for family,
for you, for Sara,
for Mike... so none of you would
ever have to spend another day
inside a prison cell or...
or live a life on the run.
Look at us now.
They're starting to
search the buildings.
- Train station.
- Airport.
Train station.
All passengers must present a ticket.
Never gonna get to our seats.
We need to go through there.
Even the pilot can't get on the plane.
This is an airport full of planes.
- There's got to be others.
- It's no good.
People will die here today.
We need another option.
- My man, Omar.
- Omar?
That slippery brother?
Trust is a luxury right now.
He can be trusted. To a
point. He has connections on
- the western coast, across the desert.
- No.
Lincoln and Michael are
coming here. That's the plan.
They don't have a next move if we leave.
Now they're out there
somewhere, God knows where.
Your friends are too
late. Look around you.
This airport is no good to them.
We're not leaving.
What is that place?
Where the westerners went
when they made their escape.
I ran into one at the Forger's Den.
I can help.
And how do you expect
to find the foreigners
with only one eye?
They're here. ISIL are here!
Come on, come on. I have an idea.
The pilot.
Okay, follow me. Follow me!
Don't lose him. Don't lose the pilot.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
No, just stay down.
Okay. Wait here.
- What?
- I'll be back.
- Benjamin...
- I'm going alone.
Don't do it.
Halt!
What are you doing here?
- On your knees!
- Halt!
Come out. Come out.
Who are you? Papers.
- Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
- Papers.
Infidels!
The infidels are in the airport.
The killers of Ramal! I've
seen them with my own eyes.
- What?
- I want my reward.
The ten million rial. I will be rich.
- Take us to them.
- Not until you promise
I will get my ten million rial.
If you speak the truth,
you'll have the money.
You kick a lot of ass for a good Muslim.
You can take the man out of the streets,
but you can't take
the streets of the man.
Why do you help me? Who are you?
I'm a man, just like you,
trying to get out of this madness,
but we're not gonna get
out through those gates.
The only way out now
is up, brother.
The 747 is done.
It's been secured by the rebels.
I'm not talking about Yemenia Air.
I have my eyes
on a different set of wings.
- Mom?
- Hey.
Sara!
You scared us.
- Sorry.
- Is everything all right?
Yeah, no, It's fine. I
just... it's been a crazy day,
made more so by the fact that
I forgot Mike's Spanish lesson.
- Spanish?
- Yeah.
- That's not today.
- We're gonna talk about it in the car, okay?
Are you sure? Is everything okay?
Really. Yes. We're fine. Thank you.
Well, let me get Mike's bag.
No, no, don't worry about it.
I'll get it tomorrow.
I want you to get in the car
and no matter what...
- You don't get out, okay?
- Hey, hey, hey! Where you going so fast?
Get in.
Thank you.
How was that department
meeting yesterday?
You usually meet with killers?
Sara. Sara. Please, please, please.
I can explain, okay? Just listen to me.
I was sick with worry.
I needed to protect you,
to-to protect our family,
so I picked up your phone from the shop
and I took it to Andrew Nelson,
my buddy in the computer
sciences department.
He did a deep dive,
some kind of data
archaeology, and he did it.
He tracked those bastards down.
Got their cell information.
So... so I called them,
thinking I could-I could maybe
- make a-make a deal with them.
- You called them.
Sara?
Sara, please, listen to me.
Sara, this was for you.
You're gonna want to get
out of the way right now.
Sara. Sara!
This is it.
Our ticket out of the country.
I'm telling you, Michael,
this is a bad idea.
ISIL are everywhere.
No, I can do this.
You really paid the
equivalent of ten million rial
for some dude's ashes?
Not just any ashes, man.
Freddie Mercury's ashes.
I would've paid twice that.
Come on.
Keep your head down.
I think it's time we get
sane and head to the airport.
No, no, no.
This is better. They
control the station.
They'll never think to
look for us here now.
They're repurposing
those trains for cargo,
not passengers.
Once we're on, it's...
it's a straight shot to the north.
They won't check the cars again.
That's what you see
when you see the train?
I see a bunch of dudes with AK-47s
who don't look a thing
like us. You really believe
we can survive 300 miles on a train
through ISIL territory?
Now that's suicide.
- It does seem risky.
- No kidding.
No, no.
We get in that line of cargo
carriers. Keep our heads down.
Once we're on the train,
lay low the rest of the trip.
Besides, we don't
need to look like them.
Tell the believing
men to lower their gaze
and be modest.
Come on.
From the Koran.
All the roads are blocked.
So you'll have to find a
different way to the border.
By train!
Heather, what now?
What now?
I mean, it was all a lie.
Wasn't it? Everything.
Our whole life, our whole marriage.
He was standing as close
as you were to me right now,
and he was chatting with
the woman who shot him.
You're saying he planned
to get himself shot
like it was some sort
of, uh, sick performance?
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, I...
- Yes. Yes, it was.
- But he almost died.
So, the plan was to wing him, right?
To just put him above suspicion,
but the shot went wide.
He gets hit.
- He knows that he's married to a doctor.
- Sara, Sara, stop. Stop.
You haven't slept in three days, right?
You're upset about the home invasion
and you're tying yourself up in knots
because the love of your life,
the father of your baby, might be alive.
And I can't get through to Lincoln.
But I saw that video.
It's him.
- Okay, and I...
- That's Michael.
And I believe you. I do.
And that matters.
That's all that matters.
No, I know.
But Jacob is a good man.
He's your husband.
- Yeah.
- And he helped you start a new life.
Together.
And that's him.
- I have to answer it.
- No. No.
- No, you don't.
- Leave a message and we'll get back.
Heather, Heather? Is Sara there?
Please, I-I need to speak with her.
Look, there's been a
huge misunderstanding
and I can explain everything.
Will you just... Will you tell her that?
And to call me?
He's tracking me.
Oh, Sara, honey. I'm your best friend.
Of-of course he's
gonna call here first.
It doesn't make him Deep Throat.
Listen,
let's just see if there's
a simpler explanation.
Hmm?
Okay.
What was the name of that
computer tech that he mentioned?
Uh... Andrew.
Nelson. Andrew Nelson.
Okay, well, I have an old
friend in that department.
We can find out
if Jacob's full of it in one call.
Okay.
_
Get on the other side of that train!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Come on, let's go.
What do you want?
Look at the picture I just sent you.
I can see the murderers now.
Where?
Not so fast.
Bring your weapons, I will stay on them.
And I call the shots now.
We checked. There's enough
fuel to get us out of Yemen.
Question is, can you
fly an old bird like this?
We'll find out.
There's another station,
30 miles outside Sana'a.
We can find a way there, hop a train.
They won't anticipate
us coming that way.
Doubling down on a bad bet.
Just like you did
seven years back with the CIA.
Look around you.
Your plans affect people,
you don't even see it.
I don't blame you for resenting me.
You're damn right I resent you.
I see it, Linc. I see it.
Every second of every day,
the people, the collateral damage,
the lives I've... affected.
But I can't start thinking about that.
Because if I do,
then it all falls apart
and none of us get to go home.
I have to stay focused,
be the man with the plan.
Just like Fox River.
Remember?
We got wheels.
Good work.
The airport's the only play.
The airport is five miles away.
The border is hundreds.
Look,
the airport might be the right choice,
but I trust my instincts.
They've gotten us this far.
And my gut says
we can still make it out through
the north. Choice is yours.
Look, man,
I agree with you, even if
I don't know you from Adam.
But...
got to go with the horse
that got you here, you know? So...
he's my horse.
Craziest horse I've ever met.
But got us this far.
Crazy only works
if it doesn't get you killed.
_
Andrew?
Uh, Professor Hayden
told us to speak with you?
Oh, yeah. Uh, yeah, right.
Sorry.
Uh, hi, Andrew.
I'm Sara Scofield.
Thanks for taking the time.
By any chance,
did my husband Jacob Ness ask
you to work on my cell phone?
Yeah, he did, uh, yesterday.
What did he, uh...
What did he ask you to do?
Uh, he said he was looking to
find the contact information
for the people who
were stalking his wife.
So I did a data dive and
gave him what I could find.
How?
They hacked your phone
and lifted the data,
but in the process, left a
very slight electronic signature
that I was able to track back to them.
Wait, who are "they"?
Don't know. It was a dummy IP address,
but the cell and location were correct.
They couldn't hide that from me.
The man himself.
Hello.
Sara, listen, I know you're upset,
but I need you to come to the
Whitney Heights police station,
right now.
Please.
So, now we got some time to talk.
Um...
Well, your name's Michael.
Cool.
You have a brother.
What else don't I know?
Serious, I need to know.
I've been traveling so fast,
for so long, I didn't even
stop to think who you really are
or what we're real doing here.
I don't even know why
you dragged me into all this, you know?
You got to forget the
past, Whip, the details.
None of that matters now.
What have my actions
been all these years?
Who's been taking care of you
through everything, huh?
Me. Right?
Right?
Yeah.
Nothing changes.
You're still my whip hand...
Whip hand, yeah, I
know, I'm your whip hand.
It's... it's not good
enough this time, man.
Can you just give it to me straight?
You know, I'm a big
boy, I can handle it.
There's a reason you're my whip hand.
A reason that's gonna change your life.
There's a light at the
end of the tunnel for you.
What the hell was that?
Oh, son of a bitch.
We got to go.
Let's go!
- There's no way out.
- Back of the hospital's
been shelled to rubble. It's blocked.
Upstairs is blocked, too.
We're gonna go downstairs.
Look for a way out.
You do the same.
Thanks.
What's going on?
Sara, just...
just come with us.
You'll see. Please.
Hello, ma'am. Um, Sara Scofield?
Yes, sir.
Thanks for coming in,
I'm Detective Kennan.
We'd like you to point out
who broke into your home.
And...
the one who shot your husband.
It's three and four.
The man and the woman was the shooter.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
There's got to be a way out.
Something... something that
connects to the surface.
Going down's not gonna work, Michael.
We need to set up an ambush and fight.
Yeah, well, fighting is
your default setting.
It's not always about fists.
I'm telling you, there's no way out.
Then find something
to fight with, you idiot.
I don't think it's that kind of a party,
but I like your style.
What are you going to do with that?
I don't know.
Beats a fist.
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪ My friends ♪
♪ And we'll keep on fighting... ♪
Rubbing alcohol?
What the hell are you doing?
♪ Till the end ♪
You'll go blind, you idiot.
It's only 95% alcohol.
I'll only go 95% blind.
♪ ...the champions ♪
♪ No time for losers ♪
♪ 'Cause we... ♪
There. There's an air shaft.
Well, it's about fists now.
♪ We are the champions... ♪
Michael?
No. It's them.
My first lover was much older than me.
He was my friend's father.
Massi was his name.
It was the greatest of scandals
that we kept to ourselves.
But his wife discovered us
and told her brothers.
Massi was taken into the desert...
and buried.
Alive.
They brought his eyes to me in a rag.
I need you to use that on me.
End my suffering.
What, this?
Ja's right. All this running is pointless.
Do you know what they
will do to me here,
away from seeing eyes?
I can't.
I won't let that happen.
Do you understand?
Listen. Sid.
I'm not giving up.
And queer or no, you're not, either.
They're in the wrong.
Not you.
What are you gonna do with that?
♪ I've paid my dues ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ I've served my sentence ♪
♪ But committed no crime... ♪
Michael, come on.
I'm sorry, Linc.
I should have come to you.
I should've asked for your help
when Poseidon offered
me the deal. I blew it.
At the time, I thought,
if I dealt with it myself,
the pain would only be mine.
But instead I opened this Pandora's Box.
I wanted to make it better,
but I only made it worse
for everyone.
And somewhere in there...
I became a ghost.
I made a lot of mistakes.
A lot of foolish, imperfect choices,
but every one of them...
every one of them I made for love.
I know. I know.
Michael,
you're the smartest
person I've ever known,
but you can't carry the
load on your shoulders alone.
You need to share the burden.
Yes.
That's family.
That's what family's for.
Sara, I don't know
what you thought, but...
I'm just a husband who
was worried about his wife.
And yeah, I-I should have told
you what I was doing, but...
Look, I felt like... like
everything was spiraling
out of control and I had to do
whatever I could to protect you.
So you thought you'd
contact two hired killers?
I was trying to play the white knight.
Not very well.
And it was insanity.
I was scared to death.
A-A blubbering idiot,
but I thought they would
respond to money, you know?
Pay them whatever it
took to make them go away.
More than they were already making:
$50,000.
Look, I, uh...
I had a tracker in it, Sara.
This little thing, but
they didn't touch it.
I contacted the police before the meet,
but we nailed them anyhow.
We nailed them.
Jacob.
I am so sorry I put you through this.
Let's do this.
A wrench and a pipe against AKs.
It'll be fun.
I've always wanted a
crack at these bastards.
♪ I paid my dues ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ I've served my sentence ♪
Come back.
♪ But committed no crime ♪
♪ And bad mistakes ♪
Get over here...
♪ I've made a few ♪
You're gonna get yourself killed!
♪ I've had my share ♪
♪ Of sand kicked in my face ♪
♪ But I've come through ♪
♪ And I go on and on and on ♪
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪ My friends ♪
♪ We are the champions... ♪
I love you, you crazy
Japanese son of a bitch!
It's Korean, champ.
Whatever. I still love you.
ISIL are like roaches.
More will be here soon.
What do we do now?
I need to take a break
from making decisions.
Linc, airport?
Airport.
Hey.
I got someone I want you to talk to.
Oh, man!
Now that's a voice I never
thought I'd hear again.
Man, you got some
explaining to do, brother,
- risen from the dead and all.
- Soon.
Where can we meet you?
Uh, hangar two. Right
off the main runway.
But you better hurry your ass up.
Hangar two?
We could be there in 20 minutes.
We can be there in 20 minutes.
I don't know if we have that long.
Wait for us. We'll be there.
We got to move.
Sid...
Sid!
I heard your call, infidel.
Wings will not carry you to safety.
One call, and my brothers
will find your friends at the airport.
_
- Sid!
Son of a bitch.
No, no, no, no, no.
Talk to me, Sid. Stay with us.
Stay with us.
Sid...
Sid.
He's gone.
Don't waste yourself on him.
You'll beat him by surviving.
You will die, you hear me?
You will all die!
Oh, my...
They're moving
more trucks into position.
- Yeah.
- We can't wait.
There won't be enough runway
to take off. We must go now.
I owe Lincoln my
life. He deserves better.
But with so many souls in our hands,
do we really have a choice?
Listen, we wait five more minutes.
Okay?
And then we take care
of the souls that we can.
Understand?
What the hell are you doing?
The hell are you doing?
Listen, we are not leaving my friends!
Shut it down. Shut it down!
You would condemn us all to death.
If you stop me, no one gets out.
Your friends can still make
it to safety. We will not.
Yeah?
C-Note? You got to
get out of here, man.
Hey, no, no, no, no. W-We can
do this thing, man. We can do it.
No! Go now! Otherwise,
you and the kids are dead!
We'll work something out.
We've been through worse.
Linc, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, brother.
Lincoln? Find Omar. He...
What?
I can't hear you. What?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
www.tvsubtitles.net