Previously on Prison Break:
I had a deal with the General.
You couldn't just
let me handle this?
If by handle, you mean
give Scylla back to the General,
then no.
I should warn you I'm
going to do everything
in my power to stop you.
I want my life back.
Linc, Mom is alive.
What?
I guess I'll see you in Miami.
If I give Scylla
back to the General,
he leaves me
and Michael alone,
and I get to spend time
with my son in peace.
What if General Krantz were
no longer in the picture?
What's going on?
- Good-bye, Jonathan.
Where are you, Christina?
I don't like your
tone, Jonathan.
Excuse me,
but it's been a while
since anyone's tried to kill me.
The General should know by now
not to mess with us.
The General didn't send me.
Christina is going
to change the Company.
She said after two days
she would make the change?
- Yeah.
Look at the date on that
laminate-- two days away.
I need to talk to her.
Lincoln's back at the plaza.
I told him to stay away.
We have a clean shot.
Take it.
Roger that.
Stevenson rooftop, 12 o'clock.
Where's Christina?!
Where's Christina?
Somebody call the police!
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
- Stay in the car.
Where is she?
Where is she?!
We got his phone;
let's get. We got to go.
We got to go.
- Let's go.
She only uses the place
in the winter, so...
we should be fine
for a while here.
(sighing
And that's Deb.
Were you guys in college
together, too?
Uh, no,
just medical school.
She's got a practice...
...in New York
and she comes down here
once a year
to teach a seminar.
God, good for her.
Nice family photos.
Sand, sun,
cheesy matching outfits.
We could have that
if we wanted... someday.
Stuart, take a seat.
Scylla is in Miami.
Our people are combing
the city as we speak.
Yes, I've heard.
Someone's attempting
a hostile takeover.
Whoever has Scylla
is trying to turn
the cardholders against me.
Oren tried to kill me yesterday.
Jonathan...
We're dumping
your cell phone.
We've already found
several phone calls
between you
and an unknown party.
Stuart... who has Scylla?
I don't know.
Think, buddy.
Think.
I swear I don't
know anything.
This can be
as painless
as you want it to be.
Who has Scylla?
You have gone
around the bend on this.
I haven't even started yet.
Come on, Linc, this guy
wasn't trying to hurt you.
He just didn't
like your tattoo.
You're a funny guy, Self.
- There's a lot of calls
on the sniper's cell
from a blocked number.
We'll need the Company
to help identify it.
What if it's your
mom's cell phone, Linc,
and we have to
pay a visit?
You got the gumption?
Yeah.
Lincoln, I don't like having
to initiate these calls.
Well, don't.
We'll call you when we get it.
Who has Scylla?
We don't know,
but we tangled
with a sniper.
Whom you're interrogating
right now, right?
He's dead.
Lincoln,
the point of this action
is not to kill as many of them
as you can!
Your methods make me question
whether you are capable
of playing
on a field of this size.
We'll get Scylla.
I want answers today.
Aren't you leaving
something out,
something a tad critical,
like it's your mom
who has Scylla, hmm?
Don't think too much.
- Let's talk about that.
Let's talk about thinking
too much, okay?
Are you stonewalling
the General 'cause it's good
for the team here,
or are you protecting the woman
who popped you out
lo these many years ago, huh?
If Krantz didn't put
you here, I'd kill you.
All right,
all right!
There's my answer.
- If we tell Krantz
that Christina has it, he may
know things that'll help us
or he may determine
that we're no longer useful.
Everybody
understand that?
We're here to get Scylla,
we need Scylla,
and the way to do that
is to stick to the plan
and to keep our mouths shut.
Hey, look at this.
Yesterday he found
us on Interstate 10,
near Route 4 in Arizona.
And "MS" are
your initials.
Yeah,
but the rest of this
could mean anything.
I'll do a search on Rockwell
and we'll figure it out.
Assuming Lincoln hasn't already.
He's been here three days
and he's got access
to Company resources.
And once he puts
his mind to something,
that's it,
even if he figures
out he's wrong.
Well, and from
what I've gathered,
he doesn't think he is wrong,
so...
If I'm MS, then who's VS?
Nomaashkaar, kaam...
No... Nomaashkaar, kaam.
Bengali has
14 different vowels.
It's a bitch
to pronounce.
Lincoln got away.
Have you ever seen a picture
of a supernova?
I have.
They're quite beautiful,
aren't they?
They're very rare;
they only occur
about once every 50 years.
We're a day away
from a kind of supernova.
A moment so powerful
it'll eclipse everything.
And nobody's going
to stop me.
No?
They haven't got it yet.
Well, I've sent it twice
already. Either they...
They got it.
They got it. Okay.
We need you to trace
who called the sniper's cell
and tell us
where he is in Miami.
Well, when?
No.
Hell, no. We need
it now. We...
Hour earliest.
What do you
mean, hour?
We get him, we get to Christina.
Damn well almost got our asses
handed to us getting these.
You want to know
what your mama's up to--
let's start there.
These things are
for tomorrow.
I want Scylla today!
Oh, sorry there, Sink.
There I go thinking again.
My bad.
Why?
I'm getting you out of here.
What is it?
- It's Michael.
He's in Miami, wants to meet.
When?
Never.
I warned him not to come.
Hello, Alex.
Glad to see
you're both in one piece.
Where's my brother?
He's not coming.
So you're working
with him now?
You work for the Company?
Sure. Fine.
Why are you here?
Partly to warn you.
I could have
saved you the trip.
'Cause we're seeing
this thing through.
What do you know?
What do you think
you've walked into?
You tell me.
Your mother.
She has Scylla.
Whoever's going
to get it
has to go through her.
I need to talk to my brother.
He's not coming.
He's a little
too busy trying
to stay alive because your...
because your mother tried
to kill him.
And if you stay here
with some half-baked plan,
she's gonna try
and kill you.
What are you doing here, Alex?
I'm trying to get
some information,
anything that can help.
You need to trust me.
- So that you
can run back
to the General with it?
Everybody can get
what they want here.
We don't have to chose between
saving our families and
taking down the Company.
We can do both.
How?
I'll know when we get there.
That's why I'm
asking you, please,
trust me.
Now, do you
know anything?
Do you have
anything?
The only thing
I can tell you is
that we're gonna burn
the Company down to the ground,
and that's with
or without you, Alex.
I'm sorry, Michael.
About your mother.
So, the guy
who was posing as a cop
yesterday must have been
working for my mother.
Yeah. Yeah,
I think you're right.
And if he was
following
her instructions, that means...
Guess that means
she wanted the two of us
transported somewhere.
At least
she didn't want us killed.
I guess I should be grateful.
Does this change anything?
No.
The fact that
she thrived
within the Company,
at the expense of...
everyone else...
...mes me want
to take them down even more.
Okay.
Rockwell Avenue, South Miami.
Let's go.
All right, the SIM card
information the Company gave us
said this guy should be
a couple of blocks over.
This better be the guy who
ordered the hit on you, Linc,
not some pizza delivery boy.
- Why don't you just shut up?
All right, listen,
he's stopping.
Lincoln,
you're gonna make a right
about a quarter of mile up.
What's the location?
I do. Whose seal is that?
India. This is the embassy.
All right, there he is.
And look who he's with.
She's got Scylla.
We need to get in there.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, if she's going in,
she's gonna come back out.
And when she does,
we take our shot.
One thing I learned
at Fox River-- just 'cause
something goes in, don't mean
it always comes back out.
You're right.
Hark, what was that?
One more time?
Look, she's got
that thing on her.
We need to move now.
We need to create a distraction.
Ready to go, T-Bag?
No, no, no, no.
Well, what do you want me to say?
Run your mouth.
You know how
to do that.
Look, when we get in,
we'll let you know.
Until then,
you keep 'em busy.
Oh, come on, Donnie.
I don't know
about this.
Excuse me?
Excuse me. I'd like a meeting
with your president, sir.
Uh... could you notify him
I'm here? Thank you.
The president doesn't live
in America, sir.
She lives in Kashmir.
She? Oh, well.
That explains a lot, don't it? Listen,
Haji, I got no beefs
with you, okay?
It's just, there comes a point
when a thinking man
has to take a stand.
You know who else
thinks? Elephants.
That's right. Elephants.
You know, they have
the largest brain
in the whole animal kingdom?
Did you know what?
Come on, Bagwell.
Sir...
You folks have a history
of mistreating
these mighty creatures,
and up till now, no one's
been lifting a finger.
Up till now.
This is private property, sir.
I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Well, I'm not
going anywhere.
Ha!
- Unlock those now!
This is station four.
I have a code 11.
Bring it!
Security camera's looking good.
Let him go.
Let's move.
Sir? Sir? America's on
the other end of that sidewalk.
You're on international soil.
For your sake, I hope
you brought the keys for that.
I have no-no gripes
with you at all, okay?
I've been calling
my congressman.
I've been writing
United Nations.
I don't care.
Did you know that elephants eat
over 500 pounds
of food per day?!
And their dung--
it can be... it
can be processed
into parchment.
You're about to be
in a big heap on that, sir.
Elephant!
- Front gate now.
Let's go.
All right, let's go.
I'm gonna text Bagwell
and let him know we're in.
All right. After 9/11,
DHS implemented some new
protocol regarding...
- Just hurry up.
It's an abomination.
That's what it is.
Why, the elephants,
next to the chimps,
have the closest DNA sequence
as us human beings.
Sir, I don't think that's true.
Sorry to inconvenience
you guys.
Your ride's here, pal.
Take him.
Hey! Hey!
Boys! Boys!
This is just
a misunderstanding.
They're going to
take you down
to visit your
buddies at the zoo.
Bagwell's in trouble.
- Are we made?
We're not waiting around
to find out. Let's go.
We got about ten seconds
before we go live all over
this place. Come on.
Okay, here we go. Let's go.
Looks good over here.
Clear here.
We got to hurry.
Have you ever seen
the Taj Mahal?
Only in photographs.
You?
Several times.
It was built by the Shah Jahan
for his favorite wife.
I remember telling that
to my ex-husband.
Do you know what his reply was?
Nomahkaar,
kaamon aachen?
That's very sweet,
Christina.
I'm fine, thank you.
Please.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry for all
the extra security,
but as I'm sure
you realize,
there's a lot of people
who would like
to get their hands on this.
Mm.
This is an overview of
the solar cell prototype.
That's just the beginning
of what's on here.
A desalination technique
that can yield
potable water
within seconds.
Hmm.
Bioengineered crops
that will subsist
in the harshest of climates.
Revolutionary vaccines.
Well, you know, that there's
a rumor floating about
that this belongs
to General Krantz.
That eight-carat
purple diamond
your lovely wife wears
on her hand.
Did you worry out
which South African country
it was taken from?
The profit margin would
be split fifty-fifty.
Your country would handle the
manufacturing and distribution.
I would act as your
silent partner.
Please.
Have a seat.
Last resort. We clear?
No, he's not clear.
We fire off a shot in here,
not getting out.
Are we clear?
We're clear.
I sense there's something
that you're not telling me.
All you have to do
is show up at the Progressive
Energies conference tomorrow,
go up on the dais,
and present this
technology as your own.
So, I'm the one
who looks like the fool
if this venture fails.
The leading minds
of this world
will be at that conference
tomorrow,
working on
the crisis
that we are facing
with our planet.
You will have
the solution.
You will be a visionary.
Dr. Vincent Sandinsky
has done extensive research
on the bargain theory.
Says that proof of its
practical application
is pretty shaky.
He's giving a lecture tomorrow
at the conference
and I'd like to make sure
that his findings
don't debunk the foundation
of our project
before we even get
off the ground.
Naveen,
the technology that
I am offering you
will catapult
your country
50 years ahead of its time.
Naturally,
a few other countries have
expressed some interest.
I'm sure that
they would be happy
to sell you this information
at three times the
price in a few years.
This is all very sudden.
Well, as I
said, I only
acquired this recently.
But I assure you,
it is going to sell.
I came to you first
out of respect to your father.
I will just say
one more thing...
Mm-hmm.
...then I will let you
do what you like.
What do you think your father
would have done with this offer?
I need a minute.
And don't worry about Sandinsky.
He won't be a problem.
This is 48 Rockwell.
Uh,
we need B23.
Row D.
Row B.
B23.
This is it.
Fernando was a great influence
on you, huh?
And vice versa.
Here we go.
Car keys.
So, there's
no itinerary,
but we do have a map to
the Everglade Memorial Airport.
And we have a gun.
I've been thinking about this.
"V" and "S"
are someone's initials.
1630 is 4:30 p.m. military time.
What if our guy wasn't
flying out,
but someone named VS
was flying in.
I found one of our guys.
Good. He'll take us to Christine.
Now where are you?
- Second floor.
Near the atrium.
Don't move!
Freeze!
23, I have Lincoln Burrows
and two male suspects
in custody.
We need to clear out.
Excuse me?
Lincoln's in the building.
I need close
this deal.
Preferably without looking
like an amateur.
Handle it.
Get in there.
Move!
Get on your knees,
put your hands
on your head.
Get down.
318.
Understood.
Move an inch
and I won't hesitate
to kill any of you.
I think we've come
to a decision.
You honor your side
of the agreement
and I will do the unveiling
at the conference tomorrow.
That's great news, Naveen.
Great news.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Is there another way
out of here?
Huh?
He just said don't go
near the door.
This is an embassy.
Christina can't risk
an incident,
just like we couldn't.
Nobody's going to kill us.
Let's go.
I don't know how
the hell they found us.
All I care about
is Sandinsky.
Is Morris on
his way?
We haven't heard
from him yet.
I'll check his status.
Here, give me that.
Who are you gentlemen with?
Christina.
Here.
She dropped this.
We're about a mile away.
Is that you?
I think it's coming from
inside the briefcase.
Private caller.
Can they track us on this thing?
Put it on speakerphone.
Hello?
Michael?
Was that your mom?
Oh, Michael, I'm so sorry.
I don't even know what to say.
There's nothing to say.
Nothing at all.
What the hell
happened to you?
Where's Scylla, huh?
They left before
we could get it.
I got the ass kicking
of a lifetime
and you come back empty-handed?
We got this.
A Post-it note?!
That's what you got?
How about some Elmer's Glue?
Did you get any
of that?
Would you calm down.
This is important to us.
If we had just told
the General...
just told the General...
One more time.
Hey, if this guy's
important to Christina,
he's important to us.
Hey, let's call the Company,
get a read on him.
I'll do it.
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
I'll be right out.
Whoever VS is,
their plane gets in in
less than 30 minutes.
We need to g our hands
on that flight log.
Sure.
Hi.
Um, sorry,
I notice you have
a sign up there that says
I can learn to fly here.
Do you have a brochure
I can take a look at?
Let me call you back.
Sure, I should have one
around her somewhere.
Thank you.
There you go.
Okay.
"Learn how to fly."
This is perfect!
Michael.
There was an exit
by the bathrooms.
I need 30 seconds.
They will kill us
if they find us.
Vincent Sandinsky.
VS. N727MG.
Let's go.
Got it.
Vincent Sandinsky's
on a plane right now.
He's heading into
Everglade Memorial Airport.
We got 15 minutes
to get to Fort Lauderdale.
With traffic, there's no
way we're going to make it.
Then stay.
Excuse me, can I help you?
Funny you should ask.
I need you to call up
to the tower
with a message for N727MG.
N727MG.
This is Everglade Memorial
tower.
We just got word
from another craft
that your port side turbine's
trailing black.
Tower, I'm clear across
the board here.
Am I still good for landing?
Now tell them he
needs to land
at the north end of the tarmac
and follow emergency
protocol.
But that'll...
Tell them.
Do you copy?
Tower, this is operations.
Have November-Seven-
Two-Seven-Michael-Golf approach
from the southwest.
We're not gonna
take any chances.
We're gonna send
a crew out to them.
Have the passengers evac
as soon as they hit the ground.
Roger that.
Now call down to security.
Tell them Dr. Sara Tancredi
needs to be let on the tarmac.
One of your passengers has had
a heart attack.
He needs immediate assistance.
Security, this is operations.
Okay.
One more mine,
and I'll be out
of your hair.
Hey.
You could be getting
in big trouble
for this, guy.
You could go to prison.
Which one?
Something's going on here.
I'm not sure what
the problem is.
Vincent Sandinsky?
Yes?
Hi. Dr. Tancredi.
Sir, I need you to come with me.
- Is there something wrong?
Uh, we have some concerns
about some health exposure
you may have experienced
during the flight.
I'm sorry, I don't...
Let's go.
Michael Scofield,
Vincent Sandinsky.
Get in the car.
Why...
- Back seat.
Get in!
Please...
don't hurt me.
I won't.
But they will.
You can take
everything I have.
Just... please let me go.
Do you know
who Christina Scofield is?
Who?
No.
Michael, I'm running
out of road.
Head for the hangars.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
What's going
on here?
Get out of the car!
Now!
Michael...
- Get out of the car!
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
- Move it!
We should do what they say.
Come on,
before they kill us.
Let's just do
what they want.
Let's just do what they want
before they kill us, please.
Get down.
Get down now!
Now.
Put him in
the car.
What do we do
with these two?
Kill them.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thanks to you, I guess. Hey.
Get out.
Here, move it.
Where are you taking me?
- Move.
What's going on?
- Go, move!
But where are you taking me?
- Move it!
What do you want to do with me?
Stop talking and start walking.
This is a mistake.
Lincoln, have you
lost your mind?
But... what's going on?
Just get in the car now.
What are you gonna do?
Shoot me?
I warned you not to come,
Michael.
I'm doing this for us,
the family.
Well, it's not over.
Not by a long shot.
What?
I... got some information
for you.
But I want to make sure
that everything
we talked about
is still heading my way.
The car, the office
and the house.
Bagwell, if you're
jerking me around...
You trying to talk me out of it?
Just tell me.
Linc and Michael's mother.
She's got Scylla.
Here in Miami.
And, General...
Fuel the jet.
We're going to Miami.
Christina Rose Scofield.
That name mean anything
to you?
No.
Then why was she holding on
to your flight information?
I have no idea.
You ever heard
of the Company?
No.
Company!
You never heard of the Company?
You ever heard of Scylla?
What do you do for a living?
I'm a professor at Dartmouth.
What are you doing in Miami?
I, uh... I just wanted
to get out of New Hampshire
for a few days.
To be honest, right now...
I wish I hadn't.
Just relax.
I got a call from the
organizing committee
of the Progressive Energies
conference that's here tomorrow.
They said they would fly me out
and put me up in a hotel
if I gave a short presentation.
Where's your cell?
Uh... it's-it's in my jacket.
Why are you lying to me?
I had it
when I got off the plane.
I swear to God.
Yeah, Michael,
he said he doesn't
know your mom,
but there's got to be
20 e-mails back and
forth between them.
They don't just
know each other.
They're working
together.
The question is, on what?
Linc.
Vincent Sandinsky.
What about the last number dialed?
There's a lot of calls
from that number.
I'll be right back.
Anything?
Not yet.
Yes?
How badly do you want him, Mom?
Michael, listen to me.
That's not an answer.
I'll be in touch.
His story checks out.
Listen, there are still
some things
we need to figure out,
but as soon as we do,
we'll let you go.
Thank you.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net