Previously on Prison Break...
Hey, John, you know,
actually, about Jesus...
...say hi to him for me,
will you?
It's him.
- Did you see him?
- Who?
The guy in the viewing room.
- No.
- It was Dad.
Where's your girl?
She'll be at my place
in about an hour.
Pretty soon,
we're gonna call in our favor.
Have at it.
Boss!
Department of Corrections is allowing
you a one-hour visit with your son.
I'll make the travel arrangements,
but I don't want any problems.
I used to have a Great Dane,
big and wild.
When she was 12, she got cancer,
so we had to put her down.
And you'd think it would be this big,
dramatic event, but...
it was very peaceful.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
One minute, she was breathing,
the next, she wasn't.
Hey!
Everything okay?
Need me to call 911?
No, no, no, I got it.
Engine's smoking pretty bad,
looks like it could blow up any second.
- It's okay, actually.
- You think?
- Yeah.
- If you say so.
Fernando Sucre
released from Ad Seg.
Cuz!
You're out.
It's good to see you.
Y'all can sign each other's
yearbooks later. Where we at?
The map is complete.
I got what I needed.
- Then we're ready.
- Almost.
I know which pipes we need to
take beneath psych ward now.
Which means our way to
the infirmary is clear.
With our new route,
we're gonna come up on the
far end of that building.
Which means we've got to walk down 30
feet of hallway to get to the
doctor's office--
our exit point.
Which means there's only one
piece left to this whole thing--
a key to that room.
No sweat.
All we got to do is run a bump and
grab on a C.O. like we did last time,
grab the keys, make a copy.
It's not that easy.
Only the medical
staff have those keys.
How you fixin' on
getting it then, Pretty?
Carefully.
No more surprises
this time, right?
Right.
Jesus...
Mary, Joseph.
- Hello, John.
- Michael.
How are you?
Any day above ground is a blessing.
Thanks be to God.
You mind? Please.
Thank you.
Lot of rumors going around.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're back.
I'm surprised you're still here.
I thought you'd be gone by now.
Well, we had a few setbacks.
Still planning on it?
That depends.
How does the idea of escaping
sit with the new you?
Oh, the old sinner who was confined
to these walls, he's dead.
The new soul
deserves to be free.
Well, the old sinner was going
to have a jet ready for us.
Is the new soul going to
be able to pull that off?
Noah had his ark, did he not?
Let's pray.
I'm gonna need a
blade... pronto.
- Hit and run?
- Yes, sir.
- And Burrows is gone?
- That's right.
- The officers?
- Two are dead, one's in critical.
Do you realize what the media's gonna
say when they get a hold of this?
We'll get him back, sir.
40 years in corrections, and this
is how they're gonna remember me.
This is Kane County.
Sheriff Ballard's a good friend of mine.
He hasn't said a
word to anyone yet.
Give us four or five hours,
we'll find him.
If I don't report this to the D.O.C.
right now...
They don't have to know.
You've always been a
by-the-book guy, boss,
but this time,
the book's gonna get us all fired.
Find  him.
The records of every phone call made to
and from every contact in Quinn's
cell phone.
Well we have our haystack, any idea
what the needle might look like?
There must be thousands
of calls here.
But to who? To where?
You know, it's gonna take us
forever to go through all of these.
What if these have nothing to do
with Lincoln and Steadman, huh?
What if we're just
burning time?
We're just that much
closer to the execution.
What's going on with you, Nick?
It's almost like you want to quit.
I don't want to quit.
Then let's get to it.
Dr. Tancredi will be right in.
- Morning.
How you, uh,
how you feeling today?
- Better.
- Good.
We got checkpoints
up in 171 by Lamont,
Sage Bridge and at the
river goin towards Romeo.
According to our
witness overthere,
this new perp was driving an 06 Mustang,
black, dark blue, maybe.
We're not gonna be able to sit
on this thing very long, Brad.
This is me, Nate. I need this.
All right.
You go back to Fox River.
I'll be in constant contact.
You mind if I...
How you doing, M. ...
Roy Hoggings. Hi.
Where you going?
Uh, I'd like to get
going if I could.
I'm late for a
meeting in Aurora.
- Where do you come from?
- Chicago.
Kind of a indirect
route to get to Aurora.
I'm ot from around here.
If any of you get so much
as the whiff of anything,
I want to know it immediately.
Makes of two us, pal.
What do you want
from me, Michael?
Sara...
I  need you to do
something for me.
What?
Wait for me.
It won't always be like this.
In this room, in this place.
Until then, I can't.
We can't.
Damn it.
I can't.
And I got to go.
- Hey, Squirt.
- Avocado.
How many times I got to say it?
You address me formal-like.
- Mr. Bolz-Johnson.
- That's better.
I think maybe you and I
can work something out.
Really?
Yeah, check it,
I got a this homie on the outside.
He can put a hundie into your
commissary account each month.
It's nice of you to
think of me like that,
but you only got
one thing I need.
I need you to get something for me.
Do your bump and swipe thing.
- Like I did with the watch?
- Exactly.
Yeah, that did me
a lot of good.
Guards found out,
they stuck me in a cell with Avocado.
So if you want something glommed,
you need to do something for me.
Kill that son of a bitch.
That's not something I can do.
Screw Honus Wagner.
What was that?
This kid in my neighborhood,
his dad had a baseball
card collection...
So I figured,
you know, I'd swipe it.
I could get some party cash,
you know?
There was one card in there.
A 1910 Honus Wagner.
Doesn't mean nothing to me, you know.
Hoops is my sport.
This card,
it was worth $300,000,
so they slapped me
with grand larceny.
That's why I'm here.
That's why I'm sitting on a nickel
getting turned out like a little bitch.
A baseball card.
Dad?
What are you doing here?
As soon as I heard they granted
you a visit with your son,
I knew they'd make
a move on you.
I mean what are you doing here?
I've got a car about
20 miles from here.
We'll switch out. After that...
I'm gonna make sure
you disappear.
Then this business will just be
between me and them. Can you move?
What are you talking about?
They're after me, not you.
It's not as simple as that,
trust me.
I worked for them.
You worked for them?
You're an alcoholic, a...
Is that what you remember?
Or is that what you were told?
Why did you leave?
I took a position with a group of
multinationals known as The Company.
They call every shot
this country takes--
what laws to pass, what judges
to appoint, what wars to fight.
Thing is, if you wanted to
rise in the ranks like I did,
you had to commit to leaving
everything you know behind.
Because then, you start to get
access to the real information.
Information people would do a lot
of things to get their hands on...
like harm your family.
You expect me to believe that?
Why didn't you reach out to us?
Why didn't you call us?
I regretted it every day
but I didn't have a choice.
Lincoln, the day I
left The Company,
I took all that
information with me.
That's why they're
doing this to you!
All  of it... to stop me.
You have to trust me.
Then you'll have to tell
me what's going on.
- I can't do that.
- Then I can't help.
Look, I did what you asked.
Green card for credit card,
that was the deal.
Then, we'll make a new deal.
Michael, if somebody
finds out...
Believe me,
I'll be in more trouble than you will.
I know,
and that's why I won't help you.
Look,  Nika, I promise you...
Look, I don't know
what's going on.
I don't know why
you're in there,
but if there's one thing those guys
that brought me here taught me,
it's that if you fight,
if you struggle,
you only make things worse.
Stop fighting, Michael.
Just think about it, okay?
I'm sorry.
There it is again, the 406 number.
It's on every listing.
Four-oh-six.
Yeah, there's over 200 businesses,
another hundred residences
in 17 different countries.
They're all calling
the same number.
- Four-oh-six.
- Montana.
Can you check the prefixes?
This doesn't make sense.
All these people from all over
the world are calling this place
in the middle of nowhere
with a population of 42.
Blackfoot, Montana.
I thought you
understood, Terrence.
If you want to talk,
we set up a meeting, at home, in person.
I saw the latest tracking.
Your polls are headed south.
Maybe the Burrows thing is finally
starting to gain some traction with
the swings.
- It could hurt.
- Good-bye, Terrence.
- You said it was almost over.
- It is.
Are we talking about Lincoln Burrows...
or your candidacy?
The only reason that
you are still alive
is because I won't
let them kill you.
Yeah, I'm pretty clear on that.
But the thing I
can't quite figure is
with the crap storm
this thing's become...
why they haven't killed you.
Figure out how you're going to
get the key to the infirmary yet?
Not quite.
You working a game on her,
or what?
I don't know.
I've had time to think.
Not that you tried to kill me,
but about how Jesus saved me.
I didn't come here, Theodore,
to inflict any more pain.
Take my hand so we can put
this behind us. Please.
Show me the palm of
your other hand.
Don't insult me.
After all you've done,
the least I ask is that
you don't insult me.
Does not a warm hand feel
better than a cold shank?
You got a point there,
John. Yeah.
Truce.
You got it. Truce.
Son of a bitch.
It's been two and a half hours and
you're telling me that sheriff's
got nothing?
I'm telling you the
roads are blocked off.
That Mustang's going to be somewhere
within those ten square miles.
All right, listen,
you got two hours to find him.
And after that,
I have got to talk to the press.
There's an escaped
killer outside our walls
and there are some things that
are more important than career.
Now you find him.
- Hey, Captain.
- I don't have time.
He says he really
needs to talk to you.
You have something for me
or do you need something,
'cause if it's the latter,
you just wasted my time.
That cellie you stuck
me with, Avocado...
Do you have something or
do you need something?
Last time I'm going to ask.
I'm asking you to just please
get me out of that cell.
Boss, please.
Boss!
Let's go!
You need to start relaxing.
It'll hurt a lot less.
Can we go on your bunk?
Sure, squirt.
Let me make it a wee
bit more comfortable.
Now we're talking it.
Are you the doctor
from the prison?
Uh, yeah. Can, I, uh...?
Do you know a prisoner
named Michael Scofield?
I do.
- You're his wife, right?
- I need to talk to you.
I think Michael has got
himself in some trouble.
And I think he's planning on doing
something dangerous to get out of it.
Thanks. Um, so what is it...?
Michael he has deep
need to help people.
So I've come to understand.
That's actually how we met.
There were these men
that brought me here.
Told me I'd have good job,
but that was just a lie.
They were going to sell me.
And until they did, I...
Michael paid them
off for my freedom.
And not to keep me for himself,
like I've heard from other girls,
but  to give me an opportunity.
He's a good man.
Yes, he is.
Nika, I want to do whatever
I can to help Michael.
To do that, I need you to tell me what
it is you think he's mixed up in.
- I think this was mistake.
- No, no, it's not at all.
God, I'm sorry.
Listen, could I just have a contact
number for you in case I see...
I  don't think
that's a good idea.
Please don't tell
him that we met.
I-I...
Something I don't get.
How could killing me stop you?
'Cause I'm the one who leaked
the information about EcoField.
They could've covered up the
scandal a thousand different ways,
but they chose to fake
Steadman's death.
And they chose you,
'cause they knew it
would flush me out.
They knew that any man with a son
on death row who was innocent,
would have to come forward.
But you didn't.
We had a cause, Linc.
We have a cause.
Their wars can be averted,
millions of lives can be saved.
So you were willing
to sacrifice one.
Yeah.
At least I thought...
But I couldn't watch you die.
You know what you've done?
The mother of my child is dead.
- I know.
- Do you?!
Then I'm guessing you know
Michael's in Fox River
and LJ's rotting
in some prison.
- I know all of it.
- If you think for a second...!
You don't have a
choice right now.
This is all on you. All of it.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm here.
'Cause there's still a
chance we can make it right.
That man in there is our
transportation out of here,
which means, now,
you go after him,
and it messes with my chances
of me seeing my family,
so I ain't gonna
let that happen.
So why don't you hand me that
shank you're holding, huh?
Good.
- Hey, Sara.
- Hey, Rick.
You all right?
Yeah. I can't find my keys.
Would you let me in?
Oh, sure.
- I'm surprised to see you here.
- That makes both of us.
Look...
You were right, and I'm sorry.
I should never have gotten
you involved in this.
- Oh, it's okay.
- No, it's not.
If anyone knew what I asked...
I'm not even sure why I did it.
- Thank you.
- Now we're even.
You didn't owe me anything.
Yes, I did.
I owed you everything...
but that's over now.
Good-bye.
The lady doctor...
she cares for you.
Bellick!
It's the sheriff.
I think he's got something.
Go for Bellick.
We just got a call from Steve
Schimek up at the junkyard.
Our Mustang is on the premises.
He seen Burrows?
Yep, I got a couple of units five,
10 minutes away tops.
Good, I'm right behind you.
Here. You ready to travel?
Place is gonna be crawling with cops.
You know that, right?
There's an unimproved
road down by the river.
There's a chance they
haven't blocked it off yet.
We got trouble.
Come on.
Through here.
Come on!
Hey!
Get out of here.
Go.
Turn around.
Bellick!
Bellick, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Thought you'd go for a little stroll,
did you?
You hear about Avocado?
Got his salchicha sliced.
- How?
- Tweener.
But Avocado's saying it
got caught on the frame
while he was hopping
down off his bunk. Yeah.
Why did he lie?
Doesn't want Tweener
to go to the SHU,
'cause he can't
get him in there.
All I have to say is as soon as
Avocado gets out of the infirmary...
Tweener's a dead man.
How's that key coming?
- What about your car?
- I just checked.
Uh, your apartment?
Uh... no,
'cause I had them this morning.
Then they got to be here.
Just retrace your steps. When did
you first notice they were gone?
When I came back from lunch.
Hey, Kev, I need to take a
look at that visitation log.
Thanks.
Michael?
I need to know where he is.
- Who?
- Fibonacci.
You see, my conversion requires
that I not only seek forgiveness,
but provide forgiveness,
even to my greatest transgressors.
Don't look at me like that,
like I'm the same old man I used to be.
I'm not.
Trust me, I need to reach out
to Fibonacci, so we can heal.
That's a good story,
but the answer is no.
I understand.
I'll be patient.
Hello.
Hey, you're now
officially on standby.
And you'll have her there.
Do you understand?
I'll do my best.
Hey, I said "Do
you understand?"
Yeah. Loud and clear.
Good. Goose Park Airstrip.
Find it on the map.
Soon as I call, you have that
bitch there ready and waiting.
Hey.
You still want me to swipe the
thing you were asking about?
'Cause I'm having a
going-out-of-business sale.
Why don't you get
yourself to Ad Seg.
For that to happen I'd have to
admit what I did to Avocado.
That'd get me what, 20 years?
I'm dead no matter what.
There may be another
way out of here.
Yeah, in a body bag.
I need to know if
I can trust you.
I'm as straight up as they come,
you know?
No, I mean really trust you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm fine. You?
Fine.
Have your hand, please?
- Here they are.
- Here what are?
Your keys, they were right
over there by your inbox.
You got a maintenance
guy waiting outside here,
says you wanted him
to change the locks.
Want me to call him off?
No, send him in.
Is it okay if I...
Yeah. We're about done here.
Is there something wrong?
No.
Unless you want to talk about
what happened this morning.
I think I have a
pretty good idea.
We're done here.
I want him under
24-hour surveillance.
He doesn't sneeze
without my knowing it.
What the hell for?
What did I do?
Someone tried to kill me.
Finding you at a junk yard eight miles
from here makes me think different.
Who was your accomplice?
What accomplice?
24-hour surveillance.
Boss.
I heard Avocado cut
his hose on your bunk.
Must have been some serious
gymnastics going on.
I got something for
you this time, boss,
but I want guaranteed
protection from Avocado,
and I want time cut off my bid.
Anything else?
Couple of big-canned whores
available to you 24/7?
Believe me,
what I got is worth it.
So are you gonna
step up or what?
This is your last
chance, Tweener.
You blow smoke again, they'll be
scraping you off the heel of my boot.
Scofield and his
whole P.I. crew?
They're escaping.
www.tvsubtitles.net