Previously on
Prison Break
Yes, I'd like the number
Channel 11 News, please.
Hang up the phone now.
This is Michael Scofield.
I'm at the Cutback Motel,
room 11...
and I want to turn myself in.
Where is that ?
It's Holland,
where I grew up.
You know that.
It's beautiful.
This message is for Maricruz.
I'll be there...
in the airport...
in Ixtapa waiting for you.
My name is Sara,
and I'm an addict.
- Hi, Sara.
I'm just looking to do my time,
I don't want any trouble.
Hey !
Break it up, convict !
No, this isn't fun...
what was fun was
when Caroline and I
would talk about you
and the schoolboy crush
that you had on her
He proposed to her.
- Hey ! Terrence ! Terrence !
- I'm leaving !
Terrence, listen to me.
Just listen.
So many people have suffered
because of this, because of you.
But when the press get here,
you can tell the truth.
You can end this.
Sorry.
We interrupt this program
for a special news bulletin
It's breaking news
out of Cutback, Montana.
Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield
two of the prisoners who broke out
of Fox River State Penitentiary
in Illinois have continued
to allude the authorities,
leaving a trail of crime
in their wake.
And today, they left behind
something else.
My name in
Lincoln Burrows,
and I'm innocent.
- We're done.
- There's no other way t of here.
Next time you decide to hold
a press conference,
do it from a room
with a back door.
Just let me think.
Montana Highway Patrol.
Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows,
You need to exit
with the hand in the air.
This is a warning.
Exit
with your hands up.
- What about him ?
- What about him he's useless.
A dead body ?
We got fingerprints everywhere.
Are you worried someone's
gonna pin a murder on you ?
So what's your plan ? Leave the body
walk out the front door ?
Yes.
- That's exactly what we're going to do.
- Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows,
You need to exit
with your hands up.
FBI.
Hold your fire.
FBI ?
- Start rolling.
- I have Burrows and Scofield in custody.
We're comin'out.
Hold your fire.
- Hold up, who are you ?
- Federal Bureau of Investigation.
- We're going to Billings.
- Wait a minute, let me see that ID again.
- Okay. Okay. Drop the gun !
- Don't do it !
Everybody calm down,
and this won't get ugly.
All right, you !
I want keys
to both of cop cars.
Now !
- Do not do it !
- Don'listen to him !
Get the keys !
Linc, get in the car.
What's going on ?
We're gettin'out of here
before anyelse gets hurt.
Lincoln, start it.
- Come on ! Come on ! Come on !
- Stay there or we'll drop him.
- I'm not gonna tell you again
- One more step and I'll drop him.
Come on !
Open my door.
Welcome back.
- Feeling...
- Much better
Update ?
Okay, you got it.
Yeah.
Get a lead on something ?
One of the CO's from Fox River,
Brad Bullick,
got locked up last night for the murder
of another guard.
Wait ! We're looking for CO's now ?
What about the escapees ?
Scofield ?
- Burrow ?
- Nothing on'em currently, also
Franklin's wife.
was taken into custody
in the North Dakota.
His wife ?
This is Agent Mahone.
How long ago ?
I'll make you a deal,
if you don't move a muscle,
- I won't blow your head off.
- No one's gonna hurt you, Greg.
Where are we going, Michael ?
Can't keep driving.
We lost Steadman.
Sara's in the wind...
- Turn it up.
- ... Terrence Steadman
President
Reynold's brother,
The president could not
be reached for comment
as she continues
to tour the Midwest,
showing up support
in key states
For entrepreneurs, orange growers,
iron workers and artists,
the American dream is alive
and well for all of us.
Reynolds travels
to Colorado today
for a scheduled appearance
in Denver...
- Pull over.
- What for ?
Just pull over.
Get out !
You wanna to drop
off this kid ?
Later.
We should get rid of Kellerman,
too. We don't need him.
Actually, we do.
We still have assets.
It's just a question
of how we use them.
Nurse !
Nurse.
- You ain't no nurse.
- You right about that.
Oh, that's a pretty shiner
you got, Captain.
Must make you think about
all the times you walked around here
in your fancy guard outfit,
turning a blind eye to everything
you saw that was wrong.
"Who me ?
Oh, I didn't see nothing."
How that blind eye feel now ?
- You son of a bitch.
- Get used to it.
Hear old one-eyed jack's gonna be
getting screwed in the socket.
- Over my dead body.
- No.
A dead man can't feel
a beat-down.
And you got a lot more
coming your way.
Come on now,
let's go.
It'll take the feds a while
to figure that out.
What time is it ?
A little after 9 :00.
- It's gonna be tight.
- 450 miles
in six hours.
What do you think ?
- Got to move now if we're gonna make it.
- Eyes front.
Hey, look at this.
It's perfect.
- You ready ?
- Yep.
Bonito campo, no ?
Más o menos.
Su acento ?
De dónde es ?
Puerto Rico.
En esta parte de Méjico, no se
encuentran muchos portoriquenses.
Está donde llega ?
Lejos.
Mil millas.
Qué es tan importante
llegar a Ixtapa ?
Qué hay allá ?
Toda mi vida.
Una mujer.
La única mujer.
Ojalá esté aquí
cuando yo llegue.
Here, Larry, that's for you.
What about this ?
Just what is this ?
It's too small
Why didn't it float ?
I need more wood.
Wood floats.
This will work.
Hey, man.
We were just wondering
if you could buy us some beer.
Yeah, sure.
Can I get some food
for my dog, too ?
Do whatever thing
you got to do, man.
You can even keep
a beer for yourself.
Huh ?
Oh, no.
My dad used to drink.
You're going to
want to see this.
We've shut down every freeway
in central Montana.
So far, no sign of them.
Go wider. Get troopers
on and 90 and 94,
all the way through Wyoming,
and call Whitefish.
Have him lock down the
Canadian border at 15.
My name is
Lincoln Burrows,
and I'm innocent.
I escaped from
Fox River Penitentiary
because I was sentenced
to death for a crime
I did not commit.
I did not murder
Terrence Steadman
He committed suicide last night
in the Cutback Motel
30 miles outside of his home
in Blackfoot, Montana.
He killed himself
out of fear.
Fear of the people who have been hiding
him for the past three years.
The same people
who want my brother dead.
They don't want you to know
who they are,
but know this :
They've stolen
billions of dollars
and murdered dozens
of innocent people.
And yet they plaster
our faces on the news,
and tell you
to be afraid.
They are a group
of multinationals
with corporate
interests.
Together, they're known
as The Company.
They are working with
the highest levels of government,
including the president
of the United States.
Damage control immediately,
before this hits page one.
- It's already airing, sir.
- Start a wildfire in Florida !
Find a lost storage unit
full of Arabs !
I do not care !
As long as it's not about
Lincoln Burrows !
And they operate
with impunity
- Go !
- under the cover of the Secret Service,
the very people
meant to protect
and serve.
- Buena suerte.
- Gracias.
Este es el final viaje para tí
No hay viajes
gratis aquí, tipo !
Lo siento.
No me entiende. Necesito llegar
a Ixtapa, por favor !
Tenemos un problema aquí ?
Usted cocina ?
Qué ?
Yo quito las plumas.
Mi esposa cocinaba.
Ella está murta ahorito.
Lo siento, jefe.
Tengo que continuar adelante.
Ése era el último bus del día.
Si usted cocina,
Le voy a dar un lugar donde pueda
dormir esta noche.
Espérese, espérese !
Usted vive allí ?
Sí. La puerta détrás del carro.
Usted sabe qué ?
.
Venga por aquí !
Much blame has
been placed
on another
innocent person :
Dr. Sara Tancredi.
Do we know how long
the videotape lasts ?
26 minutes, beginning to end.
It's all online.
I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I can only hope that,
by now,
you've found your
safe haven.
Start a transcript.
I need every word.
... your commitment
to help others,
and I put you in a place
that's every
doctor's nightmare.
I wish I could do things
differently...
Call Montana, have them send
an agent to talk to the cameraman.
I wanna know what he saw, what he heard, what
they're wearing, anything he can give us.
- --people murdered by government operatives.
- Yeah.
One man, Special Agent
Alexander Mahone,
is responsible for
multiple deaths.
He murdered not only John Abruzzi
and David Apolskis,
but also the last fugitive
he was assigned to chase :
a man named
Oscar Shales.
A man who escaped from prison
two years ago,
who remains one
of this country's most wanted
despite the fact
he will never be found.
- The guy's nuts.
- He'll do whatever it takes
to make the deaths
look official...
like they happened in the line
of duty... disappearances,
- Hey, thank you.
- Sure. Here you go.
What's the wood for ?
I'm building a raft.
I need more wood if I'm going
to make it to Holland.
Holland ?
Yeah.
You want to see it ?
The raft ?
You're going to try
to get from here
to Holland in that ?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, good luck, Gilligan.
I'm going to take a leak.
How are you going to know
where you're going ?
Do you have, like,
a map or anything ?
Yeah.
I do.
It's-it's right...
It's right...
Oh, it's right here.
That's your map ?
I really hope you make it.
You know, every morning,
I wake up and...
wonder what it would be like
to just disappear.
And you're just gonna do it.
I think it's great.
Okay.
What happened to your arm ?
My dad drinks, too.
What's going on ?
- Oh, nothing.
- No, no. No, no, don't...
- Let me go. Let me go !
- I just want to fix it.
No, I wanna make...
Stop !
Matt, will you take
me home, please ?
No, I...
Freak.
All right, now, Brad,
- how we doing ?
- I could be better.
Yeah, that's a
nasty contusion, but
it should go down
in about 24 hours.
I got your paperwork here for
your transfer back to Gen Pop.
Already ?
Move 'em in, move 'em out.
You know the policy.
Katie...
You look nice today.
You worked here over
ten years, right ?
Something like that.
That's a long time
we've been friends.
Brad,
if you think I can pull some strings
to keep you out of Gen Pop,
- I can't do that.
- Please.
Please, You can't send me
back there.
Do you want that responsibility,
knowing what they'll do to me ?
Just listen, please.
One more night.
Just let me stay here tonight.
I know you can do that.
And when you go home,
just leave that
door open for me.
They hung a sheet behind their heads
on the wall.
One of them...
the guy with the gun...
he found it
while Burrows and Scofield were
talking about how far they had to go.
Scofield said something
about 450 miles
in six hours.
450 miles to where ?
I don't know.
450 miles
in six hours.
Any point on this...
circle could be
their final destination.
75 miles per hour,
- stopping for gas.
- It's doable.
- Yeah.
- Where are they ?
I'm not sure.
I still need more time.
This can't happen fast enough,
Mr. Mahone.
They've already
done irreparable damage.
Scofield made the video
in a storage facility
somewhere between
Great Falls and Helena
not long after sunrise.
From there,
the witness said
they had 450 miles
to get where they were going.
There's Seattle,
Portland, Salt Lake, Denver...
Denver ?
Yes. What ?
The president is speaking there
this afternoon.
3:00.
Six hours from when they made
the video.
They're going after
the president.
A tape purported to be made
by escaped convicts
Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield
was immediately dismissed
by the Justice Department
as entirely baseless,
which brings us back to the story
we'll be continuing
to follow throughout
the day.
The terror threat has been raised
to Orange
as a storage unit rented
by several Arab Americans
was suddenly...
They buried it, dumped it off
the front page
- and buried it.
- It's what they do.
They can spin it all they want,
it's out there now.
Give it time,
the tape is going to work.
This is a Hail Mary, man.
If we don't get to her...
Getting to her is the easy part.
It's what we do after
- that's the problem.
- Which is why this has to happen quickly.
Once anyone knows we have her,
the curtain comes down.
Well, I'll notify the White House
to cancel...
No. If there's any change
to her itinerary,
the brothers will know
something's up,
- they're gonna go right back into hiding.
- We've found'em before.
- we can certainly find them again...
- These are not pets, Agent Wheeler.
Yeah, thanks,
I'm pretty clear on that,
but if you're going to use
the commander-in-chief
as bailt. It's certainly not...
You have a problem with the way
that I do things?
Yeah.
And I'm not the only one.
Is that right?
Internal Affairs has asked me
to run all your moves
through them from here on out.
Then get a pen
and make sure you get this
word-for-word.
The president's day
does not change.
The only lead we have is that we know
where these men are headed.
So we're gonna keep
quiet about this
and let 'em come.
Now, get out of my office.
They're two of the most
recognizable faces
in America.
How do they think they were going
to get anywhere near the president?
Because it's not just
the two of them anymore.
I'm gonna go take a closer
look at that video.
If I may, sir, the president...
are you certain we should keep
her in the dark on this?
Because there is a
scenario where...
she could be useful.
It is...
her ass on the line, sir.
And I think we're all pretty clear
she's been known to get her hands dirty
when that line gets too close.
Maybe we should let her know
just how close it is.
Viajar sin dinero es dificíil.
Cómo le parece el pollo ?
El de mi esposa era mejor.
Hace cuánto murió ?
Una semana.
Lo siento.
Cuánto tiempo duró casado ?
42 años.
Cuál es el secreto ?
Estás casado ?
No.
Pero espero que pronto.
Se necesita mucho
dinero, sabes,
el matrimonio, digo.
Gracias por el consejo.
Estas huyendo de algo ?
En busca de algo.
Un hombre viviendo
con una esperanza
Te dices eso comme si fuera
algo malo
Esperanza es para la gente
que vive sin gracia
Hay un cuarto.
de atrás, con una cama.
Acabó ?
Gracias
No. Gracias a tí.
Lo peor que hay es comer solo.
Buenas noches.
They did a good job
masking the room.
No reflections, no flares.
Audio markers, church bells,
construction, traffic, anything?
The room tone tells us they were
in a large space...
about 100,000 cubic feet.
So the kid with the camera...
his story matches up?
We clocked the quality of light
with the time of day, and it
pretty much fits
his wheres and whens.
- All right, content.
- The usual tells...
eyes, hands, feet.
Burrows, we were able to baseline him
off the footage from his trial, so
we got even more
clarity there.
I escaped from
Fox River Penitentiary
because I was sentenced to death
for a crime I did not commit.
I did not murder
Terrence Steadman.
Okay, there.
The eyes.
- See it?
- Yeah, slight shift to the left, then up.
Yeah, blink rate's up here
versus the pattern.
He committed
suicide last night
in the Cutback Motel,
30 miles outside
from this home
in Blackfoot, Montana.
He's lying.
Seems so.
Okay, here,
Burrows, arms folded.
He's protecting himself.
- We'll do whatever it takes...
- Not a lot of confidence in these words.
...like they happen
in the line of duty.
Okay, that means something
other than what he's saying.
- Like our father Aldo Burrows...
- Posture, shoulders in,
for emphasis.
- Really wants your attention here.
- Our attorney, Veronica Donovan...
- I was on the phone when they shot her
- Right there.
- like an animal.
- Adam's apple.
Zoom in, zoom in.
- What is he saying ?
- He's swallowing. ######
- That's a lie.
- Yeah.
His behavior is textbook.
If there's anything in here about
what they plan on doing in Denver,
they're gonna tell us.
If you say it that way,
it plays too earnest.
'Course it will--
it's the truth.
Okay, but the truth sends them home
to the wife and kids.
Lies will keep them busy.
I'm not telling a lie
to the whole country.
- It's our one chance to say it out...
- Yeah, say whatever the hell you want...
tell them you're the Green Lantern...
but I know how they break down these tapes.
I've done it.
Every detail matters.
Bin Laden crosses his legs...
right over left...
tells us something completely
different than left over right.
- It's not the same message.
- To them, it is.
If you want this plan to work,
whatever you say with your mouths,
you need to be saying something
different with your bodies
- and your eyes.
- Slightly up and to the left.
Yes.
Much blame has been placed
- on another innocent person...
- President's motorcade is rolling in.
- So far no sign of the brothers.
- Right there.
What's Scofield doing
with his hand?
We've been throwing them
a bunch of fast balls.
What do you say
we mix it up a little?
Like what?
- We think it's Morse code.
- For what?
Right now we've got a phrase,
"The water is warm."
Any idea what that might mean?
What the hell does that mean?
Nothing.
But it'll take the Feds a while
to figure that out.
We have teams checking
the surrounding counties
for the water temps.
It might be a message
to an accomplice.
The North Platte river runs through
the city. Maybe they're trying to use...
It doesn't mean anything. He's traveling
with an ex-Secret Service guy.
I'm guessing they're spoon-feeding us
every lead they want us to follow.
So all this is just a distraction
while they go after the president?
They had to know the tape
would be discredited.
They had to know that we'd talk
to the cameraman.
- There's something else going on.
- Much blame has been placed...
on another
innocent person,
Dr. Sara Tancredi.
Sara, if
you're listening,
I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I only hope by now you've found
your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment
to help others
and put your in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
Sara, if
you're listening,
I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I only hope by now you've found
your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment
to help others
and put your in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
of your commitment
to help others
and put your in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
I've considered many ways
to apologize,
but I must
arrive at one.
There's more of the same here.
Body language, his tells...
If you ask me, it doesn't look like
he means this at all.
I don't care what it looks like.
Play it again.
- I don't see...
- Play it again.
I only hope by now you've found
your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment
to help others
and put your in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
His voice... would you say
he sounds sincere
when he's talking to her as opposed to
when he's talking about their crimes?
- I... I guess you could say that.
I-  did say that.
Would you say that?
- but it's too late for that now.
- Yeah.
It's too late for you
and for others.
- People murdered by government operatives...
- This isn't about Terrence Steadman,
and it's not about
their innocence.
What do you mean ?
They're not going after the president,
they're going after the doctor.
I want everything we've got
on Sara Tancredi...
friends, families, pen-pals.
If anybody so much as wrote her
a thank-you note,
I want to know where the hell
they are now !
Adónde lo ha encontrado ?
Hallé fuera al pueble.
Llegando al sur por el camino 15
Reconocimos tu coche,
pero no a él
Yo veo
Me alegro que lo trayeron
para atrás
No tuve chansa de darle dinero
para la gasolina.
En se le prestase el coche
Sî.
Puedo mandar un oficial
para que te traigan el coche ?
No se preocupe.
No es lejos.
Él puede caminar.
Gracias. Buenas Noches.
Yo...
Encuentra tu muchacha.
Después, encuentra
la gracia de Diós.
Sara Tancredi.
Dad dead, mom dead.
E-mail account shows a minimal list
of contacts with very little activity.
Credit cards used mostly
for groceries,
sporadic clothing shopping
and, uh,
the purchase
of single movie tickets.
And ob-gyn records tell us
she's had
very little in the way
of sexual relationship recently.
To tell you the truth, I would say
the bulk of her life was her work.
Excuse me, sir,
where are you going ?
Apparently, we took
out a janitor.
When it all comes down,
all of this will get cleared up.
Well, it ain't coming down
if we don't get Sara.
She'll be here.
I want to speak to my brother.
We got to start thinking about
what to do if she doesn't show.
Or if she does.
What if the only reason
this guy's helping us
is to get whatever
information Sara has ?
What if this is just
one giant setup ?
Well, good night.
It's about time you come home.
Been out with that
Feytek boy again ?
- Sasha.
- No.
You may look like me...
but you take after your mom
when it comes to boys,
now, don't you ?
Hopefully, with a
little better taste.
Damn it, girl, you are gonna
show me some respect.
- I know Sara didn't have many friends.
- She's sort of a loner.
But you were her friend.
Yeah. I like to
to think so, yes.
And you have no idea
where she is now ?
No.
This is a transcript of
the Scofield-Burrows videotape.
I highlighted the part where
he talks directly to Sara.
Mean anything to you ?
No.
You have no idea where
she might meet him, if...
that's his plan ?
No.
Is Brad Bellick still here
in the infirmary ?
- Yeah. Why ?
- You must be loving this.
I didn't drive
all this way to gloat.
Well, then what the hell
you come here for ?
First, I really...
got to tip my cap to you.
You've managed to draw a bead on
the convicts more often than my own staff.
Well, thanks
for the "attaboy," but...
as you can see, the correctional system
doesn't share your gratitude.
I won't take much of your time,
but I do have a few questions.
- About...?
- Sara Tancredi.
She listed you as a reference on
her job application to work here.
You know her well ?
I'd know her a lot better if
you can get my ass
moved to Ad Seg.
I have no influence with the D.O.C....
you know that
If you want my help, you do.
I'll talk to the warden
and see what I can do...
right after you give me
some answers.
Scofield likes to communicate
with Sara via coded message.
Do you recognize
anything here ?
Anything that he may be trying
to tell her ?
No. I mean, he's saying
he's sorry.
Not that that's gonna do any good
with Dr. Cold Shoulder.
But...
What ?
Ad Seg.
Yeah.
All right, you see here,
it says this stuff
about "another chance."
"Safe haven".
- That's out of the big book.
- What big book ?
Alcoholics Anonymous.
Sara's in recovery.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
Those are the names
of some of the chapters
in the book they use in AA.
Do you have a copy of
the Alcoholics Anonymous book ?
Sara, if
you're listening,
I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I can only hope by now
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment
to help others
and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
I've considered many
ways to apologize,
but I must
arrive at one.
- It's getting late.
- I know.
She's not here.
I know that, too.
There is a chance
she didn't get the message.
Or maybe she's just sick
of all this.
The girl bailed on you
back in Gila.
What makes you think she's gonna
come running back now ?
The same thing that's been keeping us
going for the last three months :
- faith.
- Yeah, well...
reality's kicking
faith's ass, man.
- Look...
- Wait, wait.
Wait ?
Man, we can't wait anymore.
Listen, listen
Once again,
Michael Crane...
please report to
the front desk.
You have a
telephone call.
Yeah. Sara Tancredi.
That's right. She might be
with them now. Just...
Yes ! Just call
the local police in Akron
and tell them to get
everyone they have
over to St.
Thomas Hospital now.
Michael Crane. I think
you have a call for me.
Here you go.
Thank you.
This is Mr. Crane.
It sounded better
than "Origami."
Even if you got the message,
I wasn't sure you'd respond.
I couldn't get to you in time.
This is the only thing I could think of.
I swore I'd leave you alone,
but I had to contact you.
Because I have something ?
How'd you know ?
Michael, back in Gila
I was coming back to you.
Somebody... grabbed me,
and they, um,
they told me
that my father had given me something.
Did someone hurt you ?
I-I got away.
Michael, I want for
this to be over.
That makes two of us.
Do you think that's possible ?
With your help, yes.
It's just a question of looking at
whatever it is your father gave you.
It's just...
It's just a key.
Well, we'll figure it out.
Together.
I like the sound of that.
Me, too.
Hello, Paul.
Madam President,
it's been a while.
I know.
I'm calling
to apologize.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
It all just got
away from me,
and I ended up hurting
the one person
who's always been
at my side.
I want you to
come home, Paul.
We can fix
this together.
But not with
those brothers
running around the country
tearing down the very office
you helped me build.
- Caroline...
- I want to make it up to you.
Please, bring
them in, Paul,
Paul, and everything
can go back to the way it was.
I have to go now.
I'll see you soon.
Did you talk to Sara ?
In a few days,
this should all be over,
one way or another.
Absolutely.
Synchro: Csivore
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net