Previously Prison Break:
A very credible witness
has just come forward,
and he's willing to testify.
He'll corroborate everything
you've said about this conspiracy.
Who?
How much do you know about Sona,
Mr. Kim?
Only what I've been
given clearance on.
There's been a, uh,
change in strategy.
How much further
would I have to go?
For this,
you only have to go to Panama.
I didn't know you were
gonna be here, Michael.
You e-mailed me. You said T-Bag
was here. It's on the Web site.
I didn't write anything
on no Web site.
This is looking more
and more like a setup.
He's got Maricruz
locked away somewhere.
You're gonna help him get
the money or she's dead.
Freeze, Bagwell!
Theodore Bagwell-- he's the one you
want for that dead chick in there.
Sucre, you'd better
pull it together.
Go get the money, please.
Who are you fooling?
You ain't going to kill me,
Mr. Michelangelo.
You ain't got it in you.
- Linc?
- Hello, Michael.
What do you want, Alex?
Bring me the money,
bring me the boat.
You are out of your mind.
We both have something
the other person needs.
Your brother for your plan.
Five minutes.
That's all you have.
- I didn't kill that man, Michael.
- I'm getting you out of here.
- I've got three weeks.
- Just have a little faith.
- I did everything I could.
- I know you did.
Señor?
- Chicle?
- No.
Soda?
Beer, my friend?
Spleef? Magic mushrooms?
Burst your brains,
split it wide open.
I'm your man, man.
Magic Mystery Tour
right here in this box.
And if I don't got it,
I can get it.
Beat it.
So you gonna do
the right thing?
Right for who, Alex?
You lost, Michael.
That's what you've done here.
And you're gonna lose
a whole lot more,
unless you tell me
right here and right now
you're gonna bring me the money,
you're gonna bring me the boat.
And you'll just
let my brother go?
Yeah.
Just like you let Tweener go.
And Abruzzi...
And Haywire.
Things are different now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The people I was working for,
they kind of, uh...
sold me down the river.
Now I just want to go out to sea.
Well, that's funny--
I'll have to remember that one.
I face more prison
time than you.
I sort of jumped ahead of you a
few spots on the public enemy list.
You're my way to freedom,
Michael, and I'm yours.
We both know what the other
one's capable of. Come on.
Let's treat each other with a little
respect here. No games. No nothing.
Just two guys doing each other a favor.
What do you say?
Where are you?
Miraflores shipping docks,
just outside of Panama City.
It's a big warehouse
right on the water.
That's a long ways.
It'll take me at least
24 hours to get there.
Well, then, I'd get moving.
- How's it feel being on the run?
- I'll survive.
Not if they catch you.
They'll send you to the chair.
- You think that's ironic?
- Maybe justice.
Mr. Kim, Alex Mahone. Call me.
Oh... justice will be served.
What I'm about to divulge to you will
in all likelihood get me killed.
- Actually, I guarantee it.
- Then why are you doing it?
Because this was supposed to be
about country, about loyalty,
about what's right,
but it wasn't because...
I wronged people who should
not have been wronged.
Those orders were given
by Caroline Reynolds,
who was Vice
President at the time.
Acting on those orders,
I planted evidence...
I procured a body,
I lured Lincoln Burrows
into that parking garage
that evening under the
auspices of a different hit.
From the ground up,
we framed him.
Perfect.
So, Lincoln Burrows gets executed,
people forget about Terrence Steadman,
the controversy surrounded
him and the presidency.
And nobody ever knows about...
the Company.
Ah, yes,
which is a shadowy cabal of corporations
that pretty much influence everything
that happens in this country.
But I fail to see how
any of this is relevant
to Sara Tancredi and the fact
that she aided and abetted,
that she jumped bail...
She did so because she feared for
her life, which was appropriate,
as I had orders to kill her.
Hey!
Are you still in
the magic business?
Siempre.
- What's your name?
- Chaco.
It's all here.
Everything Mr. Kellerman said is
corroborated in these documents.
In light of this evidence,
my question, I guess, to you is
whether your time and resources
are best spent in pursuing
charges against Dr. Tancredi.
No. My office will drop all charges,
effective immediately.
But, Your Honor, I would like
to devote my time and attention
in prosecuting this man,
Mr. Kellerman.
Officer.
I literally don't even
know what to say to you.
It was good knowing you, Sara.
- Yeah?
- Where are we?
I'm in Panama. Nice place.
Good weather. Cool breeze.
Where are we with the brothers?
When you get them
where they need to be,
I want to come down there
for visual confirmation.
Then I suggest you get on a plane,
because by the time you get here,
I will have Scofield and
Burrows where you want them.
And then this whole
thing is over.
Sara, it's me.
It's a strange thing...
leaving a message for someone
you know is never gonna get it.
I can only assume
the worst, so...
this will be the last
message I leave for you.
I just wanted you to
know that I made it.
But it's no good without you.
Anyway, you remember when I...
remember when I told
you about those...
50-cent beers in
Baja at happy hour?
They're even cheaper down here.
If by some miracle,
you do get this...
I need you to listen close.
Sara... Sara,
I suggest we get you out of here.
It's going to be a media circus outside.
It'll only get bigger.
Let's go.
Sure.
Larger, unexpected fireworks
at the trial of Dr.
Sara Tancredi in Chicago today.
New testimony has implicated
that former President Reynolds
was complicit in the falsification
of her brother's death.
The fall out from all this,
the purported killer Lincoln Burrows
who has fled the country
on a nationwide manhunt
will be exonerated of all
charges effective immediately.
Oh, my God, Bruce,
Lincoln's a free man.
Michael left me a message.
Okay... my God.
He doesn't know.
He's still planning on running.
Uh... Come on, Michael,
come on, come on.
- Let me do the introduction.
- Fine, but I'll do the talking.
- Okay, I got to go to him.
- What's that, about 3,000 miles, Sara?
It is. So we're going to
have to swing by my hotel
and you're going to have
to get me to the airport,
because, Bruce, he's got to know
he doesn't have to run anymore.
What he's doing right now
is going to get him killed.
The stars are finally
aligning, sir.
Mahone's got Burrows.
Scofield's on his way.
I will make it happen.
I'm going down there myself.
Just one is needed.
Uh, I assume we both
know which one that is.
I will call you when
I get down there.
I just... I...
I want you to listen really close, okay?
- Alex, Alex, slow down.
- Okay, okay.
We talked about getting back together,
about giving it another shot.
Yes, and I said that
maybe we could.
Alex?
- What about Colombia? Cartegena?
- Go there?
You got summer break coming up,
don't you? Same with Cam.
- Yeah, but...
- I'm not far from there right now,
and I was thinking that why not just
stick around and have you come down?
You always wanted to go, didn't you?
Visit the homeland?
- Yes, but you didn't.
- Yeah, but I do now.
Uh... Yeah. I mean, I suppose
we can maybe do two weeks
at the end of the summer...
- Is that a yes? That's a yes, right?
- Yes, yes...
Come on, great coffee, great beaches,
wildlife parks for Cam.
Alex, look, it might not work out.
You've got to be prepared for
that, okay?
I... It can't be
like it was before.
It will never be like before.
I know what's important now.
I know what matters.
Well, I guess I could...
I could look online.
- I don't know, I should go.
- Just come be with me, Pam.
Be with me.
Hey...
You've got nothing to
worry about, okay?
It's you I'm marrying.
Senor Gonzalez...
*What are you doing?
*Leaving.
*That's ridiculous.
You're hypovolemic.
*You're down 3 pints of blood.
*That's 30% of the blood
that's in your body.
*Kidney damage,
brain damage, even death.
*American Embassy please.
*Connect me please.
- U.S. Embassy operator.
- I'm looking for a friend.
A missing American friend.
He could be in the hospital.
Could be in jail.
What's the name?
Bellick...
Brad Bellick.
Hey! Hey,
do I get to call my lawyer or what?!
What are you
savages down here?!
I get to call my
lawyer or something.
Freakin' banana benders.
Finally. That's him.
That's the guy.
He's the one who killed that girl.
Good job, guys. Bueno.
Hey... Aren't you going
to release me now?
Hey.
Hey!
- You're busted.
- Am I?
- Where's the money?
- Pretty boy's got it.
He's out there
with a royal flush
and you're in here with a busted
straight. Hardly seems right, does it?
Your hand don't
look much better.
- Maybe I got an ace up my sleeve.
- You know something I don't?
You should rest your leg, boss.
*DeJesus, how goes it?
*Chaco, what's going on?
*I have a guy for you
with a ton of money.
*What the devil is this?
*Calm down.
I just want to do business.
*Get out.
I was told we
could make a deal.
You're a long way from home, boy.
Ain't no deal for you here.
You haven't heard
what I have to offer.
Guy looking like you do...
coming here...
the only thing you're
offering is jail time.
*You crazy,
bringing a cop here.
I'm not a cop.
Check online.
Type in "Michael Scofield."
- That means nothing to me.
- Could mean 100 grand.
This takes longer than 30 seconds,
you're in the canal.
Bait... for the catfish.
Hey...
*Here he is.
You just gave me a 100,000
reasons to turn you in.
That's true.
I guess I'll just have to
give you a few more not to.
You know I'm innocent.
- Yeah? Probably.
- And yet you don't care.
I don't care about anything other
than getting my life back, no.
Your wife know who
you really are?
Yeah, you know how it is.
Good men doing bad things
because of circumstance.
I'd call her back
if I were you.
Tell her to forget
you were ever born.
Oh, you would, would you?
Stop the cancer from your
life spreading to theirs.
Cancer of my life.
I wouldn't be begging her to
meet me in this third world dump
- if it weren't for you and your life.
- There's no way out of this.
For you or for any of us.
For me there is.
How much of it have you spent?
100,000... 200,000.
Of course, down here,
it'd be more like a million.
Be Louis XIV or something like that.
The Sun King of Panama.
You ain't gonna be
seeing much sun now.
I don't know.
You know, Bagwell,
out of all the guys,
all eight of 'em,
you were the guy I was hoping would
go down in a blaze of gunfire.
Why don't you give me your best shot.
Finish the job.
Maybe I will.
That Siamese cat smile just makes me
want to open you up that much more.
It's Cheshire.
Cheshire cat smile.
Señor Bellick.
I'm free?
What the hell's this?
Hey, wait... wait a minute. What
about him? He's the one that did it.
Bueno suerte.
"Bueno suerte"?
"Bueno suerte," what's that mean?
Bueno suerte--
what does that mean? Bueno suerte?
Good luck.
*Relocada Station. This way?
*Yeah.
*You need some help?
Bellick.
Bellick!
Where is she, Bellick, huh?!
Where is she?!
Where's Maricruz?!
You want to know where she is,
find a way to get me out of this!
Get me out of here! Get me out!
Maricruz...
Michael, that's
a beautiful boat.
Just promise me you'll change
the name when you take it.
I don't think my mother
would have approved of you.
Consider it done. Come on.
- Uncuff me.
- No, not yet.
So is this the part where
you go back on your word?
Hands up. Hands up.
No. And as of now
they want you alive.
- Why?
- That's a good question.
Figure it out someday on your own time.
Where's the money?
- Cut him loose.
- No.
Come on, Alex, you already got the boat.
Show a little good faith.
The money. I want...
- Yeah.
- I'm here. Where are you?
- I'm inside the warehouse.
- I'll be right there.
Here we go.
Hello. Hola.
You speak English?
Yes, yes.
Miraflores Docks.
Yes, there's been a murder.
A well-dressed Asian man has
just been shot by two Americans.
Come. Yes, come.
So you kill him
and frame us. Why?
So everyone will
leave me alone.
'Cause that's all I want.
That and the money.
It's not gonna happen, Alex.
- Let him go.
- Give me the money.
- Give me the money!
I am dumbfounded.
Don't be shy.
They're all yours.
You said you'd have them
right where we wanted them.
This isn't right
where we want them.
- That's your job now.
- Oh.
This is as far as I go.
Or is there soemthing else?
Another reason we're all here.
Like that. Like a double-cross.
Yeah, just like that.
Say good-bye.
Great minds think alike,
huh Alex?
Come on. Come on.
Once seated, your four-piece will
be mounted to the floor mount.
During transport,
do not speak to either...
I know the drill.
Get in.
- So, what do we got, 30 minutes?
- Yeah, something like that.
- Why didn't you take the freeway?
- Rush hour.
- Aw, hell.
- What?
The engine light just came on.
It just got serviced at motor pool.
Yeah, we better pull
over just to make sure.
All right, I'll check it out.
In the French Resistance
it was considered a high honor
to face a Nazi firing squad.
- I thought I told you to be quiet.
- Meant you did your job.
The highest honor was to
smile when they shot you.
Took you long enough.
Lake Gatun, Eastern Canal,
approaches to Cartagena. $27.50.
What's that crossing take?
Two days if you're under
full sail all the time.
Good time of you to be down here.
No storms, nothing.
- Had enough storms recently.
- Enjoy it. It's a beautiful crossing.
- I plan to.
- This boat here, who's it belong to?
Señor? We got a call that this boat
was used in some illegal trafficking.
It's the wrong boat, pal.
You can check it if you want to, but...
- Hey, you can't just...
- This is Panama, friend.
Get acquainted
with the law, huh?
Yes, I definitely think
you need to get acquainted.
Chico.
Oh... I...
Vamanos.
- You think they got him?
- It's a pretty singular boat.
That's a lot of coke
to be carrying around.
If you're at the helm, man...
Be doing some serious time;
ten years minimum.
Yeah, you would. We lost the boat.
At least we got dead man's money.
It's out ticket to
the rest of our lives,
minus what I'm sending
Westmoreland's daughter.
Hey.
- You showed up.
- We had a deal.
- This is my brother.
- Hey.
This way.
So we get out of here,
and we never look back.
We never look back.
I want to thank you,
Michael, for everything.
You're welcome.
It's the best I could do
with the money you gave me.
That'll work.
- Gracias.
She's very pretty.
She'll get us where
we need to go, right?
Not the boat, señor.
So, I got your message.
Thank God, I found you guys.
"Thank God" is right.
Michael, Lincoln's free.
What?
Uh, it's all over the news.
Paul Kellerman came forward
and he had everything documented
and he made a full confession.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Everything?
- Everything, all charges.
Whoa.
What, uh...? No more...
That means you don't
have to run anymore.
What about Michael?
Uh, a friend of my father's getting
into it, but he's pretty confident
that under the circumstances nobody's
going to pursue you on this.
I need a drink.
I'll go see what I can find.
Here. Help me out of this.
We did it, Linc.
- We did it.
- Yeah.
No...
you almost did it.
You want the money?!
Take the money. Take it.
You think this is
about the money?
Pocket change like
five million?
Then what is it about?
My brother's been exonerated.
The President stepped down.
We're not a threat anymore. It's over.
You may be done with us,
but that doesn't mean
we're done with you.
The police are on their way.
It started with me.
- Let my brother go.
- Oh, that's sweet. That's sweet.
You don't hear that much anymore,
that sort of fidelity in families.
Two brothers that'll go to the
ends of the earth for each other.
Too bad only one
of you survive.
Don't!
We got to go.
My men are ordered to fire
if you don't come out of
there with your hands first.
Come on, come on.
Murder is not something that we take
lightly here on Panamanian soil.
So come on out of there and
there will be no more death.
Michael, I took a man's life.
Don't think about that now.
You and I have got a date, remember?
Two limes and a couple of beers,
don't forget that.
This is your last warning!
Give me the gun.
I took a man's life.
We're going to walk
out of here together,
and we'll tell them
exactly what happened.
Look at me,
look at me, look at me.
Then we're going to tell
them what happened.
- Okay.
- We'll explain everything.
And I'm going to do
whatever I can to help you.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Now give me the gun.
- Here.
I love you.
I love you, too, Sarah.
- Okay.
- You all right?
- All right.
- Yeah. Come on.
Don't move! I'll shoot!
- Michael, what are you doing?
- Nobody moves! Nobody!
You sacrificed
everything for me once.
- No! Don't move!
- No, I can't let you do this.
Now it's time to say thank you.
- It was me. It was me!
- He's innocent!
- I did it! I did it!
He's done nothing wrong!
Michael! Tell them the truth!
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Ooh, getting impatient.
Reminds me of when we were in college.
- Did you buy the tickets yet?
- No, I'm still looking.
- Don't.
- What?
Forget about them.
Forget I ever existed.
Excuse me.
Do you speak English?
- Yes, can I help you?
- Yeah.
I'm looking for a woman--
Sarah Tancredi.
She was brought in to give her
statement and then released.
You just missed her.
Sarah!
Ah... ah!
I thought you'd never show up.
Okay, uh,
when am I getting out of here?
That's the thing.
There's been a hiccup.
A hiccup.
Look, you guys got me...
you got me fair and square in Mexico,
all right?
I did what you wanted me to do.
Now it's time to cut me
loose just like we agreed.
Getting caught wasn't
part of the agreement.
I got caught running your setup,
being your bait.
Now I got you Scofield down here,
I got you what you wanted.
You got caught, Bagwell.
Hey, where... where you going?!
Where you going?!
I got you what you want!
I got them boys down here!
I did what you told me to do!
Do you hear me?!
I did what you told me!
This is as far as we go.
General...
I trust this is a
safe place to speak.
It's Scofield.
They got him.
Scofield back in the penn.
Got to be honest,
I didn't think we'd
see it happen.
You know he's gonna break out.
It's in his blood.
That's exactly what
we want him to do.
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net