I didn't kill that
man, Michael.
If you didn't kill
Terrence Steadman,
how the hell did someone
make it look like you did?
- I'm getting you out of here.
- That's impossible.
Not if you designed the place,
it isn't.
Better be open, bro.
You're asking me
to break the law.
I'm asking you to make a mistake;
forget to lock up.
We're in.
Who killed Terrence Steadman?
Nobody.
Terrence Steadman's
still alive.
Hello, Terrence.
Sound the alarm!
What's going on?
Hey!
No! No!
- What do we do now?
- We run.
The escapees, who were they?
Got a list right here.
Read it to me, if you could.
Michael Scofield, structural engineer,
five years for armed robbery.
Benjamin Miles Franklin,
former U.S. Army,
eight years for possession
of stolen goods.
John Abruzzi, don of the
crime family of the same name.
Life without parole for
conspiracy to commit murder.
Charles "Haywire" Patoshik,
60 years for
second-degree murder.
Fernando Sucre,
five years for
aggravated robbery.
David "Tweener" Apolskis,
five years for grand larceny.
Theodore "T-Bag" Bagwell,
life for six counts of kidnapping,
rape and first-degree murder.
And Lincoln Burrows,
scheduled to die next week for the
murder of President Reynold's brother.
How long has it been since
they got over the wall?
8:00 last night.
Scofield-- he and
Burrows were brothers.
That's right.
And he's the mastermind
of this whole thing.
That's what they're saying.
I want everything
they've got on him.
Where are they?
What the hell is that?
Let's go.
All we got to do is make
it to the other side.
What?
Make it to the other side.
Come on, guys!
Pick it up!
The thing is
gaining speed, man!
It's going too fast!
Go through!
- What?
- Go through!
Go!
Freeze!
I will gun you down, Scofield!
Where's the aerial
and the others?
They're back on the
ground refueling.
Son of a bitch.
Sir, Media's ready.
I'd like to, uh, talk about John
Wilkes Booth for a moment if I could,
Abraham Lincoln's killer.
12 days,
that's how long it took to find him.
In his journal during this period,
he wrote that
the shadow was his friend,
the night his domain.
He acknowledged that
whatever neuroses
drove the criminal to commit the
original crime is compounded,
magnified by flight,
by the sounds of dogs at his heels.
Fear becomes paranoia,
paranoia ultimately psychosis.
I bring this up,
because, in 140 years,
the fundamental mind of the
escaped man has not changed.
The escaped man is still human.
He is still afraid,
and he will stop at nothing
in his attempt at flight.
Fortunately for us,
while our quarry has shadow
and night as his ally,
we have something far greater:
television.
I would encourage
everyone who is watching,
everyone in this country to take
a good look at these faces.
These men right here are now the
eight-most-wanted men in America.
I thought I thought this out.
You saw all those
guys back there?
The key is they're back there,
and we're up here.
Yeah, and how long is
that going to last?
Yeah, especially since we
don't have a pot to piss in
thanks to Abruzzi's
magically disappearing jet.
Hey, you were never going to
be on that plane, brother.
And don't think I don't know where
you were going either, Scofield.
- Where am I going?
- Oh, I don't know. Utah?
When were you planning on
telling us about the money, man?
What money?
$5 million that Westmoreland
planted in the desert in Utah.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You wish I didn't know.
Wait, wait. What money?
Warden?
It's a little early for the FBI to
be showing up, don't you think?
Look, I get it.
It's still your investigation,
but once those criminals cross state
lines, it'll become a federal matter.
Yeah, well,
that is not going to happen.
I hope you're right.
That's why I was going to
suggest that we cut through
any interagency politics from
the outset. Full transparency.
- Absolutely.
- Good.
Then maybe you can tell
me about Dr. Tancredi.
There's nothing to tell.
From what I'm hearing,
she may have abetted the escapees;
opened the door that
allowed them to get out.
Like I said,
there's nothing to tell.
You're not being very
transparent, Warden.
Look, I don't discuss my staff.
Maybe you should, because she
may be the key to this thing.
We need to speak with her.
Right now, Mr. Mahone, she's not
going to be speaking with anyone.
How are we doing?
Well, the IVs are
hydrating her.
We got her on a naloxone infusion,
half milligram per hour.
What do you think
the chances are?
Well, we've done everything on our end.
It's really up to her.
Either she fights and lives,
or she quits and dies.
Hey! What do you think...
Do whatever thing
you got to do, man.
Oh, and... boy...
you call the cops,
I will put this thing right here...
...in your eye.
Thank you.
Structural engineer, huh?
Not the kind you'd expect
to get that much ink.
Not the kind at all.
How long do you think it'd take
to get something like that?
Hundred hours... 200.
Tattoo artist who gave it to him must
have spent a lot of time on him then.
I'll find out who it was.
- Mr. Bellick.
- Don't talk to me.
Fine, but it's going to make
collaboration kind of hard.
Collaboration? I got men
out here in harm's way,
and you're giving
press conferences.
The press is a tool.
It'll bring those men back
quicker than bloodhounds will.
We don't need you.
We're hot on these guys' trail,
and it's just a matter of
time till we nail them.
The problem I find
with being on a trail
is that by definition you'll
always be behind your prey.
We'll see about that.
I'm not armed.
You'll have to excuse me if I'm a
little short on trust at the moment.
I assure you, young woman,
I'm the furthest thing from a threat.
I think the Percocet
pretty much ensures that.
Good, then you won't mind if I
capture this moment for posterity.
Won't do you any good.
You don't care that someone's
going to be executed
for your murder while
you're just sitting here.
I'm not the one choose Lincoln
Burrows as the fall guy.
Who did?
Your sister, the president?
You don't understand.
I'm a prisoner to all of this.
Oh, come on.
You could have come forward.
You could have stopped this
thing before it even got started.
No, I really am a prisoner.
And now, you are, too.
The moment you let that
door shut behind you.
Didn't it strike you as curious
that there wasn't any
security out there?
The doors only open
from the outside.
The glass is two inches
thick, bulletproof.
There's no getting out of here,
young woman.
We got to dump them now.
Can't. They know about Utah.
All the more reason
to dump them.
If they get caught, they feds will
know exactly where we're going.
They'll tell them.
We just got to make
sure they stay afloat
until we're off in Utah,
doing what we got to do.
You really think the
money's going to be there?
Charles might have had a flexible
relationship with the truth,
but at the end...
at the end, there'd be no
reason for him to lie about it.
I figure once we bag it,
we cross over into Mexico,
take a whole bunch of bumpy second-class
bus rides till we hit Panama.
You really got a fix on
this dive shop thing, huh?
Yeah.
Right now, I wouldn't mind swinging in
a hammock for the next ten or 20 years.
We got half the
country after us.
We ain't making it
to Panama or Utah.
Not without help.
Veronica can't help us.
How can you say that?
We don't have money, clothes...
I already got all that.
I thought the plan
was Abruzzi's jet.
Abruzzi's jet was Plan A.
- Then we got...
- Everything we need.
Where?
Storage.
Scofield designed the tattoo,
not you?
He brought the entire thing in,
every element.
I mean, look at it;
it's the freakin' Sistine Chapel.
I knew the guy was an
engineer or whatever,
but man,
his skill as an artist was unbelievable.
What else? What can you tell
me about him as a person?
Uh, he was cool, you know.
But talk about a detail nazi.
Everything had to be perfect,
exactly as he drew it.
I always sort of had the
feeling that the whole thing
was some sort of inside joke
that only he was in on.
- We have your number, right?
- Yeah.
I may be calling you.
Thank you.
Foley!
What was the name of that long
road we took to get to the prison?
English Street.
And out in front of the prison,
the two streets that intersect with it?
- Fitz and Percy. Why?
- Thank you.
- Saddle up.
- Where we going?
Somewhere where we can stop being
cons and start being civilians.
You know, why don't you cut
out all the riddles, Snowflake,
and just give it
to us straight.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
Hi.
Hey... little one.
- What are you doing?
- Well, uh...
We're just fishing.
With no poles?
Well, we like to
fish with our hands.
Yes, eh... hand-fishing.
I think the question is,
what are you doing out here?
Hunting.
Gracie?
Gracie, get away.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're those guys
from Fox River.
Don't any of you move
a freakin' muscle.
Get away from her.
Get away from her!
Okay, okay, just..
relax, relax.
Sir...
You stay where you are.
- Let her go.
- Put the gun down!
- Right now.
- You let her go!
John, let go of the girl.
- Shut up!
- Let her go.
Put it down. Drop the gun!
You drop the gun.
Drop it now.
Put the gun down.
One.
I'll pull the trigger.
Two!
Good boy.
Get the gun.
Pick it up!
Don't you hurt her,
don't you...
Hey!
You're going to be
all right. Okay?
Run to Daddy.
I ain't going to say anything,
to anybody, man.
You're not gonna get
hurt so just calm down.
- Where's your car?
- Up on the road.
I need your keys.
You're being considered an accessory
to this; you know that, don't you?
I know very little right now.
You opened the door
to the infirmary
that allowed Scofield to escape,
didn't you?
No.
Did you have a sexual
relationship with Scofield?
No.
But you had feelings for him.
Seven other men got out,
you know.
Who?
Oh, I am sorry, sir.
It's Saturday; we're not open.
Well, that's sort of the point.
Sorry, sir?
See, I'm going to
need some work done,
and I'm going to need
it done privately.
I'm sorry,
you said you needed the work done?
This is a medical clinic,
isn't it?
Well, of course it is,
sir, but for animals.
Oh, man, what happened to you? You
need medical attention. Sir, listen...
I'm going to get an ambulance.
Nobody's going to be doing
any calling here, Doctor.
- Fine.
- That's right.
What do you want?
You know what? That's it.
I want Eye-Tie out of
the car right now, man.
That was a little girl!
Don't you have a heart?
God! I have a daughter.
I have a little girl!
I got one, too.
But if I hadn't done what I had to do,
we wouldn't be on our way to
see 'em right now, would we?
Turn right up there.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
Where we going?
Oswego.
That's west, man. We need to go east.
My family's back in Chicago.
And you think the cops
don't know about it?
You think they're not
just sitting there,
waiting for you to come
running back home?
What's the matter with you?
Well, what about New York?
- What about it?
- My girl's pregnant, bro.
Understand your love is
your weakness right now,
and they know about it.
Doesn't mean it
has to stop you.
You just got to be
smart about it.
Get to Oswego.
Oswego was not on
the way, Snowflake.
It's not where Oswego is.
It's what's in Oswego.
Captain, Scofield's credit
card transaction history.
Spent a lot of money here in Will
County before he was incarcerated?
Exactly.
He was from Chicago.
Why does a guy from Chicago
come all the way out here and
spend north of eight grand in all
these places in little over a month?
Car wash, voice mail,
storage, car rental...
- We got guys looking into it.
- Good.
Hey, Captain, what about the Feds?
Should we tell them?
What do you think?
Captain Bellick?
We got something.
Hunter up by Tamarack just
ran into five of the cons.
So this is where
Scofield lived?
Yeah, up until about two months
ago when he was incarcerated.
Mother's dead,
father's a deadbeat.
You got nothing in the whole
world but your brother.
So you plan.
And you scheme for months...
...till you get it right.
Every single element.
And then you destroy
all the evidence.
I want divers down
in the river.
You won't get cell coverage.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Digital carriers
don't have cell towers
way out here in
Western Montana.
How about shutting
up, Terrence?
Just trying to save
you some effort.
They're like a web,
these people.
The harder you struggle,
the worse it gets.
Sounds to me like a coward
trying to justify himself.
If I stay out of the way and stay quiet,
I stay alive.
That's what they said;
that's what they told me.
And you're willing
to live like this,
in a hermetically-sealed box while
everything out there goes to hell?
Self-preservation is
a strong motivator.
So is the truth.
Don't.
Young woman?
Do not.
Don't.
How you doing, buddy?
I'm pretty freaked out,
that's how I'm doing.
They took your car, didn't they?
1978 Grand Cherokee.
- Yeah.
- Which way did they go?
Up that way north
toward Oswego.
Oswego. Pardon me.
Scofield's paperwork-- get it, Jimmy.
- The credit card stuff.
- Right here, Captain.
Of course.
Where is he going to put all
the crap you need to disappear?
We're going to Oswego, boys.
You have a visitor.
Thank you.
Thanks.
You look disappointed.
No. I thought you were
going to be my father.
You heard from him?
His office.
Well, brought you a
change of clothes.
- Figured, you know...
- Thanks.
And your purse.
You left it in the infirmary.
I'm in a lot of trouble,
I think.
I, um...
I need to apologize to you.
They threatened my job
if I didn't talk, and...
No, no, no, no. No.
One thing you learn when
you're walking the steps
is that you never outsource a blame
that belongs in your own backyard.
Well, you're not the first correctional
worker that fell for a con,
trust me.
He never cared.
Not one bit.
What are you thinking about?
Mistakes.
You had to do it.
Not like I did.
I ruined her life.
Well, there's nothing
you can do about it now.
That's not true.
You fell for her, huh?
- Where's Oswego?
- Half mile maybe.
Good.
What are you going to do,
Terrence, shoot me?
Blow my guts all over this house?
Then what?
You can't leave, remember?
You kill me,
you're stuck with me.
- I'm safe here.
- You're a prisoner here.
But I'm still breathing.
If I go outside...
one step, I won't be.
You look at me...
like I'm the devil.
I gave up my family.
My teeth.
I eat Percocet all day
just to dull the pain of
my miserable existence.
You have no idea what
I've been through.
What you've been through?
This isn't about you, Terrence.
Don't.
Blackfoot Sheriff's Department.
Hello? Blackfoot
Sheriff's Department.
Hello. My name's Veronica Donovan.
I need you to send a unit
to the house at the end of
Light Road as soon as possible.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but are you calling to report a crime?
Yeah.
By the President of
the United States.
Send the car.
I'm sorry, sir,
I don't think I can do this.
There are nerves...
Look, you need a
specialist, okay?
I don't...
You need somebody who
knows what they're doing.
I don't have the luxury
of choice here, Doctor.
My hand has been in that box
for hours now. It is dying.
Sir, I am not capable
of doing this.
I only have one hand,
but I could stick this in your
neck before you get to that door.
Now, if that's not
incentive enough for you,
I see that you have a Mrs.
Gudat out there.
With a name like that
in a county like this,
old Mrs. Gudat would not be too
hard to find now, would she?
Fine.
I can promise you nothing.
Story of my life.
I'll have to put you under.
Do I really look that stupid?
Sir, I cannot do a procedure
like this without an anesthetic.
I have to cut away dead flesh.
Nobody can undergo a procedure
like this without an anesthetic!
I ain't nobody.
Schweitzer was the
plumbing company
that made the toilet Scofield
took off to get out of his cell.
Allen bolt was the fitti.
It's all here, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Ripe Chance Woods. There a place
in the vicinity with that name?
Got someone looking into it.
DOC's moving on a storage
facility in Oswego.
Captain, manager says that
Scofield's got a lease on unit 164.
It's still active.
We got guys on 8th Street,
3rd Street, then the alley.
If they're in there,
Captain, we got 'em boxed.
We push right up the gut, then.
Any one of them makes a threatening
move, put a hole in 'em.
You got it.
Officer...
This is my collar, smart guy.
Back the hell off.
Close the door.
Still nothing on this place?
Nope. They're coming
back with nothing.
No place by that name
anywhere in this country.
Or any other country,
for that matter.
Let's go.
Son of a bitch set us up.
Not one word.
Officer...
Nothing.
Oh.
Oh, that kid's clever.
It's not a place, it's a name.
Your PDA, you got it?
Yeah.
Bring up the census
of this county.
Far back as it goes.
Somebody's going to see us.
Keep digging.
We're gonna go to hell, guys.
Swear to God,
we're gonna go to hell.
Help me out.
You are one sick cat,
you know that?
What are you looking for?
We got to go to
the cemetery. Now.
Originally, this was supposed to be a
week's worth of clothes for me and Linc.
But, uh, figured you all need
just as much help as we do, so...
You're just doing this out of
the goodness of your heart, Fish?
That's right, John, the heart.
You remember what that is,
don't you?
Damn, Snowflake,
this is tight, man.
It's like I said, we got to stop
being cons, start being civilians.
Nice. Trousers are a little
bit too short, don't you think?
Chop your feet off.
You're good at that.
This jacket ain't exactly the best
thing, you know what I'm saying?
You want variety, hit Target.
Linc.
What do we got?
Money, passports...
pre-paid phone cards.
- Archie Ryan?
- Did you see mine?
Phineas McClintock.
Whoa. These?
Keys to a car that's waiting for us
a couple hundred yards from here.
That a two-of-us or five-of-us?
That's a two-of-us.
- They know?
- Not yet.
Guy-Guy-Guys, we got company.
Guys, we got to roll.
How did he know?
We're civilians; remember that.
Civilians.
I'm sorry, uh.
Do you know what time it is?
No, sorry.
I can't go outside. They'll kill
me as soon as I show my face.
You're wrong about that.
As soon as you show your face,
this whole thing is gonna be over.
You can have your
life back, Terrence.
- Promise?
- I promise.
- Hello.
- V, it's me.
We're out.
Thank God you're okay.
I saw the news.
You got to stop.
I need you to turn yourself in.
What?
I found Steadman.
I'm with him now, Linc. He's alive.
You're going to be exonerated.
Come in.
Steadman... What are you talking about,
you found Steadman?
Terrence, come on, let's go.
Afternoon.
- Veronica.
-
The police are here.
Look, I need you to
stay where you are.
Ma'am.
I don't want to lose you.
Ma'am, put the phone down.
What?
Mr. Steadman,
take a few steps back.
Ver... Veronica.
Veronica.
Oh, my God.
Veronica!
I thought you knew that all calls to
the local station are routed through us.
This is federal land, remember?
Mm.
And, uh, as for your little toy here,
it's contraband.
You gonna tell us how
you got it in there?
I brought it when I got here.
- Whatever for?
- To protect myself.
Mm. That's what we're
here for, remember?
There's a plan to make
all of this right.
In less than a day,
the trail has gone cold
in the pursuit of what
are now being called...
Yeah, that's fine.
Stay on top of it, all right?
DOC's still doing
a sweep of Oswego,
but the guys have
basically vanished.
I wouldn't be so sure about that,
Mr. Ives.
I don't know how you
can be so confident.
It's not like these guys left
a map where they're going.
Actually, that's
exactly what they did.
Scofield had the entire
thing on his body--
how to get out that prison,
how to disappear afterward.
That's all there.
I promise you that it's only a
matter of time before we know
everything that is
in Scofield's head--
where he plans to run to,
how he plans to get there.
So when the time comes
that he does get there,
we'll be waiting for him.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net