Previously on Prison Break.
Mr. Kim. Sara Tancredi.
I'm on it.
Is pursuing her the
best use of your time?
- It is.
- I'll let the President know.
- I contact the President directly.
- I'll contact her.
No family with
Patoshik? Nothing?
Yeah. Until about four years
ago when he killed them all.
Fernando Sucre--
he was in Las Vegas around 2:00.
Out west,
just like Bagwell and Franklin.
You know D.B. Cooper?
The money's in Utah,
and they're all going to get it.
You're one of them
Fox River boys.
- Come on. You got the map?
- No. Someone else does.
Before I destroyed it, I committed
it to my photographic memory.
I have the information, you have
the manual requirements necessary
to unearth Westmoreland's
buried booty.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Should be dead ahead.
The bastards built over it.
It's gone.
We have to open
up in 15 minutes.
So, it doesn't matter.
I dare you.
- I said no.
- I dare you. Please?
The ranch is gone, Michael.
Well, the five
million might not be.
And you gonna find it how?
What, you got a divining
rod tattooed on your ass?
I don't want to hear
anything out of your mouth
other than that your
photographic memory spits out
regarding that map.
You watch your
tone with me, boy.
I will watch you get tossed to the side
of the road to fend for yourself, boy.
Because if you can't remember
where that silo was,
you're worthless to us.
- Yo, let me out!
- Shut up!
- The map!
- Uh, uh, okay.
Okay, okay, all right,
all right, all right...
The ranch...
The ranch was in the center of a box--
Sheep Road on one side,
Kokosing Road perpendicular.
In the center of the property
was the ranch house.
And the ranch house was
surrounded by trees.
Every tree here is
a year old at most.
Except those.
Where is the silo?
In... side the trees.
I want to say on the left,
but that may have been a barn.
I remembered the
best I could, gents,
but I didn't know this place would
now be smothered in tract homes,
so, you know, I'm sorry that
I'm not Rainman over here.
- Mahone.
- Lyle Sands.
We've been briefed on all the men at
large. The full force and resources
of the entire Salt Lake City
field office are at your disposal.
Thank you.
Do you have those files my office
- requested on the D.B. Cooper case?
- We're pulling them now.
And this is the D.B.
Cooper case from 30 years ago?
Correct. If I can get those files
immediately, I'd appreciate it.
Hey, sorry, but I have to ask.
Aren't you here for the Fox River Eight?
I am, and they're here in Utah
to get D.B. Cooper's money,
so how about those files, Lyle?
Silo.
Silo, silo, silo, silo.
This is stupid.
We're going to get made out here.
Ah, shut it.
I think I remember.
If I had to bet,
I'd lay it all on the silo
being on the left of the
ranch house inside the trees.
No. It's outside the trees.
Right there.
You see those two trees?
They're shorter than the rest.
They were all planted
at the same time, but
those two didn't get
as much sunlight.
- Something was in their way.
- The silo.
Our money should be right
there under that garage.
You better be right, boy.
This isn't a
high-end subdivision.
They slapped this
place up overnight.
The silo's foundation
might still be there.
To save money,
they probably just laid the concrete
for the garage floor
right on top of it.
We'll dig straight down.
If we hit the foundation, we stay.
- But if not, we go.
- Let's do it.
- Oh, man.
- Uh-uh.
Ain't no problem that a screwdriver
to her temple won't fix.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
People die all the time, boys.
Five million dollars
comes once in a lifetime.
Let me out!
Well, we got to do something.
And it's not going to
involve hurting anyone.
I got an idea. First,
we're going to need some supplies.
110% do not agree with this.
Everybody's got to pitch
in to make this happen.
But back in the big house,
the boy proved he couldn't be trusted.
Which is why we're
doing it here.
If he gets caught in town,
he ain't got a clue where the house is.
Besides, you're the one we
can't turn our backs on.
Oh.
You know,
I could have died in there, man.
Well, guess what?
We need you to do something.
I need you to do something for me.
I want my cut of the money.
Well, we'll talk once you
prove we can trust you.
What do I got to do?
I want you to go back
to that Garden Center
and get everything on this list.
Then gas up the car.
And we'll meet you right
back here in an hour.
- All right.
- And David...
Don't screw this up.
This ain't Fox
River no more, man.
You're looking at
the real deal now.
But I want my cut.
I'll be back in an hour.
Let's go.
Mistake.
Big mistake.
Come on, man.
Am I glad to see you.
Did you walk here?
Well, no... it's...
it's just a long story, man.
Thought you were meeting
up with your family.
I met a...
I met a few roadblocks. You?
Yeah.
Let me guess...
you're going to Tooele.
Yep.
Well, it looks like we're
going in the same direction.
Hopefully we're not too late.
Can I hitch a ride?
Hey...
I'll make it worth your while.
Got some good news, sir.
Got our first tip on Patoshik.
Spotted at a burger joint
in Cedar Grove, Wisconsin.
Just hand it over to
local authorities for now.
The only thing we're working
today is Utah and D.B. Cooper.
Got it.
Lyle.
There's a guy here listed
as having the only
D.B. Cooper bill ever found in
circulation, Harold Jenkins.
Yeah, D.B. bought gas from Jenkins with
a hundred on the day of the hijacking.
We checked the serial
numbers and they matched.
- You worked the case?
- Fresh out of the academy.
And nobody's cracked it yet.
What makes you think that these
escapees know where the money is?
Because they may have been locked
up with the real D.B. Cooper.
This Jenkins from the gas station,
he still alive?
Should be.
He was only 18 at the time.
Let's go say hi to him.
We're sorry.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
Please check the
number and dial again.
I'm assuming you're here because
you have updates on Sara Tancredi?
Yes, um, Scofield sent her
a message through the mail,
that phone number that
was disconnected.
You know, to be honest, uh,
I was expecting to
brief the President.
Yeah, about that, uh,
right now, as you can imagine,
- Caroline's quite busy.
- She's always been busy.
I've been working side-by-side
with her for 15 years.
Paul, she's the President
of the United States now.
Yes, Bill,
and I helped put her there.
Well, if you'd like for
her to remain in office,
you'll take my advice and just
stay on the sidelines for now.
She needs to be completely insulated
from anything regarding Lincoln Burrows.
I want to talk to her.
You report to me now,
and only me.
You're not to try and contact
Caroline again without my approval,
and you don't show
up here unannounced.
Finish the job you were given;
get Burrows.
If you're telling me the road to
him leads through Sara Tancredi,
by all means, pursue it.
And once that's been accomplished
and this whole thing goes away,
we'll go about transitioning
you back into Caroline's life.
Now do you have
anything else on Sara?
The President has
unwavering faith in you.
Wants to make sure
you go through the
Senate approval process
with your eyes wide open.
So what are we up against?
Key allies in the House and Senate are
Meyerhoff, Barnwell and Summerville.
We're counting on them
to sway the middle.
But who's the opposition?
Senators Blake and Killoren have openly
vocalized their opposition to you as VP.
Any indications to why?
Political payback for the President's
vote on the energy bill last month.
Took them by surprise and
they don't like surprises.
- Lance, this is, uh, my father Frank.
- Pleasure to meet you, sir.
It's nothing to
lose sleep over.
Frankly, the biggest
issue we have to address
are the charges
facing your daughter.
Governor, are you with me?
Absolutely.
No, just chill, dawg. Listen,
once we roll out,
we bounce out of town,
we'll drop a dime and
they will find you.
Just be quiet. Just chill, man.
Woody?
Where you at? Woody?
I need Sheriff Williams.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Woody?
When'd you learn
about electricity?
I used to steal copper wiring
from transformer boxes.
Sell 'em on the docks,
make a few bucks.
When you were at school,
of course.
I was just looking, Pretty.
What's that old chestnut?
"I can look at the menu.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna eat."
We get in, we get the money, we get out.
That's it.
No, absolutely.
We're good.
Now it's just up to the kid.
Did you get everything?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
What?
Nothing. It's cool.
I handled it.
- Whoa!
- What?!
Whoa.
Okay. Check it.
This fool came in the shop.
He was acting all shady.
He got a bad vibe,
so he picked up his celly phone, he
started to make a call, so I popped him.
You did what?!
I hit him with a shovel, man!
I didn't know what else to do!
So I just, I tied him up and
in put him in the back room
with that other country hick.
- Here we go. Here we go.
- I came through, you gimp!
- Who was he calling?
- The sheriff.
Man, man, I don't know, dude.
It just, it set off...
- Did the call go through?!
- Maybe, man...
What do you mean, maybe?
Did the call go through?!
Yes. No, I don't know! I don't know,
man. Yo, but I got the gear.
We got to move on this now.
Yes?
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
Is your electricity out?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a Harold Jenkins.
- Right here.
- Alexander Mahone, FBI.
I'm staying 50 feet away
from her at all times.
What the hell else
does she want?
I'm not here about that.
- What are you here for?
- D.B. Cooper.
People still want to know
about that guy? Unbelievable.
You worked the gas station in
American Fork where he filled up.
Yeah. Normal-looking guy.
Barely said a word.
There were some discrepancies in the
statement you filed 30 years ago.
In the report, it's noted that you
said he filled up at 7:00 a.m.,
but on another occasion,
you said it was 7:00 p.m.
- Which was it?
- Both.
- He gassed up twice?
- Yeah.
- Full tanks both times?
- Yeah. Why?
A systems what?
It's a systems
diagnostics test.
Footage from our gopher cam picked up
exactly where your line was corrupted.
- And who corrupted it, you guys?
- Maybe.
All I know is my supervisor called
and said he wants me and my crew
to get over here and fix that
problem double-quick, double-time.
So... you're not with
the electric company?
No, ma'am.
Now feel free to call your company,
but I should tell you,
all they'll do is send over some tech,
maybe tomorrow if you're lucky.
And he'll spend a whole day
trying to find the problem
and another day
trying to fix it.
But we're here right now and we're
ready to turn your juice back on.
- My juice?
- That's right.
And, uh...
and that's your... crew?
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, D.B.
Cooper was driving a 1965 Chevy Nova.
There's no record on file
that Cooper even had a car.
But Charles Westmoreland did, and
the car registered to him at the time
was a 1965 Chevy Nova with
a 16-gallon gas tank.
Back then, a Chevy that size probably
got what, eight miles to the gallon?
Now, D.B.
stopped at the station in American Fork,
gassed up once early that day
and then came back later that
same night and gassed up again.
Now, why would a guy headed to Mexico,
which is a straight shot south,
drive off the main road
for an all-day detour?
The money.
Exactly. Cooper/Westmoreland jumped
out of a plane with $5 million.
But Westmoreland didn't have the
money on him when he was arrested.
He ditched it before he got caught.
Give me that Magic Marker.
From American Fork, he couldn't have
gone further than 64 miles in
any direction.
I want everything you've
got in that perimeter.
Those cons are in one
of these towns, and
if there's so much as a cat missing in
one of them, I want to know about it.
The defective cable runs
right beneath your garage.
We're gonna have to dig up
the floor to get to it.
Well, who's gonna pay for this
and what about the
cleanup and the repair?
Well, the company
will cover all costs.
We'll just dig a small trench,
once we're finished,
we'll re-lay the cement.
It'll look as good as new.
How long is it going to take?
One way or another,
we'll be out of here today.
We really need to
get started, ma'am.
We wouldn't want a pretty
little thing like yourself
sitting in the dark tonight,
now do we?
Now that depends on
who I'm sitting with.
Touche.
Fine, that's okay, y'all go ahead
and do whatever y'all need to do.
Jeanette, the noise
might be substantial.
You might want take in that
tennis game after all.
Oh, no it's...
it's too hot for that now.
Plus, I'm gonna keep
an eye on y'all
and make sure you
don't steal anything.
Ma'am.
- How are you?
- Good.
All right, where's Tweener?
He's next door plugging
in the extension cord.
We're going to have
to cut up the cement.
Yo, we gots company.
What's up, snowflake?
As always,
your timing is flawless.
I don't follow.
Well, let me try to
explain it to you.
We're trying to
run something here
and we can't have people
walking in off the street.
Oh, oh, okay,
so you want us to leave
and then you can just
mail us the check?
Sucre, I know you trust me.
And you know I'll cut
you in on that money.
But the two of you being here
right now jeopardizes everything.
I'm not going nowhere.
I want my share of the money.
Wait a minute. Hold on, man.
Ain't we did this dance before?
You know, I say I want in,
you say no.
Then I threaten to tell somebody
about what's going on here.
Then you decide to play nice and
then we're one big, happy family.
Why don't we just stop wasting time,
all right?
Thank you.
Damn, man, you still alive?
- And kickin', home boy.
- How'd you find us?
Man, if I can do rapid deployment
of satellite communications
for Uncle Sam all
over the world...
How are you guys doing?
Who are you? Who are they?
I, uh,
I had to call my supervisor.
He sent them right over.
This job is a top priority.
We want to get this done as quickly
and efficiently as possible.
Well, Jeanette, like I said,
there's a lot of work to do,
and it's going to be noisy.
- Oh, drinks. I forgot to ask.
- We're good. Thanks.
Yo, man, this is not good.
We got her up in our grill
checking in on us all the time.
The boy is right.
And since I can't dig,
I'll volunteer to keep her occupied.
You don't touch her.
Who are you, Sister Mary Francis?
I know how to play nice.
I'll be watching.
Billy? Is that you?
Yep.
Oh.
Thank you kindly.
Well now,
how did you get out of working?
Union rules.
Uh, one crew member
always has to supervise.
I'll check on them in a bit.
- Lemonade?
- Mm.
Hmm...
More ice.
Yeah. And I like mine
with a little... Oops.
But since you're on the clock,
I guess you can't...
join me?
Just two fingers.
Been a while.
Yeah?
Whiskey always makes me feel...
irascible.
I don't know what that means.
But I do like the sound of it.
Are you wearing Angel perfume?
I am.
Oh, hmm...
That reminds you of an ex,
I take it.
Yeah.
Now, was that good memories...
or bad memories?
Both.
- Did you talk to Maricruz?
- I don't want to talk about it.
I got to get some
water or something.
Use the hose on the
other side of the house.
Sucre...
down the road,
if you're in
trouble, europeangoldfinch.net.
It's what we can all
use to communicate.
Post a note on
the message board.
- What's it called?
- Europeangoldfinch.net.
That's a bird, right?
I got something.
It's the silo's foundation.
Hells, yeah.
Thank you, Charles.
We just need to find the
edge and dig underneath it.
We'll get the money...
hit the back roads.
- Uh, well...
- What's wrong?
We gots to stop in Tooele
first and gas up the ride.
I thought you already did that.
Man, when the garden center thing
happened I just forgot, all right?
I want you to go
back into town--
I want you to gas up that car.
Because I'm not driving around with
millions of dollars in the trunk,
do you understand?
Man, why do I gots to do it...?
Okay.
Better check in on our friend.
Miss Tinsel Toes.
Billy?
Yeah.
I made you a sandwich.
Peanut butter and jelly
with the crusts cut off.
Just like you like.
I'm so glad you came back.
I don't want to say
I told you so, but
that was just not
the girl for you.
Where is that?
Where's what, sweetheart?
That painting.
Oh, it's Holland.
Where I grew up. You know that.
It's beautiful.
Oh, there's no place better.
It's so peaceful, so...
so protected from this crazy world.
Hello, Operator?
There's an intruder in my house...
Hello, ma'am? Ma'am?
Are you there?
Is anyone there?
Heard you had some
activity in Tooele today.
A bit. Don't see how it
warrants a visit from the FBI.
A stolen car was dumped
just outside of town,
belonging to a woman who went to school
in St. Louis, am I getting that right?
Yes, sir.
And then here, the owner's
girlfriend reports him missing,
and then his buddy comes by
to check it out and he...
goes missing, too.
Yeah, but Woody and Chet have
been known to drop everything
and go boar hunting when the
opportunity presents itself,
and they don't tell
their old ladies.
Mr. Mahone, I'll bet you my lunch money
there's nothing amiss around here.
But Woody's dad'll be showing
up soon with the keys and...
you can look for yourself.
Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?!
Mr. Mahone.
Shh.
They're here.
Those escaped convicts.
They're here in town.
Who's there?
It's the police, ma'am.
You okay?
Yes.
Can you tell me what happened?
There was this strange man.
I made him a peanut
butter sandwich.
I thought he was Billy.
And once the kids went to sleep,
we'd take a bath.
A long... bath.
And afterwards,
I'd just sit there and watch her...
do her routine, see.
Rub her lotion on,
comb her hair.
Dress up in her
nighttime fineries.
Oh, you're killing me.
She had this spot on
her neck right... here.
Gave her goosebumps every time.
And that perfume...
My ex.
He was an accountant.
He was really buttoned up.
He was ram, damn,
thank you, Sam.
Well, shame on him.
Why did it end with that
lady you were talking about?
Just went out separate ways.
Do you know...
what I think the best cure
is for a broken heart?
Do tell.
Get back on the bike.
Whatever bike it is.
Amen to that.
Speaking of.
Could you do something for me?
I'm certain of it.
Come here.
Only you have to
be very discreet.
They don't come any discreter.
You know that, that big guy the
strong guy that, that doesn't...
speak much?
Would you go in
there and ask him
if he would like to have a drink with
me after he punches out? Please.
You've just been playing me
this whole time, haven't you?
Come on. Don't be like that.
Would you just go in and
ask your friend? Please?
Hey, Dad.
Sarah. I've been
trying to reach you.
Uh, yeah. I've been meeting with
my defense attorneys all day.
Um... You in Washington?
Yeah, but I'm coming
back on the next flight.
I thought you were going
to be there for a while.
No, no. Plans changed, okay?
Sarah, do you remember that guy that
I met with you in your apartment?
- I want you to stay away from him.
- Who, Lance? From my, my group?
Yeah, yeah, that's him.
He is not who he says he is.
And I found out some
other things, too.
- What are you talking about?
- You were right.
- Sarah?
- I gotta go.
Yo.
Uh, just one second, sir.
Thank you.
How can I help you?
Just put $40 on three.
I'm sorry. Uh...
What pump was that?
Three.
Oh, that one's been sticking.
Okay, well, then,
I'll move the car.
Ah, no. Don't--
Don't trouble yourself.
I'll have the, uh,
mechanic come out and pump it for you.
Hey, we got a customer
waiting on three!
Yo, look, man,
I'm in a hurry, all right?
Oh, he'll be right out.
Just one second.
Put your hands behind your
head and drop to your knees.
Drop!
Where are they?
Where... are... they?
All right, man.
One hand or not, I think Hillbilly
needs to be up ahead digging.
What you think?
Good man.
Oh.
What the hell are
you doing up here?
Uh, I'm sorry, Jeannette.
I just didn't see you downstairs.
I heard something.
Don't bother. She's got the
hots for the big, strong one.
I'm sorry, Jeannette.
We're gonna...
we're gonna get
back to work now.
No, I think y'all are done,
and I think y'all
need to leave now.
We're almost finished.
No, I think you
are finished, okay?
And I want you to
leave my house now.
Sucre, check it out.
Cop.
Thank God.
Oh, let her go, T-Bag.
She's our only way
out of this, pretty.
Don't say a word, you old whore,
or I'll cut your throat out.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net