Previously on Prison Break
Sona's a one-way street
What goes in
never comes out.
Since the riots of last year,
they lt here us to rot.
They figured we would just destroy ourselves,
but instead we've thrived.
How about we work together, you know,
help each other out?
You're on your own.
Get me out of this! You want to know
where she is, find a way
to get me out of this!
Maricruz... Maricruz.
We can assisyou should you ever decide,
say, to break out of here.
This conversation's over.
We're trying to do this the easy way.
Think you can do me a favor?
We have a lot to discuss, Lincoln.
Specifically, your brother.
How are we coming with the transfer?
You got to stay.
What are you talking about?
Dad, I'm so sorry.
They got me and Sara.
You got a week to find this Whistler guy.
Otherwise, they, uh, both die.
Where you from up there, bro?
Chicago.
Michael Jordan.
Yeah.
You meet him?
It's a big city.
Oh, yeah, big city.
Thanks for saving me a spot.
Hey!
Ejected!
You ever have sex with blond cheerleader?
Yeah, sure.
You're the man, bro.
How long's the water been out?
Since riots last year.
Government blame us.
They say, "Screw you, you break it."
No water.
Gracias.
Real quick.
There's an inmate here named James Whistler.
I'm looking for him.
Welcome to club.
Everybody looking for him.
Why's that?
He killed the mayor of Panama City's son.
In bar fight.
Mayor not happy.
Hey, hey.
So where is he now?
Disappear.
Some say he might even escape.
Hey. Hey!
"I don't have no money.
I don't have no money,"that's all I hear from you,
you know that?
But then I see you with this, huh?
Life must be good, eh?
Look, I'm-I'm hungry, okay?
You worry about me being hungry.
Hey, hey, hey,hey, come on.
Me being hungry.
Come on!
But you eat all the time.
Okay, I can see you up there.
Hey, tranquilo!
There's gonna be more water.
When?!
I said there will be more water.
Whew!
Later, bro.
Go.
Spare a little?
I need some information.
Absolutely.
You slipped this note in my pocket yesterday.
Why?
My memory's a little foggy on account of thishirst.
Yeah, it's starting to come back to me now.
A little more agua there.
The note.
This guy gave me some rat meat in exchange for putting that
in your pocket and the pocket of the guy you were set to fight.
Why?
He's nuts, that's why.
Anybody who can live down in those sewers
doesn't have all his faculties.
Where in the sewers?
Whistler!
Whistler.
My name is Michael Scofield.
I was  to get you out of here.
I'm going to assume they told you I was coming.
Or that someone was coming.
Whistler.
Last chance.
I'm not coming down here again.
You're here to get me out of Sona.
Are you surprised?
It's just that it's gonna be a bit difficult
getting me out of this hole.
Seeing as if I go above ground
and another inmate spots me,
I'm a dead man.
There's a, there's a slight misunderstanding
that I have with the mayor...
You know what? It's none of my business.
I'll come back and get you when the time is right.
I may not make it that long.
That's your problem, my friend.
I've got problems of my own.
So you work for these people?
The ones that want me out of Sona.
Look, just stay put.
As long as no one knowsyou're here,
you should be safe.
I'll be back.
Why do they want meout of here so badly,
can you at least tell me that?
Is this the part where you pretend you're innocent?
Just a pawn in all this?
If they told you anything about me before you came here,
you'd know that to be true.
I just want to know what they want with me.
Stay put.
In an effort to save some time,
I'm gonna have to insist
that we just skip right past all the threats I know
you're prepared to layout.
Should anything happen to Sara to LJ,
you will scour the Earth and hunt me down
and rip my heart from my chest
and bup, bup, bup.
I absolutely know how you feel,
as would I, okay?
So that's done.
On to business.
Did you brother get the message?
Good. You and I will meet here every day.
I'll want a full report of the prior day's progress.
When I call your cell phone, answer.
Don't ask me stupid questions.
Don't waste my time.
Get a plan together.
Execute it.
LJ and Sara will be traded for Whistler.
Are we clear?
I want a picture of my son and Sara to prove they're alive.
Fine. I can do that, next.
Why us?
I'll answer that question
so we can put it to bed and you can focus on your work.
There's a political spotlight on Whistler
due to the nature of his crime.
Raids, bribes, what have you,
are not an option.
We have to go in through the back door, so to speak.
This can't be done in a week.
You have a week. That's it.
Are we clear?
What's your name?
Susan B. Anthony.
I'm assuming you weren't
born by immaculate conception.
You're right, Lincoln.
Family trees being what they are,
moms, da, brothers, sisters.
Anything happens to my son or Sara,
I'm not coming after you, Susan.
Get to work.
His man knocks over the water!
Now, didn't you see how Lechero just walked away?!
He doesn't care about us!
He doesn't give a damn!
Living like a king up there!
Come out, what are you, afraid?!
Come on!
Lechero, come out!
Por favor.
Por favor. Vete.
Vete, perro.
Why you so interested about that guy down there?
No reason.
Then why you whispering, college boy?
Why don't you lower your voice already?
What's in it for me? I'm sorry.
Do you have any other friends in here besides me?
I'm it.
Friends don't let friends go hungry and thirsty All right.
All right. and damn near half-naked.
I said "all right;" I'll take care of it! When?
When I can.
What's the big deal?
Why's he hiding?
Who's he hiding from?
Mayor get message to Lechero
saying if Whistler guy gets killed here in Sona,
whoever kills him gets to go to court,
gets to see a judge.
Judge friendly with mayor.
Kill him, and-and
then you get to get out of here and be free?
That's what Lechero say.
This'll stay between me and you.
If your friend wanted you to know, why didn't he tell you?
Cause... 'cause you and I are friends now.
Unless you want to be enemies.
Friends.
Good. Me, too.
Sucre?
Sucre, get me out of here, please.
Where's Maricruz?
Yeah.
Yeah, Maricruz-- she's good, she's okay,
but-but not telling you anything
until you get me out of here.
Tell me where she is right now!
You shoot me, you'll end up inside this hellhole.
I'm done.
I don't care anymore.
I can only guess she's dead by now,
so you're dying with her.
I never had her!
At that house in Mexico,
I chased your aunt and Maricruz off.
I told them I'd lock 'em up
for accessory if they didn't hightail it.
I swear to God.
And the crucifix?
I ripped it off
Maricruz before she ran.
There was no phone in that dump, so I knew you wouldn't
be able to call from the road to...
to make sure I wasn't lying.
I-I conned you.
So...
so Maricruz is...
She's picking grapes.
I have no idea.
Now, just lower the barrel.
Put the gun down.
Now, I came clean with you and helped you out,
right, buddy?
So you got to return the favor.
Call my mom in Joliet-- Edna Bellick.
She's listed. Sucre?
I never laid a hand on Maricruz.
I would never do that!
Sucre, help me, please!
Sucre, help me!
Help me!
Oh, man.
Oh.
Hey.
You find Whistler?
Yeah.
What's his story?
I don't know, and maybe
it's better that way, huh?
I just got
to get him out of here, right?
Come on, man, come on.
We got to keep moving, we got to keep moving.
What's the next play?
Whistler got a note out
on a dead body yesterday.
I don't know what it means or who it's for.
But we need all the leverage we can get,
and, uh...
I need some money.
No one's ever broken out of this place before,
let alone with a week to plan it,
so...
you tell these people, whoever it is that took Sara
and my nephew...
you tell them I get it,
and I'm going to do everything I can.
I'm going to break this guy out of here,
or I'm going to die trying.
And if it's the latter,
then that should count for something, right?
Th's got to count for something.
You tell them that.
I will.
Tell them.
I'd trade places with you in a second.
I know.
Whistler?
You're not safe here.
I can take you someplace that is.
If you're here to help me,
then just leave me alone.
Please.
Sucre?
Linc!
What are you doing here?
Michael's locked up.
For what?
I don't know. I'm sorting it through.
I could use your help.
We're in a... we're in a bad spot.
Uh, I feel for you, man, but I'm done with bad spots, Linc.
I'm going to go see Maricruz.
I just talked to my cousin Petey,
and he told me she's back over in Chicago.
Hey, you're still wanted in Chicago, remember?
I'll figure something out.
All right.
If you change your mind, I'm staying at the Plaza del Sol.
I won't. I'm-I'm out of here, bro.
I'm going to go see my girl.
Listen to me. The innocent people in your life--
you got to keep them innocent-- if that means walking away
from them, that's what you got to do.
Good luck, Linc.
Banco de Versailles, por favor.
Have we had our laughs with him yet?
He's useless, man.
You want to get rid of him?
Huh? Then you cut the mango. Huh?
You caused me
a big, big problem out there today!
You understand that?
Now there's no more water.
They'll live.
Oh, yeah?
They'll live?
Yeah? Well, you tell them that, then.
Hey, come out, Your Majesty.
Teodoro!
Are you scared of...
little people like us?
There's water here.
Give each man a little, hey?
At once.
The kings have their heads chopped off.
Hey, Lechero!
Don't worry about us!
We're fine!
He may have ruled the streets
out there, but in here,
he's just like us.
Just like us!
Come out!
What, are you afraid?
Come and look at me!
Come on!
Lechero, come out.
The American in his underwear-- you seen him?
T-Bag.
Boy, you're going to be drinking your own urine
before you get any of this.
I just need to speak to Señor Lechero, please?
Why don't you do yourself a favor-- scamper.
But I got something. Oh, yeah.
You got yourself the untouchable status.
Get myself killed just talking to your mangy ass.
Andale.
But I got information.
Good information.
Are you out of your mind, huh?
Hey! Hey! Hey! He's got info.
Pick a... pick a kneecap, huh?
I got information! I just want food and clothing.
Patron, please.
Hold on. Hold on!
This better be informative.
Or it's your kneecap next.
This morning, before that whole, uh, water thing,
I, I heard you and the lads talking
about that Whistler character, how ne's found him.
Well...
I just want food and clothing...
Just tell him, idiot!
There's a guy hiding
down in the sewers.
I-I figure he's hiding from you, right,
because you run this place, right?
And so I figured you'd want to know everything
goes on here, so...
Fine, shut up.
It just might be Whistler, si, patron?
¿Si?
Is he Australian?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Courtesy of the Lechero's munificence.
All right, now, y'all need to back up a tad now.
Hey.
How long you been in Sona?
Three years.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
And as far as you know,
no one's ever broken out of this place except,
uh... except maybe this Whistler guy?
You Americans ask a lot of questions.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Come on. Please.
Come on! I have a family.
S-So do I.
Come on.
Stop!
Stop, okay?
Just...
He's coming with me.
Just back up, Michael. Just...
You don't actually think that killing somebody
is going to help you get out of here, do you?
That does seem pretty strange, doesn't it?
But this is a really strange place,
one I want to get out of.
Then I'll help you.
I'll testify for you,
whatever it takes. Wow.
Wow, look at that halo
that just appeared above your head.
It's amazing.
I don't have a choice, Alex... What'd you tell me
yesterday?
What did you tell me yesterday?
Huh? "You're on your own, Alex."
Back up. Back up!
You...
you don't want this.
Let me help you, Alex.
Hey, your majesty!
You got to shut him up.
Come on!
I need this bolson to call me back.
I need to talk to you.
Don't ever walk in here
without being called! I'm sorry.
But it's worth the breach in etiquette.
Is it now?
I thought you could use my help.
There are ways I can be of assistance.
No.
Whistler don't mean
nothing to me, man.
I have five consecutive life sentences-- I ain't coming out
of Sona no time soon.
And why should I deprive other men of chance at freedom?
Huh? I need you to trust me.
Oh.
Trust you?
I don't know you good enough, brother.
Teodoro.
Si, patron?
Can I trust this bobo?
He's a snake.
He stabbed me
in the back every chance he got.
A snake who stab a man in the back.
I never hear of such a creature before.
We got to stop this!
Just give me two more minutes.
Leave now!
Leave!
Crumbs!
That's what you're giving us!
Your crumbs!
Hey, Lechero,
how's your television?
How's your whore?
Come on, what are you scared of?
Hey.
I need some, uh, some moonshine.
Moonshine? Or some alcohol.
Booze.
Booze, yeah.
I need it now. A liter or a gallon--
whatever you can get your hands on.
It's not good time for party, bro.
Bring it to me in my cell.
Vamonos.
Come on, Whistler.
What are you...
Whistler, stop!
Stop!
What are you...
Whistler...
Just come up top with me.
You got
a better chance coming up with me.
At least you can plead your case to Lechero.
Just get...
Go to hell.
Just...
His best batch, he say.
It's fine.
I'm going to need some plastic bags.
You didn't get it for to party, did you?
Plastic bags, as many as you can get.
I'll make it worth your while, I promise.
Gracias.
Excuse me?
You speak English?
Yeah.
We've met.
I mean I saw you yesterday at, uh,
Sona
Yeah. You know, uh,
you could lose the whole grieving widow thing.
You're Whistler's girl, right?
I'm sorry, I have to be somewhere.
I've got, uh, I got to do something, all right?
Do what?
Give me that back
or I'll call the police.
You're not going to call the police.
Why does he want this?
I don't know.
He's just a fisherman.
A fisherman?
Well, tell your fisherman friend...
tell your fisherman friend Scofield's brother has this.
Why won't you people
just leave him alone?!
You think we want to be forced into this?
You think we want to be here, lady?
Forced into what?
What are you talking about?
All right, hold this.
Hold it.
Watch the hallway for me.
I'm friends with everybody here, bro.
That's how I keep alive.
You and I are friends, right?
Yeah, but looks like you got enemies.
What I did for you, getting you those things...
No one will ever know.
Lechero! Lechero!
Whoo!
Stand up, stand up.
Stand up.
Come on.
Back up! Back up.
You can have him,
but two of you will die in the process.
You first? You first. I'll wrap this right around your head.
Move. Move!
Lechero!
Lechero! Lechero!
Enough!
Let me go down there.
Let me cut just one throat.
Just one.
And then regroup later
with a real reason
to come after you. Shut your mouth.
He's right,
Sammy.
Lechero! Lechero! Lechero!
So, what we going to do, boss, huh?
We just going to sit up here,
hope they run out of rocks?
Lechero! Lechero!
We have a problem.
What is it?
Ran out of water.
So, you mean you've got a problem.
Look, there was an accident here.
The tank tip over.
My men need water, man.
I'll see if I can get the water truck there day after tomorrow.
No, I need water now!
I guess it's too bad there's no guards
in there anymore with you, huh?
You could
take hostages, have a riot, make demands.
Day aftertomorrow.
Lechero...!
You call me and you raise your voice at me like that
again, you're not going
to see water for two weeks.
Hmm? ¿Entendido?
They got Whistler.
Enough!
Now, I'll decide this!
You'll decide nothing.
You can't deliver, Lechero.
You're done here.
Now what?
What?
What do we do?
You've been outbid.
Wait. What are you talking about?
What are you ta...?
What are you talking...?
That's, uh, very useful.
Very useful.
And Whistler's clear?
Yeah.
Clear as the blue sky, brother.
Hello?
Baby, it's me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I... I've been so scared, I've been praying
every day.
I did, too, babe.
I just thank God youokay.
Petey called me after he had talked to you,
and he said that you might be coming back here?
That's what I told him.
Yeah.
You have to be so careful.
Baby,
I've been thinking, and, um,
the only thing that I...
that I care about right now
is that you and the baby are okay.
That's all that matters to me.
I'm not coming back.
It's not because I don't love you, because
you know I do--
I love you more... I love you more than anything,
but... all I do is bring you down.
I'm no good for you.
That's not true, that's not true.
Oh, it is, it is, it is, and...
sometimes the only way
to protect the people that you love
is... is by staying away from them.
however long that takes-- I'll find you.
I'll find you, and, uh,
and I'll make you and our baby proud.
Te lo prometo.
Te lo prometo, mi amor.
I wish we could go back.
I would give anything to go back.
I wish that, too.
I wish that, too, baby.
I love you so much, baby.
I love you, too, baby.
Good-bye.
Bye.
You know, they told me that your brother
got all the brains,
but I didn't realize you were this stupid.
What do you want, Susan?
No sooner do I tell you to stick to the plan,
than you go and hassle Whistler's girlfriend.
You need to quit
playing Sherlock Holmes and leave her alone.
Why?
'Cause I said so.
How about that? All right.
How about you beat it, so I can get to work?
I will
as soon as you give me what you took from her.
I took nothing from her. I got a gallon
of bleach, a tarp and a hacksaw in the trunk of my car.
One hour, tops--
you're off the face of the earth.
It's just a bird guide.
I am not going to ask you again.
Toss it.
Tomorrow-- bar.
Progress report. I will be waiting.
(footsteps approaching, man gasping)
So it's water you want.
Here's your water.
Thank you.
So, how are we getting out of here?
I have no idea.
Captioning sponsored by 20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and VOLKSWAGEN.
Closed captioning is brought to
you in part by Maple Leaf
Simply Fresh.Refrigerated
entrees, never frozen, and
found near your grocers deli.
Its a revolution in food!
ro
www.tvsubtitles.net