Previously on Prison Break...
What are you doing?
You know I have what you need
and I'll give you the rest
after I know that Sofia, L.J.
they're all safe.
My book!
Get up!
What's this place?
We'll make the exchange here
on our terms.
An abandoned warehouse 5 miles
down the road.
Be there in 20 minutes with my son.
They must've closed all
the roads out of Panama.
What do we do?
Whistler still claims
he's a fisherman?
If he's not a fisherman, what is he?
I don't care what he says!
I don't know anything about Scofield!
You sure you don't want
to change your story...
I guess this is where I say good-bye.
My truck!
What are we gonna do now?
Do you have a cell phone?
- I lost 'em. Come and pick me up.
- Where are you?
let me guess.
- If anything happens to him...
- That depends, doesn't it?
I'm at the warehouse, like you said.
Where are you?
Chasing your buddy.
Where do you think I am?
Get back here. I have L.J. and Sofia.
I'm ready to do the exchange.
- Call you back.
- What?
- The plan's shot. She's already there.
- OK. So now what?
It took me two weeks
to hook up that warehouse.
- We'll figure something.
- I was trying to fix this.
- You were calling them to pick you up.
- So no one else would get hurt!
You really think I would
put anyone's life at risk?
You already have.
I can't go back to Sona!
You're not going back to Sona.
Do you want some water?
Or do you want
to tell me where Michael Scofield is?
I don't know where he is.
I knew there was something off
about you from day one.
I guess I just know a
con when I see one.
Maybe you'll get to be
employee of the month.
- I'm waiting.
- There's been a change in venue.
I finally get to talk
to the brains of the outfit.
We're at the Plaza De Francia.
So you're thinking public place,
safety in numbers,
plenty of witnesses to protect you.
I'm thinking public place,
wanted men, police,
lots of witnesses to identify you.
Plaza de Francia. Ten minutes.
Round everyone up.
Subtitles: swsub.com
It's anarchy in here!
We gotta hide!
- I gotta help him.
- He's the most hated person in here.
- If we're around him again, we'll...
- He gave me a home!
He gave me third-degree burns
down my back! He can go to hell!
I owe him this much.
You don't want to help, then don't.
Get outta here! Shoo fly...
Just a few more steps, only a few more.
Then it's home, sweet home.
This is my house!
Easy, now.
Get out!
- He's gonna get us killed.
- He's gonna get us out of here.
What can I get you?
Club soda.
You been to Panama before?
First time.
What did you do back, in the states?
I'm in sort of a transitional period
right now.
In between jobs.
Sorry to hear that.
Yeah, we've all been there.
I'm sure something will come up
before long.
I'm hoping
it's right around the corner.
You're gonna give me some real
information on Michael Scofield.
Or it's gonna be your funeral.
I don't know where he is.
I don't know how to reach him, I swear.
Which one is it gonna be, papi?
- Hello, Gretchen.
- Where's Whistler?
Over my right shoulder.
You know, you're the first
to ever break out of Sona?
Where are they?
Bring them out.
I've worked with a lot of intelligent
people in this business, but you...
You wouldn't have to worry
about the company
trying to kill you if you were
on their side. They certainly pay well.
There they are.
Give me Whistler
and I will give you L.J.
If you move, you're dead.
- It for hand-off.
- Roger that.
- What is he doing?
- I lost him.
It's not the point of the exchange.
Just a confirmation
- that everyone's still alive.
- They're alive. Let's trade.
You'll get a call in five minutes
telling you where to go next.
And when the exchange
is over and L.J. is safe,
you and I are gonna
spend some quality time.
When the exchange is over,
you better run for your life.
Gracias, papa.
One more stop.
There's a storm brewing
out there in the yard.
You tell them come in.
I'm not scared.
Well, I am.
You might want to put that down.
You're the last one
I'd expect to see at my side.
I take offense, patròn.
I've had many foot-washers.
Many men have come in
with sheep's clothing,
only to let the wolf come out.
I am not trying to hurt you.
I am trying to save you.
Save me?
I'm gonna die here.
Your life is in jeopardy
just being with me.
Not necessarily.
As I was being escorted
back inside today, one of the guards
offered us
a chance to buy our freedom.
If a guard spoke to you, he was lying.
It's impossible to get out.
maybe you've been
too busy dying to notice,
but there's a new colonel outside.
Little Suzy Sona ain't playing so hard
to get no more. She has her price.
- And we gonna need some money.
- No.
Then you will die in here.
The lobby of the museum of antiquities.
- Why?
- Because that's where Whistler is.
You're overthinking things.
I've seen it too many times before.
The 1st plan goes to hell,
then you start tap-dancing,
and, trust me, it always ends badly.
You have five minutes.
Unbelievable.
You know what to do.
- What's so funny?
- You.
Thinking you can outsmart my uncle.
Walk.
Metal detectors.
I thought we were
building a circle of trust.
Come to the southwest
corner of the first floor.
Fine.
But that's it.
No more stops on your guided tour.
If I don't walk out of here
with Whistler, I'm gonna snap LJ's neck.
And yes, I can do it.
Here we go.
- Is everyone in position?
- Roger that.
It's the last bottle of rum.
Good-bye, patròn.
How much do they want?
50,000.
We're not in Tijuana
haggling over a blanket.
We're talking about your life!
Even if I could...
find the money, who could
I trust to bring it in?
There is one person.
- How do you know James?
- You're working my last nerve. Move.
Everybody stays cool and we
will all walk out of here.
As soon as we get LJ,
you get Whistler.
But LJ comes to us first.
Go ahead.
Thank God, you're safe.
What about the coordinates?
You said first thing you would do
once you had Whistler was to get
the rest of the coordinates.
Is she serious?
I'll give her exactly what she
wants when we get out of here.
- But it's not safe. We need to go.
- I want to see them.
Sofia, come on.
- Let's get outta here.
- Wait...
You wrote those numbers
on a piece of paper.
You gave her half at Sona and said
you'd give her the other half now.
I know, and we'll discuss it later.
Welcome to the real world.
I'm sick of keeping your princess
- in a bubble. Let's go!
- This is between us.
- Where are the coordinates?
- There are no coordinates.
Come on.
Stop kidding yourself.
It's time to leave.
And what are you still doing here?
If I were you and I couldn't
bring weapons inside,
I'd have agents at every exit ready
to shoot as soon as we stepped outside.
Then it really doesn't
matter what exit you take, does it?
I'm gonna go out that door.
Maybe you should take that door.
Actually, that door is locked
in the event of an emergency.
- What emergency?
- This one.
We're all walking out of here.
Together.
That's very dramatic,
calling the cops on yourself.
You wanna go back to Sona?
They're not looking for a con,
they're looking for a thief.
Whatever I told you, it
was always to protect you.
You'll understand,
if you just let me explain.
All this because I knew Scofield?
- Tell me where he is.
- I don't know!
Even if I knew...
All right.
It'll be here shortly.
Now that we have the money,
how do we get it to the guard?
We don't.
What do you mean?
We were supposed
to bribe the guard, that was the plan!
This is the plan.
This is business.
And you, of all people,
should understand.
- Help me hold him down.
- What the hell you talking about?
Do it.
It's just a matter of time, anyway.
But from one thief to another...
out of respect,
make it quick.
If you don't fight me,
I will.
Adios, homey.
Over here.
- What's the problem?
- I found this in his pocket.
- Would you care to explain this?
- I've got no idea what it is.
It's plastic. It's from the gift shop.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
- What?
- Stay where you are.
- Why?
- Where is your identification?
Dad, dad... you can't do this.
You can't do this. The cops'll start
asking questions. We gotta go.
Go, I'm not leaving.
What are you gonna do, James?
You go back there, you'll get arrested,
and that won't do any of us any good.
I ought to kill you right now
for what you did to her!
Enough!
I did what I had to do
to get you out, period!
You remember what's at stake, James.
We're moving.
Stop the van. I can't leave her.
She already left you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Dad, you've got to go!
I'll stay with her! I promise.
You've got to go. Dad?
Could I get some help?
Do you have everything?
The book is gone.
What do you mean, gone?
Is it true?
- he's really...
- Yeah.
How do you want me to give you this?
The guards,
they won't let me in anymore.
I only want what I asked for.
Hold on to the rest for a few days.
If you were to consider
leaving with all that...
I just want you to know
I'd be very cross with you.
I've been known to have a
bit of a temper problem...
when betrayed.
A deal's a deal.
You've done so much for me.
You have my word.
Wait.
It's okay.
I'll wait for you.
You ready?
I'm all right.
Where is Michael Scofield?
If it's him...
you're gonna find out where
they are, or I'm gonna answer it myself,
so they can hear you scream
when I blow your head off.
Sucre. Thank God.
- When you didn't show up at the boat...
- I'm really sorry about that, papi.
I got into a little bit
of trouble at work.
Are you all right?
- Where are you?
- You guys get L.J?
Yeah. He's fine.
What about Linc? Is he okay?
He's fine.
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm fine.
It all worked out.
I'm about to catch the bus, papi.
Take care.
Kill me if you want.
No, papi.
You're gonna wish we had.
Lechero is dead!
I come before you now to bury the man.
Not to praise him,
for there is nothing
praiseworthy about his rule here.
Having one of our own dictate to us?
That's just not the natural order.
All cons
are equal!
I have the last remnants...
of Lechero's cruel empire
in my hand.
An empire which I...
willingly participated in
and witnessed first-hand.
Money...
made off of your backs
and off the backs of your family!
It's yours.
And I'm here to tell you
I'm giving it back.
Welcome home, papi.
- She's gonna be okay.
- Good.
Uncle Mike...
I wanted to wait
until we were safe to do this, but...
but...
I found this in the room
where Sara and I were held.
I thought you might want to have it.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
How's Sofia doing?
- She's good.
- Good.
The cops will be leaving soon.
- You can go up and see her, then.
- Good.
She wanted me to tell you something.
She said there's something in
her apartment underneath her bed.
- Something about Whistler.
- I'm not interested.
What is it?
This is over. It's done.
I said, "what is it?"
You're late.
And you owe him for my drinks.
Give us a minute?
Nice tip.
She handles the money.
You in?
She'd better be able to handle
a lot more than that.
Because if she has done what
you think she has...
Sara...
she's the weak link.
And he will find her.
And then Scofield will find you...
and me.
And I'm not paying for your mess.
Are you in or are you out?
I'm in.
I need your gun.
"Jason Lief."
You heard of this guy?
No, but if he's important to Whistler,
he's important to me.
Slow down.
I get to Whistler, I get to Gretchen.
This is the one chance we have
of sticking toge...
They killed Sara.
I'm sorry about that.
I know...
Listen, man...
I did everything I could, you know.
- Everything.
- I know you did.
But I gotta go.
www.tvsubtitles.net