My name is Michael Scofield.
My brother is facing
the electric chair,
framed for a crime
he didn't commit.
What is it about this case that the
Secret Service is so interested in?
The man killed the vice
president's brother.
After his appeals
were exhausted,
I knew there was only
one way to get him out.
This is the police.
Put down your weapon!
Michael.
- I'm getting you out of here.
- It's impossible.
Not if you designed the place,
it isn't.
Have you seen the blueprints?
Better than that.
I've got them on me.
I've been at Fox River
nearly a month now.
In that time,
I've assembled a group that
has all the resources we
need to not only break out,
but to stay out.
I'm Michael, by the way.
- Dr. Tancr...
- Tancredi like the governor?
While we dig on the inside,
our lawyer searches for
the truth on the outside.
I have information that will lead to
the exoneration of Lincoln Burrows.
Somebody on the inside claims
they can exonerate Lincoln.
Someone's been talking.
Anyone that's a
threat is expendable.
They're ready for you,
Madam Vice President.
24 hours from now,
my brother is scheduled to die,
but the way I see it,
24 hours from now,
we'll be out of the country.
It's there.
It can't be done.
We're not getting out of here.
Unfortunately, Pretty,
that ain't an option.
You are gonna get
us out of here.
Unless you're gonna use your
shank to take out the pipe,
put it away.
I'll put it in your neck,
you don't get us out of here.
- Bring it down a peg, T-Bag.
- Shut your mouth!
Remember, Pretty,
I am serving life plus one.
So if I get busted
for attempted escape,
I'm gonna throw in a homicide,
no problem.
That's like a
parking ticket to me.
- You okay?
- Felt sick again.
Yeah, you took your I.V.s out.
Yeah, I didn't want to throw up on the
floor, so I just came to the drain.
Just let me walk this off.
I'll be fine.
Lincoln, there is no reason for you
to be here if your I.V. isn't in.
Everything all right in here?
It's fine.
Why isn't he cuffed
to the table?
What's he gonna do,
steal a cotton ball?
Can't have him walking around, Doc.
You know that.
What was that?
Put your wrist out.
You gonna turn this
into something?
I'm not gonna say it again.
Put your wrist out.
Hey, Keith,
come check this out!
Keith?
We got to go. Now.
Give me the rope.
Give me the rope now!
Tie that off.
Okay, I'm down.
We got to go, Michael.
It's done. Let's go.
Did it break off or
did someone break it?
I don't know.
Here's the other half.
Hey, hey. What's up, Brad?
Heading over to Sharkey's.
It's two-fer Tuesday.
- Want to hoist a few?
- Man, I'd love to,
but my wife is cooking dinner,
and I told her I'd be home.
Wuss. Anybody else?
Suit yourselves.
Hey, none of the Sheetrock in front
of the break room's been touched.
Ah, the P.I.'s
letting it dry out.
Still?
- Westmoreland!
- I'm caught on something.
Come on! Come on!
Stay there. Stay down there.
Why was this door locked?
Wasn't locked, boss.
The fan kept pushing it open,
so we just had to wedge it closed.
You've been in here all
night not doing a damn thing.
Room is still wet, boss.
Nothing we could do.
It's not like we were
having a picnic.
Bunch of shiftless,
no-good convicts.
You got something
to say, Scofield?
Wrap it up.
And all four of you,
get your asses back to the block.
Hey. Get these nitwits
back to the cell block.
You seem to be one light.
Right here, boss.
Oh, no. No way!
I should be halfway to
seeing my family right now!
Let's go.
Now!
Keep it moving.
Move it! Let's go, ladies!
You think he knows?
L incoln.
I'm here with Henry Pope, who is the
warden of Fox River Penitentiary,
where Lincoln Burrows is scheduled to
die by electrocution at 12:01
a.m. tomorrow.
Warden Pope, can you tell me what's
going to happen in the next few hours?
There are strict Department
of Corrections guidelines
that govern every
aspect of an execution.
Measures taken to make sure that the
process goes as smoothly as possible.
Such as?
The  correctional officers
will do a walk-through.
We'll review the
list of witnesses.
The chair will be checked and re-checked
to make sure there's no problem.
And Mr. Burrows himself?
Have you spoken with him?
What are his thoughts
in these final hours?
I'd say that's between
him and his God.
And maybe the governor.
I understand Burrows' attorneys
are going to request a stay.
I wish them the best of luck.
Does that mean you
believe he's innocent?
It means...
I believe in the process,
but I don't relish the prospect
of taking another man's life.
Whether it's just or not, there's
no joy that lies before us today.
Okay, thank you
very much Warden.
And we will be here with
you throughout the night
watching and waiting to see if
Lincoln Burrows does, in fact,
become only the 13th person to be
executed in the State of Illinois
since 1976.
Just so you got one less
thing to worry about,
I want you to know
I ain't mad at you.
Thank you.
- How long until...
- 16 hours.
Are his lawyers
making any progress?
Is there still a
chance with that?
No. There's only one person who
can really stop this execution.
I need to see my brother.
Just to talk, for five minutes.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll try.
Hey.
Um... I'm sorry.
I'm told that you have to
wait until final visitation.
Would you talk to your
father for me? Please?
Believe me, my father knows where
I stand on the death penalty,
and I'm just as clear
on his stance...
Sara, uh, Dr.
Tancredi, I'm sorry. Um...
This isn't about the morality
of the death penalty.
This is...
This is about killing an innocent man:
my brother.
And, surely,
your father can't be in favor of that.
Just talk to Lincoln's attorneys,
just for an hour,
and I swear to God,
you'll be convinced of his innocence.
Michael, I would pick
up the phone right now
if I thought there was any chance
that I could make a difference.
But you have to understand.
I'm the last person in the
world that my father listens to.
He hates what I do,
he hates what I believe in.
And if I'm the one asking for
clemency for your brother,
your brother won't get it.
I'm sorry.
Look, if Terrence Steadman
is still alive, Lyle,
then it can't be Terrence
Steadman buried in the ground.
Yeah, but a secret informant claims
that Steadman is still alive?
I don't know, Nick,
it all sounds pretty far-fetched.
You're  his clerk,
just get us on the docket.
Nick, you're asking him to
commit political suicide
by granting a stay of execution to
Illinois' most notorious death
row inmate.
Officially, all we're asking
is for an exhumation order.
If he grants it, he can order a
stay until the tests are come in.
An exhumation order?
Well that's better-- digging up the
vice president's brother. No way.
Lyle, Lyle, look, we took Intro
to Civ Pro together, remember?
We studied for the bar,
day and night,
in that crappy little
apartment of yours,
talking about how we're
going to make a difference.
Nick, you filed an
eleventh hour motion,
and Judge Kessler's docket
is full this afternoon...
Come on, Lyle,
everyone knows you run that courtroom.
You can't adjust
things around a bit?
The informant that was killed yesterday?
I was there.
I know firsthand these people
will do whatever they can
to frame Lincoln for
Steadman's murder.
All we're asking
is to be heard.
I'll give you 15 minutes
this afternoon-- that's it!
- Thank you, thank you!
- Yeah, you're welcome.
He doesn't even
know what happened.
- He knows you tried.
- Do you think so?
He's your brother;
he knows you, so yes.
I promised I would
get him out of here.
You promised a lot
of people, Pretty.
- Enough, man, all right?
- This don't concern you, boy.
You don't get a man's hopes up
like that, and then just...
Back up or I'll beat your
skinny ass into the ground.
And it wouldn't
take much to do it.
All right, ladies, Rec time's over;
back on the block!
You owe me a ticket
out of here, Pretty.
And I will collect.
I'm really am sorry
about your brother.
Thanks.
Look, I know you were
counting on this, so...
Let me worry about my problems.
I know you've got enough
on your mind right now.
For what it's worth,
over the years, I've known
a few men who've sat on that chair,
and as the day gets near,
all you can really do
is pray it goes quick.
Once, about ten years ago,
there was a man caught a few sparks,
not enough to do the job.
Had to wait another three weeks
while they reset the whole process.
It may sound crazy, but he said it
was the worst three weeks of his life,
'cause it not the lightning that
kills you... it's the wait.
So take solace in the fact that
your brother's wait is over.
So if something
happens to the chair,
he's got three more weeks?
There's a lot of protocol
in killing a man.
A new death warrant,
another medical clearance...
A lot can happen
in three weeks.
- Yo, what the grapes, yo?
- Thanks.
- What y'all talking about?
- Nothing.
Keep it together, come on!
Go! Keep it together!
I'm going in.
It's daytime.
I'll hang a sheet.
Do you have any
questions about...
what's going to happen tonight?
When I get to eat,
where I'm supposed to walk,
how it's gonna feel when
they tighten the belts...
Any of that gonna
help come midnight?
Some feel it's best
to be prepared.
- How's Michael?
- He's anxious to see you.
Unfortunately, we've been told that
that's not possible until
final visitation.
You've been through
this before?
No.
Just so you know,
a doctor needs to be present, so,
for what it's worth,
I'll be there tonight.
- Can I ask a favor?
- Yeah. What?
When I'm gone, can you...
Will you look out
for my brother?
What were you doing back there?
Hmm. So you like
doing that, too?
Dipping  the fry in a shake?
Hells yeah.
Mmm. Good times. Good times.
So what's going on out there?
Nothing, you know?
Just staying out of trouble.
I meant in terms of any...
"office gossip" you might have for me.
So check it. This one fool has
been trying to cop a joint.
So I'll keep ear
hustling for that.
We had an agreement.
You were supposed to bird-dog
Scofield and get back to me.
I been trying, man,
I've been working the corners. Trust me.
I ain't got nothing.
I seen you talking to him
in the yard and the geezer.
Yeah, I talked to Scofield
but he ain't told me nothing.
Then it's a hundred bucks
for the burger and fries.
Boss, you know I
ain't got no money.
Then you better start
selling your ass.
A hundred bucks by
the end of this shift,
or there's gonna be a bidding war to
see who gets you as their new cellie.
Beat it.
In the yard today,
I did hear Scofield say something.
And?
He said if something goes
wrong with the chair,
his brother gets three
more weeks to live.
We're square. Get out of here.
- How is it going in here?
- Ready for liftoff.
- Chair's working?
- Yeah. Why?
- Run a test.
- Already did.
The electrical contractor signed
off on the diagnostic this morning.
- We're good to go.
- Run it again.
Why?
Run it.
It ain't working.
Son of a bitch.
I don't know what could have happened.
So once they redo all the paperwork,
your brother gets three more weeks.
- Right.
- So we got time.
Not a lot, but some.
Are we still going
through the infirmary?
If  I corrode that pipe again,
they'll know something's up.
You got another way?
Right now, I'm just worried
about getting through tonight.
Careful, there's 2,000 volts
running through that thing.
Oh, God.
Give me the strength to walk...
Give the strength to walk...
I want to see my brother.
When we move you to
Final Visitation.
- When's that?
- Right after we do this.
Just...
It's your last day, Linc.
I'd prefer to keep you out of
cuffs as much as possible, but
I need some assurances.
You've always been
straight-up with me, Stolte.
You have my word.
Your Honor, from the outset, Mr.
Burrows' case has been tainted by
a conspiracy characterized
by destruction of evidence,
distortion of the truth,
and witness intimidation.
Again, Judge, I have to object.
These are some serious accusations
with absolutely no proof.
No proof? What have I been
arguing for the past 20 minutes?
You got me.
Judge Kessler, Mr.
Tucci might not appreciate the weight
of what we've just presented,
but surely you must.
As Ms. Donovan stated,
a top video forensic analyst
has disputed the authenticity
of a surveillance tape
that was the key piece of evidence
in convicting Lincoln Burrows.
That's the tape that no
longer exists, right?
Because your client
had it destroyed.
Unless my client is a rusted water
pipe in the County Records office,
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
Judge, Ms.
Donovan's apartment was blown up
in an attempt to
silence both her and me.
That was independently corroborated
as a gas leak, Your Honor.
Judge, a month ago,
a Secret Service agent named Paul
Kellerman visited my office.
I saw Kellerman last night, when he shot
and killed another agent, Daniel Hale,
right after Hale told me that
Terrence Steadman was alive and well.
Your Honor,
I'm presenting to the clerk an affidavit
from the Director of the
Secret Service agency.
It states that at no
time has there ever been
an agent of that organization by the
name of Paul Kellerman, or Daniel Hale.
In addition, there were no other
witnesses to this shooting.
pÑNo bullets were found,
no blood, no shell casings.
The only witness to this alleged
murder is Veronica Donovan,
Lincoln Burrows' ex-girlfriend.
Now, Your Honor,
I feel for Ms. Donovan.
- Save it.
- I do.
But desperation causes
desperate acts.
And  that's what we're seeing here today,
Your Honor.
My client, the Vice President
of the United States...
Judge Kessler...
Do either of you have any
evidence that is admissible?
Even just tangible?
Your claims, if true,
are terrifying.
But anything, or anyone,
that could verify your story is either
gone, missing or dead.
I know time is of the essence.
I'll reserve judgment for now.
I'll take your arguments
into consideration,
and I'll have a decision
within a few hours.
These little bastards are the bane
of my existence, I swear to God.
You get this a lot?
Yeah, they're attracted to
the heat when they're cold,
plus, they got collapsible
vertebrae or some deal,
so they can squeeze through a crack
yea big, if they're determined.
And he shorted the wire
just by biting on it?
Not by chewing on
the wire alone,
but if the tail touches metal,
it acts as a ground,
and boom, fuse pops.
- Along with the rat.
- I'll be damned.
So, can you change the fuse?
Yeah, there's another one
right here in the box.
Can do it now?
Right after I notify the State
and fill out the paperwork.
Now, hold up a minute, you two.
Both of you.
We're gonna give more time
to a guy who killed the
Vice President's brother?
This guy's a terrorist.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Forget about losing our jobs,
we could all face charges.
Only the three of us know.
Real easy to keep it that way.
It's your guys' call.
- How much longer?
- Six hours.
Open on 40!
Scofield, your brother's gonna be
transported to Final Visitation soon.
You can meet him there.
You look surprised.
You knew it was
scheduled today.
No, I...
You were saying?
They'll be transporting you to
Final Visitation in a minute.
Thanks for keeping
your word, Linc.
Linc, you're gonna have
to change into these.
What's that?
At the moment of death,
the body becomes incontinent, so...
- It's a diaper?
- Yeah.
You need to wear it.
Make me.
It's a good look, huh?
It's, uh, for the electricity.
Hair gets in the
way or something.
I did everything I could.
I know you did.
Last time I had my head shaved
was when I was running with Derek.
- Remember Derek?
- Uh, yeah.
Bet me 40 bucks I wouldn't shave it.
I said, make it 100.
Still owes me.
- Have you heard from Veronica?
- She's supposed to be coming.
Is there any news on the appeal?
'Cause there could still be a chance...
Stop it. Michael, please.
This thing's gonna happen.
I got to get my head straight.
Let's just share memories,
swap stories,
talk about the damn weather,
anything but torturing myself
with the idea of hope.
I can't take it anymore.
All right.
- You can't go, LJ.
- I don't care.
I have to see him.
You can't go to the prison.
You'll never make it through the gate.
There will be cops everywhere.
Look, you got to wait until we get
all this cleared up, all right?
It's the judge's clerk.
Lyle, what do you got?
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
They ruled against us.
Yeah.
I'm going to go and see him.
I'm going to stay here with LJ.
You gonna be okay going alone?
Yeah, I'm going to be fine.
Tell Lincoln...
you know, just, we tried.
Go to the back room. Go!
You're the attorneys
for Lincoln Burrows?
You letting me win, Michael?
No.
Mm-hmm. Show me your cards.
- I'm not going to show you my cards.
- Show me your cards.
- Give me your cards.
Gin.
Funny, that.
Three out of five.
How often would you
make those for LJ?
Whenever I had him on weekends.
Maybe the only decent
thing I ever did for him.
No. You were there for him.
Not enough.
I don't know how they can
stomach stuff before...
We lost the appeal.
Your friend Sara
came by, though.
- Did she hear you out?
- She did.
Is she going to
talk to her father?
I sure as hell hope so.
It doesn't matter
any more, guys.
You've done more
than enough for me.
That's the most
important thing.
I couldn't bring LJ.
I know.
I can get him on
the phone, though.
What do I say?
LJ... it's your dad.
- Hey, Dad.
- LJ.
- So, this is it.
- Yeah.
I am... I want you to, uh...
stick with Veronica and Nick and
clear your name. You'll be all right.
I wish I could be there, Dad.
Me, too.
'Cause there's something
I want to tell you.
What's that?
I had a dream last night.
You and me were working on a house,
pounding nails.
And in the dream...
it felt like we were older.
It was so clear.
The whole dream.
And when I woke...
I knew that today wasn't
going to be the end.
That...
That we'll see each
other again, Dad.
I know it.
I love you, Dad.
Those numbers support Burrows' claim
about Terrence Steadman's
pending indictment.
Now, with the related murders,
and then the confidential informant,
I just wanted to make sure that you
were fully aware of the circumstances.
I'm fully acquainted with
the Burrows case, Sara,
but I never heard
about any of this.
Well, I hadn't either until I spoke
with Burrows' attorneys this afternoon.
And I understand that most of this
evidence is technically
considered circumstantial,
but I think you'll agree
it's hard to ignore.
How did you get
involved with all this?
These men are my patients.
It's my job advocate for them.
Come on, Sara, how many of these
guys say that they are innocent?
80, 90 percent?
I mean, it's not like you're asking
me for a new bike here, kid.
Being tough on crime,
capital punishment--
it's all part of a philosophy
that I believe in.
Part of a philosophy that I
campaigned on, was elected for.
I have to go back to Fox River.
I have to be there when
they kill this man.
The least you could do
is review his case.
And, Dad, if it helps...
pretend it didn't come from me.
I've never given a damn about
what people thought of me.
Never.
The last couple of days...
I gotta admit, you know...
Lee Harvey Oswald,
John Wilkes Booth...
Lincoln Burrows.
I'm gonna go down in
history with these freaks.
Bitch of it all is
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it!
It's time.
Warden!
- What is it?
- It's the governor.
Yes, Governor.
Okay.
I understand.
The governor has reviewed
your case fully.
He's not granting clemency.
Let's proceed.
You did your country and
your party a great service.
It won't go unnoticed.
- Thank you, Madame Vice President.
- Thank you, Governor.
Can't go past here.
Once he's in the death chamber,
you'll be escorted to the viewing room.
Can I...
Yeah.
I've loved you since the
first time I saw you.
Uncuff him.
Let's go, son.
- I didn't kill that man, Michael.
- Swear to me.
I swear to you.
Preparation can only
take you so far.
After that,
you got to take a few leaps of faith.
Don't give up on me.
What if something
happens to you?
You just have a little faith.
Just have a little faith.
How about every Sunday,
we have our own special breakfast?
- Just you and me.
- Yeah.
Give me your hand.
You got to have faith, LJ.
I love you, Dad.
I came in here a man.
Give me the strength to
walk out of here a man.
Transcript: Raceman
Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net