Previously on Prison Break.
I'm looking for someone.
A guy named Lincoln Burrows.
The man killed the Vice
President's brother.
Why you want to see
Burrows so bad anyhow?
'Cause he's my brother.
I'm getting you out of here.
It's impossible.
Not if you designed the place,
it isn't.
- You've seen the blueprints?
- Better than that.
I've got them on me.
Nick Savrinn, as of now,
both of you are dead.
This is Bellick.
Our wing has been breached.
Marilyn, no!
The chair isn't the only way to
take a man's life in prison.
What are you doing?
Your father's already in trouble.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Come on.
My first assignments on PI,
we were up here cleaning out toxic mold.
PI didn't go there.
We'd never assign inmates to do that.
Tyler, Robert.
This here must be
your daughter.
It's over!
We don't need him no more.
You're not gonna kill him.
One for the team.
17 days from now they strap my
brother to an electric chair...
Send 50,000 bolts coursing through
his body for a crime he didn't commit.
I'm here to make sure
that doesn't happen.
I've been in Fox River
nearly three weeks now.
In that time, I've managed to
get out the back of my cell
and into the old steam pipes
that run through the prison.
Those pipes are our way out.
Think of this place
like a map of the U.S.
Our cell over there,
that's New York City.
The infirmary, our exit,
that's California.
The pipes beneath our feet
that connect the two...
Route 66.
Our ticket out of here.
I assume we're
doing this at night.
That's right.
We're locked up, Fish,
and your boy is in solitary.
How are we just gonna
fly out of our cages
and right into your cell,
right into New York City?
You're not.
You're gonna meet me half way,
in Saint Louis.
Route 66 runs directly
beneath that building.
It's the only building sitting
on top of those tunnels.
All we gotta do is
get in there on PI...
and dig ourselves an on-ramp.
Shortly after,
we hit the infirmary.
Then we'll be
outside those walls.
What's in there?
It's an old storage room.
Figure John here can pull
all the strings he needs.
It's not that easy, Fish.
That's a restricted area.
I got to be able to
justify it to the bulls
and how it's got to be some
actual work to be done in there
for me to get in there.
You follow?
Then you better figure it out.
'Cause if we don't
get in that room,
we're not getting out of here.
Feeling kind of left out.
New York? California? Saint Louis?
What are we discussing?
Talking baseball, actually.
Now that's a subject I just
happen to know quite a bit about.
What a shame.
The conversation's over.
Really now?
That any way to
treat a teammate?
I'm coming along on this endeavor
whether you like it or not.
'Cause I've got a hell of
a singing voice otherwise.
I won't take that
piece of crap along.
- I won't do it.
- Me neither.
We won't have to.
He'll be out of the picture soon enough.
The state provides
$25,000 insurance,
plus donations from the Illinois
Corrections Officers Foundation.
That's the last thing on
my mind right now, Warden.
Do you know who killed him?
We have some leads.
But I can promise you this:
we are not gonna rest until
we find out what happened.
His pictures are missing.
He had a photo of
our daughter in here.
Not to worry. We'll find them.
I begged him not
to take this job.
Shauna, I am so sorry.
I'll walk you to your car.
Captain.
I need to speak with
you for a second.
I'll meet you in the hallway.
I want the son of a
bitch who did this.
Now you do whatever you
need to do to find him.
You understand?
I've got five boxes.
You want to give me a hand?
Veronica?
That phone call was textbook scare
tactics. That's what they want.
They want to scare us from
doing what they know we can do.
- And what's that?
- Expose them.
This guy bothering you again,
Miss Donovan?
No, Lucasz. The other night was my
fault. It was a misunderstanding.
Okay, but if you
need anything...
Trust me.
You'll be the first person I call.
Here.  Let me.
Those boxes contain seven years
of criminal appellate work.
If there's a precedent
in there somewhere
that can help us suspend Lincoln's
execution, we're gonna find it.
You can just leave those by the door,
Lucasz. I'll bring them in.
Oh, that's okay.
I've got your key right here.
If I didn't know better,
I would say Lucasz was sweet on you.
Very funny.
F ire.
What?
Fire. We burn the place down.
How's that gonna help us?
A few years ago,
the chapel burned down
and the D.O.C.
realized they had some toxic issues--
you know, asbestos,
lead paint, you name it.
They couldn't find a contractor,
so they put the inmates on the job.
We spent like five,
six hours in there at a time.
But the good news is no guards
came around almost at all.
Can you get us in there?
Been doing a little,
uh, thinking.
I'm gonna need a PI card,
aren't I?
I mean that's where this whole
thing is happening, isn't it?
It's on its way.
You're slow-walking me,
aren't you?
Why would I do such a thing?
You think Bellick's gonna pop
me for shanking that C.O. Bob.
Maybe you'll take a little walk
and tell him for yourself, right?
Then, I'll be out of
your hair for good.
Well, I got news for you.
If I go down for killing Bob,
believe me,
I'm gonna take a
little walk of my own.
Tell them about that hole
you got behind your toilet.
So...
how about that PI card?
I don't know if you remember,
but that summer
before fifth grade,
when I stayed with
you a couple weeks,
and you thought I broke
your glass coffee table...
And when you came home,
I denied it.
But you told me you could care
less about the coffee table.
You just didn't want
me lying to you.
And you said I'd feel a lot better
if I just told you the truth.
And you promised
not to be angry.
I remember.
Well, I broke it.
I know.
You know, if there's anything that
you want to get off your chest,
you can tell me.
And I promise I
won't get angry.
You want to know if
I killed that guy.
I, uh, went there planning
to do something wrong.
But I didn't kill that guy.
Someone's working hard to
make it look like I did.
Anyway, there's a chance the
execution may not happen.
What?
Veronica's working my case.
I got a reporter coming today who
actually believes I'm innocent.
So I ain't dead yet.
LJ, look at me.
You got to have faith, kid.
Just have a little faith.
-  Kellerman.
- Well?
- Taken care of.
- Good.
Now move on to
the second thing.
If you could see what
we're looking at,
believe me,
Burrows is gonna get the message.
Which is what you've
assured me of before,
yet that message keeps
getting returned to sender.
Now move on the second
thing and report back.
We're headed there now.
You're thinking too much.
Yeah, God forbid.
He's gonna toss every cell in this
block until he finds the killer.
He tosses this one, he's gonna find
the hole back there in a heartbeat.
I know.
We got to turn him in.
That's the only way it'll stop.
We turn him in, he'll talk.
So we're screwed either way,
aren't we?
Which one?
Right there. Saint Louis.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Clean up detail.
We thought this was storage.
This look like storage to you,
you idiot? It's a restricted area!
It's the guard's break room.
Now back it up!
- Back it up, now!
- Sorry.
Won't happen again.
Frickin' break room.
Are you kidding me?
They must have changed
it since the retrofit.
The bulls are camped out in there.
They'll never leave.
- You got a backup plan?
- There isn't one.
It's the only room sitting
on top of that pipe.
It's the only way out,
and we've gotta get back in there.
Impossible, Fish.
Maybe not. Check it out.
I don't get it.
How does he get in there?
He's a trustee,
ones with a high security clearance.
- Why him?
- He can be trusted.
How does one become a trustee?
Just have a spotless record
for the last 30 years.
Pretty much count's
all of us out.
Which means we've
gotta get him on board.
Forget it.
The guy's a Boy Scout.
Mr. Westmoreland?
Hey, Michael.
Have you found your cat yet?
Still M.I.A.
- You can always get another.
- I don't want another.
Besides, it's a moot point.
She was grandfathered.
Once she's gone, no more pets.
Wouldn't be an issue if
you were on the outside.
Still tugging on
that leash, eh?
Yup.
And this is the part where I
extend a formal invitation.
'Cause you still
think I'm D.B. Cooper?
I don't think, I know.
The way I see it,
you're in here doing 60-to-life
for vehicular manslaughter.
It would have been 20,
but the car you
were in was stolen.
Felony murder rule
cubes up your sentence,
and here you are.
Hitting that woman was an accident.
But the car?
No one accidentally
steals a car.
So the question is,
why would Charles Westmoreland
be in Arizona boosting a car
ten states away from
where he lived,
and only ten miles away
from the Mexican border?
And why, two days before that,
would someone make a phone call to
his wife from a motel in Portland,
a stone's throw away
from the airport,
out of which, shortly after,
Flight 305 was hijacked
by one D.B. Cooper.
Seven hours after
the hijacking,
records show Charles Westmoreland
was treated for a busted knee
at a free clinic
in Brigham City.
Only way to get from Portland,
Oregon, to Brigham City, Utah,
in  seven hours was in a car,
breaking every land speed
record known to man, or flying.
It's public record D.B. Cooper jumped
out of that 727 about an hour after
take off.
Taking a dive at 10,000 feet
with $1.5 million in cash
in a hastily packed parachute,
might make for a
pretty rough landing.
Rough enough to
shatter some bones,
maybe even a left knee.
D.B. Cooper would've had a car
waiting for him when he landed.
According to DMV
records in 1971,
Charles Westmoreland was the
proud owner of a '65 Chevy Nova.
As it happens,
a '65 Chevy Nova with the
registration number scraped off
was found abandoned with a blown
gasket along the Arizona border,
a mile or two away from where
you accidentally hit that woman
with your stolen car.
Interesting story.
Interesting man.
But you didn't
answer one thing.
What's that?
Maybe I did hurt my knee.
I did steal that car.
And I did accidentally
hit that poor lady.
But how could I have hijacked a
plane in Portland on November 24
when I was in Folsom finishing up
a 30-day drunk and disorderly?
I hope you aren't hanging this
whole escape on that money,
'cause I'm not the one
in possession of it.
Thanks for the invite though.
Veronica.
Veronica. Come on.
We're okay.
How is this okay, Nick?
Somebody just tried to kill us.
I know. I was there.
Then act like it, okay?
We just watched a man burn to
death right in front of us.
My God.
Lucasz...  my God.
It's okay. It's okay.
We just left him there.
There was nothing we
could do for him.
He was dead as soon as
he opened the door.
I am trying so hard to
understand all this, Nick.
Who these people are,
what they want,
how we just walked away from there
without even calling the police.
We did it because these people we're
dealing with won't stop until
we're dead.
Now, if they think we're dead,
like they do right now,
maybe we get a little
breathing room here,
we figure out what
our next move is.
No, we should go to the police.
I've been telling myself the same thing,
but you know what?
They're bigger than the police.
Now, we go to the authorities
and all we're gonna be doing
is broadcasting to them
that we're still alive.
And then we got that target
right in our back's again.
We can't hide forever.
No, no, maybe not forever, but
I think I know a place we can,
at least for a little while.
We just have to go in
there ourselves then.
Like I said, unless the old man's in,
it's not possible.
And even if it were,
with the guards in there,
there's no way in hell they're just
gonna sit back and watch us start
a fire.
See, I already figured that part out.
I've been thinking.
And?
That thing you're doing
at the Pope's office?
- Using rubber cement?
- Yeah?
Can you get some out of there?
Maybe. Why?
Look, there's a coffeemaker
in the guard's room, right?
I've got a hookup with one
of my boys in the kitchen.
If we can get rubber cement in
the bottom of that coffeepot,
when the burner goes on...
It's a good idea.
But without Westmoreland,
we're never getting in that room.
He doesn't want to be
a part of the escape?
No.
Then what does he want?
He's gotta want something.
Everybody wants something.
Come on, kitty. Come on.
Yes, that's a good girl.
I don't believe it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Where'd you find her?
In the yard, by the chapel.
Why do I get the feeling there's
a string attached to this?
Not a string, just a favor.
-  I'm not D.B. Cooper.
- That's all right.
'Cause it's not gonna take D.B.
Cooper to do what I need done.
What's that?
All I want you to do
is take a certain coffeepot into
the guard room at a certain time
and turn the burner on.
Why?
Let's just say it would be
in everyone's best interest
if a fire were to
start in there.
Marilyn, did you think he
was the arsonist type?
I'm not.
I'm the clean-up crew type.
The type that gets access
to all kinds of tools.
Michael, I'm grateful for this.
I really am.
But I've made it a point to keep my nose
clean ever since I walked into
this place.
32 years without a blemish.
If that parole board date ever comes,
I wanna be ready.
I can't jeopardize that.
Sorry.
Michael.
Thanks, though. Really.
After what you went
through in the riot,
I thought you might
take a day off.
I'm fine.
I, uh, couldn't find anybody
to cover for me anyway.
I hope you don't feel
like you owe me anything.
I do.
I'm, uh...
I really appreciate
what you did for me.
But?
But you told me that you had been
up in the crawl space for PI,
and PI was never
assigned to go there.
We're done here, right?
Michael, don't be like that.
I just...
I just want some answers.
Thanks for the shot, Doc.
Sue Parsons. Headline Press.
Thanks for coming by.
I appreciate you
taking the time.
looking into my case.
So what can you tell me?
From what I understand,
you have numerous people working
on your behalf as we speak.
Yeah, um, well, Veronica Donovan,
she's my attorney, and
Nick Savrinn, he, uh,
works at Project Justice.
Savrinn, okay.
Have they gotten very far?
Nothing to go to court with.
Not yet, anyway.
You ever think it's
just time to let go?
Accept what happened?
Let go? Yeah.
Accept what happened? Never.
I mean,
would you if someone had set you up?
Destroyed your life?
I guess I'm thinking in
terms of the pain and anguish
it's caused your
friends and loved ones.
People who care about me,
they believe me.
That's all that matters to me right now.
It's all I got.
You have a son.
Lincoln, Jr.? LJ?
Yeah. Why?
I have a source that tells me
if you accept what happened and
stop fighting your execution,
your son will be
left out of this.
If not,
I hope you said good-bye to him
when he left here this morning.
- Who are you?
- One Burrows is gonna die.
Up to you which one.
Who are you?!
Hey!
Don't let her go.
She threatened my son!
Please, no!
She threatened my son! No!
- LJ Burrows?
- Yeah.
I'm Officer Hale
with Juvenile Court.
We just need to do a quick
survey of the residence,
make sure the environment here is
reflective of the terms of
your probation.
Your parents home?
No, but they'll be
home any minute.
Well then...
better get started.
LJ and his dad--
you never said how it
went this morning.
Sounded fine.
Of course, everything a 15-year-old
boy tells his mother is fine.
Look, no offense, but can I see
some kind of identification?
Sure.
LJ, we're home!
LJ, you here?
Oh, my God.
Drop the phone, lady.
This is the only warning I'm giving you.
Drop it.
Run!
Pick up, pick up.
Please answer. Come on.
LJ...
we're not here to hurt you.
911... send.
You really think you're going to get
to four buttons before I get to one?
Come on.
LJ, get out of here!
Mom? Mom?
Where are you going, LJ?
What do you want from me?
Cooperation. That's all.
You want cooperation?
I know what you look like,
you son of a bitch!
I'm going to the police.
Going to the police? I don't think
that's such a good idea, LJ--
I mean, with your prints on
the murder weapon and all.
I didn't touch
the murder weapon.
Of course you didn't.
I know that and you know that.
I just don't think you're
going to have much luck
convincing Ballistics of that.
Who the hell are you people?
Just concerned neighbors.
Heard a bit of a ruckus
at the Rixs' house.
Gosh, you know, I guess we
really should've seen it coming.
I mean,
all the signs were there--
drug use,
decline in academic performance--
but we didn't think he'd
ever do something like this.
No one's going to believe that.
Yes, they will.
And when they catch you--
and they will catch you, LJ--
they're going to
try you as an adult.
You know what that means?
We can help you, LJ.
We're the only hope you've got.
No, you're not.
She made that choice, not you.
Let's find the kid.
You got Marilyn back.
Sure did.
That's good.
How long ago you quit smoking?
A little over nine years now.
You don't mind, do you?
I feel a kinship
with you, Charles.
More than any other con here.
And we've seen a lot,
haven't we?
Sure have.
And correct me if I'm wrong...
I've always treated you fair.
I've always
appreciated that fact.
I've known Bob since
he was 18 years old.
I got him this job.
You can imagine how
responsible I feel.
I can't help you
with that, boss.
I think you can.
Word is he died in
front of your cell,
and you were right
here when it happened.
We've both been around
long enough to know
that when a con starts
that snitching business,
he's not long for this world.
Don't put me in that
position, boss.
If you don't tell me
who killed Bob before
I leave this cell,
our friendship goes with it.
That's a nice cat.
Westmoreland knows,
and his jaw ain't that strong.
What's this?
Nothing.
- You stalker.
- I am not a stalker.
I just... I don't get it.
What is there to get?
He doesn't fit the
profile. Right?
The man's got a graduate degree.
He lives in my neighborhood.
Guys like that hang
out in Streeterville.
They drink single malt scotch.
They-they pay $200 for Cubs tickets.
They don't rob banks.
Maybe he couldn't
afford season tickets.
Maybe that's why he
robbed the bank.
Thank you.
I'm actually being serious.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
Why do you care so much?
- 'Cause he lied to me.
- They all lie to you.
Maybe because he's the one guy
in here I can actually get to...
one guy I can...
make a difference with.
Go home, girl.
You keep burning it at
both ends like this,
you're going to
drive yourself crazy.
Good night.
I'm sorry, Burrows.
Both of them were dead by the
time the paramedics got there.
- What about my son?
- He's missing.
The police are treating
him as a fugitive.
A fugitive?
They found his prints
on the murder weapon.
That's impossible. I...
- I, uh... I need to call him.
- No, I can't do that.
What do you mean, you can't do that?!
His life's in danger!
Burrows, the police have instructed me
that this is an ongoing investigation,
and as such,
any contact you make with your son
could potentially aid and
abet him as a fugitive.
I'm sorry.
Warden, please!
Let's go.
That's messed up.
Aw, jeez. Does he even know?
I don't think so.
What's up, T?
We family, right?
Hell, yeah, we are.
Well, I'm in a quandary,
and I need your help.
Name it.
Bellick's squeezing tighter
and tighter around here.
And you were right--
eventually, somebody's mouth
is going to start moving.
Thing is, Trokey,
if I get popped for this,
what with my priors and...
predisposition to violent behavior...
I'll spend the rest of
my life in the SHU.
But if you come forward with
only your drug convictions
and a whole lot of remorse...
- I can't do that, T.
- I ain't finished yet.
No need. I ain't going down
for murdering no hack.
I mean, you understand that,
don't you?
You ain't mad, are you?
No, Trokey, I'm not mad.
I need out. I got to find him.
You will. Both of us. Soon.
They're coming after
my family, Michael.
You got to trust me.
We're gonna get this done.
How? Tell me. Michael, tell me.
You can't, can you?
I've got to get out of here now.
LJ's in trouble.
Scofield.
How about it?
Just stick with me.
Yo, Bruce, hey!
If you go out there,
they will gun you down.
I don't care anymore.
Well, you better start thinking
about what you're doing,
'cause you can't help
LJ if you're dead.
What the hell's going
on over here, huh?
- We got a problem?
- No.
Well, then get on your feet.
Let's go!
Son of a... What the hell's going
on in building two? Come in.
Fire in the guard's break room.
Thanks.
I didn't do it for you.
Found the source. Someone in
here smoke these? Lucky Strikes?
Bellick.
Captain Bellick,
got someone to see you.
What the hell do you want?
I know who killed Bob, sir.
I don't know how
that got there.
It's not mine. It's not mine!
You set me up.
It's bad enough
you killed a guard.
Don't try and lay it off
on somebody else now.
You set me up! He set me up...!
Your father lived here?
Yeah. He wanted some place that
was completely off the grid.
A place the government
didn't even know existed.
Tapped into the power lines.
A well supplies the
place with water.
Last few years of his life,
he barely even left the property.
- It's...
- Yeah.
When you spend so many years fighting
cops and prosecutors and judges
trying to take your freedom
for something you didn't do,
you use every cent you had
on attorney's fees,
you wind up losing anyway...
15 years of his life.
Almost all of his
son's childhood.
I guess I can forgive him
for wanting to hide away,
be left alone.
We'll be safe here until we
figure out our next move.
Yeah, hold up here a minute,
hold up here.
Uh, seems to be a
bit of confusion.
I'm supposed to be on this,
uh, detail.
I don't think so.
Oh, John. You can't be serious.
Not after our long,
illustrious history we shared together.
All those nights
in New York City.
In California.
In Saint Louis.
They were good times,
weren't they, John?
Tell the badge here about 'em.
'Cause if you don't want to,
uh, I certainly could.
I want this place gutted.
The drywall's got to be torn out,
the studs got to be removed.
Boss, we've got some
toxic issues here.
Asbestos to start with.
Take it up with the union.
All I'm saying is,
this room is your only priority now.
Better be brand-spanking-new
when you're done.
If anybody's thinking
about getting cute,
trying to trunk one of
these tools out of here,
Brady's got the outline of every
single piece of hardware in here.
And at the end of every day,
every single piece
better match up,
or you're all
going to the hole.
Let's go.
This goes down four feet,
connects to the mainline below.
All we've got to
do is widen it,
and we've got ourselves
an on-ramp to Route 66.
They're gonna hear this, man.
They won't.
Come on, Pretty, we a team now.
- Best get cracking, hey?
- You, shut up.
Really think you're gonna get to
four buttons before I get to one?
I don't have my glasses.
How about you read this for me?
Tell me the news,
the latest developments.
Evidently there was
an explosion in a Gold Coast
apartment in Chicago yesterday.
Gas line.
Everyone inside was killed.
Shame. Anything else?
How about that kid up in Oak Park,
the one they say killed his parents?
- Oh, they got him.
- They did?
He's in custody.
Good. I imagine heads would have
rolled if he hadn't been caught.
Lives would have been lost.
How about you hand
that back to me?
Now that it's yesterday's news,
we can put it behind us,
can't we?
Move on to the next
chapter of our lives.
You're not just doing this for me,
you know.
Or my brother.
Yes?
They're ready for you,
Madam Vice President.
You're doing it
for your country.
Madam Vice President!
Synchro: Travis
Resynch: Schenavi
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net