Previously on Prison Break...
When were you planning on
telling me that your mother
was behind you on this?
You have today,
one day.
When Burrows brings
Scylla back to us,
you will be the one
to put a bullet
in his brain.
Naveen Banerjee,
the son of Prime Minister
Nandu Banerjee.
Soon, this will
all be behind us,
and maybe I can
meet my grandson.
Where's Linc?!
There's an energy conference.
The Panda Bay Hotel.
He'll be there.
Christina's plan...
what she needed
to profit from Scylla,
an incident
that'll domino
into global warming.
No!
They rented this in Linc's name.
Look at this.
- It's a setup!
His hands are
all over the shells.
Lincoln's right back
where he started.
It really is too bad
about Michael.
We gotta go.
I need a doctor here!
There they are!
They're up there!
Let's go upstairs, now!
Move it, move it!
Look, let's just blend
into the crowd.
No, we can't go that way.
The door is locked, Michael.
Stand back.
This whole thing
is falling apart.
Is it?
Is it really?
What, do you think
this is funny? Huh?
How long you think
it's gonna take
before the General
sees this on the news?
If he thinks we
can't get Scylla,
how long do you
think it's gonna take
before he comes after us?
And then he comes
after our families?
Yeah, it's really
funny, isn't it?
Michael, where are you?
We're still in the hotel.
Is there any other way
to get out of here
without being seen?
No, there's cops and feds
all over the place.
Did you get Scylla?
No.
Some guy got assassinated.
And guess who got set up for it.
We need Scylla.
Scylla is gone!
The only thing I care
about right now
is getting out of here.
Oh, yeah?
Where you gonna go, Michael, huh?
With the Company breathing down
our back again.
Scofield, it's Don.
What do you want?
To try to fix this.
How?
By stabbing us
in the back again?
Put Alex on.
He's a little
preoccupied right now.
Look, you want to
be mad at me, be mad
at me after we get Scylla back.
Now listen to me.
Okay, the southwest
loading dock is a
large industrial door.
It's not conducive
to a quick exit.
They only have one cop on it.
When you get to the door,
I can incapacitate the cop.
Problem is, we're
on the other side
of the hotel, and they've got
the ground floor covered.
What else can you
see on the outside?
Nothing, just the cop,
a couple of Dumpsters, jack
pallets and some laundry bins.
That must mean the
on-site laundry's
on the other side of the hotel,
near the loading dock door.
If we get to the laundry,
we can get to the door.
You said we can't
make it across the hotel.
But we can get
access to the roof.
Hotels use rooftop ventilation,
so the hotel guests don't
smell the laundry fumes.
Okay, so, listen, take
the ventilation system
to the laundry room; if you
can get to the laundry room,
you're gonna get
right by the door.
Put me on speaker.
Alex, you want to get
The Company off our backs?
Go to 4 Dunn Place.
Sara's holding my mother there.
Make her tell us
where Scylla is.
And clear our names in all this.
Mahone, you need to do whatever
you gotta do to get her to talk,
you hear me?
Do whatever you gotta do.
Got it.
Come on.
It is complete mayhem
at the Panda Bay Hotel
where Naveen Banerjee,
the son of India's
Prime Minister,
has been assassinated.
Amazingly, there have
been unconfirmed reports
identifying the assailants
as none other than
Lincoln Burrows, the man
who'd been suspected
of murdering Terrence Steadman,
and Michael Scofield,
his mastermind brother...
Christina sandbagged all of us!
If the brothers are caught,
we have no control over what
they might say
to the authorities.
Get down to that hotel
and make sure they don't
have that opportunity.
Uh, General, I'd be
more than willing
to take on that assignment.
And I assure you I will
dispatch of it efficiently.
This is not an Alabama
coon hunt, Teddy.
Don't judge me by
desperate actions
I've taken when there's
been a gun to my head.
I ran an entire
prison gang syndicate.
Hardened felons
called me "Mister."
I'm so much more
than a snitch.
And if you continue
to treat me as such,
it will be your loss,
General, not mine.
Son, I have the fate
of a multi-trillion dollar
enterprise in my hands,
and you want me to let
you earn your stripes
now?!
Take care of the brothers.
Here we go!
This should be it.
Perfect.
They say ours should
be here shortly.
I want you guys on full alert
and get all geared up,
all right?
It's them!
Stop!
They could be on any floor.
Can you override the door locks?
Yeah, they're electronic.
We control everything
from down here.
I want every room in this
hotel locked down now!
Why don't we just take
the stairs to the roof?
Because we'll set off
the fire alarm.
The ducts in the crawl spaces
above these top floor rooms,
that's how we get
our rooftop access.
Once we find the laundry vent,
we take that down
to the loading dock.
That should do it.
Go! Go!
What's going on?
They locked us out.
We can't get to the roof.
Let's head back down.
There'll be cops
in the stairwell.
We can't go up,
we can't go down...
We're trapped.
There has been a new development
in the Panda Bay assassination.
An anonymous source
has provided FOX
with documents
showing a wire transfer
from Chinese operatives
to Burrows and Scofield.
The fallout from this from
a geopolitical standpoint
is staggering.
Relations between
China and India...
Nandu reached out.
He wants to meet with you.
This couldn't have
worked out better.
Nice audible on the
Chinese document.
Thank you.
Now we just...
watch the dominoes
begin to fall.
I just wish they weren't
falling on Michael.
Christina, you gave him options,
he made his choice,
he picked his side.
Yes, but he is my son.
My only son.
And right now it is believed
both Burrows and Scofield
are still in the hotel,
but it appears
the police are closing in.
Live just outside
the Panda Bay Hotel...
No, no, no, you see,
that's the problem, Michael.
There's cops everywhere.
It's like a freaking
cop anthill out here.
Look, it's just a matter of time
till they find you anyway.
Find out what their
plan of attack is.
Sure, you know what?
Yeah, I'll just go up
and ask them, all right?
They look like
a real friendly bunch.
We don't have much time,
so get it done now!
Burrows and Scofield
could be armed to the teeth.
It's tight quarters
in the stairwell,
so I don't want a lot
of shooting, all right?
This guy's from
Homeland Security.
I'll file my report as soon as
I've apprehended the shooters.
Whoa, whoa, let me
be clear here, Captain.
The shooting that happened today
wasn't your typical gangbanger,
public service killing
you're used to here in Miami.
This was an international
assassination with ramifications
that directly affect the
security of this country.
So, if you turn your
back on me again,
I'll jam you up for hindering
a federal investigation.
You understand?
Fine.
But I want you on my hip.
I'm not gonna have you running
around playing weekend warrior
so you can go back
to your buddies at the office
and tell them you saw some
real gun play, understood?
Not a problem.
Now, why don't you
start by telling me
how you're gonna
diffuse the situation?
We're gonna gas them out floor
by floor until we find them.
Whoa, hold on there, Tex.
If you use gas you're gonna
compromise visibility,
and I can't afford
another diplomat
getting shot in the fez.
We're using chloropropane.
It's colorless, it's odorless.
They won't even
know what hit them.
All right, listen up.
I want two men in the east
stairwell with the gas,
two at the base
of the west stairwell
in case they try to
come back down again.
I'll have backup detail
ready, all right?
Let's go, move, move!
Sara?
Oh, my God.
Sara.
Sara,
you hurt? You okay?
I'm fine. Christina's gone.
There's a knife
in the last drawer.
Do you have any idea
where she went?
No.
She has Scylla.
She set up Linc
and Michael.
She could be
anywhere.
Michael and Lincoln?
Yeah, they were framed for the
murder of an Indian official.
It's all over the news.
That was Christina's plan,
and...
Where are they now?
They're trapped
at the Panda Bay Hotel.
The police are looking
for them.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
You can't go there.
The cops are everywhere.
- I really need you to get out of my way.
Well, that's not
gonna happen.
You don't care for me,
I don't care for you
much either,
but I owe Michael, okay? Run.
He's in a sea of trouble right now.
- I'm not abandoning him.
I'm not telling you
to abandon him.
There's nothing you can do for him.
Listen, I'd run
if I could run.
But if I run,
they go after my wife,
so I have to jump back in.
You don't.
I'm not running.
I'll stay here, okay?
That way, Michael
knows where I am.
So does Christina.
If she wanted me dead,
I would be already.
Suit yourself.
Alex?
Thanks.
And if you see Michael,
tell him I'm here.
Yeah.
I know how difficult
this must be for you.
Mr. Prime Minister,
I, too, lost a son
when he was just a child.
Was your son murdered
by an assailant's bullet?
Of course not.
I've heard the news that
the Chinese are behind this.
Yes, I've heard
that as well.
And that's why
I'm here.
Not to discuss how my son died,
but how to avenge him.
Your technology--
as you put it--
I've heard rumors
of its varied applications.
Nandu, let's take a breath here.
No! The time to take a breath
expired when my son died.
Your son and I had planned
to use the technology
for humanitarian endeavors.
Warfare applications
were not our goal.
But now they are mine,
and at the end of the day,
you're a businesswoman
with a product
and I am a buyer.
I want to commit
to all the intellectual property
you possess.
I want the People's
Republic of China
to feel the pain I feel
right now!
Do you comprehend
the ramifications
of what it is you're proposing?
More than you know.
If it is what you want.
I must go now...
to make arrangements
for your payment and arrangements
for my child's burial.
Yeah?
Congratulations.
You're famous again.
You're all over the news
for killing Gandhi.
I figured as much.
Yeah, well, it gets worse.
They're gonna gas you out.
When?
They already started.
They're going floor-by-floor.
They're about at the third
or fourth floor right now.
Why are you just
telling me about this now?
I had to leave the lobby.
I can't make anybody
more suspicious.
Hello, Michael? Michael?
Linc, I need
your help.
When I was in fourth grade,
I... I got an A for guessing
all the answers on this test.
I never thought
I'd beat those odds.
What kind of loser
gets set up
for two high-profile
assassinations within five years?
Are you kidding?
This is not your fault.
If they didn't get
away with it then,
they're not gonna
get away with it now.
But I need you to focus.
I need your help, Linc.
Right. Let's
get out of here.
601-30 on Tac Two.
Darrin Hooks, Homeland Security.
Can you point me
to whoever's in charge here?
Homeland? How many of you guys
are they sending here?
Agent Self's already inside.
Who?
Agent Don Self.
Got here a little
while ago.
Yeah, it's Hooks.
The name of that agent
that was supposedly killed
recently in L.A.?
Was his name Don Self?
It's all falling out
exactly as Christina planned it.
Now she's going to have
everything she ever hoped for.
She's trying to reignite
the 1962 China-India Border War
which ended in an uneasy truce
when neither country could
withstand the losses
they were sustaining in those
remote and desolate
mountains.
If she succeeds
in provoking another war,
and framing China
for the killing of India's
Prime Minister's son,
it's certainly
provocation enough.
She'll set off
a military conflict
that will last for decades
that may never
be resolved.
Why didn't you do it
yourself?
Power, money, seem
to be things you love.
Because if India's involved,
that drags in Pakistan.
Then Russia's gonna want
to defend its borders.
Then within a year,
Europe's in it
and after that,
the United States.
It's an apocalypse
in which everyone loses!
And Christina has always
been too prideful
and too unstable to accept it.
Got it.
Can I help you?
Hi. Yes, I think you can.
Agent Self.
Donald Self?
Agent Darrin Hooks.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
Hold it. Hold it right there.
Don't move.
What the hell are you doing,
Hooks?
You always pull guns
on fellow agents?
Yeah, when agents
that are supposedly dead
and are found later in a hotel
with the guys that killed him.
You mind telling me
what you're doing here
with Burrows and Scofield?
My cover called for me
to be dead, okay?
People were catching on
to what we were doing,
and my death freed me up
But Burrows and Scofield
have been set up, okay?
There's no record of you
in covert ops.
That was by design.
Look, when this is all over,
we'll call the home office,
I'll punch in my clearance code,
you can buy me
a couple of drinks,
and we'll share
some laughs about this.
But right now I need
to do my damn job.
No.
You're gonna follow
and we're gonna
clear this up right now.
Okay, but what I said about
Scofield and Burrows is true.
They've been set up.
You need to look into this.
Oh, I'm gonna look
into everything
as soon
as we get outside.
Let's go.
Did you clear
the loading dock doors?
No, but someone else did.
What do you mean?
Someone must've taken him out.
Which means there's someone
in the hotel
other than the police
that's looking for you.
Linc,
we got to move.
Got more than just
the cops after us now.
Whoa, whoa.
You know what you're doing?
No.
Let's go.
Captain Hutchinson!
We've got a room breach
on 16.
This is Hutchinson.
Scofield and Burrows are on 16.
I repeat, Scofield and Burrows
are on 16.
Go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
This way.
Make sure the
door can shut.
We need the pressure to build.
They're coming.
They're coming!
We're on 16.
Copy that.
On my mark.
Go.
# #
Backup detail!
Move! Go,
go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
Go, move!
Move, move!
What the hell happened?
They booby-trapped us.
They made a move
for the roof.
All right,
get them to a hospital.
All right.
Let's go! Move, move, move!
Stop right there!
Don't make a move
for that weapon, Burrows.
Take the masks off.
Take them off now!
Hands behind
your head.
You'd better pray to God that
my men are found out all right.
It was a concussive blast.
They're just unconscious.
Shut up.
Easy!
Easy.
And I'd follow that advice
about not going for your guns.
The General would
like you back at the office.
Now.
Did all go well at the hotel?
What's going on
with Sara and my mother?
Christina escaped.
Sara's okay.
She's in the condo.
Excuse me, would you boys like
a little alone time
to catch up?
What exactly do you
expect from us?
You need to take
responsibility
for your failures.
Hey, we failed nothing.
This whole thing
was a setup.
You know it.
- Lincoln Burrows
was outsmarted.
Who could have anticipated that?
I think you need to accept
that this is over.
I've been holding a chip
for far too long.
It's time
to play it.
I made you boys a promise.
You would find Scylla
and I would see to it
you got some cash
and had the slate wiped clean.
I intend to keep
that promise.
However, if I keep
one promise,
I have to keep them all.
Now...
I wonder
who the big winner will be.
Don't do this.
- Don't do what?
When I sent you those envelopes,
I wasn't just playing games.
I made it very clear
that you
had one day
to accomplish your job,
or there would be
consequences.
What's that?
The consequence.
Call our man in Queens.
Queens? What are you calling
New York for?
Put it on speaker,
please.
Yes.
- Move
on subject four.
I'm a block away.
ETA is less than two minutes.
You son of a bitch.
You son of a bitch!
My wife is a
defenseless woman.
Mr. Self didn't inform you
that he had a wife, did he?
Well, I wouldn't talk
about my wife either
if I'd had a few too many
bourbons, got behind the wheel,
and turned
a beautiful young woman
into a piece of broccoli.
Don't do anything.
I assume that is
why you tried
to run away with Scylla?
To screw
a government
that was giving you benefits
that would only pay
for a county
facility overlooking
the Belt Parkway, and to sell it
so that you and she
could disappear
and be hidden forever.
C'est la vie.
I have the subject in sights.
She's in a wheelchair
under a tree
in the hospital courtyard.
Do I have a go?
Please don't do this.
Okay, please,
you can kill me,
okay, you can kill me
right now,
please, kill me.
You don't need to do this;
we'll get Scylla.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Well, that's what we're trying to do!
We're getting it.
But you have to know what awaits you
and your loved ones
if you don't.
We understand, okay?
Execute the order.
- Please don't do it!
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
Get help, hel--!
I believe
you made a request.
Bagwell,
make sure he's dead.
Does everyone understand now?
Are we all on
the same page?
Good.
Let's get down
to business.
Three-quarters
of a billion dollars
in a numerical account
in Luxembourg.
If you are still worried
about humanitarian efforts,
write a check
to UNICEF.
All the data will be delivered
within 24 hours.
That's what I expected.
You played it perfectly.
Reach out
to our contact in China.
I have a feeling
they may be interested
in what we're selling as well.
Christina, I
don't advise
playing both sides
of this coin.
Pigs get fat
and hogs get slaughtered.
Reach out to China.
No!
Keep our people
at every private airfield
in Florida and in Georgia.
We can't have
Christina leaving the state.
She played on
India's emotions,
which probably means
she'd want to meet
with one of their
emissaries today
while they're
still running hot.
She could still
be in Miami,
maybe at
the embassy.
No, she's not at the embassy.
Any deal she makes
with India
will be
strictly off the radar.
Right now
she's concerned
with two things.
One is closing the deal
on Scylla,
which I'm assuming
she's already done,
and the second is getting paid.
No sign of Self.
How much can she get
for Scylla?
Half a billion from India,
the same from China.
Overseas account?
Foreign wire transfer?
I doubt she's taking
any food stamps.
She's going to want confirmation
that that money is
safely overseas
before she leaves the U.S.
We find the money,
we find
my mother.
Normally it takes
three business days
for an international
wire transfer to clear,
unless the bank is
a Federal Reserve signatory,
in which case
the transfer is immediate.
You think she'll head
to the bank?
All she has to do is withdraw
a few grand from the millions
that that buyer has probably
transferred overseas
already.
She'll know
it's all there.
So let's find a Federal Reserve
signatory bank in Miami.
We'll have a shot
at finding her.
And Scylla.
There, Michael,
you see, that's
why I didn't put
your name
in the bowl.
You're the only one here
that's irreplaceable.
Agents, informants, muscle--
they're nice to have, but...
finally they're replaceable.
There's a branch
about 20 minutes away.
That mind
of yours--
it's one in a million.
Nice to see it finally working
for me.
I do not work for you.
Not yet.
It's legitimate,
I assure you.
Oh, okay.
I just want
to withdraw the $10,000
so I can be sure
the Luxembourg account
is properly set up.
Well.
Is she in there?
Yeah, I saw her
through the window.
She's talking to a tall,
dark-haired guy.
They're the same guys
who set us up at the hotel.
We wait until she comes out,
just jump.
- So...
what do we do
about her security?
I mean, we jump her, we gotta
jump the guys she's with,
and God knows how many other
agents are gonna come crawling
out of the woodwork like ants.
Look, um...
I hate to bring up the obvious,
but last time I checked,
you two still disagreed
as to what to do
with Scylla
if we actually get it.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Well, let's skip the damn thing.
I mean, who's gonna stop us?
A 17-year-old
security guard?
No, probably the guy
with the gun.
He'll open fire
as soon as he sees our faces.
Then, uh... maybe they
shouldn't see our faces.
So then the pizza guy showed up,
and Wayne jumped
out of the bushes
and tried to grab the pizza,
but the...
but the guy...
My God.
Are you okay, mister?
Yeah.
Go call 911.
Go, go.
- No.
No, don't call anyone.
Okay?
Don't call anybody.
Don't call anyone.
You know, once baby
brother's got his little hands
on that magic box of yours,
I don't think it's going
to be too hard for him
to trick Magilla Gorilla,
if you know what I'm saying.
No,
I don't.
And you really think
that Scofield's going to
risk his nephew's life?
He's gonna
figure out something
before he hands first prize
over to the bad guys.
Scofield thinks pure,
like a little Cub Scout.
Burrows, he just thinks
like a cub.
He's right.
I don't feel comfortable
having Scofield
out there with something I want
while I'm stuck here
with nothing he wants.
I need leverage.
You saw the way
Mahone pulled Scofield over
when they first got here.
Bet you a wooden nickel
they was talking
about little Dr. Underpants
and her whereabouts.
Too bad we don't know
where that is.
Wrong again, Curly.
While everyone was up here
flapping their gums,
I took the liberty of toddling
down to Mahone's car,
checking out the last address
he put in his GPS.
There's a gambler's chance
we might find the leverage
you're looking for right here.
I'm on it.
No.
You wanted to get
in on the action,
here's your chance.
Okay, I'll just count this out
for you.
That won't
be necessary.
All righty.
Here's a printed record
of your transaction,
and I think a balance
that high, are you sure
you don't want to talk to one
of our investment specialists?
No, thank you.
Everybody down
on the ground!
Now!
Nobody move,
nobody gets hurt.
You, down.
Oh!
What are the odds?
Don't.
The case.
I'll take that.
Hi, Mom.
Scofield and Burrows
leaving the bank, now!
Take Scylla and go!
We gotta stay together!
I said go!
Come on!
I think he's out.
Move in.
After today's events,
how much egg does the U.S.
court system have on its face
for exonerating Lincoln Burrow?
in the first place.
- An omelet's
worth, Paula. If you remember
I was never in favor
of the exoneration.
Lincoln Burrows
is a thug for hire, and his
little brother is no better.
I'm amazed
that the court system just
glossed over the warning signs.
Such as?
- For one,
they should've never let Burrows
and Scofield in the same prison.
They should've looked
at Scofield's past.
It's clear that he had
no criminal background.
Why would a brilliant structural
engineer rob a bank?
Maybe he needed
to pay off his student loans.
It wasn't about the money.
What do you think
the judicial system is going
to learn from all this?
This has been a huge
wake-up call for the courts.
Judges will have to look
all the relationships
in his life...
Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh.
Easy now, Doc, easy.
It's just your friendly,
neighborhood T-Bag.
Now I'm gonna need
your cooperation.
Get your hands off me,
you son of a...
- Hand,
not hands,
thanks to your boyfriend.
Now, as I was
saying before,
I just need
your cooperation.
All right.
He's taking too long.
Something's wrong.
We gotta go back for him.
He said he'd catch up.
No, something's wrong.
Call him.
Michael,
now that we have this,
what the hell are we
going to do with it?
He's not answering.
Linc?
I heard about the bank
robbery on the radio.
You boys just can't stand to be
out of the news, can you?
I assume you've got Scylla?
We're getting close.
We'll keep you posted.
I wouldn't hang up just yet
if I were you, son.
Michael, we're in the apartment.
I know you have it.
Otherwise,
Christina would never have
risked a public shootout.
Now, I'm going to make
this easy for you,
bring me Scylla,
or this time, Sara's death
will not be faked.
What is it?
The General has Sarah.
Take it.
I swear if you touch her...
Hello, son.
I believe you have
something I want.
And I have something you want--
although I'll never really
understand why.
All right,
maybe we can work
something out.
I gave you the opportunity
to work something out.
You rejected me, Michael.
Look, let's meet
and talk about this.
Now the time for talking
passed about the time
you put those ski masks on,
don't you think?
So, here's what I'm going to do,
Michael.
I'm going to shoot Lincoln
through the right rib cage,
just grazing
the lower quadrant
of his right lung.
It will slowly collapse,
making it very difficult
to breathe.
If he doesn't get
medical attention,
within five hours,
he'll be dead.
Christina... Mom... please
Linc!
Second hand's spinning, Michael.
Looks like you have
a little decision to make.
Scylla
or someone you love.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net