Previously on Prison Break:
When I sent you those envelopes,
I wasn't just playing games.
Move on subject four.
My wife is a defenseless woman.
- Execute the order.
Please don't do that!
Don't call anyone.
You wanted to get in
on the action,
here's your chance.
Three-quarters
of a billion dollars
in a numerical account
in Luxembourg.
All the data will be delivered
within 24 hours.
Case.
I'll take that.
Hi,
Mom.
I know you have it.
Bring me Scylla
or this time Sara's death
will not be faked.
Linc!
Looks like you have
a little decision to make:
Scylla...
or someone you love.
Just think this
through, Michael.
I have, and we're
saving them both.
How?
I will figure it out.
Your brother's
bleeding to death.
I wonder if we
can get them
to bring Linc and Sara
to the same place.
Right now,
your only advantage
is that neither party knows
that there's another player
that has leverage on you.
You bring them both together,
you lose your tactical edge.
I'm not abandoning Sara.
I didn't say to do that.
What I am saying
is that Sara has the advantage
of not having a bullet
in her chest.
One at a time.
Big surprise.
The dumb one got caught,
the smart one got away.
I'm beginning
to see a pattern here.
He's never gonna give it to you.
Hmm, I disagree.
He truly cares for you.
No matter
how many times
you've shown you
don't deserve it.
You know, you two
are truly a classic study
of nature versus nurture.
Same environment, same parents--
you're completely
different.
Why do you think that is,
Lincoln?
Because Mom's a psychotic bitch.
Hello, Michael.
All right, you win.
I'll give you Scylla.
Just give Linc
whatever help he needs.
Not until I get what I need.
Edison Shipping Yard,
B Dock, 45 minutes.
And bring my brother.
45 minutes?
Cutting it close.
He doesn't
look so good.
Just be there.
Is is worth it, Sara?
Do you ever go back
to that night
and wonder how things
would have gone
if you had just left
that infirmary door
locked?
All the people who's lives
would have been saved.
Hell, your father
would still be alive.
You ever think about that?
Mm-hmm.
And now that Michael's
returning Scylla to me,
it was all for nothing.
Assuming he does return it.
If the situation were reversed,
if Michael were here
and you were
holding Scylla,
what would you do?
You'd bring it back
for the same reason
you left that door unlocked;
because you
couldn't let
an innocent man die.
Your heart betrays
your better judgment.
So does Scofield's.
You know, you're probably right.
Because if Michael had used
his better judgment
the night he stole Scylla
out from under your nose,
he would have killed you.
Get her out of my sight.
Take it.
Either take my pocket
or I take yours.
Understand?
The authorities
are blanketing the streets
looking for
the primary suspects,
Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield.
The brothers, famous for one
of the most daring
prison breaks in recent history,
are considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
Homemade explosives?
You got a better idea?
Maybe the best way
to save Linc--
to save everyone--
is give Christina what
she wants.
I'm just trying to find a way
where the people that we love
don't end up on an autopsy table.
- And I'm not?
Better get your story straight,
Alex.
This whole time
you've been saying
we should give Scylla
back to the General.
What, you didn't hear
what he did to Self's wife?
Self made his own bed.

Yeah, and we're sleeping in it.
Let's say,
best-case scenario, okay,
that maybe somehow we're able
to get to Linc and Sara.
Okay, what then?
General's still got somebody
watching my wife.
What's the plan
to keep her safe?
What about LJ?
What's the plan
to keep him safe?
I can't think about
that right now.
Maybe we go to your mother
and try to make a deal.
I mean, there's no love lost
between her and the General.
With her contacts,
if we give her Scylla,
maybe she can find out
where the agents...
We're not giving up
and we're not giving it back!
We're gonna save everyone!
What the hell
are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
You're in Recovery,
Mr. Self.
Apparently, you
had quite a fall.
Luckily, someone found
you and called 911.
They did what?
The doctor will be in shortly
to go over your history.
No, no, no, no.
Tell the doctor
to go see the next guy.
I'm going.
Actually, I can't.
There's some men here
waiting to
talk to you.
What kind of men?
The kind with badges.
Mr. Self, my name
is Agent Chris Franco.
This is Agent Wilson Wright.
We're with the Bureau.
We'd like to ask you
a few questions.
About what?
Let's start with where we
can find Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield.
Be ready to pick us up.
Better not get too close
to that thing when it goes off.
And you better not get too far.
All right, if Michael
tries anything,
take out both knees.
I don't want him dead,
I just want him immobilized
and eager to talk.
And what do you want
to do with Burrows?
Once I get Scylla,
dump him off the dock.
Yeah, one of them guys
from the news,
I think I just seen him.
Interesting choice.
I would have thought
you'd picked something
a little more public
for your own protection.
Something a little
more public
isn't safe for me right now,
thanks to you.
Did you come alone?
Did you?
Come on.
We can have at least one
honest conversation, can't we?
Actually, I'd like that.
In spite of what you think,
I never wanted
to see you get hurt.
What did you want?
Understanding...
forgiveness.
But when I made my choice,
I knew I'd never have
any of those things.
But you will have power,
won't you?
Yes, and you'll have Lincoln.
Quite honestly,
I think you're getting
the short end of the stick.
Speaking of which,
I need to get him
to a hospital, so where is he?
Where is Scylla?
I need to know he's alive.
Satisfied?
Follow me.
Now, you wouldn't have some
little trick up your sleeve,
would you, son?
I'm done playing games
with you.
Good. Then bring
Scylla out to me.
If I bring Scylla out in the
open, your man will shoot me.
Well, then I guess
we have a standoff.
The only thing is, what I want
isn't gasping
for air
and losing a pint of blood
every ten minutes.
Give it to me, Michael.
You know I can't do that.
You're running out
of options, son.
I said no.
This is Give it to me, Michael!
Christina, we gotta go!
Come and get it.
Go get it.
Son of a...
Come on, come on,
Michael.
Michael, we gotta go now!
Now!
So the government
helped you out?
After all we've been through,
you know how crazy
that sounds, huh?
Well, the proof
is there.
Every morning I wake up
my little girl,
and she's healthy again, man.
Where are you living?
Actually, uh, that's why
I came down here to talk to you.
You know, uh...
We were in protective custody
while I was waiting to testify
against Mahone,
but his case fell through.
Anyway they wanted to not
only renege on my deal,
they wanted to put my ass
back in Fox River.
So, what are you doing here
in Chicago following me?
I was wondering if you, uh,
had any idea
of where Michael and Linc were.
Wait, wait, whoa, whoa,
where you going?
Look, you in a bind
with the feds,
and now you want to know
about Mike and Linc?
Come on, come on...
- What, you gonna bust me, too?
No, I am trying
to help you, man.
And them.
Okay, man, don't you
watch the news, Sucre?
They are in a lot of trouble.
Big time.
And the only way
they can get out of it
is if you help me find them.
We're just trying
to find the two men
behind this assassination.
Well, obviously your clearance
level isn't high enough
for you to fully grasp
the operation
that I've been involved with.
All right, then how about we
tell you what we've grasped so far.
The dead body of your partner,
Agent Miriam Holtz--
autopsy shows the bullet
she was shot with
was fired from an agency-issued firearm.
- Right.
The disappearance
of your direct supervisor
at Homeland,
a Mr. Herb Stanton.
Okay.
We also got a number
of DHS transportation officers
with interesting information
concerning a warehouse
back in Los Angeles
that you were conducting some
kind of secret operation out of.
So when an international
political figure
is assassinated
on American soil
by two men taken into custody
by a Homeland Security agent,
who by all appearances
has gone rogue,
you tell us what we're supposed
to think is going on.
What's going on is you're
talking to a federal agent
like I'm an accomplice
to a crime
that I had
nothing to do with.
Do you have
any idea
how many years I've served
my country?
Do you have
any idea to the extent
that I've served my...?
What is this, Gitmo now?
As a Homeland agent,
you are aware, I'm sure,
that anyone who impedes
an investigation
into an act of terrorism
has virtually no protection
under the law.
Okay! Okay!
Okay.
Now...
where are Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows?
I don't know where they are.
Okay?
But I could find out.
Well, Michael clearly
cares more about winning
then he does about
saving your life.
Looks like you're not going
to live long enough
to be an uncle.
What? What?
Sara hasn't told anybody.
Christina, Banerjee's
on the phone.
He wants to know why he hasn't
received the technology.
If Michael doesn't call
in the next ten minutes,
you're gonna wish he'd let
you fry back at Fox River.
Hello.
I thought we had an understanding.
I thought I made the stakes
crystal clear.
You did, and I'm trying.
And I'm trying not
to kill Sara,
but that would be a lot easier
if I had something in this hand
besides a gun.
Look, every cop and fed
in this city is looking for me.
The last thing I want to do
is jeopardize her life
by getting arrested and having
the very thing you want
locked up as evidence.
Well, I appreciate you taking
care of my interests, Michael.
I do.
And believe me, for that reason
I will take care
of your interests,
but if I don't see Scylla
in one hour
I'm unleashing Bagwell to play
doctor with the doctor.
Am I clear?!
I need more time.
One hour!
Doesn't Michael understand?
He's playing chicken
with other people's lives here.
My life's beenhreaned
I'm not talking about yours.
That boy has messed up
every chance I've ever had
at freedom.
This is my last shot.
You really think
when this is over
you're going
to be free?
Better than free--
I'm going to be employed.
The General's getting me
an honest-to-goodness job
with an office
and a desk.
What kind of a job
is he going to get you, huh?
What's he going
to trust you with?
The General hires professional
killers, not amateurs.
Not uneducated criminals
who rape and kill.
You mind your tongue,
little lady.
The only thing
you're getting
when this is over is a slit
throat and an unmarked grave.
Actually,
your only chance at a life
is to get out of here.
And if you take me with you,
whatever's happened
between you and Michael,
if you get me back to him,
the slate could be wiped clean.
With Michael and me...
that slate's never going
to be clean.
And if he doesn't give
the General what he wants...
...it's going to get
a hell of a lot dirtier.
What are you doing?
I need to make
sure Linc's okay.
I suppose that little explosion
was meant for me.
Let's pretend
that was for the cops.
Please, Michael, stop.
You're embarrassing yourself.
You should know by now that
you can't outthink me.
I'll always be one step
ahead of you
because I'm your mother.
Is Linc okay?
Hm.
I remember the
first time
I caught you in a lie.
I could see it in your eyes,
just like I could see it today.
Put him on the phone.
You're not in a position
to be making demands, son.
Actually, if Linc is dead,
I have no reason
to give you Scylla,
which puts me in exactly
the position you describe.
Yeah.
Hey, it's nice to know
you're still breathing.
How much time do I have?
Not much.
The General has Sara.
He's giving me an hour
to exchange her for Scylla.
I need to know where you are,
so if you can give me
any kind of signal.
Don't know.
Look, if I'm going
to save you both,
I need something.
- Banerjee again.
There's just not enough time,
Michael.
I can do this, Linc.
I can do this.
There's something
you need to know.
Sara's p... Sara's pregnant.
It's... it's okay.
You're going to be a dad.
No, I understand.
Now, if you just give us
a little more time...
Go to her, Michael.
I'll find a way, Linc.
There's not enough time.
There's just not enough time.
Let me go out knowing
that I did something for you.
Give me that!
- Let me...
Linc?
I'm sorry about what's ever
happening to Linc.
And I know you have to
protect your family,
I understand that,
but, Michael, what are we going
to do about the rest of us?
What are we going to do
about my wife?
Alex, I don't...
I don't know
what you want me to say.
You haven't gone a day
in your life without a plan.
Please don't start now.
All I know is
I have 43 minutes
to get this
to the General.
I am done making plans.
And to hell
with everybody else.
Well...
maybe it's time I take a
page from your book, Alex.
Hang out on
the sidelines,
survey the field.
When the time is right,
back the winning horse.
at's what you
think I'm about?
Tell me something, Alex,
which horse are you backing now?
Because I'm not quite clear
on that.
At least you got a decision.
They took my son.
I didn't
get to choose.
I'm just trying to do
whatever it takes to...
to not lose everything.
So am I.
So if there's something
you need to do to protect Pam,
you should do it.
Do you realize
after what you pulled,
you're completely worthless
to me now?
You've been worthless
to me all your life.
I know you and Michael think
I was a terrible mother.
Couldn't agree with you more.
I warned Aldo.
I told him
I was not cut out for it.
It is not in my nature!
He used to call me
his Lady Macbeth.
I knew there was a reason
I hated Shakespeare.
You hated it
because you couldn't
understand it.
You couldn't understand
it because...
your real mother was as dumb
as a day-old doughnut.
You asked me
how I could just sit
and watch my son
go into the chair.
The answer's simple really.
You're not my son.
Michael already knows.
That must be why it's so easy
for him to play with your life.
I guess we have that in common.
Now, go find my son.
Your information
leads to an arrest,
we'll make sure the courts
can't touch you.
Right.
Well, you put that in writing
and then we're in business.
No, no, the only thing you get
to demand in writing
is what we put
on your tombstone.
Last thing you're going
to want to find out about
is the brothers killing
somebody else
while you're in here harassing
your only source
of intel.
It needs to be
in writing,
and signed
by the attorney general.
I don't trust anyone who says
they work for the government.
All you have to do...
is call the brothers.
Get them on the phone,
let me talk to them.
And then they can make up
their own minds, all right?
I'm just trying
to stay out of all this.
I finally got my family back,
and I'm not about
to risk losing them again.
I know this feels good today.
But what about
a couple months from now, huh?
When the only job you can get
is under the table
or some labor gig,
where every minute
you'll be worrying about the guy
you're sweating next to,
if he's gonna drop the dime
in a heartbeat
because he recognizes you.
How is finding Linc and Mike
gonna change any of that?
This guy sought me out, okay?
He knows everything
about this whole thing.
Well, is he government?
'Cause if he's government,
I don't want...
I didn't trust him
at first either!
Okay? But it's something about
being in the pen
where you start to decipher who
is a player and who is a punk.
And this guy
is a player.
Just like Scofield.
So the only thing
that we have to do
is tell him
where the brothers are,
help him get
this device thing back,
and-and so he can put it
into the right hands.
And then what? Hmm?
This brother has juice.
He can erase
our entire record.
Now, I'm not talking about cash
and all that flashy stuff.
I'm just talking about
straight up freedom,
living like a man.
You feel me?
No, of course, Nandu.
It... Yes, yes.
We just ran into a few
technical difficulties, so...
No, I understand.
Now, if you just give us
a little more time, then, um...
No, no, no. No, no, don't.
please don't
get on the plane.
No, I can...
You just cost me three-quarters
of a billion dollars!
Good.
At least the day
wasn't a total waste.
I was gonna wait
till I found Michael
and just kill you
in front of him, but instead,
I'm gonna take you out
the same way you came in--
alone.
You better be calling me
to tell me you've got Scylla.
Whoever you've sent after it
is too late.
Michael's giving Scylla back
to the General
in exchange for Sara's life.
Who the hell is this?
Alex Mahone.
I don't believe
we've had the pleasure
of meeting.
Oh, yeah.
Alex Mahone.
You calling to rub
this in my face?
Calling to see
if you'll make me an offer.
I can get Scylla for you,
if you promise to give me
what Michael can't.
What's that?
Protection for my family.
If your people can get my wife
away from whoever
the General's got watching her,
I'll get you Scylla.
You can get me Scylla?
Mahone...
you son of a bitch.
I've got no particular love
for Burrows.
Sounds like
the feeling's mutual.
Yeah, but unlike his brother,
the guy's always been
straight with me.
And he helped me track down
the guy who murdered my son,
and for that, I owe him.
And you don't owe Michael?
Not anymore.
His choice, not mine.
Tell you what.
You give me Scylla,
if Lincoln's
still breathing,
you can have him.
I like that deal.
Hickory dickory dock.
Tell me, has Scofield
ever run up your clock?
Has he been man enough
to go there?
Or is he
saving it up
for the wedding day?
Michael is more man
than you can ever hope to be.
How would you know what
a man is like, huh?
Of the two of us, I bet
I've been with more of them.
Look at you,
all buttoned up...
frigid.
Tell me, what does it take to
loosen up a gal like you, huh?
Music?
Flowers?
Touch?
Where the fingers
do the walking down
to where only...
Stop it!
Please.
My, my.
I do like a woman
with manners.
Michael, you better be
calling me
to tell me you're close.
We're almost there.
Good. But I've changed my mind.
The exchange will be made
at a location of my choosing.
Forgive me, but I don't
really trust you,
except on unfamiliar territory.
You bring Sara unharmed, and...
I'll meet you anywhere.
Uh, there's an old parking lot
where Pelican Drive
meets the beach.
Be there in 20 minutes.
And I'm supposed to trust
that you're just gonna let us
live our lives, huh?
Believe it or not, Michael,
the last thing on Earth I want
is to ever see you or any member
of your family again.
You stay out of my way,
I'll stay out of yours.
Bring me Scylla.
20 minutes, Michael.
All right.
20 minutes!
About earlier...
I do think you're in it
for yourself.
Fortunately for me, that's meant
you've also had my back.
More than once.
And for that,
I'm grateful.
Take the case.
Get out of here.
What about Pam?
I got it handled.
Good luck.
Looks like your boyfriend
straightened his priorities out.
That's too bad.
We were just starting
to get familiar.
Teddy, what are you doing?
You said we was gonna bring her
on the exchange.
All I'm giving Scofield today
is a slow death.
So what are we gonna do
with her?
Whatever you like.
Perhaps we've finally
found a job
for which
you're perfectly suited.
Mr. Mahone?
I'm on my way.
And Michael?
I don't want
to talk about Michael.
Well, it seems Michael did
a poor job choosing his friends.
None of us choose this.
This happened to us.
The only thing we choose
is how it ends.
So just get your people
in place to help my wife.
How does that sound?
One of our assets
with the Bureau
says that two agents
are questioning Don Self
at Miami Mission Hospital.
And the attorney general
just issued a proclamation
for his immunity.
You think he's a threat?
Perhaps.
Question is, to whom?
Hello?
Michael, it's Don Self.
How's it going?
Well, well, well.
Thought you were dead.
If I had a dollar every time
I've said that about you.
You sound funny, Don.
What do you want?
What do I want?
You saw what that bastard
did to my wife, right?
I want revenge.
Where are you,
so we can hook back up?
That's not necessary.
This whole thing's
about to be over anyway.
What do you mean
the whole thing?
What's going on?
I'm hanging up now, Don.
Hello?
Scofield's
on a burner.
They're harder
to trace.
We're gonna
need more time.
Well, he's gonna call back.
He just gets a little riled up.
But he'll call back.
- When?
After he kills somebody?
You heard; this thing's
about to be over; Lord
knows what that means.
Get him back on the phone,
Agent Self, now.
So this cat said that
Scofield and Linc
should recognize him
when they see him.
Recognize him from where?
Look, I don't
know, man.
Look, we've been in
a lot of messed up places.
I'm just saying,
it makes a difference.
Besides, I mean, did he say
what he was gonna do
with Scylla if he gets it?
All this guy said is that he
couldn't go to the government,
'cause no one government
should have that much power.
Now, look, man, you want to ask
him yourself, he's right there.
He even give you a name?
Said call him Paul.
Sir.
If anyone tries to
escape, aerate them.
Keep an eye out
for anything suspicious.
Scofield's a tunnel rat.
You know...
I wasn't the only fox in the
river to fall asleep at night
dreaming about treasures
was tucked beneath
that white coat of yours.
Every guy let their minds
wander-- eenie, meenie,
mynie, mo-- in between you
and Nurse Katie,
sometimes settling on
the both of you.
You digging that?
All you old junkies
like a little
dirty talk.
Let me see where
those tracks are.
I think I can, I think I can.
If you let me go, I can tell the
courts that you saved my life.
I think I can.
Teddy, if you let me go,
I can petition for leniency.
I could tell them
you saved my life.
I still have connections
from my father.
You know, I was always thinking
the way I was gonna get revenge
on Scofield was to kill him.
Just driving that knife
right into his bleeding heart.
And now...
standing here
looking at you,
I'm thinking there's
something worse
than death for him.
Please, no.
I'll return you in one piece.
But that piece
gonna be a little used.
That's all.
And every time
he looks at you...
every time he wants
to be with you...
...he's gonna see me.
Nothing!
We got to get back
to the loft now.
Hey, Michael, this is
Don calling back again.
Listen, I know
you have a beef with me.
All right?
And I understand,
but I think I have
a way to get us
all out of this.
Okay, just please call me back.
How many messages
we going to
leave this guy before
we move on to plan B?
Look, he's going
to call back, okay?
Excuse me, gentlemen, I need
to check on the patient.
Just take a
few minutes.
He's going to call back, okay?
There's coffee
down the hall.
He's going to call back.
Just be patient, okay?
We're going to get him.
How's it going, Doc?
It's going well.
Is this
your first time with me?
Huh?
What is that?
I know you, right?
What...
Oh, yeah.
Ooh, I bet you was a tomcat
back when you was using, huh?
See, nowadays, you like to
look a fella in the eyes,
but back then...
Back then, oh...
Back then, I bet the last
thing you wanted to do
was see who you was
keeping company with.
That's self worth for you.
See, I've always
felt that the partner
you choose to be with
is just a reflection
of how you're really feeling
about yourself in that moment.
And I got to tell
you, sister,
right now, old
Teddy is feeling
like a million bucks.
Oh...
I'm going to be a
gentleman about this.
I'm going to let you choose.
and I'm going to give you
just what the doctor ordered.
What, you got something to say?
Just that while you
and the other cons
were taking care of
yourselves, I...
Katie and I were going
over your medical records
trying to figure out
how best to
manage your care,
figure out what
makes you tick.
The thing I remember
about you, Theodore?
Nothing makes you tick.
You can't... tick.
What exactly are you implying?
That the reason you rape
and kill and make pain
is because you
can't make love.
You've got neurogenic ED,
probably caused by
injuries you sustained
during your own
childhood sexual abuse.
That is a lie.
Talk all you want about
what you're going
to do to me, Theodore.
You and I both know
there is very little
you can actually do.
All right.
You are just going to take
back every word you just said.
You hear me? You hear me?!
There's no reason
to be ashamed of it, Teddy.
So many men suffer from it.
Shut up!
I don't know
what is more insulting:
You thinking
I'm erectorally challenged
or you thinking I'm going
to let you break out of here.
Hmm, let me think about that.
I'm going to go
with the first one.
Now,
I'm going to show you
just how functional I am.
Michael!
Please.
It's all right.
Come here.
You all right?
Get me out of here.
Show me.
Why don't you come inside, Alex?
We have a lot to talk about.
Before we do any business...
I'd like some proof
that Pam is safe.
We have an asset embedded
in the Company operations room
who was able to access
the details of her location
and the position
of her bird-dog.
That's great.
That's not good enough.
I need to know
that she's in the clear.
I'm ready to
execute that order,
but first, I need you
to hand over Scylla.
It's only a matter of time
before the General realizes
that I turned my back on him.
And Michael.
And when he does,
he's going to want revenge.
Go make the call.
Alex.
This isn't about threats.
This isn't about games.
This is about how
people do business.
I would be a fool if I gave
you everything you want
before I had some
kind of guarantee
that I'm going to get
everything I want.
You've been busy.
Here it is.
Where's the rest of it?
All right.
I've kept my end
of the deal.
Time for you
to make good on yours.
Make the call, please, and
Linc and I will be on our way.
Well, if it's okay with you, I'd
like to check this out first,
make sure everything works
before anybody
goes anywhere.
Lock him up.
What are you doing here?
Saving your ass.
I couldn't make
that choice, Sara.
I had to save you both.
If there's something you need
to do to protect Pam,
you should do it.
Alex.
There may be some way
we can save everyone.
The bad news is
my mother can read
my every move.
She says it's
because she knows me.
The good news is
she doesn't know you.
I knew the General
would never honor
his end of the arrangement.
I knew...
I knew he'd never
bring you to the exchange, so
I did what I had to do.
How big an explosion
are we talking about?
Big enough to end all this,
so we can...
maybe start something new.
I mean, if that's...
what you're feeling.
Come on, you got to get
off the table. Come on.
We got to get to the
other side of the room.
Over here.
Slide down the wall.
You ready to get
the hell out of here?
Yeah.
There's something wrong.
I'm not getting
any kind of connection.
Michael.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net