Previously on Prison Break.
Those ass-hats are worth more
dead than you and I are alive.
Somebody's gonna get that money--
might as well be me.
You know, a job like that might
go a little smoother with
an extra pair of hands.
I want divers down
in the river.
- Are you Scott Kolbrenner?
- You must be Debra Jean.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yeah, same here.
Apparently, Fibonacci's
coming up for air again,
and if he testifies at that hearing,
a lot of people are going down.
Caroline. They're
taking her in.
Of course,
I'll keep an eye on her.
Hi, my name is Sara,
and I'm an addict.
Hi, my name's Lance,
Hi, Lance.
You did one hell of a job, Doc.
It's okay for you to leave now.
Oh, I'm leaving; you're not.
- Where to, sir?
- Utah.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- So which one of them was it?
- Maybe Scofield.
Probably gonna find his
brother in there, too.
Are you meeting up with her,
the doctor?
I don't know.
I knew the little whore
would take us right to 'em.
What happens when you get to Mexico?
Where will you go?
It's best if you don't know.
It's best for everyone.
We'll drop you off
in the next town,
and I'll wire you that 10,000,
like I said.
Shouldn't take more
than a week or two.
Michael.
We got company.
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
Who is it?
It's Bellick!
Hold on.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Can this thing go any faster?!
What do you think?!
Look out! Look out!
Nobody move!
Oh, good to see you again, boy.
No need for anyone
to get hurt, Boss.
Boss? Oh, there's no need for
formalities anymore there, Sink.
I'm no longer an employee of the state,
thanks to you.
- I think somebody wants that reward.
- It's not about reward money, friend.
Your pal Manche told me all
about your little treasure hunt
for Westmoreland's stash.
Get in the car.
We're going to Utah.
All the cops following
you all over the country,
when all they had to do was
tail the tail, you know?
- Move that moneymaker, sweetheart.
- Let's move it, convict.
If you know about the money in Utah,
why do you need us?
Well, the excitement
of the escape,
Manche didn't hear
everything Westmoreland said
before the old bird kicked the bucket,
but he heard enough:
Utah and five million.
You'll fill in the blanks.
Hey!
Don't even think about
getting cute, smart-ass.
Now, you and your brother are gonna
take me right to where that money is,
or the whore gets
dead real fast.
Ask me if I'm bluffing.
The dredging of the river under
Scofield's apartment bore some fruit.
Found a hard drive
under the river bed.
Serial numbers match an
order that Scofield put in
with Dell a few months
before he was incarcerated.
They've recovered about 12
percent of the data so far.
And this is helping us how?
Blood tests came back.
B-negative all over that crash site.
- Scofield and Burrows are both...
- B-negative. I know.
- I'll reach out to the media.
- How about don't.
If it gets out that
the guy who...
...who masterminded this
whole thing is possibly dead,
the other six cons are gonna
get their guards up even more.
It is our policy-- excuse me...
It is our policy not to announce
deaths until they're confirmed!
We've got an exploding
car and a blood match.
- Well, then do more tests.
- On what?
On the bumper. I don't know.
I don't care. Just delay.
I want those guys out there getting
more complacent, not more careful.
...to forge ahead with
its nuclear program.
In national news,
the eight escaped convicts
from Fox River Penitentiary in
Illinois are still at large, and...
- Hey, I was listening to that.
- Yeah. Yeah, I want to hear this.
- Really? You like John Denver?
- Yeah.
Country ho...
Take me home
To your place
I've got cash
Country ho
In West Virginia
Take me home,
My country ho...
This is good, this is good.
- Don't quit your day job.
- What?
Nah, I just need a little
tequila to get my karaoke on.
Yeah.
Here, yo, slow down.
We're doing, like,
65 in a 60...
- Yo, slow down.
- All right, Dad.
Yo, we can't be
having that, man.
Tickets are, like, 200 bones.
I never thought I'd say this,
Scofield, but
I thank God for the day
you walked into Fox River.
And out of it.
It's gonna be okay.
I don't want to hear
from you right now.
You told me nothing would happen.
You promised me.
That's one pissed off commie you
got on your hands there, Scofield.
Didn't your mama tell
you how to treat a lady?
Or was she a whore
like this one?
- Linc!
- Got a problem there, Burrows?
We only need one of you to take
us to the money. Remember that.
Let's go, buddy. Let's go.
I'd been really drunk
at the wedding speech.
And this was the first time
that we'd spoken since then.
And it was cleansing.
It was really cleansing. Thank you.
Good share, Ralph.
Well, we're out of time.
Unless there are any
burning desires...
Actually, I'd like to...
you know, if there's time.
Of course.
- I'm Lance, and I'm an addict.
- Hi, Lance.
My, uh, mother died of M.S.
last week.
She just... gave out.
Just like my grandfather did,
just like my sister did.
Just like I...
Um, if I may?
Lance, M.S.
isn't usually considered genetic.
- Really? What are you, a doctor?
- Uh, I am, actually. Sorry.
Thank you.
All right, everybody,
face the wall and look straight ahead!
Eyes front.
- How was your flight?
- Bumpy. Everything is ready?
We got a container ship
down at the navy yard.
The captain's one of ours.
He's got a stateroom listed as
a cargo hold on the manifest.
You and your family will be on
it when it sets sail tomorrow.
Six days from now, John,
you'll be in Sardinia.
Good work.
Sylvia.
Dad!
We missed you.
I missed you, too.
It's over, it's over.
Come on. Come on.
What the hell are you doing?
Mind your own business.
What kind of son of a bitch doesn't
have a spare tire in his car?
The kind that already used it.
Well, then you're just the sad sack that
has to go back into town to get a
new one.
- That's like three miles.
- That's right.
All right, everybody out.
That way, come on.
- Careful.
- Don't touch me.
Just relax.
You know,
I believed everything you told me,
and I did everything you asked.
I risked my life for you.
For what?
For $10,000, I risked my life?
And this entire time, you've had
$5 million just waiting there.
You're a bastard, Michael.
For all the aggravation, I hope you
got to hit that a few times, Scofield.
Ba-ba-boom-bah.
We're going to wait
it out in that shack.
Keep moving. Come on.
Go in there. Come on.
Fantasia, get going.
I need to talk to you... alone.
What do you want?
To ruin his life like
he's ruined mine.
Where you coming from?
Me? I was just hitting
the head, boss.
What's your name?
Clyde.
Clyde May.
- You got any ID, Mr. May?
- I don't, uh...
drive anymore,
so don't really have ID per se.
Camel jockey left a big box of boom-boom
under my jeep back in Kandahar.
- You military?
- Was.
- Which one's your vehicle?
- These two sleds right here.
That is,
in between rides, anyhow.
Ain't much of a bag to
be hitchhiking with.
I travel light.
And you're just hoofing it out
here in the middle of nowhere?
I do have the right
to see a little bit
of the country I lost my hand for,
don't I?
Why don't you tell me what
this is all about, Officer.
We got a vehicle here
without a driver,
and at present, you're the
only driver without a vehicle.
Hell, is that what
this is all about?
Why didn't you say so?
Dirty hippie kid dropping
a deuce in the facilities.
Came in with that car
not two minutes ago.
Check it out.
- What were you, Army?
- Hell no. Corps.
Well, then. Semper fi, brother.
What outfit were you?
- 196th.
- 196th?
Never heard of it.
Where they out of?
Hey, Elkind!
What the hell, man?
I didn't do nothing.
Found these in his knapsack,
after he said he had no car.
What?
Semper fi, brother.
Semper fi.
Stop stressing;
it doesn't do any good.
Maybe you ought to
start stressing,
if they're going to put
a bullet in our heads.
They need us.
They need us to get that money.
I admire your optimism.
She's rolling, man.
I can feel it.
So you want to ruin Scofield's life.
Well, get in line.
What are you really
looking for?
Same as you... money.
Money? You want money?
Ten grand, how's that sound?
We do it right now,
right there on those floorboards.
Not in a thousand years.
Beat it then.
You got nothing else I need.
Typical man.
I'm talking about millions of dollars,
and you'd piss it away for sex.
That's right.
And I was hoping you wouldn't
let Michael outsmart you, too.
Scofield ain't
outsmarting no one.
You think that tire
went flat by accident?
What are you offering?
I can find out where the money is.
He trusts me.
- What do you want?
- My fair share.
You find out where that money is,
your fair share is $200,000.
Out of five million?
It's not even...
I got the gun, girl.
You're lucky you're a partner at all.
I'll be right back.
Fibonacci's in D.C.
Yeah, and he's in Denver,
Atlanta, Miami...
No, no, no, no, no.
This time, it's for real.
He's testifying again.
He's in Washington right now.
- The Globe Hotel, Room 116.
- Is this information any good?
It's from New Jersey.
Fishhead Tommy wants to pay tribute.
Get the car.
Look at this room, John.
Look.
We can be a family again.
But you want to risk it all, disrespect
us, and for what, for vengeance?
- He betrayed me.
- I don't care.
He betrayed us.
I'm sorry you...
will never understand what happens...
when you're in prison.
But you could go
back to pris...
I swear to God...
I'd rather die than go back.
There's no going back,
never, ever again.
Christ saved you, John.
Don't turn your back on him.
Don't turn your back on us.
I...
I don't know,
about 20 miles from Gunnison.
He's coming; I have to go.
- Who was that?
- Nobody, it's just my father.
Hey, listen. Do you mind if
we stop at the next motel?
It's only like 4:00?
Yeah, but we've been
driving forever.
It's cool, I'll drive.
I really just want to stop.
But if we get on the
road now, maybe...
Scott, it's my car,
and I'm tired of being in it, okay?
All right.
Can you believe it?
Of all the players in this thing,
it's the rat that could give
us our first collar. Come on.
You guys need to use the can,
hold it.
If you need to tinkle, sweet pea,
I'll watch you any time.
Sit down.
Hands behind your back.
Took your time.
It takes time to gain
a man's confidence.
You're right.
He'll bite on anything I say.
You just tell me
where we trap him,
and I'll tell him that's
where the money is.
Hey, you're the guy from
the gas station, right?
Yeah.
I'm the guy who was
having car trouble.
Seems to be purring
along now, huh?
Yeah.
Water pump.
200 bucks for this heap.
Well, they'll get you.
Look, I hope I'm
not out of line,
but I heard you telling the
cop back there about your hand.
My old man was killed in
'Nam when I was a kid,
and so I have the utmost
respect for our servicemen.
- Just serving my country.
- A lot of us are grateful for it.
Listen, if you need a
ride or something...
Well, to be honest
with you, my...
my dogs are kind of barking.
Well, all right. Jerry Curtin.
Clyde. Clyde May.
My kid Danny's riding shotgun. I hope
you don't mind sitting in the back.
- Hi. I'm Danielle.
- Hi, yourself.
- Hey.
- What do you want?
- I need to use the bathroom.
- Again?
- I have a small bladder.
- That ain't all you got.
Get up.
Well?
They plan to trap you.
The big one--
he's got friends in Utah. Criminals.
A town called Panguitch.
They grow drugs on the farm there.
They'll tell you that's where
the money is, but no money.
Just old friends with guns,
waiting for you.
Easy enough.
We take a pass on Panguitch.
- Where's the money really?
- I'll find out soon enough.
But $200,000 was old price
for this information.
- I want a new price.
- She's trying to renegotiate.
If it wasn't for me,
you'd be face down in a marijuana farm.
- One third.
- Ha!
It's gonna take a lot more than
information if you want a million-six,
sweet pea.
- Such as?
- You know.
Piece of that can
anytime I want it.
- Is that it?
- Aren't you gonna slap me?
I've slept with men for a lot less,
trust me.
And what happened to
"never in a 1,000 years?"
That was negotiating.
So.
Deal?
Deal.
We got a $150,000 here, John.
With Vittorio's
place in Solanas,
we'll be able to live
off the interest.
Where's your father?
Everything all right, boss?
Yeah. Let's get
this over with...
so I can get back to my family.
She'll get it done.
Nika and I have come too far together.
When money's on the line,
you trust no one.
Sometimes you have to.
Not if you want to survive,
you don't.
You really don't trust anyone,
do you?
Can you blame me after
all that's happened?
No, I mean before that.
Before prison.
Every time I trusted someone,
I got burned.
Every time I got close to someone,
I got screwed.
I know better,
and so should you.
That's right, the Lotus Motel.
I don't know the number.
I can't talk anymore; I have to go.
Oh, check it.
I know this might be a little
forward and all, but, um,
let me ask you something.
You got a man?
I mean, a boyfriend?
No. What am I thinking?
You're Mormon...
I'm not Mormon. You think all
girls from Utah are Mormons?
They are, aren't they?
Well, yo, hey.
Yo, then you can party, right? Hey.
When I land, I want 12 armed agents
waiting for me on the ground.
Tell them I want to go straight
to the motel from the airstrip.
You got it.
I was an ass before.
I apologize.
A little bit.
It's all right. Here you go.
- I was a huge ass.
- I apologize.
I'm not going to
argue with you.
Well, I mean, what were the odds
that you were actually a doctor?
Uh, all right, fair enough.
They're probably not good, but, um...
And I should not have interrupted you,
and I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, too.
- Well, then, apologies accepted.
- I recommend the blueberry pie.
- Well, blueberry pie it is.
- Hey, there, Danny.
- Hey.
Sure is nice of your daddy to
buy me a room for the night.
Yeah, he's always helping
out with vets and stuff.
Yeah, good man.
But I was wishing we could have
kept going on toward Utah.
Lots of light left in the day,
lots of road to go.
When Dad's back acts up,
we stop.
Young Miss?
That's kind of insulting, isn't it?
Hmm?
I mean, you're a grown woman.
But adults are always trying
to infantilize girls your age,
treat you like children.
No duh. My dad won't let me
get earrings, and I'm 14.
You see?
That's what I'm saying.
You are more than
perfectly capable of, uh...
- of making your own decisions...
- Tell my dad that.
Yeah, but he won't want
to hear it, right?
Because he wants to keep
you as a baby. Right?
Even though you're...
you're more than old enough to
to choose how you want to-to dress,
or, uh, accessorize.
What are you doing?
Just in need of a friend,
that's all...
No. No. I'm telling my dad.
Wait!
She's got it all wrong.
Go wait outside.
You and I are gonna
work this out.
Jerry... you really
don't want to do this.
Thing I like about you
is your determination.
I've got family in Kladno that have
been waiting for me to send for them.
They know what kind
of work you're in?
They think I work
at Starbuck's.
Mmm. Mmm.
How stupid do you think I am?
My daddy always said,
"Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice,
and I put you in the ground."
Any more games,
and I stop the hooker's air, understand?
Thanks for the dance,
sweet pea.
- You bitch!
- Fooled you.
I carried it;
the cons can change it.
Oh, you really suck,
Bellick, you know that?
- Roll 'em.
- Let's go.
Put your hands
behind your back.
Thank you.
You're as stupid as the prison doc,
you know that?
Ignore him.
He conned her, too. Made her think
he loved her, and look what she got.
An overdose and a shot
at 30 years inside.
What are you talking about?
Guess you haven't been reading
the papers, have you, college boy?
Cops found your girlfriend--
fish-belly white,
garglin' her own puke.
Shut up.
But what do you care, a long as
she left the door open for you?
- Shut up!
- Hit a  spot, didn't I?
Dad...
It really is like the
best pie I've ever had.
You know what it
needs though...
- Hmm?
- Some crack.
No, I mean, you know, not a lot.
A pinch.
- A pinch of crack?
- A pinch of crack.
A pinch of crack,
a dollop of smack. Mm.
- That's good pie.
- That's so wrong.
No?
I'm sorry.
Hello.
- Sara... it's me.
- What do you want?
I don't have time to talk.
And there's every chance they're
listening to this call right now,
but there's a lot
I want to say.
Please don't hang up on me.
I don't...
I don't want talk to you.
I heard about...
I heard about what happened.
I want you to know that...
I want you to know
how sorry I am...
for everything.
Sorry's not going to do
me a whole lot of good
with what I'm up
against right now.
Listen... anyone with any ties to
me and my brother is in danger now.
I have no ties to you
and your brother anymore.
There is a way I
can protect you.
It's already in
your possession.
What are you talking about.
It was real, Sara.
You and me...
It's real.
Michael? I...
Michael?
How long to the motel?
Approximately ten minutes, sir.
Let's make it five?
Ooh. Yo, I haven't taken a
shower like that in forever!
- Where are you going?
- I was going to surprise you.
Surprise me how?
I was going to get
some tequila and lime.
All right, well, hold up--
No, no. No, it'll only take a minute.
Stay here and relax.
You seem kind of nervous.
- I do?
- Yeah, you're sweating.
Maybe I am nervous.
Trust me, girl, you got nothing
to worry about, all right?
- I'm one of the good guys.
- You seem like it.
Hang on tight.
I had the manager unlock
the door. Gotcha.
If you're looking
for the rat, John...
Fibonacci's 2,000
miles from here.
Who are you?
Local cops or Feds?
Feds, John, only roll out the
best for a man of your stature.
I deserve to know
who turned on me.
Tony?
The man was facing RICO rap.
He did not want to to prison.
I'm sure can appreciate that, knowing
what you know about the place now.
Whatever you're thinking
about doing John...
don't.
You are going back
to Fox River today
or the morgue,
that's your call.
Coming out.
Weapons come out first, John.
Forgive me.
Yeah, I'm coming out.
Easy, John. Easy.
We got a weapon, right hand.
These are serious men here.
They have instructions to shoot
at the first sign of aggression.
Please. I'm asking
you, respectfully,
drop the weapon,
kneel and put your hands on your head.
I kneel only to God.
I don't see Him here.
John!
I think I screwed up.
My dad's an Air Force colonel.
Total Nazi. One of those...
nightmare overprotective dads.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah?
Well, I called him.
Told him I was
traveling with you.
I told him that we were
staying in the same hotel room.
- Girl.
- What?
You got to learn how to lie, girl.
What you thinking?
I don't... Yeah, I--
for some reason I don't know how.
He was mad enough when I told him I
was staying in a hotel room with a guy,
that was one thing...
Yeah, yeah.
But when I told him I was staying
in a hotel with a guy that...
I maybe sort of liked...
he lost it.
Wait.
- Wait, what?
- Is that okay?
At least let us
take you into town.
No.
If I'm seen with you,
it's a lot of trouble for me.
I can walk; it's only a mile.
We never would've made
it this far without you.
But now you're
crossing the border...
without me.
You can't go where we're going.
It's not a life for you.
Then that's it then.
It's over for good.
Thank you.
Be safe.
Good luck.
I loved you, Michael.
And I thought I was going to get
that back, but you just used me.
That's not true.
I deserve more than this.
I deserve more than just being the
girl you call when you need something.
You really think you're
gonna find the money in Utah?
I don't care about
the money in Utah!
I don't want any more crime.
I turn you in, I get $200,000.
Legal money.
You're the policemen's
problem now.
Nika...
Don't come any closer
or I'll shoot you!
No, you won't.
Good luck to you.
- Hey.
Um, HQ called. They're asking
why you didn't intercept Abruzzi
when he was walking
towards the motel.
The man was a mob boss.
The right move was to get him trapped.
They're saying the way you played it,
there was only one possible outcome.
HQ has a problem with
the way I do things,
they can pick up a gun and follow
me into the field next time.
Scofield always knew the
rat was the key to Abruzzi.
We just put it out on
the wire and Abruzzi bit.
Speaking of Scofield...
That crash was staged.
Pig blood.
Smart kid.
The problem with...
being that clever is
that sooner or later,
you end up getting too
clever for your own good.
Good night.
You have no idea
what you're in for.
Synchro: Travis. Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net