Previously on Prison Break:
The bracing is going to be tricky.
Unless the tunnel gets the proper support, it's
all going to come down on our heads.
Listen, I want you to call her up,tell
her you've got some information.
Make sure she picks you up,and
get in the car,all right?
Lincoln bought a gun.
Just thought you'd want to know.
If you're really leaving,take
me with you. Please?
I don't want to be here anymore.
You don't want any part of this.
There's a part of me that doesn't
want to believe he works for them
'cause he's the man I loved,the man
who was going to take me to mparis.
If he doesn't take you,I will.
Impressive,blanco.
Too bad you won't be around to enjoy it.
How long is this going to set us back?
All right. We got 24 hours
to dig out that tunnel.
You mean the one it took you guys
three days to dig the first time?
Let's just say, by some miracle
we are able to part the dirt sea, Moses.
Then what?
How you plan on getting
around the guards tower?
Michael, Mr. Whistler here says that,you
know, you got stopped last time by a cloud.
I'm still working on that.
I'd like to know if this girl's gonna put out
before I spend any more time buying her drinks!
I agree,Michael.
You know as well as I
do what's riding on this.
I'd say I know better.
I don't care who knows what so long as somebody
knows how the hell we getting out of here by tomorrow.
You coming?
Not today.
James and I have a lot
of things to clear up,
but I'm done trying to
do it through a fence.
You ever wish you could go back in time?
Just to remember how it was
like when things made sense?
Every day for the last three years.
Is that Whistler's girlfriend?
Why is she staying in the car?
Guess she thinks she'll see him tomorrow.
You've been spending a
lot of time together,huh?
And?
You sure that's wise?
Where are we?
Behind schedule.
But we should be on the same side
of the fence by tomorrow afternoon.
What do you mean,"should"?
The tunnel gets us
into no-man's-land.
To get to the fence,we're going to need
a new diversion of the tower guards.
What time?
Daytime's still our best option.
They double the guards at night.
- And the jeep patrols?
- Yeah.
And,uh...there's something else.
What?
T-bag's coming.And mahone.Bellick.
Oh,yeah,there's a drug lord,too.
You know what?It's not about
them.It's about whistler.
- We got to do whatever...
- you don't need to know who whistler is.
What about what he's worth?
My son's life.
I just wish there was
another way to do this.
To save lj without
handing whistler over.
Look,man,that's it. There isn't.
I know.
Listen,you worry about the
tunnel,I worry about the guards.
- See you tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
Hey,now,don't skimp
on the braces up there.
In fact,if you want to
add a little extra,just...
you know,we can work on this
railroad all...the livelong day,
but it don't matter if scofield doesn't
know what happens once we get off the train.
Once we get out of here,it's
every man for himself.
Scofield's not
responsible for any of us.
Is that so?
You obviously don't know
him very well,shakespeare.
When we broke out of fox river,he
tried to screw every one of us.
Half the men ended up either
dead,captured or worse.
The guys who are easiest to catch
are the one's who spend more time pissing
and moaning at each other than running.
My only advice to you,ecclesiastes 6:13.
"Separate thyself from thy
enemies,and take heed of thy friends."
How we doing,alex?
Well,if those braces hold,we could
be to the surface sometime tomorrow.
Let's rotate.
Keep everybody fresh.
Welcome to the coal mine,canary.
*******
Cho!
Don't drop your body-water
upon me like that!
Hey,it ain't coming from me,I swear.
Engineer,come. Look at this.
- We hit a pipe or something?
- Oh,no.
That's right above our tunnel.
That's not going to hold till tomorrow.
So what do we do?
We leave tonight.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ
Prison
Break Season03 Episode11
tonight?
I thought you said a nighttime
escape was impossible.
S up,the tunnel will collapse
again,and that'll be the end of it.
It'll be the end for you.
You're the one on a deadline.
What if it gives out while we're inside?
- We end up like buried treasure.
- You want out,get out!
Look,you're not pulling this off tonight
without all of us working around the clock.
And none of us are ever making
it out of here without his plan,
so if you tell me that you can figure
out a way how to do this at night,
then I-- we-- can figure out a way
how to get that tunnel dug in time.
Let's start digging.
I think you dropped something.
I've read in old newspapers
that make it to sona
how americans hold others
to standards they ignore.
How they think no one
should have power but them.
I tell everyone it's a
lie,but I see it's true.
*******Aving.
And I think that after
everything I've done to help,
I think it sucks you're
not taking me with you!
I know it doesn't seem like it
now,but I'm doing you a favor.
I'm giving you a gift.
Oh,wow,life in prison. Thank you.
I've always wanted one of those.
It's better than a life on the run.
I don't belong here.
- All I did was give a guy...
- you're not going!
I'm sorry.
It's for the best.
How do you know what's best for me?
Y cuanto me va costar?
Okay,muchas gracias.
It's good to go.
You know where and when to be,right?
If you're not there,we're screwed.
You all right?
I'm fine.
- I'm just going to grab my stuff.
- Yeah.
Probably best if you
and james disappear.
I know. I know.
You know where to meet us,right?
Playa blanca.
You'll be on the...
- 3-12.
We'll see you tomorrow then.
Good luck.
You,too.
hey,it's that susan chick.
She wants to meet again.
Good.
Let her know everything's on track.
We want to make her feel
as comfortable as possible.
Why shouldn't she be?
She's going to get
her guy tomorrow,right?
Well,if Michael's conscience
doesn't get in the way.
What do you mean?
He's having doubts.
About if he can pull it off?
About if he should.
But he's going to go
through with it,right?
What are you looking for?
Where the power lines connect
to sona's exterior lights.
If cutting the power out there was an
option,why didn't we do that in the first place?
One,the power out there
isn't controlled from in here.
And,two,there's that.
Every prison has a backup generator.
Even if we cut the lights,they'll
just come back on again immediately.
Well,that's a big,bloody problem.
Tell lechero I need his phone.
Change of plans,linc.
We're doing this tonight.
Tonight?
What happened,Michael?
Rain,dirt,tunnel,problem.
How long can it hold?
That depends.
Depends on what?
When the rain stops.
You said breaking out
at night was impossible.
Yeah,well...
you want to tell me how
you're going to pull this off?
For starters,I need
to get ahold of sucre.
Sucre,do you know
what I do for a living?
I have a pretty good idea.
I read people.
And you,my friend,are a coloring book.
I think you left this imy car.
Look. That...that was just...I mean...
no. No,no,no,no.
My fault.
I guess I just didn't make myself clr when
I laid out the terms of our arrangement.
So I'm going to try again
as simply as I know how.
Anything happens-- anything
at all i wasn't expecting--
and there will be one less
pregnant girl in chicago.
Look, Michael and Lincoln
don't tell me everything.
Fernando,this is your last chance.
I want a yes or a no.
Are the brothers gonna
break whistler out of sona?
Yes.
Are they planning on
handing him over to me?
Yes.
Where do you want me to shoot maricruz
first,in the bun or in the oven?
Okay!
There's one thing I heard.
It's Michael.
He's,he's having some
concerns about whistler.
What kind of concerns?
About handing him over.
You got to understand,he broke
out some pretty bad guys last time.
I think he's never
forgiven himself for that.
He's planning on leaving him behind?
Maybe. I don't know.
Hello,Lincoln.
It's going down tonight.
Tonight?
Should I be worried?
I called you first thing.
I'm being straight up with you.
That's refreshing.
So I'll see you tonight.
You show me yours and
I'll show you mine.
It's going down tonight.
Do you know about that?
I didn't know,I swear.
Get out of here.
How'd it go?
She found the bomb,linc.
The one we put in her car.
How did she find the bomb,sucre?
I don't know,bro. I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Look,I'll make it up to you,I swear.
You can start now. Michael's
in a bit of trouble in sona.
What kind of trouble?
The rain stopped.
- Does that mean...
- No.
The damage is done.
We can't risk waiting.
anything interesting?
Like some coordinates the company
might want to get their hands on?
If they didn't want me out of
here and your nephew was safe,
would you still be doing this?
Breaking out?
No.
Why would you choose to stay if
there was a chance at freedom?
Well,I guess that's the
difference between us.
I'm wiing to pay for my sins.
And I'm not?
That's a good question.
water's coming down pretty
fast up in here,patron.
Yeah. We have to dig faster.
You know,I've been thinking.
It doesn't have to be
every man for himself.
You and I can help each other.
If i need a hand,I'll
find someone with a spare.
while it's true I may be
lacking something in the west,
I more than make up for it in the north.
Think about it.
Scofield's got us down here
doing manual labor; slave labor.
I ain't no slave.
I'm doing this for me.
Why do you think scofield's
up there and we're down here?
He's planning something.
Who among us isn't?
what the hell is that?
OK,let's unload here
Make the animals walk through the filth
Come here
Let's go
Good.Good!Keep going!
- we're good.
- Yeah.
We're all right. Okay.
yeah.
Hello,Lincoln.
Long time no see.
Not long enough.
I was thinking that we could
have a little chat in person.
Make sure we're all on the same page
about what's gonna happen tonight.
All right.
30 minutes,this location. I'm
sending a text. Can't we just...
Jorge!
Sorry.What's up?
It's payday
You're first
You need to pick up your check
**gracias.
See you later.
hello.
Hey,papi,it's me.
Lincoln said you needed some help.
How much do you know about electricity?
Hey,you're back.
I'm not real comfortable being
alone down here with those...
what's that?
Syrup; honey.
Make a little pile of
dirt. Gather some dirt.
Scofield said we got to make something
to cover the hole once we get out.
So when the lights go back on it's
gonna look like nobody ever left.
Go ahead. Spread it around.
I was thinking...
we should be a team,you know?
Not just during the escape,but after.
Like,like butch and sundance.
Butch and sundance died.
Well,I mean in the other parts.
Here's an idea.
We go along with scofield's plan,and
then when everyone stops to take a breath,
we grab 'em,burroughs,scofield,bagwell.
We take 'em back home to face charges.
Hell,we'd be heroes.
Might even get a book deal.
We could write it
together,alex. How'd that be?
- A book deal?
- Yeah.
Gonna make you happy,brad?
You got a better idea?
Yeah,I do.
Something to do with a wife and kid?
Yeah,something like that.
You got room for one more?
Come on,alex.
What's a guy like me gonna do?
Let's just let scofield get us out of here,and
then we'll worry about everything else,all right?
All right.
Come on. A little more dirt.
Listen very carefully and
do exactly as I tell you.
You sure you don't want linc to do this?
He knows more about this than I do.
It's not about what you know.
It's about where you work.
And as a sona employee,my friend,you have the
unique ability of not getting shot for being here.
You see the admin building?
I see it.
Go to it and make a left.
To it and left. Got it.
On the other side is a berm.
There should be a metal cage.
That's the backup generator.
Okay,I see it.
Don't let the tower guard
see you get too close.
Just act casual.
When I say now,you
run and duck behind it.
Almost.
Hold on.
Now!
Okay. Okay.
There should be some
writing near the bottom.
I need the name of the manufacturer,make
and model number,anything.
Yeah,yeah,yeah,I got it,I got it.
It's,uh,it's,uh,prana industrial.
Model number 3210.
1-800-555-1212.
All right. Thanks.
That's all I need.
You really think you can
pull this off tonight?
You want to know the truth?
No,I just want all of it go down smooth.
For everyone to get what they want.
Yeah,I do.
Listen,even if you get this
worked out with the lights,
what are you gonna do
about the jeep patrols?
We're just gonna have
to take our chances.
Maybe you don't.
You all right?
Yeah,I'm fine.
Where's lj?
Somewhere safe.
Take a load off.
Can I offer you a drink?
What's going on,susan?
I just wanted to get everyone together
so we can discuss tonight's agenda.
Maybe nail down a few guidelines.
It's the same as
before,nothing has changed.
Actually,I was thinking we should
probably include all the players.
Don't you?
What are you doing in here?
Just keeping watch.
Make sure nobody tries
to get down to the tunnel.
Who are you calling?
Yeah,hi. Is this,uh,customer service?
Yeah,I'm,uh...
I'm a sub working,building down here in
panama,and,um,we got a client on-site.
They're asking questions about the
3210 generator we're installing.
Yeah. Exactly.
anyway,they want to know,if
the main power shuts down,
how long are they gonna be in the
dark,um,before the generator kicks in?
Yeah. Thanks.I'll hold.
You're a very good liar.
That's the timing?
No,that's,uh... that's it.
Appreciate it.
Well? We gonna make it?
We should have just
enough dark to make it out.
With everyone?
You with whistler?
Yes.
Susan has got a message.
Why?
Put him on.
It's for you.
Yes?
All right,I got him. What now?
Tell him I want him to listen very
carefully to the following instructions.
- She wants you to listen real care...
- I can hear.
Instructions about what?
James?
Was that sofia?
Is she there?
Yeah.
What's going on?
He wants to know what this is about.
All right. I'll tell him.
no!
Was... was that just...
is that sofia?
Is that sofia?
Have you figured out the
coordinates yet,james?
Please.
Almost.
Wrong answer.
- No!
I'll get them for you when
we get out of here,I swear.
All your promises,your
guarantees-- they mean nothing.
I'm pretty sick of waiting around
for you boys to screw me over.
I want those coordinates
by the end of the day.
we gotta figure this out.
Gotta do something.
We both know that you can't
just hand over that information.
Why?
Why can't I?
Once they get what they want,they'll have no reason
to keep you or your girlfriend or my nephew alive.
So what do I do?
I,I just,I just let them torture sofia?
We'll work something out.
We'll think it through.
I already have.
Whistler...
whistler.
What is so special about him anyway,huh?
You think he has anything to do with why them
people wanted scofield down here in the first place?
It's really none of my business.
What exactly is your business,alex?
Something on your mind?
I'm just saying...
if we needed a bargaining
chip,do you think...
a sharp stick in that dull
limey would help us out?
There is no "us."
You and me are a lot more
alike than you think,alex.
We both know how it feels
to lose a great love.
How it feels to kill a man.
And we both ended up in here
because of Michael scofield.
Wouldn't it be poetic
justice if we could just...
return the favor?
Justice,huh?
If there was an ounce of
it left in this world...
you'd be lying face down in the same unmarked
grave as the rest of your inbred family.
The only difference between me and you,alex,is
a badge,and the last time I checked,
you didn't even have that,so you can just
keep on hoping for your happy endings,
alex,you just keep on plowing
ahead with them blinders on,
you know,but the thing
about them blinders is...
it makes it really
hard to watch youback.
It's gonna be better soon,I promise.
He's right,you know.
If james loves you the way he says
he does,he'll give us what we want,
and then you and your white knight
can ride off into the sunset.
Unless you're already with him.
You scared,susan?
Do I look scared,Lincoln?
To pull something like this...
you desperate?
You need to stop fighting with me.
If you really understood what was going
on,you would know that we're not the bad guys.
Could've fooled me.
Haven't you ever done the
wrthings for the right reason?
What are the right reasons,susan?
What is it about whistler
that's so important.
I could tell you.
But then I'd have to kill you.
You're gonna do that anyway.
Whistler gives us what we
want,maybe I won't have to.
Linc called.
They're on their way.
I figured them out.
The coordinates.
I'm gonna hand them over.
I thought you should know so you can
take whatever precautions you can.
What if,uh...
what if you give them
the wrong coordinates.
It might buy us some more time.
Maybe linc can get sofia to safety.
Like he did with sara?
I'm sorry. I...
I didn't mean to. I,uh...
I just don't know what else to do.
I'm damned if I do.
I'm damned if I don't.
There's no way to win.
It's not about winning anymore.
It's about surviving-- which
is not the same as giving up.
But you can go gracefully.
There's honor.
Protecting the ones you love.
Honor's a luxury men
like us can't afford.
Can you promise me we'll
make it out of here tonight?
No games.
Can you honestly promise me?
I can promise you I'll
do everything in my power.
I wish that were good enough.
If you do this...
if you give them what they want...
everything that's been lost
will have been for nothing.
Monjares.
What's up?
Take it easy.
Yes,I'd like to speak to
Officer Monjares,plesae
Hey Arturo.phone for you!
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I'm kind of in a hurry
I got some place to be
What's that?
Friends of mine are moving tonight
And they need my help
Tell them you're gonna be late
Let's go
Walk
linc,he's gonna...
he's gonna give it to them.
Relax.
I'll see you in a minute.
What are you talking about?
All clear.
I suppose introductions are
unnecessary at this point.
What are we doing here,gretchen?
We're here to say good-bye.
I promise you,sweetheart,they're
not going to hurt you anymore.
Do you have the coordinates,james?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- I tried to run away...
- this is not your fault.
It's mine.
When I took this job,I knew
they weren't good people.
I just didn't know how bad they were.
And everything that's happened...
it's all because of me.
And for that I'm truly sorry.
The coordinates.
Just pass them through.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm buying some goodwill.
You're buying her funeral.
You know I have what you need.
And I'll give you the rest.
But only after I know
that sofia,that lj,
and that these men here...
they're all safe.
Do you understand me?
James...
everything's gonna be all right.
I'm impressed.
It seems our fisherman grew
himself a set of oysters.
Can you really trust
these men with her life?
Yeah.
Yeah,I believe I can.
All right,james.
But there's been some confusion about the
timing of things-- last-minute changes,et cetera.
I'm gonna make this clear
for everyone involved.
If time runs out and I don't have
the second half of those coordinates,
lj and the senorita stop breathing.
Say good-bye,sweetheart.
Lincoln! Linc...
don't be stupid, Lincoln.
I've helped you.
Now you help me.
Please.
Just get us out of here.
- Bout the timing on the backup generator?
- Yeah.
All we got to do now is cut the
power to the exterior lights.
How are you gonna do that?
I'm not-- it can't be
accessed from the inside.
How much time have I got?
Let's say,uh,5:15 tomorrow morning.
That should give us enough time to dig
out the tunnel before the sun comes up.
All right. What about whistler?
What about him?
Well,he manned up-- he could've handed
over the information, but he didn't.
Still concerned about handing him over?
I've got my concerns about
pretty much everybody,linc.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Mostly, I'm just tired.
Tired of choices...
consequences.
I just want this to be over... tonight.
Let's do it.
When you're on the run,
you're always looking over your
shoulder,listening for the sirens,
wondering if that pretty girl across the street
is staring at you because she wants you,or...
because you're wanted.
You change your name, the way you look...
and leave everything you ever knew behind.
And the ones you love,they're
the ones who have to pay.
That's what's waiting
for you on the outside.
That's why I couldn't bring you on.
Because nothing good can come of this.
Can anything good come from staying in?
It has to be your decision. I...
I cannot be responsible for you.
You won't have to be.
Does your father still have
that phone number I gave you?
I think so.
Well, tell him to call my brother if he wants
to find out where to pick you up tomorrow.
Does that mean...
it means if a million
things fall into place...
I'm gonna see my father tomorrow.
Don't let anyone see
you with that phone.
I think we did it,Michael.
I believe we're ready.
She's a little wet, but she's ready.
Makes me think of the first thing
I'll do when we're gonna get out.
Just,does anybody know what's
spanish for "don't shoot"?
No dispare.
No dis what?
Just relax. Nobody's gonna get shot.
Just don't panic.
As soon as linc cuts the power,we go.
What about the jeep patrol?
Taken care of.
What about the backup generator?
Backup generator?
Nobody said anything about...
there's a lag from when the power cuts
out to when the generator kicks back in.
Well,how long a lag are
we talking about here?
30 seconds.
You expect us to run in 30 seconds?
As soon as the lights go out, I'm gone.
With or without you.
Please,my friends
They're
expecting me and--
I have some bad news,Jorge
We won't be able to pay you today
That's fine,I-I
can wait until-
When we ran your identification
through processing...
We found a slight problem
What..kind of a problem
You have a warrant out for your arrest
noW.
Let's go.
Off the bus! Now!
As soon as the lights go
out, we got to be ready to move.
You want to tell us what the hell
the taquito's doing down here?
He's coming with us.
I don't think so.
That's not up to you.
******
Oh,you got to be kidding me.
See,we made up our own decision here.
Well, with the time frame
being so short and all,
we'd feel a whole lot better
about things if we go first.
What are you gonna do,kill me?
T-bag: No,no.
- See,if we ain't first,he's not ***
- All right! All right! Just...
Look, I think I can explain all this
If I could just get some
paperwork from my car
You're not going anywhere
Understand?
all right.
All right,go. Just go.
Just go.
Every man for himself, right?
You want to move up in line, too?
No,I think I'm gonna stay back here.
I just don't want to turn my back on anybody.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ
Prison
Break Season03 Episode11
www.tvsubtitles.net