Previously on Prison Break:
I got nothing against you, kid.
- What are you doing, man?
- What they do.
Your pal Manche told me all
about your little treasure hunt
for Westmoreland's stash.
We're going to Utah.
Fooled you.
Hands behind your back.
- Make yourself at home.
- Sure.
Your father got a call
from the White House.
They withdrew his nomination.
According to them,
his confirmation was
going to be a problem.
My father is not
a suicidal man.
Governor Tancredi,
not part of our plan.
Anyone who knows anything
has got to be dealt with.
If someone's a liability,
they go.
Tancredi was becoming a liability.
So was his daughter.
Wait, what?
Burrows is scheduled
to be released
from the Klipton Detention Center in
Kingman, Arizona tomorrow morning.
LJ is out there;
I'm going to get him.
Take care.
Charles Westmoreland...
God bless you and your
wrinkled old sack.
- It's all here.
- Where's Sucre?
Drop the bag.
No one's going anywhere.
What the hell are
you doing, man?
- Sucre, whatever it is you want...
- I want the money, all of it.
What, are you robbing us?
The money was never yours to begin with.
This is about business.
$5 million worth of business.
So this is how it's
going to go down, huh?
After everything.
Once a thief, always a thief.
You just figuring that out?
The backpack.
Now!
Don't do this, buddy.
Yo, take a look
around you, papi.
It's three of us,
it's one of you;
you are outnumbered, man,
and we will come after you.
It'll be the last thing you do,
my brother.
What, are you going to
shoot at all of us?
Probably not.
But I will get two.
Now... which two
is it going to be?
That's what I thought.
Adios, amigos.
I don't believe this.
We have come all this way
and done all of this work.
Thought you was
compadres, Tattoo?
So what are we going
to do now, man?
The police are going
to be here any second.
Ain't no way I'm letting that
dunderpate ride off with five... !
It's your choice.
It's all right.
All right,
I'm going to give you this, and, uh...
you should be able to cut
yourself free in about an hour.
- So what's the plan, man?
- Well, you can do what you want.
I let that psychopath
T-Bag loose once.
I'm not going to do it again.
Make a nice little present for
the police when they get here.
Where is he?
I don't know, man, look, I got to...
I got to go.
Uh, good luck.
They're going to get you.
Ms. Tancredi.
I didn't mean to startle you.
What the hell are you
doing in my house?
No reason to be frightened.
I used to work with your father.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
My father didn't
commit suicide.
What are you doing?
Making sure it doesn't
look like I did!
People will ask questions if the day
the governor was found killing himself,
his daughter is found dead in
what looks like a struggle.
Well, then.
What if they don't find her?
In an apparent attempt
to avoid jail time,
the governor's daughter
skips bail and disappears.
We're talking about your last minutes,
Ms. Tancredi.
Please don't do this.
That stuff on that table is premium.
It's grade "A."
Do yourself a favor,
go out on a high.
- Look, I'm begging you here.
- One last ride.
Oh, God!
Adios, amigos, huh?
- What? Too much?
- You were great.
This thing is
freaking heavy, dude.
Won't be so bad
after we split it up.
- Three ways: me, you and Linc.
- Four.
We're going to send a share
to Charles's daughter,
with her father's love,
just like we promised.
What about C-Note? I feel kind
of bad about the whole thing.
There's no way to know
if we could trust him.
Once we get down to Panama,
we'll send something up to his family,
make sure he's taken care of.
Five million dollars.
I can't believe
I'm going to be...
Where the hell is the money?
The backpack... now!
Mr. Burrows?
Merry Christmas from the state.
Here's a list of options
available to you.
Places to stay,
businesses that are
more open to hiring men out
of the correctional system.
Any questions you might have
about your immediate future?
No.
Well, the number on
there is toll-free.
If you encounter any problems,
you can call there 24-7.
Thanks.
Wait a second. You know what?
Why don't you tell me
where you need to go,
and I'll make sure
you get there.
You know,
I think I'll be all right.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Thank you.
Kid didn't bite. He's on foot.
All right.
Have your men follow.
Remember, it's the father we want.
We can't go back.
You said it, without the money,
we're screwed. We can't...
- Just let me think.
- Maybe it's still back...
Just let me think!
Let me think.
Maybe it's still
back at the house.
The money's not back at
the house unless T-Bag is.
He must've switched the packs.
Wh-what do we do...
What do we do now?
We still got the five grand we
took when we pocketed the money.
It's not gonna be five million,
but it might be enough to
get us where we're going.
All units be advised.
Escaped convicts from Fox
River have been positively ID'd
at 1131 Monterey Lane.
We have dogs being
dispatched to the location.
I want every road in or
out of town blocked off.
I don't care if it's on wheels,
rails or hooves.
I want it stopped and searched.
I thought you said we
would have a head start.
It was the gunshot, buddy.
One of the neighbors must've heard.
How fast can that thing go?
I don't know.
Both of us, it could probably...
We're never gonna get
out of here on the roads.
We need to find another way.
He's in your office.
I can't believe they're
calling me back here
when my escapees are out there.
I want to know who this guy is.
Said his name was Sullin.
Son of a bitch.
Let me know if anything
breaks on the convicts.
- Alex.
- Thanks for coming in.
You want to tell me
why Internal Affairs
is pulling me out of the field
in the middle of a manhunt?
It's been a while since we've
had a sit-down, hasn't it?
Not since the Shales escape,
am I right?
Yeah, yeah.
What's going on, Richard?
Well... that's precisely
what I'm here to find out.
And you're not getting
out of here until I do.
Oh, my God. Civilization.
What can I get for you boys?
- You tell me.
- Two waters, then.
And the use of your phone,
if you'd be so kind.
Don't worry, it's a local call.
First thing I do, we get home:
clean underwear.
Then what?
I guess go back to that liquor store,
beg for my job back.
We had it. We were so close.
I can still taste that money right
there in the back of my throat.
Well, nothing that a
couple of Keystones,
an hungry man
Salisbury steak dinner
and a night in front of
the TV won't take care of.
Hey, Mom, it's Brad.
Hey, listen, me and Roy,
we ran into some car trouble and...
we were wondering if you
could come pick us up.
I don't know, hold on.
What the hell town is this?
Thought you said this
was a local call.
Hey, Bradley, check this out.
...these individuals were
reportedly the prisoners
who escaped from the Fox
River penitentiary in Illinois
just a couple of days ago.
What were they doing all the
way out here in Tooele, Utah?
Well, Jeanette Owens, whose garage
they dug up, has her own theory.
They pretended that they were some kind
of workers from the power company,
and that they had made a mistake
and they'd have to do some digging.
Hey, Mom, on second thought,
can you wire us some extra scratch?
Turns out, we ain't done yet.
Hello.
- Bruce, I need your help.
- Sara?
Bruce, my father
didn'tcommit suicide, okay?
Okay, just calm down.
Where are you?
He was looking into
the Burrows case and
I think that he found something
that they didn't ho know.
And now, I think that they
think that I know it, too.
All right,
I want you to listen to me.
I'm gonna send someone
over to pick you up.
I'll bring you back here, and we'll
sort all of this out, I promise.
Just tell me where you are.
Uh, I don't know,
I'm at a pay phone on...
Third and Harper.
Do you have your cell in
case I need to reach you?
Uh, I do, but I thought it
would be tapped. I don't know.
Someone's on their way.
Just stay right where you are.
Thank you.
- I'll give you 80 bucks for them.
- Come on, man, they're worth...
Worth a lot more to the person
they actually belong to.
These are ladies clubs, doctor.
I'm guessing they're hotter in
a monkey's jockstrap. 80 bucks.
Thrwo in the cooler,
and you got a deal.
- We got to lose the bike.
-Uh-uh. No way.
The roads are sealed.
It's the only way we're
gonna make it out of here.
I can't, bro.
I promised Petey...
You're not getting that
thing across the river.
And every minute we spend trying
is a minute we don't have, okay?
I'm sorry. We gotta move.
I've heard about
these kinds of places.
They got leeches, you know.
I'll take the leeches in here
over the handcuffs back there.
I don't know, papi.
Sort of depends on where the leech
leeches, you know what I'm saying?
Stop kidding.
- Are alright, buddy?
- I can't... I can't move!
You feel like you
broke anything?
No, I don't think so.
Can you get it off me?
This thing's not going anywhere.
I'm gonna check your foot.
That's allright buddy.
It's stuck.
Call 911.
Kelli, my name is Sara.
I'm a doctor. You're gonna be okay.
Can you hear me?
You'll be all right.
Take some deep breaths and...
Kelli?
Kelli.
It's gonna be okay, right?
I mean, if you can get
eight people out of prison,
you can get my Puerto Rican
ass out of this, right?
Can't you?
Come on!
Damn it!
Do you hear that?
I know that sound.
There's a dam up river.
It's a signal.
It means they're
opening the locks.
That means the water
level's gonna rise,
and when it does,
the log will just float right off.
Yeah?
Canine units at the scene
have multiple scents
and are spreading
out into the field.
These guys can't have
gotten very far.
There were six cons
back at that house.
They'll be tracking us
in every direction.
It'll take an hour just to make it
over this far, and by that time,
the water level will rise,
we'll be long gone.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm sure.
Ask any of the 20 cops there,
John Abruzzi was armed.
John Abruzzi drew his weapon...
He never should have been
allowed to get that far.
Richard, let's be clear.
If you knew how things needed
to be handled in a manhunt,
you'd be out there running one
instead of hamstringing
the men that are.
The FBI's primary objective in
investigating fugitive matters
is to affect the swift location
and capture of the fugitives.
You have two dead bodies, Alex.
I've got two dead
felons, Richard.
Now, maybe that doesn't play well
from a public relations standpoint,
but from a public
safety standpoint,
Abruzzi and Apolskis
were by the book.
Shooting of an unarmed kid at
point-blank range is by the book?
Come on.
Incident report,
David "Tweener" Apolskis.
You know, I'm curious,
was he cuffed during transport?
Yeah.
Says in here he somehow managed
to grab your primary weapon.
You carry that in
a shoulder holster?
- Hip.
- Left, right? Right, left?
- Left.
I'm sorry,
I get confused sometimes.
So just so I've got this right,
you were driving along alone
with a cuffed prisoner, and
somehow he reaches forward across
your chestand grabs your weapon.
Huh. It's too bad you didn't
react that quickly with Apolskis.
Maybe he'd still be alive.
What does an origami bird
have to do with any of this?
Michael Scofield
sent it to her.
And since your brilliant
plan to eliminate
Sara Tancredi from the equation
failed so completely--
I wouldn't say it failed
completely at all.
There's a dead woman
in a phone booth.
Civilian.
A certain number of bodies
you can sweep under the rug.
President's rug is getting so full,
you can hardly stand on it.
So what do you
suggest we should do?
- You ever go fishing, Bill?
- Just make your point.
There's two ways to catch a fish.
You cast out a big net and hope
you get what you're
looking for.
Or you choose the right bait
and guarantee that you do.
It's a simple strategy,
plays across the board.
LJ will lead us to Burrows.
Sara will lead us to Scofield.
And how do you intend
to follow Sara,
when the only lead
got is an origami bird
with an out of
service phone number?
Maybe it's not a phone number.
What do you have?
Junior's on the move,
but still no sign of Burrows.
Sir, the guy's in hiding,
maybe he doesn't even
know his kid's out.
The cop that was
held hostage in Utah
has Burrows splitting off
from the rest of the group
just after word of LJ's
release hit the wire. He knows.
Now if we want to know
for sure if he's there,
we need to do something
to draw him out.
Hey, you mind
sparing some change?
No.
- Come on.
- No, I'm all tapped out.
You got something.
I'll take whatever you got.
Look, seriously, I just got out
of lock-up. I would if I could.
Sorry.
I see,
you think you're better than me, huh?
I don't think I'm
better than you.
- Yo, where you running, little man?
- I'm not running anywhere.
This isn't how it's
supposed to go.
The whole reason I went
along with the break
was to have a life with
Maricruz and my baby.
And now what?
Get some two-bit job?
Always be looking
over my shoulder?
What kind of life is that?
You can come with me and Linc.
To Panama. Start over.
The longer you stay here,
the more chance there is you'll
never make it to Panama.
You've got other
people to think about.
Your brother,
your nephew. Sara.
She's meeting you down there,
isn't she?
I don't know.
We never talked about it.
- But you're hoping.
- Just give it a rest, will you.
The dogs are locked in.
We've got two trails merging.
They were definitely here. They've
headed east towards Drucker Ranch.
They've gone off-road.
Any additional units,
we need to setup a one-mile
perimeter and then start closing in.
It's getting deeper.
So how come this freaking
thing ain't moving yet?
Let me check.
You all right?
Look, Michael...
I understand if you have to keep going,
you know.
Just shut up.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, but, look,
just think about it.
- You know, if I leave you drown.
- No, I know, but just...
The water level's
getting higher, Sucre.
How many seconds can you
hold your breath? 45? 60?
That's how long you've
got to live if I take off.
How long do you
have if you stay?
How long till the dogs
lead the cops here?
What you're suggesting
is not an option.
Look, I ain't trying to
be a hero or nothing.
We both know there are only
two things that can happen now.
Leave me here...
or we both get caught.
- Bruce.
- Oh, Sara.
I know we said not
to use this number,
but I just needed to
know you were okay.
My driver said he went to pick you
up and the place was a crime scene.
Yeah, the woman that he saw,
the woman by the pay phone,
that was supposed to be me.
And I had to leave her there.
I didn't know what to do.
Bruce, who are these people?
They knew exactly where I
was going to be standing.
They knew where I
was going to be...
- Sara?
- It was you.
What are you
talking about, Sara?
I just need to know
where you are.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me, we'd like to check on
a friend of ours, LJ Burrows?
He's getting some stitches.
We just want to make
sure he's all right.
And you can see him when he's through.
It's policy.
You don't get it.
I get that that kid
defended himself.
You going to tell us why you
attacked him in the first place?
- I told you man.
- I know, some guy paid you.
- Some guy paid me to do it.
- Excuse me. FBI.
What do you mean
somebody paid you?
What the hell does
it sound like, man?
Some dude gave me 50 bucks
to give the kid a beat down.
It's Burrows. He's here.
- How you feeling, son?
- Dad?
We got to move.
Well, there's not much you can do,
you know.
Excuse me, ladies.
I need to ask you a few questions.
I'm on the, uh,
follow-up investigation team.
Excuse me.
Uh, we're just curious.
Did you see if the convicts actually
found what they were digging for?
No. But sure sounded
like they did.
The Spaniard, he took off with
one of my daughter's camping packs
and he left the other
ones in a real tizzy.
Sounded like he screwed
'em over something fierce.
And they just let him leave?
Well, they weren't happy about it,
but, yeah.
He took off on his motorbike,
and then they left
a few minutes later.
- Together?
- No.
The pretty one and the black fellow,
they left first,
and then that dirty Southerner...
he snuck out the back.
But he was moving kind of slow,
you know,
the weight of that backpack
and that disability that...
Wait a minute,
he had a backpack, too?
Yes. He came back in and slipped this
into my brassiere on his way out.
He said it was to
cover the damages.
Um, we're going to need
to keep this as evidence.
Thank you for your time.
Get in the car.
Seven, three, six, space.
Three, three, nine, space.
Eight, six, eight, seven.
And what exactly
are you looking for?
A pattern. A code. Anything.
What? What are you trying
to tell me, Michael?
They say...
people come into your
life for a reason.
Maybe my reason was to help
you get out of Fox River.
You know,
to help you save your brother.
No.
- To help you save your brother.
- No.
It's okay, papi. Let me go.
We're a quarter mile up the river
below the dam. They're close.
It's now or never, Michael.
I want you to hold your breath.
- Okay?
- Why?
Just do it.
I'll be right back, I promise.
What the hell are you doing?
Redirect all units
to the river.
I want you to go under.
And then stick your arm up,
above the water, high.
And then when you start
running out of air,
wave it back and
forth so I can see it.
And I'll come back and get you.
Okay? All right,
give me your hand.
One... two... three.
Come on. Come on!
Sucre!
Talk to me.
Well, there is one possibility,
but it's almost too rudimentary.
We know we're not looking
at a phone number,
but maybe we're not
looking at numbers at all.
What's important are the letters
that correspond to that number.
Three dots, third letter "R."
Three possibilities per number.
That's thousands of letter combinations.
But only one of them's
spells out a word.
Question is where.
Hey. What are you
in the market for?
Four wheels and a gas pedal.
Hey, Petey. Uh, it's me.
Uh, listen,
I got something to tell you.
Yeah, well, I was wondering
when you were gonna call.
Yeah, a lot has come down since
we last talked, and, uh...
Gee, I know, I heard.
You ruined it.
Yeah. Um... You heard already?
Well, brother,
everybody's heard, man,
and let me tell you something, man.
Hector is pissed.
What does Hector
have to do with it?
It was his wedding.
Wait, man.
What are you talking about?
Your bike.
- The wedding.
- What about the wedding?
Well, you know the part where,
uh, you say, "I do"?
Maricruz said, "I don't."
She did?
Left homeboy standing at the altar
holding his spam in his hand,
if you know what I'm saying.
What were you telling
me about my bike?
All right.
I'll go get your keys.
I got a couple stops to make.
First is this place
called Blanding.
Then we'll meet up with
Lincoln in a couple days.
I can't go.
She said no, papi. Maricruz...
Maricruz told that son of a...
She told him no.
- Can you believe that?
- That's great.
I know. Now, I just...
No. Go on. Get your girl.
What about Panama?
We said that we were gonna...
Some other time.
Panama's not going to go anywhere.
This is, uh, in case you run
into trouble down the road.
In the river...
I told you to leave me behind.
Yeah, well, I tried, but, uh,
then I got tangled up
in the rope, so...
Okay, here you go.
Thanks, and, uh,
we'll need another car.
Do you really think the
diaper sniper got all of it?
Only one way to find out.
If you were Bagwell,
and you just got your hands on
$5 million, where would you go?
You think you're the only
one who feels betrayed?
I'm gonna get out of here some day.
And when I do,
don't think I won't remember
what your front steps look like.
Let me get this straight.
You paid that meth-head
to whoop my ass?
Yup.
Feds were waiting for me to come
get you. It was the only way.
- It worked, didn't it?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it got me four stitches.
Adds character.
Here, take that.
There's some ice in there.
Put it on the eye.
Keep the swelling down.
I've been in a few
fights in my day, too.
Too many.
There's one more bird.
Clean it. Every surface,
like she never came home. Go on.
You know,
waiting for your flight from Utah,
I had a little extra
time for due diligence,
so I decided to dig a little
deeper on your history,
or rather lack of one.
Starts off simple enough.
Poor family.
Mom leaves, cites spousal abuse.
Somehow your dad holds
onto custody, and
by the look of these
pediatric meds,
he beats you like a harp seal
for the next four years.
Big shock-- poor, abused kid,
not a lot of options--
he joins the military.
Will there be any actual questions,
or is this just a show-and-tell?
Okay, I got one.
How does a guy go from infantry
grunt with less than stellar marks
to the Gulf 1, special ops,
to the Federal Bureau
of Investigations,
leading the largest manhunt
this country's ever seen?
I have all these dots.
And there's just no way to connect them.
Looks like you need to work on
your clearance level... Dick.
- Or maybe I just work on you.
- You want to do this?
I will chain you to this desk
until I get some answers I
cannot fertilize my lawn with.
You sure you want to do this?
I know what they tell
you to do overseas, Alex,
and let me make it
perfectly clear--
We do not do it
on American soil.
Sir, uh,
there's a phone call for you.
I'll take it later.
Uh, sir,
you're gonna want to take this now.
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
I, uh... I'm with him now.
Where you going, Rick?
I thought we were really
starting to get somewhere.
Let's go.
Alex.
You got something for me?
Open it.
The numbers correlate to
the letters on a phone.
Only on this one, none of the
possible combinations make sense.
We think it's a location,
a rendezvous point for Michael Scofield.
You find it, you find him.
You know, you could have
gotten me out of there sooner.
You know, even we have to
go through certain channels
to make things appear
on the up-and-up.
You know all about that,
don't you, Alex?
Keeping up appearances.
Good.
I was just making sure
that we're still clear
on the directive
of this manhunt.
You know, I understand the reasoning
behind Burrows and Scofield,
but these other men--
criminals that they may be--
there's nothing in their
profiles to suggest...
You've been hired to do a job.
The reasoning does not concern you.
Don't ask any questions about us,
and maybe we'll continue
to make sure no one asks any
questions about you. Are we clear?
They all die.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net