Explain something
to me, Blanco,
One minute you plead
for your friend's life,
and the next minute
you want to take it.
This man...
this man is no
friend of mine!
What happened to your
girlfriend has nothing...
Her name was Sara!
And she was a good person.
And she'd still be alive
if it wasn't for you.
So it's revenge, eh, boy?
An eye for an eye?
Once you make such a
declaration there's no going back.
There's nothing to go back to.
Good.
Then we have a fight.
Now, both of you,
go and assign your belongings,
and pray to
whatever god is yours.
Come back here
in 15 minutes.
Fight, fight, fight, fight...
fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight fight...
You need anymore help?
You've done
more than enough.
Here, take that, man.
It's not a lot, but it's
enough to get you started.
Oh, no, no,
I can't take this.
I did this because I
wanted to help you guys.
Hey, buy a car,
get a bus ticket,
do whatever,
just get out of here.
Thanks.
I'm going to get
some gas, okay?
I'll meet you in the front.
All right.
Is she coming with you
to do the exchange?
Yeah.
You think that's a good idea?
I mean, what if
something goes wrong
- and she gets hurt?
- I need some incentive
just in case Whistler
doesn't want to go quietly.
You think any of this is
going to go down quiet?
They're just going
to give you LJ
- just like that?
- Doesn't matter what I think.
I know what these
people are capable of.
I'm not going to
gamble with my son's life.
Maybe you don't have to.
Alex.
Yeah.
We'll be arriving at the
courthouse in about 15 minutes.
Then the hearing
will begin shortly.
All and all this whole thing will
be done within the hour.
Good.
That sounds good.
So with this deal...
what specifically are they
expecting from me?
They need to
know everything.
About the President,
about the company.
They want to
confirm that you have
viable incriminating information
and that you can be a
cooperative witness.
If I cooperate fully...
I won't just be incriminating them.
You're worried about all those
skeletons in your closet,
but you have full immunity.
Everything will be fine.
All you have to
do is tell the truth.
Stay calm.
Better knuckle up.
Look, I don't know
what you're thinking,
but killing me is not
- going to solve your problem.
- Relax.
I'm not going to kill you.
Then what the hell
was all that about?!
You want to make it out of
here without being seen,
you need a diversion.
Now we have one.
You're off your head. Do you
know that? They're waiting...
We don't have time for this.
It's almost 3:00,
and that means the tower
guard should be drugged by now.
At 3:13, the sun's going to hit
the other guard tower.
We'll have the cover we need.
It's now or never.
Listen, Michael, I, uh...
I meant what I said about Sara.
If I were you I wouldn't
mention that name again.
We're getting out of here now,
and then I'm trading you for my nephew.
And then I'm going to find out
who's responsible
for taking her life...
and I'm taking theirs.
---www.opensubtitles.org---
Prison Break
Season 03 Episode 07
"Vamonos"
- Listen, Scofield...
- Not now.
I just... please.
I heard you out
there in the yard.
Is that true
about Sara?
Yes.
That's not... I mean it's...
What'd she...?
I'm sorry, Michael.
I mean it.
She was a good person.
I'm sorry.
Is something wrong?
If anyone asks,
just tell them your fuel
pump's leaking, all right?
No, no, no, I'm going to
the beach with you.
No. I need you to keep a lookout.
When they get here
I'll call you, all right?
If everything works out today,
You and me-we're both
going to get what we want.
Stay here.
Sorry about that.
That's okay.
I know you're
just doing your job.
I bet you're as ready
for this to be over with as I am.
Hey, you know, once
we get out of Panama,
Me and my dad and my uncle
we're going to open up a
scuba shop somewhere.
- Build a house on the beach...
- Lovely.
go swimming every day.
- I never lived by the ocean...
- You can stop.
I always wanted to, you know?
I get it.
You're a human being
with dreams, plans for
the future, all that.
Whether you see it isn't
up to me anymore.
It's in your uncle's hands now.
So let's just hope that
he does his job.
What are you waiting for?
Where's Mahone?
He's gone.
What, just like that?
Why? I mean, how?
How about we worry a little bit
more about us, huh?
You know, he got out of
here kind of suddenly.
How do we know he's not
ratting us out right now?
Sullins.
When did this happen?
Are you sure? Yeah.
I'll handle it.
Something wrong?
A couple of the Panamanians
might have gotten cold feet.
Exactly how cold?
They just need
some convincing.
It's nothing to worry about.
It's all gonna work out.
Meantime, we're gonna take
you to a hotel room.
Up until an hour ago,
this was a done deal.
So... what's happening?
Relax.
This is still your best bet.
Unless someone's offering you
a "Get out of Sona free" card.
Now, remember, we'll only
have four minutes of cover,
so once you hit the ground you
run straight to the fence.
Don't look up,
don't look back,
don't say a word.
What if they see us?
If someone yells stop,
you stop.
That's it?
That's it.
It's time.
Where's Sammy?
So, who goes first?
Right now my life isn't worth
a damn without yours.
If this doesn't go as
planned, the first guy
through that window's
gonna get shot.
That guy can't be you.
I'll go.
I got it.
Come on, come on, come on.
This is it.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two... One.
The glare.
- Where's the glare?
- I don't know.
Come on
This is it.
Someone's coming.
Good luck.
You, too.
We're losing the light.
Go back. Go back!
Go back!
Come on! Come on!
That was our only chance.
Damn it!
Find out where they are.
Do you hear 'em out there?
They're waiting for us.
- It's only a matter of time.
- I know. Come on.
The damn thing's
not coming off!
Hey, Gringos!
Come out and play.
Come on! Come on!
Nowhere to hide, Malditos!
Gringos!
Come out and play!
We've got to go.
They can't find us here.
But what about this?
Stash it!
Come on!
Go.Go...
Where are you off to, Backra?
Where you boys been?
The bathroom?
This has all been
a terrible mistake.
Has it been?
We've, uh, we've worked it out.
There's no need to
take this any further.
You clearly don't understand
I can't have your foolishness
spread in this place.
I gave you every
chance to pull out.
Please.
We know the rules!
Two men go in,
one man comes out!
Now,
this quarrel must be settled.
Let's go.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
What are you
gentlemen waiting for?
You two don't make this
more interesting, I will.
Sorry, mate- if only
one of us is getting out...
How's it look?
They got LJ in
the back of the van.
- He seem all right to you?
- Yeah, I think so.
All right,
how many people they got?
She's got a driver and a
bodyguard- that's it.
All right. You know I appreciate
you hanging around, man
Hey, we started this together, bro.
Let's finish it that way.
Come on, Michael.
Where are you?
What you doing here?
You're supposed to
be keeping watch.
Just checking, making sure
everything is all right.
They're running a bit late,
that's all.
So, what's the plan?
You gonna swim out, wait for
the police to pass, and...
meet with a boat somewhere?
Something like that.
And then what?
You know what,
you need to get back
- to the car...
- Don't move.
I'm impressed.
You've actually got the guts to
look me in the eye
as you stab me in the back.
What are you
going to do, shoot me?
Don't.
I can't let you hand over
James to those people.
You need to think about
what you're doing.
I have!
Every since you told me what
they did to Sara.
When they get here,
James and I, we're leaving.
Where to?
I don't know.
Somewhere they won't find us.
So, this whole time,
you played me.
Like you've been playing me.
Bringing me here to
be your lookout?
But it's okay.
We were both here
doing what we had to
for the people we love.
You do this, you may as well
be shooting my son yourself.
I'm sorry.
They should be out by now.
Any sign?
All quiet.
How much longer do you
want to give them?
I know you wanted to live
by an ocean your whole life.
Sad to think
the closest you'll get is
being buried under one.
You're not gonna kill me.
- Oh?
- You need me.
You already killed Sara.
Anything happens to me,
you're out of bargaining chips.
If Michael doesn't get
Whistler out today,
I won't need to
bargain anymore.
You'll all be dead.
Hurtdo?
Kick him in the junk, Scofield!
What are you looking for, boy!
There are no draws here!
If this isn't finished
by one of you,
I'm coming down
to finish both of you.
Hurtdo?
End it.
God! God forgive me.
They should have
been here by now.
Maybe they get out.
They should be on their way.
- They didn't make it.
- So what do we do now?
I don't care what you do,
but I'm taking the car.
What?
What the hell's going on?
Put your hands
up on your head!
You come down here.
Now!
We are going to find
out who is behind this.
What?
Were you going to let me know
what the hell's going on?
Lincoln?
I'm here.
Good. Where are they?
They're in the car with me.
I heard the alarm.
They were long gone before
that thing went off.
Well, if they had such a head start,
why are you so far behind?
Listen, do you want me
to talk to your drive?
I want you to put
Whistler on the phone.
What?
Put him on.
He's in the trunk.
But, if you feel that
strongly about it,
I can pull over and you two
can have a nice little talk.
If we're real lucky, maybe
some cops will swing by.
I'm sure they'd like a word, too.
You know what?
Just get LJ ready.
Whoever tried to escape
assaulted one of my men.
And, as you know,
any attempt on the life
of a Panamanian soldier
Warrants the death penalty.
This attempt was made
from cell #212.
And if memory serves,
that cell belongs to
members of your crew, no?
You.
You are one of
the Milkman's boys.
Is it your cell?
I'm going to take
that as a "Yes".
I thought we were
compadres, you and I.
I let you run your business,
have your whores.
When you asked me for your own
personal supply of water
when the plumbing went down,
did I not provide it?
When you asked me to get rid
of the phones,
make them contraband,
so you could
control the trade in here,
did I not comply?
I do all this for you.
And in exchange,
you were to do one thing
for me.
Keep these men in line!
Maybe we just backed
the wrong horse.
Perhaps there is another in
here better suited for the job.
Good luck, Bredda.
You know none of us tried
to break out of that cell.
I do.
Then you must know there's
only one guy here
foolish enough to try.
Nice to see
you back in form.
Thanks.
Any news from Sullins?
He's working on it.
It doesn't matter
what people say.
What do they say?
You know people,
how they talk. About?
The men,
the ones they say you killed.
Is it true?
Because, if it is, you
can talk to about it.
Is that a fact?
Yes. You can trust me.
So let me get this straight.
Sullins sends you to be good cop?
That's not what this is.
There never was a deal,
was there?
Sullins just wants me to confess
so he can bring me up on more
charges back in the States.
The deal is legit.
The hearing was supposed to be
an hour after we left the prison,
and I'm still waiting.
So why don't you just come
clean, Felicia, huh?
For old times' sake?
How about it?
How about you do me the
same courtesy, Alex?
I'm not blind.
My brother was a user.
I can smell the stuff a mile away.
Don't you accuse me of being
the one who's hiding something.
Hey, I just got confirmation
from the radio.
The guards took a head count and
they secured the perimeter.
No one made it
out of there today.
Sucre, what's going on?
Looks like they're packing up.
Whatever you do
don't let them take LJ, all right?
Linc? Linc?
Sucre?
Get the hell
out of here now.
Look out!
Dad!
Let her go
Drop it or I swear to
God I'll put a bullet in her head!
Now you let him go!
You let him go now! Dad!
LJ, I'm going to get you out of this,
I promise.
You sure you want to make
promises to your son you can't keep?
Watch your mouth.
I'll let you in on a little secret.
When you choose
this line of work, you know it's
all going to come down
to a moment like this.
So kill me.
Let him go.
- Let him go!
- Kill him.
Kill him.
Dad!
It doesn't matter
what you do to me.
The operation failed.
So put your gun down, Linc.
Kill him.
Dad!
No!
No
Give me one more shot.
To do what?
Let me find out what
happened in Sona.
Let me talk to Michael.
We can still get Whistler.
We can make this happen.
We...
We can do this.
Put him in the van.
Sucre!
You all right?
What happened?
Body bags.
Look, what happened out there...
Happened out there. It's over.
All right then.
Right, just so you know,
I wouldn't have
gone through with it.
Lucky for us, we'll
never have to find out.
So what do we do now?
You know where are you, boy?
Well, I'm no doctor,
You but I'm just guessingboy.
your mother had a little bit too
much to drink one night
Keep talking
and you're going to be next.
How you want it, brother?
Fast or slow?
Think I like to
handle this one myself.
Do you have children, Mr. Scofield?
Maybe someday.
That's very optimistic for a
man in your position.
Myself, I have five.
Three boys, two girls.
Now I used to tell them a story-
I believe in your country
they call it,
"The Boy Who Cried Wolf. "
You know it?
Well, then you know
the moral of that story
is even when liars tell the truth,
they can never be believed.
But your life's on the line, boy.
Are you trying to break out of
this prison, Mr. Scofield?
No.
Are you trying to break
out of this prison?
We both know
that's not possible.
Answer me!
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me the truth.
I want to hear it.
- You want a reason to kill me.
- No, boy...
I have good reason to kill you.
Because of you,
it's no longer possible
for me to effectively
govern this prison.
Justified or not,
the men no longer
have faith in me.
That leaves only one
thing for me to do
to guarantee my survival.
You are breaking out of this
prison, Mr. Scofield.
And you're taking
me with you.
Well, I've got
some good news
and I've got
some better news.
Let's start with the good.
Panamanians are back on board.
And the better news?
You're going to get to have
a really nice sleep on that bed.
I thought that I...
After the hearing I was going to
be on a plane back to the U.S.
You said...
I did, and you will be,
but it's just too late to do
the hearing now.
We'll get to it
first thing tomorrow.
- Tomorrow morning?
- Sounds about right.
Please... is there something,
is there anything
that we can do to
help speed things up?
When a genie
grants you a wish
you don't really tell him
to make it snappy.
This hearing
needs to happen today.
The hearing needs...
needs to happen right now!
Listen to you.
You know,
you are unbelievable.
I have dropped everything
to come down here
and drag your sorry ass
out of that hellhole...
- You don't understand.
- I've made you a deal.
- I can't... I can't wait.
I can't wait.
You know, I am so glad
I have made this trip
to help your esteemed colleague.
I am just tickled.
Cuff him.
Is that necessary?
I'm sorry.
I can't wait.
Hey, have you seen Whistler?
No.
I spent my whole career
trying to keep bad
people behind bars.
Like somehow by doing my job
I was making the world
a better place.
And then...
then you hear about what
happened to someone like Sara.
Damn if it doesn't seem
like there's more bad people
out there than in here.
I warned the brothers what
would happen if they failed.
If I give them more time now,
I may as well hand them
a condom and
a cigarette to go with it.
You know, I came all
the way down here.
The least you could do is
offer me an opinion.
I thought we agreed it was best
for you to not come here.
And I thought you needed to
be out in seven days.
I need to know how this delay is
going to affect things.
Well, it won't be comfortable,
but it will be possible.
Oh, well,
thank you, James,
but that doesn't exactly
ravage me with confidence.
And what would?
Your ass on a plane.
Four more days.
If I'm out of here by then,
I can still do it.
Trust me.
It'll be fine.
I'll let the brothers know.
Gretchen.
About Sofia...
She's fine.
Burrows is taking real
good care of her.
Good luck, James.
---www.opensubtitles.org---
Prison Break
Season 03 Episode 07
"Vamonos"
www.tvsubtitles.net