Previously on Prison Break:
- So where to?
- Anywhere we want.
I'm not the brother you remember.
I've changed.
And I am gonna do something
that a lot of people are
gonna think is horrible.
And you just remember the
brother you grew up with.
She's not here.
- Yeah?
- The ship is leaving.
I'm already on board. Love you.
Why are you telling
me this now?
If I had to it all over again,
I'd do it different, you know?
Collar bone and rotator cuff.
Six inches to the right, you're dead.
You've come so far.
How much further
would I have to go?
Well, you're lucky.
For this you only have to go to Panama.
- He found him.
- Where?
He just boarded a
plane to Panama City.
What the hell's he
doing in Panama?
You like wigs?
For the right money,
I like anything.
What about the message board?
The goldfinch thing?
There is a message from Sucre.
- Still running, huh?
- Says the Bag still has the bag.
He's in Panama City at
the Fin Del Camino Hotel.
If you're there and want to help
put that bird back in the cage,
let me know. Sucre."
See ya soon.
Michael!
Scofield...
one thing's for sure,
you're just as pretty as advertised.
Prettier, even.
You got to help me, please.
I'm coming for you.
Are you ready?
No!
You say a word, I'm gonna cut
your throat out, you old whore!
Scofield!
- Hello?
- Pam, it's me.
- Cam's napping.
- Yeah? How's he doing?
Good, it was his first
day back at school.
- That's great.
- Where are you?
- I'm, uh, out of the country.
- Is everything all right?
Remember how I always said
that the day would come
and I'd be done?
Leave the Bureau and never look back?
- Yes.
- Today's that day.
I have one more thing to do,
and once I do it,
everything is going to fall into place.
And I'll be done.
I hope you mean it.
Pam, if I didn't have this
job hanging over me anymore,
if I were free,
if I were free...
Alex...
I need to know.
I'm not saying no.
I will make this right,
I swear to God.
And you and me and Cam...
I have to go.
I never stopped loving you,
Pam, ever.
Just be safe, Alex.
- You in position?
- Yeah.
- I'll be there in ten minutes.
- Got it.
Es bueno?
Es bueno.
Gracias.
- Necesitas los otros?
- Son tuyos.
- Gracias.
- De nada.
- Michael...
- What's wrong?
Que paso, Scofield?
Come on. Move it.
I love it.
Mr. Above It All down here trying
to sniff out that $5 million
just like the rest
of us riff-raff.
See? You ain't no better
than me, Scofield.
I want T-Bag locked up.
It's the only reason I'm here.
Aw, Dudley Freakin'
Do-Right, huh?
I didn't know you were
gonna be here, Michael.
What are you talking about?
You e-mailed me.
You said T-Bag was here.
It's on the Web site.
What? No.
I didn't write anything on the Web site.
- To you or anybody else.
- Is T-Bag in that hotel?
Yeah, a couple feds staking
it out across the street.
Well, then you're gonna
help us get it then.
Maybe you missed the
part about the feds.
I don't care. I didn't travel
2,000 miles down the diarrhea trail
to get to this backward-ass
country to not get my $5 million!
Well, that's too bad
'cause this is looking more
and more like a setup.
Then get that little college
boy brain of yours to work then.
And if you don't
think I'm serious,
just ask your old cellie
here what length I'll go to.
He's got Maricruz
locked away somewhere.
You're gonna help
him get the money
or she's dead.
Yeah, I'm a big jerk, Scofield.
Shame on me.
Michael, I'm in no position
to ask you for anything.
I need your help, papi.
I do.
Are you in or what?
- Get the gun off me.
- I asked you a question.
I said get the gun
off me or I walk.
All right,
you'll get your $5 million.
You get Maricruz,
and I get T-Bag.
- Win, win, win.
- But you got to do actly what I say.
Thank you, bro.
Alright, Einstein,
what you thinking?
And it's the third day of testimony
in trial of Dr. Sara Tancredi,
daughter of the late
governor Frank Tancredi.
So far, pundits feel the
prosecution is well on its way
to meeting its burden of proof
and getting a conviction
on all counts.
Defense counsel,
you may proceed.
Your Honor, at this time I ask this
tape be marked "Defense Exhibit D."
Objection. Your Honor,
this tape is the very propaganda
that Michael Scofield and Lincoln
Burrows released to the media
that was summarily debunked.
The jury still has
a right to hear it.
The tape is hearsay.
Unavailable witness exception,
Your Honor.
The witness is only unavailable
because he's a fugitive on the run.
Be that as it may,
his statement on this tape
exonerates Dr. Tancredi.
Your Honor...
The tape is allowed.
The State's objection will
be noted in the record.
Much blame has been placed
on another innocent person--
Dr Sara Tancredi.
She had nothing to
do with our escape.
Sara, if you're listening,
I know I can't ask
you another chance.
I only hope by now you've
found your safe heaven.
The trial of the late Governor
Tancredi's daughter, Dr. Sara Tancredi.
Continues today in Cook County.
Dr. Tancredi,
whose medical license has been suspended
pending outcome of the trial,
is facing multiple counts...
- I'm gonna kill him.
- And go right back to prison.
I don't care.
Once we get the money and he tells me
where Maricruz is, I'm gonna kill.
If you find Maricruz,
you're going marry Maricruz
and live happily ever after.
Yeah, after I sink a
knife in Bellick's chest.
Bellick and T-Bag will get theirs,
trust me.
Didn't Fox River teach
you anything, man?
Cause the same rules
apply out here.
It doesn't make a difference
if you're guilty or innocent.
- It's who survives.
- You're not that guy.
That son of a bitch took my girl,
locked her up somewhere.
I am that guy now, Michael.
Look at me.
The only reason I'm not five
miles away from here right now
is because I want to help you
find Maricruz, not kill Bellick.
And if that's your game,
I'm gone.
Believe me, I understand the
impulse to pull the trigger.
But if we lose ourselves,
we lose everything.
It's been a week.
I don't know where she is.
- I'm scared.
- We'll find her.
We'll find her.
What the hell's this?
Atención, caballeros y damas,
este edificio esta en fuego.
Por favor, siguen hasta la salida
mas cercana en una manera cuidadosa.
Now, if you start
acting like a cowboy,
this whole thing's going south
real fast, remember that.
Here we go.
You're not going to like
how this ends, Lincoln.
I'm giving you a chance.
Right now.
Just... back away, all right?
Just back away.
From the son of a bitch
who killed my dad?
You're done.
Those bullet holes don't heal too good,
do they, Mahone?
Toss me the handcuffs.
Hand 'em over or I swear to God
I'll blow your head clean off.
Americans?
Oh, thank, God. Do you know
where the Cathedral Guadalupe is?
Never heard of it.
I was supposed to meet my old
lady there a half hour ago.
That's great.
They say you can't miss it,
but I missed it.
I was wondering you had maybe a
travel guide or something on you?
Why don't you just
keep on walking, pal?
Well, excuse me for
thinking I could ask
for a little help from
some fellow Americans.
Listen, beat it.
So how we doing today?
Sucre, the gun.
Come on.
Get in the alley.
It is a global problem.
48% of North American lakes are
eutrophic. It's 53% in Europe...
- Kristine.
- Yeah?
- It's your brother, Paul.
- What, what's going on?
Hello.
He's in this building right here.
We got to move.
Let's see your I.D.
Feds?
No, if these guys were,
they'd be after T-Bag. You guys Company?
Come on, Sucre,
let's wrap these numb nuts up.
What are you guys doing here?
What do you want?
I don't like this.
Something's up.
Come on, Sucre, let's move it.
Now, let's go, come on.
Let's go, Michael.
We know you're in
here, Bagwell!
Three to one...
do the math.
Okay, okay,
I don't want any trouble.
Slide the gun over.
We can work
something out, boys.
Slide the gun over.
Where's the money?
Who called the cops?
You got three
seconds, hillbilly.
- One...
- In there.
Get it.
You want it, you get it.
We don't have time
for this, Bellick.
Nothing stupid now.
You're not playing a game.
Open it.
Sucre, move your ass!
Michael!
It's a trap.
Freeze, Bagwell!
Get the money!
You want the girl,
get the money!
Don't.
We can work something out.
Move.
- Somos la policia!
- Aah! Innocente!
Sucre, we got to go.
Theodore Bagwell-- he's the one you
want for that dead chick in there.
Anybody speak English?
I didn't do it!
I swear to God I didn't do it!
No, please, please!
We can do a little
divvying right here,
then we'll go our
separate ways.
Sucre, I want you
to get us a car.
What's going on?
What's the plan?
I said, get us a car.
Looks like you've made
some friends lately.
I don't follow.
That little set-up back there--
just a little out of your league.
Looked almost professional.
Let's say that's the case.
What's it worth to you to find out?
Because I am
in possession of some information
that you might need, pretty.
Okay. Tell me what you know.
Maybe I'll let you walk...
without the money.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You're gonna let me
traipse on out of here?
Depends on the information.
Who's pulling your strings?
You know, I got a hunch you're
speaking with a forked tongue, pretty.
So I'm gonna tell you what,
we go someplace public
with a car waiting for me to leave,
and then...
then I'll tell you. Deal?
No.
Oh, my God.
Paul.
That is only the second time...
a weapon has ever jammed on me.
First time was during
training for Gulf One.
As soon as it happened, the commanding
officer, he got in my face and he said,
"Son, a weapon jam
on the battlefield,
you might as well
call that suicide."
Kristine, I've, uh...
done things...
Damn!
Damn.
I love you, Paul,
whatever it is that got you here.
And there's a way out,
believe me.
My...
entire... my entire adult life,
I've followed orders...
And I did terrible things,
because I thought they
were right, and...
it turns out I did those
things in service of nothing.
So that's what I'm
left with-- nothing.
You have me.
Yeah, okay.
And you have a clean slate.
Anything. Everything.
It's available to you
starting right now.
- The things I've done, Kristine...
- Undo them.
Paul, there's always a way.
Maybe that gun
jammed for a reason.
Come here.
Don't...
let your pride get in
the way now, pretty.
Save it.
Locking me up ain't gonna
help your situation none.
I have information.
- What's the plan?
- We're gonna take him to the embassy,
we're gonna make
sure he's deported,
then we'll go looking for Bellick,
all right?
Si.
Meanwhile, I want you to
ride in the back with him.
I'm telling you, you are being
penny-wise and pound-foolish.
Get in the car.
Pound-foolish. Pound-foolish.
Pound-foolish...
I'll tell her about the offer.
- Well?
- 12 years.
No.
No. The jury heard
Michael's tape.
They heard a
convicted felon lie
for a woman that he clearly cares for.
He's got no credibility.
Sara, we need to take a hard
look at what they're offering.
Due respect, Marty,
we aren't going to prison, I am.
They've made it very clear that they
want somebody to hang for this, Sara,
and unfortunately, you're the only
one they've got in their grasp.
There's no avoiding it.
This is the plea agreement. We can
walk you through it if you'd like.
12 years?
He didn't answer.
I certainly hope your brother
makes it back to that boat.
And if he doesn't?
You should see yourself.
You look like you're hanging
in there by a thread.
I just want this over with.
Then you should never
have come down here.
In case you hadn't noticed,
me and my brother don't quit for no one.
Thank God for that.
Because it's guys that are
accused of things like you are
that guys like me in business.
Kept...
guys like me in
business, rather.
It's gonna end
bad for you, man.
Couple of things in
this world I'm good at.
One of them's looking into a man's
eye and knowing when he's beat.
- How far to the embassy?
- Just hang in there, buddy.
- And then what?
- We're gonna turn him in.
And how do we not get busted?
Before we get there,
I'll pull over.
We'll hog-tie him
with duct tape,
and we'll dump him out,
and hit the road,
and I'll call the cops,
tell 'em where we left him.
- Then how do we get Bellick?
- Don't worry, we'll find him.
Y'all ain't getting
within a mile of Bellick.
Nobody asked you.
He's got a point,
though, Michael.
- Just keep the gun on him, okay?
- I mean, if Bellick's locked up,
what's good the money
going to be to us?
Buddy, I told you we'll fix it.
- My girl's life is on the line here.
- Sucre, you better pull it together.
Ambulancia!
Shh, shh, shh.
Easy. Easy.
Buddy, you're
gonna be all right.
Go get the money.
Please. Quick.
Venga! Venga!
Bueno. Bueno, bueno.
Por favor...
- Pressure. Pression.
- Si, si, si.
What exactly is it
that you want, Pretty?
I'm turning you in.
Is that it? Really?
It ain't about the money?
'Cause, if it is,
you can tell me.
Ain't nobody here but us cons.
You can walk or get dragged.
But it's up to you.
No. See, when you had the gun on me,
I afforded you a certain respect.
But here?
Well, the scales are tipped back my way.
So I'm going to spell
out the present options.
Either we split this money,
and you can go get your legs tattooed
or whatever the hell
it is you want,
or they're going to find your corpse
slumped over that there chair
with your pants down
around your ankles,
'cause it's been a long
time coming, Pretty.
Well, I got my answer.
Whenever you're done yakking.
Bring it, bitch.
Who are you fooling?
You ain't going to kill me,
Mr. Michelangelo.
You ain't got it in you,
so why don't you let
me do the killing?
All right.
Thank you.
Okay, Sara.
Now, here's how the plea
is going to go down.
The judge is going to need you
to allocute to the charges.
He's going to ask you if you
intentionally left the door open.
- You will say yes.
- Right.
Then he's going to ask you if
you gave support and comfort
to Michael Scofield and Lincoln
Burrows since the escape.
You'll say yes.
And the sentence will be
immediately handed down.
The prosecution is asking
that you do your time
in a maximum security facility.
I think the judge is
going to agree to that.
Okay. Um...
With good behavior, how many years of
my sentence can I expect to serve?
On a 12 year sentence?
You'll do nine years.
I'll be out before I'm 40.
I'm sorry, Sara.
Sara? Are you ready for this?
What?
A very credible witness
has just came forward,
and he's willing to testify.
He'll corroborate everything
you've said about this conspiracy.
Who?
Help!
Linc!
Hola. Uh... Do you...
do you speak English?
Good. Good. I need to, uh...
I need to get in contact with every
hospital in the Panama City area.
A friend of mine was, uh...
A friend of mine was
in a car accident.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to have to call you back.
Linc?
I'm sorry, Michael.
What's wrong?
Hello, Michael.
If you touch my brother,
you're a dead man.
Oh, please.
You don't have to worry about that.
But, when it comes
right down to it,
he's just like you.
He has a heart that
won't kill a man.
Give me the handcuffs
or, I swear to God,
I'll blow your head clean off.
- What do you want, Alex?
- I'll tell you exactly what I want.
But first things first.
When the authorities
captured Bagwell today,
the money was
nowhere to be found.
Now, I can only assume that
you've got the money...
aboard the Christina
Rose right now.
It's an amazing plan, Michael.
Take the money, take the boat,
disappear forever.
But you...
are not the only one
that needs to disappear.
- You still there?
- Yeah, I'm still here.
Good. Because I'm going to say this,
and I'm going to say this once.
Bring me the money,
bring me the boat.
- You are out of your mind.
- Not really.
We both have something
the other person needs.
It all comes down
to this, Michael.
Your brother for your plan.
Five minutes.
That's what you have.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net