Previously, on Prison Break:
I need you to let me
get us out of here.
If you try
to screw me over again,
I'll kill you.
Because if Crazy steps
out of line,
all I got to do
is shoot him
with 40 CCs of "shut your trap,"
and it's beddy-bye.
Scofield and his
whole P.I. crew,
they're escaping.
You know I can't
let you leave
here, boss.
( clangs )
( grunts )
( screams )
( gasps )
And I've been clean
for 18 months now.
I want to help people get from
where I've been to where I am.
I'm getting my brother
out of here tonight,
and I need your help.
You're asking me
to break the law.
I'm asking you
to make a mistake:
forget to lock up.
Leave the door unlocked
when you leave tonight.
The inmates in the psych ward
all wear...
White.
Peroxide acts
as a bleach.
Camouflage.
Where's your girl?
She'll be at my place
in about an hour.
Pretty soon, we're going
to call in our favor.
I'm getting on that plane
with or without you.
I can't let you do that.
There's been an acceleration.
What you want, a bigger plane?
Well, not everybody
gonna have a ticket.
If you can't convince
a doddering old fool
what the best thing is
for this country's economy,
perhaps you're
not the kind
of helper
we're looking for.
I'm breaking out,
and you're going
to make sure
my brother goes with me.
You son of a bitch.
We're going to take this
real easy, Warden.
I just need you to do
a couple things for me.
You just bought yourself
ten years.
C.O. MACK ( over radio ):
Warden?
Bellick's truck is here, sir.
I'm staring right at it.
Should we start looking for him?
Michael, if
you just put
that shank down...
Tell the guard
you spoke with Bellick,
and he said he's taking
some personal time.
You can't possibly
get away with this, son.
I don't think you want
to find out how badly
I want to get my brother
out of here.
Sir?
Mack.
Yes, sir.
I just spoke
with Bellick.
He's walked into town.
He's taking some personal time.
Is he all right?
Sir?
He's fine.
Copy that.
Okay.
I just need you to do
one more thing.
Have Lincoln transferred
to the Infirmary.
And he needs to be there
overnight.
How long have you
been planning this?
That is a conversation
for another day, Warden.
Pope to base.
C.O. ( over radio ):
Go ahead, sir.
Have Lincoln Burrows transferred
to the Infirmary.
I want him held overnight
for tests.
Copy that.
Once we're gone,
you'll find Bellick
in a hole
under the guards'
break room.
I'm sorry you got caught
in the middle,
but one day,
you'll understand
why I did this.
You'll never make it
over the wall.
( grunts )
I'm sorry, Henry.
( panting )
Everything all right?
Yeah, um, he's getting an earful
from someone
over at the D.O.C.
Oh. Is he on with Mr. Drushal?
I'm not sure, but, uh, it's
turning into a conference call
and he said he didn't want
to be disturbed.
Oh, well, of course.
Have a good night.
Mmm.
You know, Michael...
You know, he can be
a big old grump sometimes,
but I hope you know how
highly he thinks of you.
There's no way he'd get
that Taj Mahal done
in time for his anniversary
without your help.
( grunting )
6:55.
That's five minutes till tier.
That's one hour
till the next count.
One hour
to get over that wall
and as far away from this prison
as possible.
( groans )
* *
You unscrewed the toilet, right?
That's five minutes
we don't have.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I just feel
like my head is
spinning a little.
( retching )
Are you okay?
If we get caught...
I can't do ten more years, bro.
I can't.
( door buzzer blaring )
C.O.:
Tier time, one hour.
There's no going back now.
If you get stuck
in one of them pipes, boy...
Bull.
Keep walking, Bull,
keep walking.
You okay?
Great.
( coughs )
It's got blue spots.
Yo, I got a late start.
Only one thing
you needed to do.
Block the gate.
I got to finish this off.
Said a prayer
for you, Theodore.
Said a prayer for us all.
I want him dead.
Anybody gets in the way...
gets run over.
( grunting )
( voices talking above )
Just a half cup, Mack.
If I have more than that,
I'll be up all night.
Thank you, bro.
( muffled screaming )
( grunting )
How many more screws?
Get C-Note out here.
Huh? Haven't
seen him, man.
That's real touching and all,
you sticking up
for a brother,
but y'all need to step aside
right now.
Something you need?
Where is he?
Told you, we haven't seen him.
( indistinct chatter )
This whole time,
everything you said was a lie.
No, no.
I-I never stopped fighting
for Lincoln's innocence, never.
They approached me
after I took this case.
Who's they?
John Abruzzi.
John Abruzzi, the mob boss?
Yes, yes.
How much did he pay you?
My father's freedom.
You said your father
was exonerated.
I lied, okay?
I agreed to keep tabs
on you. In exchange,
Abruzzi had some guy who was
already doing a life sentence
cop to the murder
that my father didn't commit.
And that's how I
get him out of jail.
Your dad's life for mine.
No one needs
to get hurt here, Veronica.
You think Abruzzi wants
legal advice from me?
All you have to do
is make sure
Michael gives this Abruzzi guy
what he needs to know,
that's it.
Nick,
you don't think they're going
to let me live, do you?
( sighs )
I got to believe that.
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Stand up.
We have to go.
Get up.
( whispers ):
Charles.
Sucre, drop the sheet.
Manche, you're next.
Let's move it.
That one's for you.
Move your fat ass.
( groaning )
That's for you.
Age before beauty.
All right.
So, you got a key
to the Infirmary?
Not exactly.
( groaning )
All right. How we doing, baby?
Not good. We're already
ten minutes behind.
Let's move it.
( grunts )
Go.
( grunting )
* *
( muffled groaning )
Help!
Help! Help...!
( muffled and distant ):
Help!
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
Help!
( grunts )
( muffled groaning )
Shh!
( footsteps approaching )
( grunting )
( panting )
MACK:
Hear anything?
( muffled groan )
There's nobody
here, man.
I swear, I heard something.
Come on, let's go.
You scream...
and I'll cut out
your windpipe, got me?
( muffled grunt )
I need his jacket
and his hat.
( grunts )
* *
Brains of the outfit,
huh, Scofield?
He's leading you
off a cliff, boys.
Now you're acting
like you still in charge.
Shut your mouth, bitch.
Pendejo.
( whispers ):
Let's go.
You.
You know, he's...
( grunts )
Ciao, bello...
Look. Please, don't do this.
Tell Michael
to give Abruzzi what he wants.
Please, Nick, come on,
they're going to kill me.
Nick.
( muffled ):
Nick!
Nick.
Everyone put your coveralls on.
I'll be back in a minute.
Yo, where you going, man?
Hey!
You heard him. Come on.
This is ridiculous, man.
( whispering ):
Eight-one-three-five...
MAN:
The scope of this,
which we're all aware of,
can cloud judgment.
I suggest we look at this
in very simple terms.
We have an employee,
she's not working out.
We fire her.
It needs to be that simple.
MAN 2:
She's the vice president
of the United States.
And that's all
she'll ever be.
She's plummeting
in the polls.
If we keep her
as our candidate,
we're handing the presidency
to her opponent,
and then everything
we hope to gain
with Caroline in office--
it's all gone.
Fine. If we ask her
to drop out,
how do we know she'll
keep her mouth shut
on everything she knows?
Samantha?
Yes, sir.
I need a very frank assessment
from you right now.
Based on your
contact with her,
will the vice president
go quietly?
No.
Absolutely not.
Becoming president
is the most important
thing to her.
If we take that away,
she has absolutely
nothing to lose.
And I guarantee you,
she will do everything she can
to take everyone
she can down with her.
We need to make a move on her.
Now.
( metallic jingling )
( chain jingling )
You okay, Doc?
( metallic jingling )
What's going on?
I don't know.
What are we
supposed to do, just sit here?
No. I don't know!
Man...
This whole thing
is messed up, bro.
Feel free not to come, Gordo.
( alarm buzzing )
We're screwed.
We're screwed!
Come on, let's go!
SUCRE:
Michael, we got to go back.
We're moving forward.
We stick with the plan.
Your ears work, fool?!
Do you hear that?!
It's the fire alarm
in Psych Ward.
SUCRE:
How do you know?
MICHAEL:
I set it off.
Why?
( alarm sounding )
MAN ( over speaker ):
Exit the building
in an orderly fashion.
( buzzing continues )
We're in the sticks.
You know how many
people would have heard
a jet like this land?
Don't worry about it.
False alarm.
Back to the Psych Ward,
everyone.
Walking with me, now.
Very good.
Just got to keep on walking.
( measuredbreaths )
MICHAEL:
Hold up!
Got some stragglers.
Cool.
Let's go!
Wait a minute.
That's not whack
shack-issue.
Everybody, stop!
Stay where you are!
I said stay
where you are.
What's the problem?
That's John Abruzzi right there.
Yeah, that's...
that's bad news.
Listen, you got
that sedative you
were talking about?
Yeah.
You got some now?
Let's have it.
This will put
him out, right?
Like a light.
( gasps )
Let's go.
Let's go!
Where we going?
Straight down the hall.
VERONICA:
Nick, please
don't do this.
( sobbing )
Come on.
What's going on?
I'm getting you
to the airport.
Go, go, go, go.
You get to Blackfoot,
you find Steadman.
There's still time for you
to get to the bottom
of this thing.
Take this, take this.
I'm sorry about this, okay?
You got to believe me,
I'm sorry.
O'Hare.
Take her to O'Hare.
Dad, still got the key
to my apartment?
Yeah, just meet me there.
I'll explain it later.
Just meet me there.
Halfway there, yo.
What's up?
I know you told Bellick.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I owed you, and I pay my debts.
But as soon
as we're out of here,
you go your way, we'll go ours.
You understand?
Oh, Sara.
It was a false alarm
at the Psych Ward.
That's what all that
racket was about.
Good, thank you.
Good night.
Hey.
Look, baby, it ain't worth it
if it's gonna kill you.
I'm getting out of here.
( measured breaths )
You're overreacting.
I don't mean to
shock you, Paul,
but I am privy to things
that you're not.
And I am telling you,
the company is selling me
down the river.
It's a Legends For Literacy
fundraiser.
Doesn't mean anything;
it's a rubber chicken dinner.
Which I got uninvited to
on the day of.
You don't do that
to your candidate,
unless the candidate is
no longer your candidate.
Caroline, you've been drinking,
you're upset.
How can you not understand this
is so beyond me.
I would think
after being by my side
for 15 years,
you would have gained at least
a rudimentary
understanding
of how things work.
Listen to me.
They're doing this to see
how you will react.
So you need to be strong.
Be presidential,
and get through this.
We get through this.
I'm figuring I'll need
a two-inch lift
if I'm gonna run
with a new set
of 30-by-nine-and-a-halfs.
Question is:
Add coil springs
or just stay
with the spacers?
What do you think?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, hey.
I ain't a hero for $14 an hour.
You do what
you will.
Uncuff my brother.
You got it, boss.
C.O.:
Hey.
Pretend I ain't here, boss.
Yeah, you and the radio.
Dad, are you here?
Dad, you got to get ready.
We got to go.
How's it going, Savrinn?
MAN:
And the guy says, "Yeah, I get
why she's lighting the candle,
but why are the other two
playing the bagpipes?"
( audience laughter )
Welcome to Laugh Line.
Just $2.99 a minute, 50 cents
What the hell?
...for each additional minute.
Where's the lawyer?
She's gone.
Yeah?
Then so's your dad.
No, no, no!
Don't.
Have you got her or not?
I can find her.
And will you have her in front
of me in the next two minutes?
It's a very simple
question, Nick.
No. But just-just
give me a chance.
You just got
to listen to me...
No! No!
Hey!
This is happening right now!
You have one
more chance!
Where's the lawyer?
( groans )
( coughing )
She's about a billion miles
away from here.
You're never
gonna find her.
Better be open, bro.
( click, creaking )
We're in.
First we got to get
that window out.
Then we got to get
the bars off.
Manche, Manche.
Is this gonna work?
We're about
to find out.
( knocking )
BECKY:
Warden?
( knocking )
Ready.
All right.
Come on.
( elevator bell dings )
What now, genius?
( slams against door )
Take your time.
But, uh...
15 minutes to get
over that wall.
( cracking )
We're through.
And you're sure you
didn't see him walk out?
Positive.
MICHAEL:
Let's go, guys,
I need those suits.
Good job, kiddo.
Come on, come on,
come on.
Take this.
( static crackling )
Haywire.
I knew it!
As soon as I saw
you go into Psych
Ward, I knew it!
Either I come with...
Uh...
Or I'm going
to make a little
person-to-person call here.
Haywire,
just take it easy.
The other
person being
a correctional officer.
He's in.
What?
You're crazy!
Okay, after Lincoln,
we go alphabetically.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold on, A-bruzzi.
You want a seat
on the plane?
Line forms after me.
Got it.
Yeah.
Go, go, go.
Hey, Roy?
Yeah?
Did you see Pope leave?
No.
No way he could
have walked by?
I haven't left my post
since I punched in.
( sighs )
( gasps )
* *
( panting )
( groans )
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Charles?
Charles.
You okay, old man?
No.
Let's take a look.
It's just a few more steps.
You can make it.
Oh, I could make it another
foot, maybe two...
but why? I wasn't
going for me.
I was going
for my daughter.
And you can do that.
Will you promise me?
Yes, I promise.
The money is buried
under a silo
at the Double K Ranch
just outside
of Tooele, Utah.
There's plenty
to split.
The government
didn't want
any more embarrassment
after I took off
with the money.
So they lowballed it
to the papers.
The truth is, Michael,
it's not $1 million
under that silo.
There's $5 million there.
You checked
the chow hall?
Yeah. Nothing.
Anybody try
his cell phone?
Oh.
Give Anna
her papa's love.
I will.
Here...
easy, easy.
( cell phone ringing )
Where is that
coming from?
( ringing continues )
( ringing grow louder )
Oh, my God!
Control, this is S & E 5.
I have a code three
in the warden's office.
Repeat, code three.
( mutters )
To the base.
Right now.
No, right now.
Sound the alarm.
Yo, bro, we got to go.
Go, Michael.
Go and don't look back.
No, no, no, no.
I better go last.
Come on, Michael!
Now, move!
( alarm blaring )
Michael, move it!
Come on.
Michael, come on.
Come on, Michael.
Move.
( alarm continues )
Come on, move!
Michael, come on, move.
( Manche yells )
Michael!
Grab my hand.
Michael, give me your hand.
Give me your hand. Come on.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
( alarm continues )
Freeze!
Stop right there or I'll shoot!
Freeze! Don't move!
Don't shoot!
Get down!
www.tvsubtitles.net