Previously on Prison Break:
- We're staying.
- Give 'em hell.
Phil, don't do this.
I've dedicated my life to this country,
to president Reynolds.
Every photo, every file--
get rid of it all.
Phil, don't do this.
- You left a message for Mr. Geary.
- I'm going to gut you, bow to stern.
- I did not kill Roy Geary.
- Bagwell set me up.
You are under arrest for the first
degree murder of Roy William Geary.
My therapist said that
I need to confront you
to let you know how
betrayed I feel.
This is the Tribune Police.
Look, as long as you do your
job with me, not a chance.
And then you can go backo
Colorado and visit your son.
Cameron.
Don't you ever mention
his name again.
What about your
friend back there?
If we're going to go down...
might as well go down swinging.
- Sara.
- Michael?
Almost made it.
Hello.
Hello. Michael?
Is that you?
Get up.
Turn around.
Turn around!
If you're going to
murder us, Alex,
you're going to have to look us
in the eyes while you do it.
Shut up.
You want me, you got me.
Let my brother go!
I don't want either of you.
I just want my life back!
You're going to kill two
innocent men to get it, huh?
Absolutely.
This is the United
States Border Patrol.
Drop the weapon and
remain where you are.
United States Border Patrol.
Drop your weapon.
I'm FBI.
These men are in my custody.
I don't care who you are.
Until we verify,
you will drop your weapon or
we will drop you. Your choice.
Hands on your head now.
DOn't move.
- You got anything to drink?
- Check the back.
Unknown rider, unknown rider,
this is DEA on guard.
Bring up frequency 1145.
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh?
What do you mean, "Uh-oh"?
Border Patrol's
on our ass, man.
How long till we get to Mexico?
We're already in Mexico, Papa.
I thought they couldn't follow
us once we crossed the border.
Hey, not since 9/11, hombre.
I repeat: this is DEA on guard.
What are we going to do?
Pull the chord. And pray.
Oh, hell, no.
Look, we try and land the plane,
we're pinched for sure.
And if we jump?
We're in the middle
of the desert.
Patrol have a hard time trying
to find us once we land.
- If we land.
- Oh, you're going to land.
It's just a matter of how hard.
Good luck, amigo.
Unknown rider...
Identify yourself.
We're receiving reports that
escaped convicts Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield
have been apprehended
just a few miles north of
the US-Mexican border.
Federal Agent Alex
Mahone with assistance
from the United
States Border Patrol
took the men into custody
just a short time ago.
Now, not a lot of information
available at this time,
but we do know the brothers were
apprehended without incident
while attempting to leave the country
through the deserts of New Mexico,
quite a long way from Illinois's
Fox River State Penitentiary,
where they escaped from
less than ten days ago.
The Fox River Eight, as the group
of convicts were once known,
are now down to four,
as only Benjamin Miles Franklin,
Fernando Sucre, Charles Patoshik and
Theodore Bagwell remain at large.
Sir. He just heard.
And he'd like to see you.
Convicts are now down to four,
as only Benjamin Miles Franklin,
Fernando Sucre, Charles Patoshik and
Theodore Bagwell remain at large.
Godspeed, gentlemen.
'Scuse me, Sarge.
I, uh, was wondering if you could,
uh, help a brother out.
With what?
I only recently returned from
delivering democracy to the desert
and, uh,
I was wondering if you could tell me how
a guy goes about getting a hold of
one of those prosthetic jobbies.
What, they make you whole
before they shipped you back?
Well, let's just say
the doctor made the bed.
He just neglected to
tuck in the sheets.
Best thing for you to do
is go on down there to VA.
Get in line.
- That simple?
- Yeah.
Till they send you the bill and
you got to figure out how to pay.
Those bastards up there in Washington
send us off to fight for them;
not a damn one of
'em fights for us.
And that is a crime.
But luckily for me, uh...
- money is not the issue.
- Is that right?
Any particular, uh,
forms I might need in order to qualify?
You know what, Mr.
Don't Ask, Don't Tell?
You figured out how to
dye that hair of yours up
like a nancy all by yourself,
you sure as hell can figure out
how to get a prosthetic for that
stump of yours by yourself.
Yeah, I think I got a pretty
good idea where to start.
I'm here with Ed Pavelka, the new
warden of Fox River Penitentiary,
where Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield
are scheduled to be returned
to sometime tomorrow.
Now, Warden,
the escape happened a mere two days
before Burrows was scheduled
to be put to death.
He's already been granted one day;
do you anticipate any further?
Lincoln Burrows is a
convicted murderer.
His escape has endangered the lives
of civilians across this country.
He is not a celebrity.
He is not a martyr.
I can assure you that whatever
leniency was afforded him
and the other prisoners under
the old regime at Fox River
will no longer be tolerated.
The only thing that Mr.
Burrows can expect
is what a jury of his peers demanded:
a speedy execution.
And Michael Scofield?
With his escape,
the aiding and abetting charges,
the felonies he's racked
up along the way,
on top of his original sentence,
I'd say Mr. Scofield
will be spending the rest of
his life behind bars. Thank you.
Who's got Mahone?
- Congratulations, sir.
- What do you got?
A call from the Illinois DOC.
They're sending a huge
contingent down there
to collect Burrows
and Scofield,
take them back to
Fox River personally.
Remind them this
is a federal case
and we'll handle the
transport. Now...
I did.
But it's an election year,
collar this big,
everybody wants a piece.
The warden called in a
favor to the Bureau Chief;
he okayed it, so here we are.
Should be there in about an hour.
I want to be placed in the
prisoner transport vehicle.
- What for?
- Just get it done.
Sir, these were the big fish.
And you brought 'em in.
You should feel
good about that.
Yeah... Yeah.
- Well, at least we're together.
- Yes, there is that.
- What are you thinking?
- I'm thinking about the old man.
What he tried to do, you know.
Tough to go down swinging
when you're locked in a box.
This isn't over yet.
We're entitled to a phone call.
We make that one call to Sara
and she has the information
Dad said she has,
we can get you exonerated before
this whole thing goes down.
Michael.
Hey.
We're entitled to a phone call.
You're entitled to
precisely squat
until you're
officially in custody.
And that won't happen until
you're back in Fox River.
So sit tight.
- It's not over yet.
- Not yet.
A lot of ground to cover
between here and Illinois.
I mean,
what are the chances we even
make it back to Fox River alive?
Saw you on the news, Alex.
- Did you?
- The brothers too.
They were a little more, um...
breathing than I had hoped.
Yeah, well, Border Patrol showed up.
Nothing I could do.
Really?
Burrows and Scofield,
can you see them from where you are?
- Yeah.
- Then put a bullet in their heads.
They're being watched.
- I don't care.
- By armed guards.
They make it back to Fox River,
it is over. For all of us.
There's not much more this country
loves than a bad man with a good story.
How much longer do
you think it'll be
before someone puts a
microphone in front of them?
- Hey, are you listening?
- Okay, with the security here,
what you're asking me to do
is tantamount to suicide.
- Do you understand what I'm saying?
- I wasn't asking anything.
That would imply you
had a say in the matter.
Pull this off and you're
halfway home, Alex.
You remember what home is like.
Don't you?
900 West End Avenue.
White fence. Red door.
Stay away from my family!
You got a little
something on your, uh...
No, uh... here, let me.
- Pardon my forwardness, I was...
- It's okay. Thank you.
Normally I wouldn't intervene,
it's just...
yesterday when I
got home from work,
I found what looked like
the Brazilian Rain Forest
lodged between my
two front teeth.
And all I could think about was
the number of people who
must've seen and not...
not a damn one of them had
the decency to tell me.
- Mild diastema.
- Excuse me?
It's a slight gap between
your eight and nine.
Your two front teeth.
And that it sometimes can act
as a magnet for food like...
broccoli and tuna
and sometimes rice.
Or relish.
All this and brains, too?
What are you, a dentist or...?
Me? No, hardly, no.
I could never.
- My ex-husband, he was...
- A bastard?
That too.
Have you ever been
to Italy, uh...?
- Denise.
- Denise, that's a lovely name.
Um...
You know, in Italy,
they have wine every day with lunch.
And what do we do
in this country?
We power our food down with
caffeine, carbonation,
and high fructose corn syrup.
No one ever takes the time
to enjoy things anymore.
Denise, would you
do me the honor
of "enjoying" the rest
of your lunch with me?
I think I'd like that.
White or red?
...and with limited financial
resources he poses no flight risk...
Unless he'd rather not stand
trial for capital murder.
The defendant has shown
great resourcefulness
in being able to travel across
country with little money.
There's no reason he
couldn't do it again.
If you don't want to believe me,
believe Mr. Bellick.
You thieving son of a bitch.
You better get down on
your knees and pray to God
that I never find you because if I do,
mark my words:
I will gut you bow to stern.
He promised to kill Mr. Geary,
and then he kept that promise.
A man like the defendant
should not be out in society.
- I concur.
- Bail denied.
Who would that be?
Only one person.
Michael, it's me. Listen,
this phone rang last night and, uh...
I went to answer it,
but I couldn't hear anything
and I wonder if maybe
it was you? Um...
Oh, God,
I don't know what I should do right now.
I don't know if I
should leave a message
or who might be listening to this,
but... um, I, uh...
I need to know that you're okay.
I need you to know that I'm not.
I didn't leave you in Gila.
Something happened to me and I don't...
um, I don't know what
to do right now.
I'm not too sure where to go,
but I know that you're the
only person I can trust
and I need you to, um...
I need you to be
okay and, um...
And I need you. Please.
Alexander Mahone, Bureau.
These are my prisoners
and I will be
personally escorting them
in their transfer vehicle.
- You can follow in the chase car...
- I don't believe you heard me.
I'll be accompanying
them in their...
The only people allowed in the
van are the driver and two guards
who've been trained and
certified in prison transport.
Are you really going to
make me go over your head?
I'll even dial
the phone for you.
Now look, this is standard procedure,
Agent Mahone.
We need to keep that environment
as controllable as possible.
The more bodies,
the less control.
These men may have knowledge of
the location of the other escapees.
This is knowledge that I...
- I need to do my job.
- And my job is to ensure
the safe and successful transfer
of these two prisoners.
Chase vehicles
are right outside.
There better be a damn good reason
why those brothers are still alive.
Bad day, Bill?
Sorry, I thought this was
someone who still existed.
How's the jerky business, Owen?
Actually, it's looking
pretty good right about now.
You call this number again,
you're a dead man.
Actually, you don't kill Burrows
and Scofield today, so are you.
You know it and I know it,
and luckily for you,
I know how to save your ass.
The brothers are already being
transferred. You're too late.
Actually, that transport van is
exactly where you want them to be.
Why?
Why? You want my help,
Bill, I want my job back.
That means direct access
to the president.
I report only to her.
You're reaching,
Paul. Good-bye.
Don't shut me out, Bill.
You think Burrows and Scofield are
a threat to this Administration?
I know everything Caroline
Reynolds has done.
Everything.
Now, before you panic,
all I'm asking
is to be allowed to finish
the job that I started.
To prove to the
president and to you
that I'm still an asset
to this administration.
What's your plan?
I have an old associate
in the Illinois DOC.
They're heading
up the transfer.
It's going to take more
than one guy on the inside.
Not if the guy's in
the right place.
Bill, you give me
the go-ahead on this,
when those brothers
get in the van,
it'll be the last
thing they ever do.
I have never done that before.
Then I guess we were making
up for some lost time.
I have to ask, Sam,
are you, uh...
are you married or something?
Me? No.
What makes you think...?
Come on.
I may be plain, but I'm not a fool.
Usually the men I end up with
are just looking for something...
on the side.
Denise, the only "side" I'm
interested in, is the inside.
And that place within you...
is not plain.
- I have to get back to work.
- Do you really?
I have to close tonight.
How 'bout I pick you up after?
We can have dinner.
- Are you sure?
- Denise...
I insist.
- Yeah.
- Good news.
You're off the hook.
Paul Kellerman has a team
ready to move on the caravan
just outside of Albuquerque.
Okay. So where does
that leave us?
When it goes down, there's sure
to be a moment or two of chaos.
A certain amount of confusion,
lots of bullets flying.
I need you there to make sure
Paul Kellerman catches one.
It's a little early to be
covering your tracks, isn't it?
The escapees--
that was our deal. That's all.
Right. Our deal.
Refresh my memory.
Was our deal supposed to end
with Burrows and Scofield
going back to prison or...
bleeding from a hole
in their heads?
We're giving you a chance
to make this right, Alex.
Just let Kellerman take care of it.
Let him be our Oswald.
Then, that makes
me your Jack Ruby.
Jack Ruby was working alone.
You've got the support of the United
States government behind you, Alex.
Good luck in Albuquerque.
I promise, sir,
this will all be over shortly
and it will be back
to business as usual.
- Do you regret it?
- What?
Knowing what you know now,
do you regret helping me?
You'd have done the
same thing for me.
- You think?
- I know.
You didn't answer the question.
I don't regret the act.
Just how it turned out.
We've got a premeditated
murder on our hands.
You wanted to steal money and
then kill the only witness.
- Are you my attorney or theirs?
- I told you I didn't do anything.
No, I'm just explaining their
theory of what happened.
Your explanation to the cops
that you didn't kill Geary
because you were
too busy trying
to steal five million in
federally insured money.
Probably not the best move.
But there is good news.
What's that?
The DA is willing to offer a deal.
25 years.
No.
Brad, they'll drop
the capital charge.
No death penalty. No.
I'd be almost 65
when I get out.
But you'd get out.
If this case goes to trial,
there's an excellent chance
you're sentenced to death.
Now, I've been doing
this a while, Brad,
and I can tell you these
things never go down good.
When the system wants you,
they get you,
one way or another.
Part of the deal's got to be
I do my time in Illinois,
so I can be near my mom.
- Where are they taking us?
- Another foster home.
I don't want to go.
I liked it there.
- I know you did.
- It's 'cause of you.
The reason they're making us move,
isn't it?
'Cause you were getting
in trouble again.
Yeah, and I'm sorry.
Seems like I've been dragging
you into trouble my whole life.
Pulled me out of some, too.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Alex. Paul Kellerman.
- Have you spoken with Bill Kim?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he filled me in.
You're staging in Albuquerque.
Now, listen.
Me jumping in at this point.
It in no way reflects my feelings
about the job you've been doing.
- I just wanted you to know that.
- Of course.
So long as we get the job done.
And we all get to go back
to our families, right?
The sooner the better.
So what do I need to know?
Fugitive Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield
have been apprehended just a few
miles north of the US-Mexican border.
- What's going on out there?
- Let me go check.
- What do you see?
- I'll let you know.
How much time is it going
to take to move the semi?
I've got my men
working on it now.
- What's going on up there?
- Are you in a hurry, convict?
Hey, we need some help getting
this rig out of the road.
Linc.
All right,
let's say we get the cuffs off.
- Where do we go?
- There.
That's too easy.
Come on.
Come on, Michael, take it.
Come on, come on.
Take it.
Take it and run.
Let's think about this.
The keys are
accidentally left out,
the door is
accidentally left open.
- It's our only shot.
- It's their only shot.
They don't have an excuse to kill
us unless we give it to them.
- How are we doing?
- Nothing so far.
- None?
- They're talking, that's all.
If they haven't bitten
in five minutes,
you haul the semi,
you tell them it's fixed.
- You release traffic.
- And do what?
If you want the rabbit to hop,
you move the carrot, Alex.
You showed.
A gentleman always does.
- Where are we going to eat?
- Wherever your heart desires.
You know, there's just one
teensy-tiny thing I
been meaning to ask.
Anything.
You know, forwarding addresses
are supposed to be confidential.
I really shouldn't
be doing this.
Well, uh... you shouldn't have
been doing a lot of the things
we did this afternoon, but, uh,
neither of us has
been smited down yet.
There she is.
I'd imagine your cousin'll
be pretty surprised
to hear about the money
her uncle left her.
You can be certain of it.
Sam, I hope you don't mind me asking,
but, um, your hand.
What happened to it?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to make you feel
uncomfortable or nothing. I just...
I want to know you.
I want to know everything
about you, and...
if this is a part of who you are,
then I want to know how it--
Oh, dear God.
I really wish you
hadn't seen that.
Okay, here's what I'm thinking.
You and some of the boys
get yourselves transferred
over to AD SEG.
That way, we can spend our days
playing Scrabble and
watching Sportscenter.
Look, Cap'n...
Then, in about a year
and a half or so,
you're gonna recommend me for one
of those work-release programs.
Then, I can sweat off the rest of my
time heaving hay and getting sun.
It ain't freedom,
but it's damn close.
Is that why you requested
to be sent here?
I go anywhere else--
as a former CO, I'm a dead man.
But here I got men to watch my back.
Get me the finest accommodations...
They're not putting
you in AD SEG.
I don't care where they're putting me.
Just take me to AD SEG.
It's not like it
used to be, Cap'n.
The COs don't run the
game here anymore.
- What do you mean?
- This new warden.
He's cracking down.
And to prove he's serious about
showing preferential treatment,
he's making an
example out of you.
Lou, what the hell is this?
General Pop.
Welcome home, Boss.
Okay, everybody,
we're moving out.
Window's closing, Michael.
Once the truck moves, we're...
If we run now, we give them permission
to put a bullet in our heads.
We stay, I'm dead within the week,
and you're locked up for life.
Or until they find
a way to get to you.
And, believe me, they will.
If we go back to prison,
we'll have a few extra days.
We'll have a chance
to contact Sara.
We don't know where Sara is.
Sara may be dead, Michael.
Let me get us out of here
the only way I know how.
- Fighting?
- Yeah.
Get the keys.
Here we go. Here we go.
Copy that.
All right, we're on. Heads up.
Hold traffic.
You know we have no idea
what's behind that door.
Nope.
- You ready?
- No. You?
No.
Let's go.
Just pray there's
another way out of here.
This way.
Hey, they're in.
And they're heading
straight for you.
- Armed?
- No.
Where are you?
I'll back you up.
Just keep moving As long as
they're running from you,
they're running toward me.
They're boxed in.
Yeah.
Hold on one sec.
Can I write a check for the
food 'cause I don't have...
Hello, Mrs. Hollander.
They say a good woman
is hard to find.
Well, if that's true,
you must be very, very...
very good. Don't be frightened.
Teddy's home.
They're improvising,
heading toward the surface.
- Where to?
- I don't know.
Look, if something
happens to us,
if we get seperated or
of us doesn't make it,
- promise me you'll find Sara.
- We're gonna make it.
- Just promise me.
- I promise. Come on.
Whoa, whoa!
President Reynolds
ruined your lives.
She ruined my life.
You want to take that bitch down?
You just found youside man,
but it's gotta be right now.
Let's go!
Now!
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net