Previously on Prison Break:
Did you see the
guy in the mirror?
No.
It was Dad.
I know that guy.
What is it?
It was fused into
Michael Scofield's skin.
Where'd it come from?
As far as I can tell,
a guard's uniform.
What's wrong?
The blueprints,
the ones we need to get from
the psych ward to the infirmary,
they're gone.
Hey, that's looking good.
You're making some
real progress.
The plaster adds
a lot of weight.
I may have to
add reinforcements.
Whatever it takes, as long as you
get done in time for the anniversary.
It'll be done. Hold this.
You know,
the Shah loved his Taj so much
that he built another temple just like
it on the other side of the river.
It was an absolute
mirror image.
Except it was darker,
it was like a black Taj Mahal.
Never heard of it.
Well, that's 'cause it
was never completed.
He was overthrown by his favorite
son before he could finish it.
- Sounds like a myth.
- No, it's 100% true.
I think.
Excuse me, Warden. Dr.
Tancredi is here to see you.
Thank you.
Adams, please escort Mr.
Scofield back to his cell.
Doctor, what can I do for you?
Uh, actually,
it's about Scofield, sir.
Come in.
What about Scofield?
The burn on his back
is fairly serious.
He seems to be recovering.
At first I assumed he was being
assaulted by another inmate,
but it found this embedded
in the skin in his back.
What's this?
It's fabric.
Came from a guard's uniform.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to remember
those blueprints...
what we lost to the burn.
Without them, we'll never be able to
navigate those pipes beneath the
psych ward.
- Any luck?
- No.
I spent a lot of time
studying those blueprints...
tracing them night after night,
considering every possible
route to the infirmary.
It's like trying to take a test
you studied for ten years ago.
P.I.!
How do they get like that,
I got no idea.
I do.
Tuggin' on too many pockets.
She tug on your pocket?
I may be social, but that's a
boundary line even I won't cross.
So how about it, Fish?
When we rolling out?
One hiccup left,
but I'm working on it.
Yeah, and what is that?
Our road map's a little
incomplete at the moment.
I don't get it.
Why not just go down there again?
'Cause one, I don't have
the guard's uniform anymore,
which means I can't get across
the yard or past the orderly.
And two, even if I did,
it's a mess down there.
I need this.
You think you're
gonna remember it?
Not with you hounding me.
Time to wrap it up. We're going
to have you start exterminating.
We're not done in here.
Well, you look done to me.
Nah, CO,
we still got the carpet to do, man.
No, Bellick is going to bring
professionals in to do that.
Wants the job done right.
- When's that going to happen?
- Tomorrow.
We got a real problem on our hands,
don't we?
Rug monkeys gonna come in here,
tear up that carpet and that hole's
gonna be smiling up at them.
- We'll have to fill it in.
- We just dug that bitch.
All we need is a
piece of plywood
and a couple inches of that
fast-setting concrete on top of it.
The carpet guys will never know
there's anything beneath it.
And the night we break out,
we'll just smash through
with a sledgehammer.
Well, okay. Let's get on it.
We've only got a couple
hours to get this thing done.
Hey, Tweener. You met Avocado?
Yo, what's up?
Lookit. She's just a baby.
Hit road.
Have a seat.
So...
Scofield. What's the 911?
It's 411, and I don't know, man.
I ain't up in his car.
You know,
Avocado's looking for a new cellie.
Boss, come on, man, I'm tryin'
to break bread with the man but
I can't jack unless I
can get to the table,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Scofield got his own peeps, up in P.I.
He don't need me.
How long this
stuff take to dry?
One, two hours.
Fire  on the line.
This place is sweet.
I heard we're getting satellite.
All the porn you
can watch, boss.
Good, good.
You know,
you girls have done such a good job,
I thought you could use an
extra pair of hands on the crew.
S'up?
Hey, man, look at my brush.
It's all sticking together.
Somebody  needs to
go clean them out.
According to rank,
that would be, uh, be you.
What I gotta do?
There's a hose out by the shed
in the yard. You can use that.
Clean those, too.
A'ight.
Sorry I busted up
the party, yo.
Who is he?
For your purposes, all you need
to know is that man in the photo
used to work for the company.
He went rogue.
And how's he involved
in this situation?
He's Burrows' father.
Wait, wait, wait.
You picked the son of a
company man to be our patsy?
The company know?
The company did know.
That was the whole point.
How about you
elaborate on that?
How about you stop with
all the questions?
You're a glorified bodyguard,
that's it.
The job's to be seen, not to be heard.
Is that understood?
- How close are we?
- Oh, we're good to go, baby.
- Got another badge.
- What is this, happy hour?
Scofield? Pope
wants to see you.
The rest of you round up,
you're done in here.
Hey, CO Patterson said we had till
the end of the day finish up.
And I say yu're done.
There's a couple hours of work I want
done in the yard before sundown.
Come on, let's go.
- We're dead.
- We're not.
- I'll get it done.
- It's gotta be done tonight.
I said I'll get it done.
Scofield, Pope's waiting.
Hey, Linc.
You going to let me out?
No, Linc,
just came to let ynow set a new date.
DOC refiled all the paperwork.
Execution's a week from
Friday at midnight.
You going to let me out
in the yard or what?
Unless I hear it from the Pope himself,
I can't.
Come on, man, ten minutes.
That's all I'm asking. Ten minutes.
I'm sorry.
Some guy just walks
into the courthouse,
drops off some medical records,
Lincoln gets a stay of execution, then--
poof-- he disappears
into the cold.
Who do you think it could be,
some anti-death penalty fanatic?
Come on, in this case,
I doubt it.
But without a name or a paper trail,
we got no way of getting to him.
So once again we have nothing.
I wouldn't exactly call a
2-week stay nothing, okay?
It's more than we
had yesterday.
Can I ask you a question?
Do you really think that you're
going to get to the bottom of this?
That they'll you get
to the bottom of this?
These  guys don't exist.
You go after them with the law,
and they'll just use it against you.
We're doing the
best we can, okay?
Law's the only we're gonna
bring them to justice, LJ.
They gunned my
mother down, man.
You think I give a
damn about justice?
I want them.
I wanna do to them what they did to me.
Come on, LJ.
It's for the courts to decide,
not us.
Look they're gonna
slip up, okay?
They're gonna leave a piece of
evidence that can't be refuted.
And we're going to be
waiting when they do.
Maybe they already slipped up.
Up at the cabin, at the well.
Quinn.
Somebody covered it up.
They must have come
and gotten him.
There's only one
way to find out.
Look, there's his cell phone.
Easy.
Okay, a little lower!
A little more.
Okay, I got it.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Pull me up.
Will you give us
a minute, Gary?
Michael, I want you to be
absolutely honest with me.
Dr. Tancredi found this embedded in
your flesh when she was treating you.
Apparently, it came
from a guard's uniform.
Have you been assaulted
by an officer?
Michael, Michael,
I need an answer.
This is not about sticking to
the inmate's code anymore.
This is about officer misconduct.
That's my responsibility.
You wouldn't want to see me
lose my job now, would you?
No, of course not.
You have been very good
to me and my brother.
But I need to know where
you got that burn right now.
Otherwise, your ass is going
to solitary. You understand?
It's your choice.
- Listen to me.
- Cool down!
Listen to me, don't do this!
Don't do this!
Michael!
No!
Michael.
Michael? Michael?
Linc?
What the hell are
you doing in here?
Linc, we're in a
lot of trouble now.
What happened?
The Pope asked some questions
that I couldn't answer.
About what?
He's got proof that I was
where I wasn't supposed to be.
He doesn't know it,
but sooner or later
he's going to put the
whole thing together.
There's no way out of this.
Yeah, there is.
You just got to keep the faith.
No.
I put my blood into this,
and it's coming apart.
Listen to me.
The whole point of solitary is
to break you, make you crazy.
You got to keep strong,
you hear me?
Don't let them break you.
I put my blood into this.
Look, baby, I'm so sorry it took
me so long to get back to you.
Turns out that our division is not
getting mobilized for a couple
more days.
When I didn't hear from you,
I didn't know what to think, baby.
I got so worried. I started watching
the news, looking for casualties.
I'm so sorry about all this.
You gotta believe that.
I started calling the
Rear Detachment Office,
asking if there was some sort
of problem with the 117th.
Uh, no.
There's not a problem with the 117th.
We're coming back.
It's a snafu, that's all.
A couple more days,
and we'll be on those hops, baby.
That's not what the Rear
Detachment officer said.
He said the 117th wasn't coming
home for another six months.
What? Uh, no.
That can't be right.
-  That's what he said.
- Ah, you know what it is?
It's because we're transpo.
You know, technically we're
on a loan-out from the 140th.
I mean,
that's why he said that.
- The 140th?
- Yeah, yeah.
It's just a few more days.
That's all. I mean...
You don't need to go calling anyone.
I'll be back, okay?
I will call you as soon
as I know the exact date.
- Okay? I love you.
I love you.
Michael's in the SHU.
Oh, God,
the hits just keep comin'.
Last thing we wanna do
now is panic, fellas.
Oh, it's panic time, old head.
We got an unfinished hole
in that room over there
that Scofield was
supposed to fill tonight.
Come tomorrow 8:00 a.m., they rip
up that carpet, our game is over.
Unless someone else fills it.
Uh-uh.
He's right, papi. You're the only one
with a toilet open to the outside world.
You're saying I go out
there by myself tonight?
That's exactly
what we're saying.
Are you kidding?
That's impossible.
Look, I don't wanna hear
impossible from you right now.
I got people waiting on me--
people that I'm gonna lose unless you
man up and get some  cojones, comprende?
That's easy for you to say, pendejo.
It ain't your ass on the line.
All of our asses
are on the line.
And you're the only cat that
can do something about it.
Yeah, maybe I can
get out of my cell.
And maybe I can get
into the guards' room.
But even if I do,
and I fill that hole in,
I'll still be in that room.
I'll be sealed in.
There's no way out.
Scofield must've had a way.
He did.
The grate at the sally port.
Oh, that's right. The one out
there in the middle of the open?
Yeah,  so you better
lace up, amigo,
'cause you're gonna have
to make a run for it.
That's ten years on my
bid if I get caught.
Better figure out a
way not to get caught.
Line it up!
Tonight, primo.
It's gotta be tonight.
Michael.
You okay? What you doing?
Trying to remember what's
beneath psych ward.
You're thinking about
the wrong thing.
You got to think about
how to get out of here.
Michael.
Man, come on. Talk to me.
Uh-uh. Absolutely not.
If I'm gonna be the one doing that
running, you gotta do some lifting, too.
I mean,
you know what you're asking of me?
You gotta do it for the team.
Hey, sister.
Your bloomers are showing.
They aren't showing, baby,
they're flying. Proudly.
I take it you are a party girl.
L.J.? Come on, were leaving.
Okay.
We get Quinn's phone powered up it
could be a gold mine of information.
No. Doesn't fit.
We just need to find
the right adaptor.
What about Quinn?
Are we just gonna leave him here?
You mean the guy who
shot me in the back?
Yeah, we're just
gonna leave him here.
You tell anyone about this,
and I...
Capitol Hill saw its
first deadlock of the term
on the Senate
floor this morning.
The hotly contested energy
bill ended up in a 50-50 tie.
That means it will now be up to Vice
President Reynolds to cast the
deciding vote.
I know I sound like a broken record,
but you work too hard.
You need to get out,
hang out with your friends more.
What about men?
If this is your exposé on my social
life, it's about to be a real sad one.
I, uh... I've had some bad luck
when it comes to relationships.
You had bad luck or
you had bad boys?
I think I've managed to
have a little of both.
Yeah, you know, you're right.
I don't tend to go for the nice guys.
I like the ones with the
deep-seated emotional issues
I can internalize
and make my own.
Mm-hmm.
- Like Scofield?
- Nope, not like Scofield.
Don't lie to me.
Every time he comes in for his shot,
you spend 20 minutes
rolling up his sleeve.
You know what?
I think he's interesting.
And I think he's attractive,
but he's still an inmate.
Promise you one thing.
And  that's that you will never see
anything happen between me and
an inmate.
Michael.
What? What'd you say?
I put my blood into this.
Stop! Freeze right there!
Get down on your knees!
Please don't shoot!
The State of Illinois doesn't look too
kindly upon prisoners who try to escape.
Charges are filed, you get sent
back to county for three months.
Come back here with ten more
years added to your bid.
I wasn't trying to escape.
Sure you weren't.
You were just out there
howling at the moon.
If I were you,
I'd start talking. Mano.
I stayed out after yard today.
I waited under the
bleachers until it got dark.
Something was gonna
come over the walls.
Drugs is almost
as bad as escape.
Last guy had heroin slingshot over the
wall got a nickel added to his bid.
It wasn't drugs.
Then what the hell was it?!
Frisk him!
What do we have here?
A pair of grunds?
You risked going to the
SHU for a pair of grunds?
Hell, you risked adding
extra time to your bid
all for a pair of panties?
My girl just wanted me to know
she was thinking about me, boss.
You got a real beefer on your hands,
don't you?
I know, boss.
It's the dumbest thing I've ever done.
I'm just scared that being here,
I'm gonna lose her.
- He did it for love.
- Then you understand.
Yeah, sure, Sucre.
I understand.
Don't let me catch you
alone next time, okay?!
Sucre!
Sink?
Sucre.
- Where's Michael?
- Other side of you.
Michael. Michael!
Michael!
Michael, come on.
Badge!
Yeah?
Check out my brother.
He's not responding.
What?
Scofield. Check him out.
He's not responding. Please.
Scofield. Scofield.
I need a medic in 12 now.
- What?
- I repeat, now.
An electronics store on Eighth Avenue.
Grab his phone.
We'll be back in ten minutes.
Stay on the couch.
You've reached Owen Kravecki.
I can't come to the phone right now.
You really think you're gonna get to
four buttons before I get to one?
Leave a message,
and I'll return your call.
Thanks. Have a great day.
Light on 12.
Would you wait outside, please?
Michael?
Okay, you're going to feel
my fingers on your wrist.
Come on, I need your eyes.
I'm going to take a
look at that hand.
You're going to be okay.
- Sucre got...
- I heard.
Papi better had
did us right, man.
Hope he had enough time.
Looks like we
about to find out.
Make it fast.
I thought we picked Lincoln
Burrows off the street
because he was some lowlife
who couldn't defend himself.
Now I learn it's all
about his father,
some old spook the company's
trying to settle a score with?
Well, fortunately for us,
the company's agenda and our
agenda have the same endgame.
Caroline, I've been
doing this for 15 years,
and it's never been about
anything other than you,
your family, and most importantly,
this country.
I need to know who
I'm working for here.
- You are working for me.
- Promise me that.
I promise you, Paul.
I got to go now.
And to what do I
owe this honor?
To the vote on the Senate
floor this afternoon.
Look, I get it. The vote comes down
to me, and I vote no. It'll get done.
Well, actually, we are going to
need you to vote "yes" on this one.
I want to make sure
I heard you straight.
You want me to vote on the
environmentalists' side?
This isn't about a vote.
This is about you and
how you look to voters.
Now, we have a nation that is growing
increasingly hungry for
alternate energy,
so if you come across
as more centrist,
you'll appeal to the broadest
swath of the electorate--
the very people who will
get you elected next year.
Besides, once that bill hits the
president's desk, he'll veto it.
Then we'll get precisely what we
always wanted anyway, won't we?
You probably don't have a
hair on your body, do you?
Just back your punk-ass up.
Hey, Tweener! Get over here.
Looks like Avocado has
taken a shine to you.
I could set you up as
cellies if you want.
Stop it, all right?
I got something
for you this time.
Scofield and his boys--
they're up to something.
How about being a
little more specific?
Whatever it is, it's got to deal
with that room they're fixing...
something to do
with the carpet.
Excuse me, fellas.
Out of the way!
Michael!
Michael! Michael!
He's totally nonresponsive,
so start him on chlorpromazine.
I believe he's in danger
of a psychotic break.
I want you to notify me immediately
if and when that happens.
Clean him up.
You scared me.
Put it down.
You're not a killer.
You don't want to make
any rash mistakes here.
Don't move!
- Go easy, go easy...
- Shut up!
LJ, there's other ways out of this,
you know, okay?
I can help you beat this rap,
but if you pull that trigger,
you really will be a killer,
and then I can't help you, okay?
I'm government, LJ. There's a
lot of things I can do for you.
The only thing you
can do for me is die!
Drop your weapon!
I said drop your weapon!
Guess you're going to have to take
a rain check on that one, huh?
Drop the gun now!
No. I did what you said.
You brought me a pile of crap.
There was nothing there.
Well, it's cool, man;
I need some more time.
You had your time.
You're a waste of my fries.
Open on 88!
Dude, just give me
another chance.
Close on 88!
Have at it.
Boss.
Boss!
You were lucky.
Kid's got a warrant
for double homicide.
Oh, dear. Are you serious?
Did you have any prior
contact with him?
Any idea why he
chose your house?
No, none. I mean, he was screaming
something like, "You killed my mom,"
and going on about me being
a government agent, and...
I don't know, it just seemed like
that kid was on drugs or something.
What do you do for a living,
Mr. Kravecki?
I'm a, uh, regional sales manager
for a dehydrated meat distributor.
What, you mean like jerky?
- Yes. You a fan?
- What kind?
Buffalo.
Have some. Really.
I'm swimming in the stuff.
One hour till lunch.
- What's the problem?
- You're looking at it.
- What, Haywire?
- Yep. He's my new cell mate.
I think I have schizoaffective
disorder with bipolar tendencies.
- Your tattoos.
- What about them?
- What are they of?
- They're just tattoos.
The man's got a
maze on his skin.
Why would he do that?
Why would he put a maze on his skin?
It's a pathway.
Where does it lead?
Hello, roomie.
You were right about my tattoo.
It is a path,
just like you thought.
And I need you to remember
when you saw it, Haywire.
I need you to remember
what it looked like.
Do you think you
can do that for me?
Who are you?
Transcript: Raceman
Synchro: travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net