Previously on Prison Break:
There's something
about this guy.
It's like he knows where we're
going and what we're thinking.
If that's true,
it's just a matter of time
before he finds out
about the money in Utah,
our way into Mexico...
Everything.
...have an attorney present
during questioning...
Caroline, they're
taking her in.
Of course.
I'll keep an eye on her.
I did it, Dad.
Just do as you're told.
Otherwise there will be consequences
that will affect us all.
My dad's an Air Force colonel.
When I told him I was
staying in a hotel with
a guy that I maybe sorta liked,
he lost it.
What are you doing here?
Where's Maricruz?
She's with me now.
- Don't push it.
- Hey, Fernando, slow down, man.
I was trying to tell you,
the wedding is in Vegas.
- Which one of them was it?
- Might be Scofield.
Probably gonna find his
brother in there, too.
- Where to, sir?
- Utah.
This morning,
authorities in Illinois issued an update
on the escaped convicts known
until now as the Fox River Eight.
Chicago mob boss John
Abruzzi was gunned down
outside a Washington D.C.
motel last night
after investigators received
a tip from an informant.
The other seven escapees are still
at large and considered dangerous.
I didn't think Abruzzi'd
be the first to go.
I have a feeling we're in
for lots of surprises.
They said seven are still out there.
So much for faking our deaths.
I bought us some time--
that's what counts.
- How much further?
- 70, 80 miles.
Good.
Means we should be hitting the
Double K Ranch by this afternoon.
Or we can keep driving,
pick up LJ and hit Panama.
We can't hit Panama!
We can't hit anything!
We can't do anything without the money.
We need to find
Charles's stash.
I know some other guys who
are thinking the same thing.
The money is buried under a
silo at the Double K Ranch
just outside of Tooele, Utah.
There's $5 million there.
Oh. Um, you know,
when I was in Cheyenne,
I pulled my ticket
out of the bag.
It tore in half, and...
I have no idea what
happened to the other part.
They didn't issue
you a replacement?
No. The young lady-- I think--
her name was Sherry--
she actually said that this half is
okay because the bar code is on it.
Well, you really need
the whole ticket.
This is exactly what
I was trying to avoid.
She said that everything
would be fine because...
That's okay. It'll do for now.
But make sure you ask for a
replacement when you get to Provo.
I definitely will. Thank you.
- It's always something, uh?
- Oh, God, I know.
I don't wanna go home.
I wish we could keep driving.
I don't think your Pops
will be down for that.
Wouldn't it be fun?
We could go to...
Hawaii?
Yo, you can't drive to Hawaii.
Yo.
I know.
I'm just saying I wish.
Whoa, whoa.
No, no. Don't get it.
They'll leave.
Just let me see who it is.
It's a cop.
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry to disturb you, ma'am.
Have you happened
to see this person?
Last night we got a few phone calls
that he was spotted in the area.
So we're going door-to-door.
Why are you looking for him?
He escaped from prison in
Illinois a couple of days ago.
Have you seen him?
No.
He doesn't look familiar.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
All right.
Thanks for your time.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This ain't...
This is not what you think,
all right? Look.
Listen to me, this...
Just... listen. Okay?
All I did was steal
a baseball card.
Okay? I'm not like those
other fools up in there.
I'm gonna go for a walk, okay?
I'm gonna leave my
keys right here.
And when I come back,
my car will be gone.
I'm sure, in a few hours,
they'll find it somewhere...
abandoned.
Wait. Wait.
I wish it could be different.
I have to go.
"Too-le."
I think it's "To-ill-uh."
Hell of a town.
Small is good.
Means the ranch'll be easier to find.
All we got to do
is get that money
and we'll be out of
here by nightfall.
Right.
Oh, sir. Soil test came
back from Scofield's crash.
Not that you need any
more proof, but...
he really went out of
his way this time.
What else do you have?
Man was violently assaulted
in Nebraska by a hitchhiker
matching Bagwell's description.
He was headed west on the I-80.
Omaha's putting together
a photo lineup.
What do you have on Scofield?
What does anybody
have on Scofield?
Uh, I've got some results
from his hard drive.
The one recovered
from the river.
We were able to use the sector editor to
restore the master boot. So
from that...
I don't care how you did it.
What do you have?
More than half the contents
of the buffer. About 60%.
It looks pretty random.
Print it up. All of it.
I want it on my desk.
Well, guess what?
No listing for a
Double K Ranch.
Excuse me. You know where I
might find a Double K Ranch?
- What you call it?
- Double K Ranch.
- No.
- You from around here?
Yeah. Born and raised.
There's no Double-nothin'.
Great. Thank you.
Looks like Westmoreland spent his last
breath blowing smoke up your ass.
There's one way to find out.
The county keeps property records.
Every plot is mapped out with
dimensions. It's public record.
But if there is a tax
assessor's office here,
it's gonna be in there,
the Municipal Building.
Lots of cops in there, Michael.
- Dispatch.
- Someone...
someone stole my
car this morning.
I'm at the Lotus Motel
off Interstate 80.
Did you see who took it?
No. I went out for a walk and
when I came back, it was gone.
This morning?
Why didn't you call before?
I... I don't know.
- Mr. Kellerman.
- Mr. Kim.
Surprised to see
you in Chicago.
- Just looking for updates.
- Sara Tancredi. I'm on it.
Is pursuing her the
best use of your time?
It is.
She's in contact with Scofield.
I was there when he
called yesterday.
We stay with her,
she takes us right to him,
he takes us to Burrows.
All right.
If you're that confident.
I am.
- I'll let the president know.
- I contact the president directly.
I'll contact her.
Keep me posted.
If you want to restore your dignity,
you need to take action.
Making amends requires much
more than saying "I'm sorry."
It means learning to change.
The apology is just
the first step.
The most important thing is
that you display honesty,
courage and compassion when
you extend your apologies.
You need to earn
your forgiveness.
We'll talk about
it more on Friday.
I've got a great idea.
What's that?
Since you are such a fan of lame,
store-bought blueberry pie,
I am going to bake you a real
pie of your choice tonight.
I can't.
I really don't need to be seeing anyone
right now who isn't my therapist.
I've been a hermit lately, too.
My partner Daniel's
away on business.
I've been sitting around every
night by myself. Kind of pathetic.
I am so sorry.
I thought you meant...
Um...
I thought...
- The pie...
- Oh, no.
That's my ego.
No, I was really
talking about...
- Pie?
- Yeah. Actual blueberries.
Like we'd make pie and
watch Fried Green Tomatoes.
I get it, I get it.
I'm the best ex-junkie
cook in this town.
Thank you. I just...
I got to clean my apartment.
It's disgusting, and I realize that
sounds like an excuse; it's not.
No, no, no, I get it. Um...
You do what you got to do.
Have a good night.
Do you deliver?
Next batch.
Just... put it on the desk.
Does any of this
stuff mean anything?
I don't know. Ask me later.
Think he's a genius
or a whack-job?
I think we answered
that question
when we assigned a hundred
agents to the case.
So why don't you go and get me the rest
of it, huh? Does that work for you?
Alackaday. I just found
me an In-betweener.
Where you going in
such a hurry, huh?
- None of your beeswax, yo.
- I know where.
Same place as every other man
who was in that room that night.
They all comin' around here
for a big family reunion
at the Ku Klux Ranch.
If they ain't here already.
Ain't no country folk in this town
ever heard of the Double K Ranch.
Seems like you've been misinformed.
Indeedy there is a Double K.
It's just a matter of who
gets there first, all right?
The stars are going to
collide in Tooele, my friend.
You're going to need
me on your side.
This ain't Fox River, all right?
I don't need any...
As you can see... I need you.
Get your grubby paws off me, you freak.
I ain't your ditch digger.
I don't want nothing from you.
I don't need nothing.
You might ...if a man knew where
he was supposed to be looking.
Hi. Are you having the Hector Avila
and Maricruz Delgado wedding today?
- Avila.
- No? Okay, thanks.
Hi. Are you having the Hector Avila
and Maricruz Delgado wedding today?
Avila.
Delgado.
Really?
When?
Stay calm.
We'll be out in ten minutes.
One at a time. Clear.
Back up.
- Are you wearing a watch?
- Uh, yeah.
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
This is exactly what we need.
It's a map of every parcel of land.
Topography, buildings...
everything.
Karl Kokosing. Double K.
I don't like the way this
guy is looking at us.
1213.
Where's 1213?
Ms. Sebern,
I need to speak with you.
Come on, man,
we got to roll now.
Ms. Sebern.
Come on. You got the map?
No.
Someone else does.
Someone got here before us.
It's the only explanation.
Son of a bitch is still alive.
Hey, pretty!
What are you going to do,
scream, man?
How the hell...
are you still breathing?
What the hell did
you do to your hand?
Easy, easy...
I recently had some work done.
- Where's the map?!
- Easy, easy...
I don't have it.
Where is it?
I'm telling you, I don't have it.
I dot have it, all right?!
You were there. We saw you.
It was gone whe I got there.
Now why don't you keep
your pooch away from me.
I'll tell you
everything I know.
It's the kid. He has it.
I saw him this morning
and I needed some help.
We made a deal, all right?
He said he would dig.
I told him where we could get a map.
What kid?
The best thing to
do is nothing.
That's how I'm going
to the U.S. Senate
to confirm my vice president,
do nothing?
Shows them you can do the job.
It's my daughter.
Sir, we need to talk
about your daughter.
What about her?
Well, the media is all over
this Fox River situation.
We think it would be best if you
could distance yourself from her...
If I hear this one more time...
I paid her bail, I walked away.
I have distanced myself.
Give me a minute.
Hey, Dad, it's me.
When you get a chance, I really need
to talk to you about something.
Um, actually a lot of things.
Uh, the most important
one is that..
I owe you an apology.
I, uh, I realize that I've made
things difficult fou lately.
And I want to take
responsibility for that.
Um...
call me back. Bye.
Hi. I know I'm early,
but I brought dinner.
Come in.
You're not a vegetarian,
are you?
No. Just shut that behind you.
You mind if I check my e-mail?
- No, not at all. Here.
- Oh, you're so kind. Thank you.
Do you happen to
have a pen handy?
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
I'm so sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Look, I have a little pencil and a pad.
Thank you.
Sir?
Yeah.
There's no Sherry in Cheyenne.
Your ticket is not valid for travel.
Hold on. That can't be right.
That can't bght.
- Excuse me for a second.
- Sure.
All right now, listen, brother.
I'm going to give
it to you straight.
Listen, I'm broke, okay?
That's the truth.
I just run into some
trouble back in...
I'm just really trying to pull it
altogether now, you understand?
Well, you can tell that to the
authorities in five minutes.
Oh, come on, we don't have to
get the authorities involved.
It's too late.
They're already waiting
at the next stop.
These guys here, they're gonna
sit with you until we stop.
I understand. I understand.
Hey!
Hey, you can't go in here!
Okay, we've got a confirmed
sighting on Franklin.
Jumped out of a moving
train in Preston, Idaho.
What is a black man from Chicago
doing in Idaho? He's got to be lost.
Franklin's in Preston, Idaho.
Bagwell's in Nebraska.
And both men have never been
across the Mississippi.
Visiting friends and family?
I don't think so. And not...
south of the border. They're due
west and we need to know... why.
Out.
What's going on, friends?
Where did you say
Tweener was headed?
Up on the main drag.
He was supposed to find a shovel.
In.
No. No, no, no.
In!
You coming back, right?
You coming back?!
Yep.
Hey, you guys! Hey!
Come on, man,
I'm gonna help you here!
I was on my ATV,
and I was hauling ass.
I was right on her tail,
and I pulled out
my gun and blam!
That bitch treed herself,
and I brought her down in one shot.
- What'd she weigh?
- Least a hunny.
Maybe one-ten.
Come on out and see us if you want.
It's gonna be a good time.
Yeah, I just might do that.
Hey, now, what you digging?
Uh...
some stuff in my
grandpa's yard.
We got a bigger one in the
back if you're going deep.
No, this will do.
Damn it if I don't know
you from somewhere.
Maybe I know your grandpa.
I doubt it, man.
He moved here, like, a month ago, so...
What's his name?
His name's Grandpa. A'ight?
Look, man, can you just ring this up?
I gotta get out of here.
Sure thing, fella. I'll ring it up.
I'll ring it right now.
I know where I seen
you on the TV.
You're one of them
Fox River boys.
- You got it wrong, man.
- No, I think I got it right.
We're closed!
Sorry, bud.
Closing up early today.
Hold on. Stay right there.
You're going down,
just like your buddy, you son of a...
Where's the kid?
Where's the kid?!
He's back here.
Get up.
Come on, tough guy. Let's go.
Maricruz. Baby, open up.
Theresa! It's me.
It's me, okay?
Fernando, what are
you doing here?
- You can't be here.
- I know, Theresa.
Where's your sister?
I need to see Maricruz.
She's getting her picture
taken with my mom and dad.
- The wedding's at 2:30.
- I need to see her now.
- You have to go.
- She's the mother of my kid, Theresa.
Please.
You don't want her to marry Hector,
do you? Do you?
I'll go see if I
can go get her.
- Wait in here.
- Okay.
Lance, I got a
question for you.
Yes?
Do you know who I am?
Uh... I happened to see
the news last night, yes.
Hey, I don't care. I've got some
skeletons in my closet, too.
One of them wears a dress.
Thank you.
I appreciate your lack of judgment.
From what I can tell,
you didn't do anything wrong,
but it's none of my business.
And you don't need to talk about it.
The whole thing just...
I never meant for it to happen.
Okay, you do not need to
answer this question.
But were you and that guy,
like, uh...
You're right,
I don't want to talk about it.
- You done?
- Yeah.
Does it worry you that he's...
out there?
Give me one second.
Dad.
- Sara, hi. I got your message.
- Please, come in.
Uh, Lance, this is,
uh, my father Frank.
- How do you do?
- Dad, this is my friend Lance.
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
I voted for you.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
Sara, I can take off.
No, no need.
It'll only take a minute.
Why don't you step into my office
and you make yourself at home.
Sure.
So, uh...
So, in my program, um...
we've been talking a
lot about making amends,
and I've been thinking
a lot about, um...
about some of the
choices I've made lately
and I know that
that affects you.
Um... and, uh...
and I...
I wanted to tell
you that I'm sorry.
You don't have to
say you're sorry.
Yeah, I do.
And it must be hard to
understand why I did it.
Um, I had no idea that I was
putting these guys back
out on the street.
I thought I was saving the
life of an innocent man and...
And I know that you didn't read
the information I gave you on Lincoln
Burrows, but he is innocent and...
a lot of the people involved
right now are dead.
Uh... I'm sorry.
This isn't why I call you.
I'm fine...
but I'm scared.
Sara...
I'm gonna help
you through this.
We're gonna get
through this together.
- Thank you.
- I promise.
Kellerman.
We ran that trace
you requested.
What'd you get?
- The line is disconnected.
- Whose was it?
- Apparently, no one's.
- What does that mean?
It's been out of
service for 17 years.
Fernando.
- Where is she?
- Oh, calm down. Calm down.
She's gonna come down
and talk to you.
She's on her way
down right now.
You and I got history.
We're family.
And out of respect for that,
I'm gonna let her make
her own decision.
- I'm not leaving without her.
- That's for Maricruz to decide.
You've been filling her
head with all this crap.
She's a smart girl. I personally
don't think she's gonna want
to live her life on the run,
but we'll see.
You know, she doesn't love you.
Yeah, I don't want to
get into that right now.
You're not raising my kid.
¿Tu me estas entendiendo?
That don't sound good, cuz.
Maricruz! Baby! Mari.
- You have to go.
- Where is she?
Please, Fernando,
they're coming!
Did you tell her I was here?
Did you?!
Maricruz...
Mahone.
I'll be right down.
- Mr. Mahone.
- Where are they?
Had a hard time getting
my hands on these.
It'd be easier to
go to a doctor,
tell him you need something
to calm your nerves.
Doctors take notes.
That's why I have a deal with you.
The way things been going,
I thought maybe our deal was over.
You don't ask me
about Shales no more.
That part of our deal is over.
I no longer need an
informant on the case.
Thought that's all you
cared about was finding him.
You can't get them all.
If you want,
I can keep an ear out on the street.
Midazolam. 1,500
milligrams every 30 days.
That's all I want from you.
We understand each other?
You gonna pay me for it?
Right there.
- What are you doing here?
- We had to come for you, buddy.
- How'd you know?
- T-Bag.
- Hand over the map.
- What?
The map. Hand it over.
He told you I had it?
We are going to sort
this out right now.
Tell me that's not
what I know it is.
It is.
But don't worry,
before I destroyed it.
I committed it to my
photographic memory.
Coming from a compulsive liar,
I find that a little
hard to believe.
I'da tattooed it to my body
but I didn't have the time.
Whenever you strip
search a lifer,
you should always
check his coin purse.
Tell us where the money is.
Now let's not dissolve into threats,
all right?
I'm going to take
the high road here
and suggest a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
I have the information,
you have the manual requirements
necessary to unearth
Westmoreland's buried booty.
- We're partners.
- And why is that?
'Cause as of this moment,
I'm your map.
So then, yo,
we split it four ways, right?
- Wrong.
- Get in.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- You're not worth 1.5.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Excuse me. Can I help you?
Oh. Yeah. Sorry, yeah.
Uh... whoo!
It's hot.
I was really wondering how
much you selling your RV for.
Probably out of
your price range.
- Come on, give me a shot.
- $40,000.
Look, I tell you what.
I'll be back in a couple days, okay?
- I can't hold it for you.
- I said I'll be back.
With cash.
Nice bike.
The wedding's at
2:30, Fernando.
We just got confirmation
on Fernando Sucre.
He was in Las
Vegas around 2:00.
Then a gas station attendant
spotted a guy on a bike
matching his description
in Mesquite...
an hour later.
Out west,
just like Bagwell and Franklin.
Yeah, but he was heading east.
And Bagwell's in Nebraska
on I-80 heading west.
And Franklin's train was heading west,
but he jumped off to the...
south...
- You know D.B. Cooper?
- Yeah, yeah, the hijacker.
But he was never found.
Yeah, but he's got to
be somewhere, right,
because someone hijacked
that plane in Portland
and jumped out over
the Pacific Northwest.
And someone was arrested two
days later in Bisbee, Arizona.
- Not the same guy.
- Same guy.
Same guy who was treated
for a broken knee
in a free clinic somewhere
around Salt Lake City.
Same guy whose Nova blew a head
gasket ten miles short of the border.
Same guy who almost got
away with a stolen car,
but he ran a woman down in Bisbee.
Vehicular manslaughter.
Arrested and booked as
Charles Westmoreland.
But he didn't have the money on him.
Which means...
He got rid of it
somewhere along the way.
Wait, wait, this is fact?
You figured all this out?
No. Scofield did. That's why he
was bringing the old man along.
The money's in Utah.
And they're all going to get it.
You know, in, uh,
Thailand they got a black market
where you can get any
kind of surgery you need,
- even a hand transplant.
- You're sick, you know that.
Keep going.
The turnoff's just up here somewhere.
Before or after Sheep Road?
What's the matter,
Theodore, did you forget?
How could I forget a road called Sheep?
It's after.
Don't you feel all warm inside
now that we're working together?
We aren't working together.
You're just here to lend a hand.
Slow down. That was it,
that little bitty road right back there.
How far is it from here?
Quarter mile if I remember
the scale properly.
Start walking.
- Frank?
- Yeah, I'm almost ready.
What time did you
say the flight was?
8:00.
Listen, I hope you get this
nomination more than anyone, but...
be prepared.
This Burrows thing may steamroll.
Well, we'll wait it out,
just like you said.
Problem is too many headlines.
His lawyer Nick
Savrinn's already dead.
His kid's awaiting trial
for double homicide.
And now his lead counsel
is classified as missing.
Well, is she missing
or is she dead?
I just thought you should know
before you go to Washington.
Bruce, is there something
connecting all of this?
It's probably best you don't
ask a whole lot of questions.
Where now?
Right up there.
The hill borders the property.
KK's on the other side.
First thing I'm gonna
do with the money?
Buy new shoes.
Second thing: tacos.
Third thing: ice cold beer.
Fourth thing:
a little toothpaste.
Mahone.
Agent Mahone,
your car's out front, sir.
The flight to Utah
leaves in an hour.
I'll be there. Thank you.
Ninth thing: a shower.
Tenth thing:
a good night's sleep.
A nice hotel. Clean sheets.
Look, stakes marking
the property line.
Should be dead ahead.
Can you see the silo?
The bastards built over it.
It's gone.
Traduction: Paqui et Cedr_c
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net