1
00:00:07,130 --> 00:00:09,180
Lj and sara will be traded for whiser.

2
00:00:09,610 --> 00:00:10,260
Are we clear?

3
00:00:10,660 --> 00:00:11,670
This can't be done in a week.

4
00:00:12,080 --> 00:00:12,750
You have a week.

5
00:00:13,240 --> 00:00:13,920
That's it.

6
00:00:14,290 --> 00:00:17,710
No one's ever broken out of this place before,
let alone with a week to plan,

7
00:00:17,810 --> 00:00:22,010
so you tell these people i'm gonna break this guy 
out of here or i'm going to die trying.

8
00:00:22,510 --> 00:00:25,500
You're going to stay on as my ears.

9
00:00:25,610 --> 00:00:29,370
You'll report back to me everything you hear when i'm not around.

10
00:00:30,770 --> 00:00:33,940
I know you've got a brother helping on the outside,
i know he ran into my girlfriend,

11
00:00:34,040 --> 00:00:36,150
and i know he took a book from her that belongs to me.

12
00:00:36,250 --> 00:00:37,570
This is what they took from me.

13
00:00:38,180 --> 00:00:41,450
So let's be clear,this is what matters to me.

14
00:00:42,420 --> 00:00:43,260
Not you.

15
00:00:44,020 --> 00:00:44,990
And not your book.

16
00:00:46,600 --> 00:00:47,980
How's lj?How's sara?

17
00:00:49,700 --> 00:00:50,470
They told me they're fine.

18
00:00:51,500 --> 00:00:52,500
What are you not telling me?

19
00:00:55,690 --> 00:00:56,770
You're not the only one affected...

20
00:00:56,870 --> 00:01:00,550
They killed sara and put her head in a box!And they got my son!

21
00:01:04,110 --> 00:01:05,510
you're running out of time.

22
00:02:15,500 --> 00:02:16,160
what's that?

23
00:02:19,380 --> 00:02:20,240
A rat.

24
00:03:22,960 --> 00:03:25,250
J.P.Getty had a formula for success.

25
00:03:27,530 --> 00:03:32,900
"rise early,work hard,stri oil.

26
00:03:33,780 --> 00:03:35,180
" just trying to get a drink of water,alex.

27
00:03:37,630 --> 00:03:44,410
As a devoted student of yr work and skills,
i-i really look forward to progress on your pl,michael.

28
00:03:44,520 --> 00:03:46,330
I'm looking forward to you getting off my back.

29
00:03:57,420 --> 00:03:59,280
Buenos,welcome to sona.

30
00:04:00,230 --> 00:04:01,030
Is that your wallet?

31
00:04:04,180 --> 00:04:05,240
Dame tu billetera.

32
00:04:06,210 --> 00:04:07,950
No hablo espa駉l,縣uh?

33
00:04:10,940 --> 00:04:11,890
You know what i said.

34
00:04:13,150 --> 00:04:13,850
No.

35
00:04:16,720 --> 00:04:18,050
That's the wrong answer.

36
00:04:27,320 --> 00:04:29,330
I am so ready to get out of here anytime you are.

37
00:04:36,180 --> 00:04:37,340
Man scofield,visita.

38
00:04:40,340 --> 00:04:41,700
Man scofield,visita.

39
00:04:45,930 --> 00:04:47,060
You look like you had a long night.

40
00:04:47,390 --> 00:04:48,000
Yeah.

41
00:04:49,610 --> 00:04:51,720
I spent most of it feeding chocolate to a rat.

42
00:04:52,280 --> 00:04:54,380
I don't have a whole lot to work with these days.

43
00:04:56,200 --> 00:04:58,180
She's got the book,man,the bird guide.

44
00:04:59,540 --> 00:05:00,210
She worked it out.

45
00:05:00,620 --> 00:05:01,860
So we have no leverage.

46
00:05:02,610 --> 00:05:03,310
No.

47
00:05:04,020 --> 00:05:08,820
Tell me something.When you were handing over the book,
did you ask for a recent photo of lj and sara?

48
00:05:08,820 --> 00:05:09,460
Yeah.

49
00:05:10,500 --> 00:05:11,120
And where is it?

50
00:05:11,950 --> 00:05:14,380
She showed me the pictures,
but she wouldn't let me keep them.

51
00:05:14,490 --> 00:05:16,140
Man,'m not in a position to bargain with these people.

52
00:05:16,240 --> 00:05:17,050
I mean,they're pissed.

53
00:05:17,790 --> 00:05:18,630
You break out tomorrow.

54
00:05:19,360 --> 00:05:21,630
Let's ju focus on that.Let's keep on track.

55
00:05:23,510 --> 00:05:24,150
All right.

56
00:05:26,820 --> 00:05:30,140
While i'm working from the inside,
i need you to take care of what happens once we're outside.

57
00:05:30,660 --> 00:05:33,170
We're going to need a getaway vehicle,
something inconspicuous.

58
00:05:33,810 --> 00:05:37,050
Whatever you find,it has to be parked 
a half mile from here by 3:00 p.M.Tomorrow.

59
00:05:37,150 --> 00:05:38,540
You mean a.M.
No,i mean p.M.

60
00:05:41,010 --> 00:05:41,980
We don't have a choice,linc.

61
00:05:43,000 --> 00:05:44,160
I ran some tests last night.

62
00:05:45,020 --> 00:05:46,660
Military jeeps patrol the perimeter at night.

63
00:05:47,290 --> 00:05:49,210
There's no way of telling where 
they're going to be in the dark.

64
00:05:50,050 --> 00:05:51,050
They were out there all night.

65
00:05:52,520 --> 00:05:54,380
We need the dark,we can't just...

66
00:05:55,090 --> 00:05:55,800
Just...Please.

67
00:05:57,830 --> 00:05:58,960
Because we're doing this tomorrow.

68
00:06:00,180 --> 00:06:00,980
In the middle of the day.

69
00:06:26,590 --> 00:06:27,340
Who're you looking at?

70
00:06:28,600 --> 00:06:29,210
That guy.

71
00:06:33,670 --> 00:06:34,420
I know him.

72
00:07:12,550 --> 00:07:14,740
mcgrady,my friend,i'm going to need a watch.

73
00:07:14,840 --> 00:07:15,510
Maybe two.

74
00:07:16,460 --> 00:07:17,450
I'm not even going to ask why.

75
00:07:19,870 --> 00:07:21,660
I'm also going to need some binoculars.

76
00:07:23,700 --> 00:07:24,660
Old guillermo has a pair.

77
00:07:25,790 --> 00:07:27,110
There's no way hehel se y tm toou,man.

78
00:07:27,900 --> 00:07:28,960
But they shouldn't be hard to get.

79
00:07:29,450 --> 00:07:30,430
Where can i find this guy?

80
00:07:52,910 --> 00:07:53,930
We leave tomorrow.

81
00:08:00,170 --> 00:08:00,780
This...

82
00:08:06,400 --> 00:08:07,710
This is how we're getting out of sona.

83
00:08:08,550 --> 00:08:10,780
Getting out of the cell block shouldn't be a problem.

84
00:08:10,880 --> 00:08:14,460
The grate and bars are weak,
but we're going to need some kind of rope,some kind of ladder,

85
00:08:14,560 --> 00:08:15,700
to let us down on the other side.

86
00:08:16,870 --> 00:08:19,180
That's why i figured out the safest line 
from here to the hole in the fence.

87
00:08:20,090 --> 00:08:23,470
We do it in the day,we'll only 
be visible to the two guard towers.

88
00:08:24,010 --> 00:08:27,420
The perimeter guards are less prectable,
but they're only on at night.

89
00:08:27,520 --> 00:08:29,570
Scurrying across the field in the middle of the day?

90
00:08:29,670 --> 00:08:31,400
It's the only way to avoid the jeep patrol.

91
00:08:32,170 --> 00:08:34,430
Now,in the yard tomorrow,there's a soccer game at 2:00.

92
00:08:34,970 --> 00:08:36,640
That should provide some distraction inside.

93
00:08:37,290 --> 00:08:41,920
And yesterday when we were digging,
i saw the glare from the sun hit this guy in the late afternoon.

94
00:08:42,590 --> 00:08:45,370
Looked like he turned away,
like maybe his vision was blocd.

95
00:08:45,850 --> 00:08:46,570
It's not much of a break.

96
00:08:47,310 --> 00:08:50,770
No,but it is one way to do what we need to do.

97
00:08:51,350 --> 00:08:54,340
As far as this other guard,
his weakness has yet to be determined.

98
00:08:59,040 --> 00:09:03,260
If we're going to get around these guys,
we've got to get to know them.

99
00:09:06,450 --> 00:09:07,590
it's not going to be easy.

100
00:09:08,560 --> 00:09:09,930
There's only one real road that goes to the prison.

101
00:09:10,030 --> 00:09:12,010
We don't want a real road-- that's not an option.

102
00:09:19,280 --> 00:09:19,960
**

103
00:09:20,370 --> 00:09:22,030
**

104
00:09:22,780 --> 00:09:23,410
**

105
00:09:23,520 --> 00:09:25,480
**

106
00:09:25,580 --> 00:09:28,970
**

107
00:09:29,070 --> 00:09:30,910
Which is why i won't waste your time.

108
00:09:31,010 --> 00:09:33,190
When whistler's free,i need to get to him as soon as possible.

109
00:09:33,290 --> 00:09:35,850
I'm still trying to work out what's going to 
happen once they get past the fence.

110
00:09:36,650 --> 00:09:39,920
Once i know all the details,i'll let you...
Lincoln,calm down.

111
00:09:40,300 --> 00:09:42,450
It sounds to me like you and your brother 
are in over your heads.

112
00:09:44,120 --> 00:09:46,000
There's a bad joke about sara somewhere in there.

113
00:09:46,850 --> 00:09:47,540
Listen...

114
00:09:49,430 --> 00:09:53,060
I'll let you know all the details once i know them,
and then i'll call you.

115
00:09:54,310 --> 00:09:56,230
I want this to work out just as badly as you do.

116
00:09:56,720 --> 00:09:57,730
More,i'm sure.

117
00:09:59,560 --> 00:10:00,190
Lj?

118
00:10:00,760 --> 00:10:01,460
Lj's fine.

119
00:10:01,560 --> 00:10:02,460
You have 34 hours.

120
00:10:05,650 --> 00:10:06,270
What did she say?

121
00:10:07,870 --> 00:10:08,950
Nothing we don't already know.

122
00:10:09,050 --> 00:10:10,860
Let'get out of here; we got a lot of stuff to do.

123
00:10:21,420 --> 00:10:22,750
Se駉r rivera?

124
00:10:23,780 --> 00:10:24,880
who?

125
00:10:25,160 --> 00:10:27,890
you're jorge rivera,right?

126
00:10:28,140 --> 00:10:29,770
gravedigger at Sona?

127
00:10:30,450 --> 00:10:31,530
so?

128
00:10:31,780 --> 00:10:33,550
would you like a ride?

129
00:10:33,550 --> 00:10:34,810
No,no.

130
00:10:34,810 --> 00:10:37,020
someone's coming to get me a little bit.

131
00:10:40,450 --> 00:10:43,470
i had an arrangement with your predecessor.

132
00:10:45,300 --> 00:10:49,470
I need you to get this inside the prison.

133
00:10:49,890 --> 00:10:51,630
I don't go inside the prison.

134
00:10:51,800 --> 00:10:53,140
neither did he.

135
00:10:53,630 --> 00:10:55,120
how about this?

136
00:10:55,330 --> 00:10:57,610
you find a way to get this delivery inside the prison

137
00:10:57,610 --> 00:10:58,750
just this one time

138
00:10:58,750 --> 00:11:00,090
why would I?

139
00:11:00,380 --> 00:11:03,920
because I would give you five thousand dollars.

140
00:11:08,160 --> 00:11:09,430
five thousand dollars.

141
00:11:09,600 --> 00:11:10,750
for just one time?

142
00:11:11,330 --> 00:11:12,850
couldn.t you do that?

143
00:11:13,620 --> 00:11:15,410
I think you could do it

144
00:11:16,360 --> 00:11:17,640
in this?

145
00:11:18,480 --> 00:11:19,670
you're crazy!

146
00:11:20,620 --> 00:11:22,590
only you can do it

147
00:11:47,970 --> 00:11:49,390
I wouldn't let 'em see you do that.

148
00:11:51,580 --> 00:11:53,160
Who?
Anyone.

149
00:11:53,990 --> 00:11:55,520
It's a drinking fountain.

150
00:11:55,520 --> 00:11:57,390
They put their lips right on there.

151
00:11:59,100 --> 00:12:00,660
You understand what happened,s sdon't you?

152
00:12:01,290 --> 00:12:03,530
You're a-- what's-it- called?-- a riah.

153
00:12:04,810 --> 00:12:07,570
I made the same mistake when i walked in here tried to hang to my wallet.

154
00:12:07,570 --> 00:12:11,700
Next thing i knew,i spent the next two days kneecap deep in human feces.

155
00:12:12,830 --> 00:12:14,630
In sona,it's every man for himself.

156
00:12:14,630 --> 00:12:16,360
Here,cheese.

157
00:12:17,250 --> 00:12:18,420
I'm not hungry.

158
00:12:18,930 --> 00:12:20,100
Yeah,you will be.

159
00:12:22,230 --> 00:12:23,740
I saw the other americans.

160
00:12:23,910 --> 00:12:25,770
So none of you have called the embassy,huh?

161
00:12:25,880 --> 00:12:27,720
us gringos ain't all butt buddies.

162
00:12:27,720 --> 00:12:28,740
You want it?

163
00:12:28,740 --> 00:12:29,790
'Cause i'll keep it.

164
00:12:49,340 --> 00:12:50,060
Let's get this done.

165
00:12:50,060 --> 00:12:53,040
We're gonna have to watch both guards simultaneously.

166
00:12:53,300 --> 00:12:56,610
Your cell should provide a good view of the guard i saw yesterday.

167
00:12:56,760 --> 00:12:58,770
Keep track of everything he does and when he does it.

168
00:12:58,770 --> 00:13:01,380
Look for that glare,see if it shows up again.

169
00:13:02,380 --> 00:13:03,450
what will you be doing?

170
00:13:03,720 --> 00:13:05,680
Watching the other tower from here.

171
00:13:05,890 --> 00:13:07,840
While our back's turned,we're gonna need a lookout.

172
00:13:07,840 --> 00:13:11,310
Well,find mahone.

173
00:13:11,480 --> 00:13:13,040
I thought we were stringing him along?

174
00:13:13,240 --> 00:13:14,550
Looks like we're out of string.

175
00:13:21,850 --> 00:13:24,730
teodoro.
Si,patr髇?

176
00:13:24,730 --> 00:13:26,590
What they say about all work and no play,huh?

177
00:13:26,830 --> 00:13:27,890
Boy need his rest.

178
00:13:27,890 --> 00:13:30,190
Your cliente keeps a tight schedule.

179
00:13:30,560 --> 00:13:32,570
Got to make sure i see to their needs.

180
00:13:36,750 --> 00:13:38,530
I gave you a more important task.

181
00:13:40,000 --> 00:13:41,470
But i haven't heard a thing.

182
00:13:41,700 --> 00:13:42,850
Then listen harder.

183
00:13:46,340 --> 00:13:47,500
Mi amor.

184
00:13:47,920 --> 00:13:49,740
Ah,mi vida.

185
00:14:00,110 --> 00:14:01,750
Into my office.

186
00:14:23,410 --> 00:14:24,670
Anything yet?

187
00:14:25,530 --> 00:14:27,440
Nope,not yet.

188
00:14:29,640 --> 00:14:31,210
So what's your story,man?

189
00:14:33,040 --> 00:14:35,220
I mean,the next chapter,when we t out of here.

190
00:14:37,550 --> 00:14:44,370
Suppose you were married to the job,drank too much,rabid insomniac,typical lawman.

191
00:14:44,620 --> 00:14:49,550
Yeah,just like you reek of live bait,have a girl in every port,

192
00:14:49,670 --> 00:14:52,910
tell fish stors or so i've heard.

193
00:14:54,540 --> 00:14:57,650
Prior to this experience,i had the utmost respect for the law.

194
00:15:00,210 --> 00:15:03,390
This guy hasn't so much has scratched his jock in an hour.

195
00:15:03,630 --> 00:15:05,990
It's not gonna be easy to get around that guy.

196
00:15:10,570 --> 00:15:11,740
I dot know.

197
00:15:24,540 --> 00:15:26,250
We might just have break.

198
00:15:29,280 --> 00:15:31,210
I'm gonna go check on scofield.

199
00:16:20,570 --> 00:16:21,610
Sorry.

200
00:16:22,830 --> 00:16:24,020
Did you see the glare?

201
00:16:24,170 --> 00:16:27,360
Hit him hard at 3:13-- he turned to his right and ignored everything to the west 

202
00:16:27,360 --> 00:16:29,760
for six minutes,as far as i could tell.

203
00:16:32,650 --> 00:16:35,400
This guy thinks he's auditioning for buckingham palace.

204
00:16:35,930 --> 00:16:37,570
He's also a sports fan.

205
00:16:37,960 --> 00:16:39,340
He's got a tv.

206
00:16:39,730 --> 00:16:42,830
Twice in the last four hours the signal went fuzzy.

207
00:16:42,830 --> 00:16:45,820
He had to turn to adjust the antennae.

208
00:16:45,820 --> 00:16:47,670
That's nothing we can count on.

209
00:16:47,670 --> 00:16:48,820
True.

210
00:16:49,290 --> 00:16:52,890
But there is a device we can build out of some pretty common materials.

211
00:16:53,020 --> 00:16:54,950
It's almost like a radio,except it...

212
00:16:55,440 --> 00:16:57,070
Transmits signals.

213
00:17:20,630 --> 00:17:21,690
Pardon me.

214
00:17:22,030 --> 00:17:23,040
You're the new guy.

215
00:17:23,610 --> 00:17:24,680
Yeah.

216
00:17:24,680 --> 00:17:26,590
And who are you?
Not the new guy.

217
00:17:26,970 --> 00:17:27,710
So what's your deal?

218
00:17:27,710 --> 00:17:30,280
Public intoxication,tourist in trouble-- what is it?

219
00:17:30,280 --> 00:17:33,430
**I don't like people asking too many questions.

220
00:17:33,430 --> 00:17:34,700
Oh,you're an innocent man.

221
00:17:35,240 --> 00:17:36,400
Nothing wrong as a matter of fact,yes.

222
00:17:36,400 --> 00:17:37,920
Is this your first time in prison?

223
00:17:37,920 --> 00:17:39,200
Uh-huh.
Why?

224
00:17:39,200 --> 00:17:42,760
Because it's obvious-- rule number one: you mind your own business.You hear me?

225
00:17:42,870 --> 00:17:44,680
You know,you might want to do the same.

226
00:17:45,520 --> 00:17:47,660
You know exactly what i'm talking about.You got me?

227
00:17:50,050 --> 00:17:51,150
Yeah.
Yeah.

228
00:17:52,190 --> 00:17:53,530
**

229
00:18:05,060 --> 00:18:07,130
when'd you meet your boyfriend,whistler?

230
00:18:08,450 --> 00:18:09,800
My last year of school.

231
00:18:10,490 --> 00:18:12,610
I worked in this place in san isabel.

232
00:18:14,010 --> 00:18:16,880
He used to come around by himself and sit down in a bar.

233
00:18:17,540 --> 00:18:19,310
Hitting on the waitress.That's romantic.

234
00:18:19,310 --> 00:18:20,520
He is!

235
00:18:21,040 --> 00:18:23,670
Every time he goes away,he brings me back a present.

236
00:18:24,810 --> 00:18:25,860
Like this.

237
00:18:26,710 --> 00:18:28,080
Those are from sedona.

238
00:18:28,080 --> 00:18:30,300
His mother lives there in a retirement home.

239
00:18:33,130 --> 00:18:33,920
What's going on?

240
00:18:33,920 --> 00:18:35,520
Out of the car,juan bobo!

241
00:18:35,520 --> 00:18:36,550
縌u?Paso?

242
00:18:36,800 --> 00:18:37,670
This is a private road.

243
00:18:37,670 --> 00:18:39,140
I can explain.
Callete!

244
00:18:39,140 --> 00:18:40,200
What'd we do?

245
00:18:40,200 --> 00:18:41,230
Shut your mouth,american.

246
00:18:41,230 --> 00:18:42,400
縌u?Paso?

247
00:18:42,400 --> 00:18:43,560
This is state property!

248
00:18:43,560 --> 00:18:44,930
No vehicles allowed!

249
00:18:44,930 --> 00:18:47,720
All roads within two miles of sona are closed.

250
00:18:47,720 --> 00:18:48,950
We,we didn't see any signs.

251
00:18:48,950 --> 00:18:49,680
Where were you going?

252
00:18:49,680 --> 00:18:51,270
san isabel.

253
00:18:51,630 --> 00:18:52,860
San isabel?
Yeah.

254
00:18:52,860 --> 00:18:53,850
This your car?

255
00:18:53,850 --> 00:18:55,030
this is my car.

256
00:18:55,500 --> 00:18:57,290
there's papers in the glove box

257
00:19:01,580 --> 00:19:03,730
this is why my friends don't visit Panama

258
00:19:03,730 --> 00:19:05,890
you cops bother everyone

259
00:19:09,680 --> 00:19:11,390
This road is not for tourists.

260
00:19:13,500 --> 00:19:16,710
If i ever catch you out here again,i'll remember you.

261
00:19:16,710 --> 00:19:18,110
It ain't gonna happen again.

262
00:19:18,110 --> 00:19:19,240
Okay,go on.

263
00:19:19,400 --> 00:19:20,500
Anda.

264
00:19:23,630 --> 00:19:25,450
You okay?
Yeah.

265
00:19:25,800 --> 00:19:26,470
This is not gonna work.

266
00:19:26,470 --> 00:19:27,540
Where's the coast from here?

267
00:19:27,870 --> 00:19:29,150
I don't know,ybe three miles.

268
00:19:29,150 --> 00:19:30,860
All right,time for plan b.Come on.

269
00:19:37,140 --> 00:19:37,970
Found some more of these.

270
00:19:37,970 --> 00:19:46,320
We can make rope out of this hammock.Come on.

271
00:19:46,320 --> 00:19:47,520
You don't want to go in there.

272
00:19:48,320 --> 00:19:50,160
If you want to get out of this place i do.

273
00:19:51,270 --> 00:19:52,400
Stay here.

274
00:20:03,530 --> 00:20:05,830
Hey!Hey!Hey!Hey!

275
00:20:05,830 --> 00:20:06,990
Move it!

276
00:20:07,170 --> 00:20:08,370
Come on!

277
00:20:12,790 --> 00:20:13,870
what is it,chained down?

278
00:20:14,410 --> 00:20:15,950
It's hanging by a thread.

279
00:20:16,170 --> 00:20:17,260
It'll have to wait.

280
00:20:17,260 --> 00:20:18,770
It's 4:30.

281
00:20:19,200 --> 00:20:21,090
We've got less than 24 hours.
We'll make it.

282
00:20:21,090 --> 00:20:22,620
Tell me why.
What?

283
00:20:22,620 --> 00:20:24,880
What's so urgent we n't get you out of here the day after tomorrow?

284
00:20:24,880 --> 00:20:25,940
I don't know.

285
00:20:26,100 --> 00:20:27,680
I don't have all the answers.

286
00:20:28,820 --> 00:20:32,730
You don't know me,i don't know you,but it's your job to get me out of here.

287
00:20:35,320 --> 00:20:36,410
We'll come back later.

288
00:20:43,430 --> 00:20:44,600
I'll take this as well.

289
00:20:44,600 --> 00:20:46,000
Down here for the summer?
Yep.

290
00:20:46,000 --> 00:20:48,790
That's what i thought,back in 1985.

291
00:20:48,790 --> 00:20:50,430
Two wives,20 years later.

292
00:20:50,430 --> 00:20:51,660
Want everything in here?

293
00:20:52,040 --> 00:20:53,190
Yeah,thanks.

294
00:20:53,390 --> 00:20:55,560
International waters far out?

295
00:20:55,880 --> 00:20:57,200
That's 12 nautical miles.

296
00:20:57,200 --> 00:20:58,840
12 nautical miles,huh?

297
00:20:59,160 --> 00:20:59,980
Is that gonna do it he?

298
00:20:59,980 --> 00:21:01,120
Uh,yeah.

299
00:21:02,310 --> 00:21:03,990
$99.25.

300
00:21:05,030 --> 00:21:06,620
Here.
All right.

301
00:21:07,600 --> 00:21:08,730
Thank you.

302
00:21:10,400 --> 00:21:11,940
What did you get?
Supplies.

303
00:21:11,950 --> 00:21:12,930
Can you pop the trunk,please?

304
00:21:12,990 --> 00:21:14,580
Who am i gonna tell,honestly?

305
00:21:14,650 --> 00:21:16,330
You could be a russian spy for all i know.

306
00:21:19,290 --> 00:21:20,260
Live out of this thing?

307
00:21:20,310 --> 00:21:22,860
I have to be prepared in case of an emergency.

308
00:21:22,950 --> 00:21:25,780
Well,we got an emergency.

309
00:21:26,830 --> 00:21:29,120
I'm not going anywhere 
until you tell me where we're going.

310
00:21:29,120 --> 00:21:30,390
Solana beach.

311
00:21:30,760 --> 00:21:32,070
Why?

312
00:21:37,330 --> 00:21:38,620
They killed sara.

313
00:21:38,880 --> 00:21:41,410
I'm trying to make damn sure 
they don't kill my son.

314
00:21:41,560 --> 00:21:44,810
You don't think for a second 
your boy's not on that list,stay here.

315
00:21:44,850 --> 00:21:46,180
I couldn't care less.

316
00:22:11,480 --> 00:22:12,850
What is it?

317
00:22:13,440 --> 00:22:14,570
It's...

318
00:22:14,900 --> 00:22:16,070
Augusto.

319
00:22:16,460 --> 00:22:19,180
He won't pay the payment for you anymore.

320
00:22:21,360 --> 00:22:25,250
I went to him for payment like every monday,and...

321
00:22:26,350 --> 00:22:30,080
He said it's not his responsibility 
and that i should ask you.

322
00:22:30,120 --> 00:22:31,650
No,no,no,no.

323
00:22:32,650 --> 00:22:36,740
You tell augusto i don't pay for sex.

324
00:22:36,820 --> 00:22:39,480
I know,i did.

325
00:22:39,520 --> 00:22:41,340
But...What i do?

326
00:22:41,430 --> 00:22:43,470
I don't see anyone else...

327
00:22:43,620 --> 00:22:44,550
Yeah?

328
00:22:45,120 --> 00:22:46,950
Well,neither do i.

329
00:23:11,350 --> 00:23:12,370
Hey!

330
00:23:15,310 --> 00:23:16,890
You in charge of the food now?

331
00:23:17,440 --> 00:23:19,610
No boss.I'm the new gravedigger.

332
00:23:20,720 --> 00:23:21,640
You need to sign in

333
00:23:21,700 --> 00:23:22,930
before you get on the truck.

334
00:23:22,980 --> 00:23:24,870
I was just about to.

335
00:23:25,500 --> 00:23:26,660
Have you read the rulebook?

336
00:23:26,700 --> 00:23:27,780
Yes sir.

337
00:23:29,500 --> 00:23:30,720
Read it again.

338
00:23:41,560 --> 00:23:44,010
On the other side,when we get out of here,

339
00:23:44,990 --> 00:23:46,210
what's gonna happen?

340
00:23:46,260 --> 00:23:47,720
We're gonna meet someone from this company...

341
00:23:47,790 --> 00:23:49,190
Apparently.

342
00:23:50,550 --> 00:23:51,840
And then they're gonna kill me.

343
00:23:52,410 --> 00:23:53,700
You know tt.

344
00:23:53,770 --> 00:23:56,320
If they wanted to kill you,you'd already be dead.

345
00:23:57,020 --> 00:23:58,870
I don't see why they keep me alive.

346
00:23:58,910 --> 00:24:01,520
It's like you said-- 
you've got something they want.

347
00:24:02,490 --> 00:24:04,820
Once i give it to them,i'll be no use to them.

348
00:24:04,980 --> 00:24:06,070
Right?

349
00:24:06,160 --> 00:24:07,820
I don't have all the answers.

350
00:24:08,110 --> 00:24:10,630
All i knows it's my job to get you out of here.

351
00:24:13,080 --> 00:24:14,430
Let's go.

352
00:24:32,670 --> 00:24:35,960
It's twofer tuesday,
my one-time special just for you.

353
00:24:36,020 --> 00:24:37,270
But there's a price.

354
00:24:37,290 --> 00:24:40,150
Lechero's getting pretty 
sensitive about the cash flow.

355
00:24:40,220 --> 00:24:41,880
Well,i'm a little short right now.

356
00:24:42,610 --> 00:24:43,590
No worries,alex.

357
00:24:43,680 --> 00:24:46,400
I am notgonna leave you hanging,all right?

358
00:24:47,040 --> 00:24:48,950
We can just start you a tab.

359
00:25:20,850 --> 00:25:22,530
??? Think he saw us?

360
00:25:22,630 --> 00:25:23,790
I guess we'll find out.

361
00:26:29,420 --> 00:26:31,230
my third year in school,

362
00:26:31,300 --> 00:26:34,430
we studied electrical 
engineering with a focus emps.

363
00:26:34,530 --> 00:26:37,070
That's electromagnetic pulses.

364
00:26:37,560 --> 00:26:41,120
If you hook up a power source to a transmitter,
it generates a pulse.

365
00:26:42,020 --> 00:26:44,080
That pulse crashes anything electronic.

366
00:26:44,190 --> 00:26:48,070
What's that,l
ike an intro into anti-terrorist tactics?

367
00:26:48,110 --> 00:26:49,050
Basically.

368
00:26:49,070 --> 00:26:52,820
These days,they have to teach 
students how to defend theistructures.

369
00:26:53,090 --> 00:26:55,370
Fortunately for us,that guard tower is...

370
00:26:55,590 --> 00:26:57,780
It was engineered a long time ago.

371
00:26:58,100 --> 00:27:00,980
I'm guessing you always 
won the elementary science fair.

372
00:27:04,010 --> 00:27:05,350
Plug this in.

373
00:27:26,920 --> 00:27:28,400
did it crash the telly?

374
00:27:29,500 --> 00:27:31,140
We're too far away.

375
00:27:32,480 --> 00:27:35,210
But it is doing exactly what we need it to.

376
00:27:51,360 --> 00:27:51,940
Get out!

377
00:27:52,000 --> 00:27:52,820
Why?

378
00:27:52,920 --> 00:27:53,900
They're coming in.

379
00:27:57,360 --> 00:27:59,680
Ahora mismo.???

380
00:27:59,800 --> 00:28:00,810
Stay here.

381
00:28:00,850 --> 00:28:02,390
Do not let them see her.

382
00:28:02,420 --> 00:28:03,490
Do not!

383
00:28:06,210 --> 00:28:07,330
Come here.???

384
00:28:35,070 --> 00:28:36,070
colonel.

385
00:28:37,520 --> 00:28:39,220
We received no word of this!

386
00:28:39,640 --> 00:28:42,340
A rifle scope was seen from the tower.

387
00:28:42,490 --> 00:28:44,470
Capitan hurtado saw it with his own eyes.

388
00:28:44,490 --> 00:28:45,680
That's impossible.

389
00:28:46,480 --> 00:28:50,800
there is a gun in your prison,
and it was pointing at one of my men.

390
00:28:51,140 --> 00:28:52,640
We are going to find it.

391
00:28:54,290 --> 00:28:55,650
Vamos.

392
00:29:13,510 --> 00:29:14,560
This looks good.

393
00:29:14,630 --> 00:29:15,230
For what?

394
00:29:15,380 --> 00:29:16,490
Have a seat.

395
00:29:16,880 --> 00:29:18,310
What am i supposed to doing here?

396
00:29:18,650 --> 00:29:19,900
???

397
00:29:26,840 --> 00:29:28,960
When was the last time look lyou saw your son?

398
00:29:32,650 --> 00:29:34,920
You know,lincoln,
i don't automatically trust people either,

399
00:29:34,950 --> 00:29:37,820
but at least i can tell 
when they have good intentions.

400
00:29:37,850 --> 00:29:38,700
Good for you.

401
00:29:41,450 --> 00:29:44,070
You know,
i'm not gonna try to prove myself anymore.

402
00:29:44,870 --> 00:29:47,120
You do your job,and i'll do mine.

403
00:29:59,700 --> 00:30:00,630
You need something?

404
00:30:00,790 --> 00:30:01,330
What?

405
00:30:01,330 --> 00:30:02,270
You need something?

406
00:30:05,460 --> 00:30:06,200
No.

407
00:30:06,360 --> 00:30:07,020
Good.

408
00:30:27,930 --> 00:30:29,850
You don't'worry.
Is all gonna be okay.

409
00:30:29,870 --> 00:30:30,500
Noit's not.

410
00:30:30,500 --> 00:30:32,990
I promise you, i will not let anyone find you in here.

411
00:30:33,160 --> 00:30:33,700
Oh...

412
00:30:33,840 --> 00:30:34,970
Lechero hate me.

413
00:30:35,140 --> 00:30:36,170
Lechero does not hate you.

414
00:30:36,170 --> 00:30:38,570
You hold a very special place in his heart.

415
00:30:38,860 --> 00:30:40,690
So many girls can take my place.

416
00:30:40,840 --> 00:30:41,330
No, he's smart.

417
00:30:41,330 --> 00:30:42,640
He knows you're better than them.

418
00:30:42,670 --> 00:30:43,630
You're a real woman.

419
00:30:43,820 --> 00:30:46,400
A woman of her own will, her own desire.

420
00:30:47,010 --> 00:30:48,040
You know what i am.

421
00:30:48,270 --> 00:30:51,640
In this world, sister, we are all prostitutes.

422
00:30:51,820 --> 00:30:53,240
You are a queen.

423
00:31:48,220 --> 00:31:49,300
Whose cell is that?

424
00:31:49,320 --> 00:31:50,250
In the corner?

425
00:31:54,770 --> 00:31:55,900
Is that your cell?

426
00:32:06,050 --> 00:32:06,840
You!

427
00:32:06,990 --> 00:32:07,790
Is that your cell ?

428
00:32:08,020 --> 00:32:09,150
it's mine!

429
00:32:09,380 --> 00:32:10,390
It's mine.

430
00:32:14,410 --> 00:32:15,390
It's mine.

431
00:32:21,260 --> 00:32:22,400
I found this.

432
00:32:23,770 --> 00:32:25,180
It's not a weapon.

433
00:32:28,440 --> 00:32:30,100
I know what it is.

434
00:32:36,720 --> 00:32:38,170
Why were you watching me?

435
00:32:52,470 --> 00:32:55,580
I'm going to ask you one more time.

436
00:32:55,990 --> 00:32:58,180
Why were you watching me?

437
00:32:58,950 --> 00:33:01,040
- I wasn't watching you.
- I Saw you.

438
00:33:02,590 --> 00:33:03,400
Answer the question!

439
00:33:03,420 --> 00:33:05,880
I don't know what you think you saw,
but i wasn't watching you.

440
00:33:05,880 --> 00:33:07,660
Cinco.

441
00:33:08,820 --> 00:33:09,420
Cinco.

442
00:33:09,430 --> 00:33:11,140
- I wasn't watching you.
- Cuatro

443
00:33:15,930 --> 00:33:16,890
Tres!

444
00:33:16,930 --> 00:33:17,970
It's mine!

445
00:33:24,850 --> 00:33:26,480
Why were you watching him?

446
00:33:28,110 --> 00:33:28,920
I...
I wasn't.

447
00:33:28,940 --> 00:33:29,980
I was, uh...

448
00:33:30,900 --> 00:33:32,150
I was watching birds.

449
00:33:34,510 --> 00:33:35,310
Yes.

450
00:33:36,470 --> 00:33:37,480
Yes.

451
00:33:41,970 --> 00:33:43,110
See?

452
00:33:56,430 --> 00:33:58,410
Why did you not speak up before?

453
00:33:59,720 --> 00:34:00,830
I, uh...

454
00:34:05,260 --> 00:34:07,010
I was scared.

455
00:34:11,310 --> 00:34:12,940
I was scared.

456
00:34:14,580 --> 00:34:15,630
Coward

457
00:34:16,340 --> 00:34:18,090
Hurtado!

458
00:34:18,630 --> 00:34:19,550
Dejelo.

459
00:34:58,370 --> 00:35:00,260
Come on.
Come on!

460
00:35:00,290 --> 00:35:03,280
Please, please, please.

461
00:35:05,420 --> 00:35:07,370
Come on.

462
00:35:22,160 --> 00:35:23,870
He's coming back up here.

463
00:35:24,680 --> 00:35:25,870
Now, don't worry.

464
00:35:26,300 --> 00:35:27,600
It's all going to be okay.

465
00:35:29,170 --> 00:35:30,930
You have a little mascara right there.

466
00:35:35,790 --> 00:35:38,190
You need to look pretty for lechero.

467
00:35:43,630 --> 00:35:45,030
Thank you.

468
00:35:47,390 --> 00:35:48,920
Wait right here.

469
00:35:54,730 --> 00:35:56,640
A patrol passed through, but they didn't stay.

470
00:35:56,640 --> 00:35:58,560
Knocked some things over then walked away.

471
00:35:58,690 --> 00:36:03,630
I hid your woman in a safe plac
but i'd be lying if i didn't say it was a close call.

472
00:36:03,770 --> 00:36:04,700
Is she alone?

473
00:36:05,050 --> 00:36:05,860
Yeah.

474
00:36:13,200 --> 00:36:14,220
Hey.

475
00:36:15,890 --> 00:36:17,740
Don't be afraid.

476
00:36:18,240 --> 00:36:19,650
No, no, my dear.

477
00:36:20,250 --> 00:36:21,320
They're gone.

478
00:36:22,200 --> 00:36:23,680
I should go, too.

479
00:36:24,050 --> 00:36:24,570
No, no, no.

480
00:36:24,570 --> 00:36:25,370
What's the rush?
Come on.

481
00:36:25,480 --> 00:36:27,230
- No, i should get home.
- Go

482
00:36:32,520 --> 00:36:35,000
Patr髇,i gave her the money.

483
00:36:36,440 --> 00:36:39,580
I was going to replace it myself 
at the end of the day,when i get my cut.

484
00:36:39,750 --> 00:36:41,130
I just didn't t a chance to tell you.

485
00:36:41,230 --> 00:36:42,550
She had no money to get home.

486
00:36:42,590 --> 00:36:43,890
Is this true?

487
00:36:45,220 --> 00:36:46,330
Yes.

488
00:36:46,730 --> 00:36:48,800
Ye with all due respect.

489
00:36:49,230 --> 00:36:51,660
Surely you don't want 
your mistress travelin' broke.

490
00:36:51,720 --> 00:36:55,420
She'd end up in a taxi 
with no way to pay the cab fare.

491
00:36:56,630 --> 00:36:58,620
Ah,you did this?

492
00:36:59,370 --> 00:37:00,420
For me?

493
00:37:00,460 --> 00:37:01,650
Si,patr髇.

494
00:37:05,970 --> 00:37:09,360
The one that does all 
the useful things for me,huh?

495
00:37:10,360 --> 00:37:12,480
And now you do the thinking for me.

496
00:37:13,210 --> 00:37:15,830
No,no,it's not like that,patr髇--

497
00:37:21,490 --> 00:37:22,540
get the bucket.

498
00:37:23,690 --> 00:37:24,990
Wash my feet.

499
00:37:34,490 --> 00:37:35,840
So what do we do now?

500
00:37:37,720 --> 00:37:38,980
I don't know.

501
00:37:39,930 --> 00:37:41,240
Well,i'm afraid that's not good enough.

502
00:37:41,320 --> 00:37:43,070
Please just give me a moment to think.

503
00:37:43,270 --> 00:37:45,140
Wasting time is not an option for me,michael.

504
00:37:45,240 --> 00:37:46,530
I need to be out of here by tomorrow.

505
00:37:46,640 --> 00:37:48,860
I know,just in time for your next fishing trip,

506
00:37:48,900 --> 00:37:50,110
or is it a bird-watching trip?

507
00:37:50,280 --> 00:37:52,740
- I forget. 
- That's my trip log,i've told you.

508
00:37:52,920 --> 00:37:54,220
I need to retrace my steps.

509
00:37:54,250 --> 00:37:56,530
I'm doing everything they tell me,
the same thing you are.

510
00:37:56,710 --> 00:37:59,450
Just,just leave me alone,please.

511
00:38:00,020 --> 00:38:01,860
You know,before I was arrested,

512
00:38:01,910 --> 00:38:04,370
a n came to my flat and took my addresses.

513
00:38:04,470 --> 00:38:08,290
They know the name of everyone 
I care about and how to find them.

514
00:38:09,060 --> 00:38:12,450
Well,they already found 
everyone I care about.Okay?

515
00:38:14,210 --> 00:38:16,710
???

516
00:38:16,760 --> 00:38:18,350
Because time is runni out.

517
00:38:38,910 --> 00:38:40,650
Look,it's hot today.

518
00:38:41,890 --> 00:38:42,870
Yeah.

519
00:38:43,700 --> 00:38:45,470
Prefer the heat than the cold any day.

520
00:38:47,580 --> 00:38:50,460
You know my brother and I 
wanted to come down here to panama and

521
00:38:50,830 --> 00:38:53,880
start a dive shop like the one we were at today.

522
00:38:54,260 --> 00:38:58,300
My boy,he was gonna leave school 
and help us start the family business.

523
00:38:58,930 --> 00:39:01,040
When this is all over,why don't you do it?

524
00:39:03,600 --> 00:39:05,260
Too much bad stuff's happened.

525
00:39:06,440 --> 00:39:08,200
Still,you can make it work.

526
00:39:08,360 --> 00:39:10,130
It's only gonna work if...

527
00:39:10,520 --> 00:39:11,700
If whistler cooperates.

528
00:39:11,730 --> 00:39:13,420
If he plays games,people get hurt.

529
00:39:14,860 --> 00:39:16,190
You understand that,right?

530
00:39:17,160 --> 00:39:19,320
He doesn't want anyone to get hurt.

531
00:39:21,080 --> 00:39:22,210
I hope you're right.

532
00:39:22,640 --> 00:39:23,880
I want to show you something.

533
00:39:33,550 --> 00:39:35,130
Our getaway vehicle.

534
00:39:36,920 --> 00:39:44,510
Now,the next time you see him,
I want you to tell him what you saw.

535
00:39:44,930 --> 00:39:46,720
Tell him we're all in this together.

536
00:39:47,690 --> 00:39:49,070
We're part of a team.

537
00:39:49,980 --> 00:39:51,120
You understand?

538
00:39:51,430 --> 00:39:52,730
Okay.Yeah.

539
00:39:52,790 --> 00:39:53,690
All right,get up.

540
00:39:58,330 --> 00:39:59,900
We're coming back.

541
00:40:00,050 --> 00:40:01,400
No,this way.

542
00:40:02,990 --> 00:40:03,750
What?

543
00:40:03,850 --> 00:40:04,840
This way,come on.

544
00:40:05,590 --> 00:40:06,540
Okay.

545
00:40:15,480 --> 00:40:18,540
If all goes well,we'll see them tomorrow.

546
00:40:35,200 --> 00:40:37,010
Job well done.Thank you

547
00:40:38,420 --> 00:40:39,610
I thought you said
I was gonna get

548
00:40:39,740 --> 00:40:40,840
five thousand dollars

549
00:40:44,870 --> 00:40:46,660
That's what I'm talking about

550
00:40:48,660 --> 00:40:49,820
No,no,no,no,no.

551
00:40:49,850 --> 00:40:51,790
You said one time

552
00:40:52,810 --> 00:40:53,470
Was it difficult?

553
00:40:53,480 --> 00:40:54,390
That's not the point

554
00:40:54,390 --> 00:40:56,230
One time is one time

555
00:41:01,320 --> 00:41:04,940
This can work out for both of us

556
00:41:23,820 --> 00:41:26,890
Michael: if we're gonna do this today
we got to replace everything we lost.

557
00:41:27,400 --> 00:41:28,280
Like what?

558
00:41:28,440 --> 00:41:29,630
For starters,a new exit point.

559
00:41:29,630 --> 00:41:31,620
It's got to be on the south side of the building.

560
00:41:32,280 --> 00:41:33,530
Look at this guy,again.

561
00:41:34,350 --> 00:41:35,230
Hey!

562
00:41:36,330 --> 00:41:37,330
I know you,huh?

563
00:41:37,810 --> 00:41:38,460
Afraid not.

564
00:41:39,780 --> 00:41:42,200
You're mcfadden,right?

565
00:41:43,500 --> 00:41:45,600
Nice,1997?

566
00:41:45,740 --> 00:41:46,510
Sorry.

567
00:41:46,670 --> 00:41:47,690
You've confused me with someone else.

568
00:41:47,830 --> 00:41:49,120
Yeah,yeah,yeah,i swear.

569
00:41:49,590 --> 00:41:51,260
You were with the ambassador.

570
00:41:53,140 --> 00:41:54,960
You've mistaken me for someone else.

571
00:42:09,310 --> 00:42:11,570
Chap's insane. ?????

572
00:42:14,920 --> 00:42:16,820
Come on,guys,got something to show you.

573
00:42:21,700 --> 00:42:25,110
I'm sure i didn't observe the guards'
behavior in as much detail as you guys,

574
00:42:25,110 --> 00:42:28,260
but i did notice something yesterday.

575
00:42:29,740 --> 00:42:31,150
Right around this time.

576
00:42:34,490 --> 00:42:35,560
That's the day shift.

577
00:42:35,560 --> 00:42:36,850
They start up at 6:00.

578
00:42:36,870 --> 00:42:38,920
Just keep looking,keep looking.

579
00:42:42,580 --> 00:42:43,330
There.

580
00:42:52,690 --> 00:42:54,310
Where'd you get your cup,alex?

581
00:42:54,480 --> 00:42:56,930
I got it in the courtyard,
but apparently it's from him.

582
00:42:57,090 --> 00:42:59,190
He has one in the morning and one after lunch.

583
00:42:59,930 --> 00:43:01,640
Man's got to have his fix.

584
00:43:04,260 --> 00:43:05,620
If we get to that cup...

585
00:43:05,790 --> 00:43:07,040
We get to the man.

586
00:43:09,120 --> 00:43:10,780
We got to move.

587
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


588
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


਍਍㤹㤹਍〰〺㨰ⰰ〵‰ⴭ‾〰〺㨰ⰲ〰਍昼湯⁴潣潬㵲⌢晦晦〰•楳敺ㄽ㸴睷⹷癴畳瑢瑩敬⹳敮㱴是湯㹴਍