Previously on Prison Break:
What you're doing up
there in the infirmary,
what it's got to do with
what we're doing here?
Four days from now,
on the night of the escape,
we'll have 18 minutes to get the
bars off the infirmary window,
and for all seven of us to get
across the wire and over the wall.
- Is that doable?
- Of course.
Maricruz, it's me.
Baby, what the hell is going on?
Well, Hector says that you
can serve your full sentence.
What are you doing here?
Where's Maricruz?
She's not gonna be coming
around here anymore.
- This is a joke, right?
- She's with me now.
I just need to know
what Michael Scofield wanted from
you in exchange for the green card.
Why would you need a
credit card in prison?
If I'd have known that this is how
this whole thing was gonna turn out,
I'd have gotten some
crap job with the Feds.
Keep talking like that, I'm gonna be
forced to put a bullet in your head.
I need to get out while
I still got my life.
Daddy! Daddy!
Things have changed. I want in.
What's up?
We've got too many people.
I've done the math,
and one of them has to go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, it's, uh, not a problem.
- Hmm. Impressive resume.
- Thank you.
Tell me why you chose to pursue
a career in engineering.
Well, um,
I've always been interested in,
uh, structure, geometry.
How things fit together.
How an object that, uh,
performs a function can...
also be a work of art.
What about the future?
Where do you see yourself in five years?
One suit, black.
That baby boy all
growed up yet?
Oh, he's gonna raise
hell the next few years.
Take after his mama.
Yeah, you know,
it's the same old same up here.
But, uh...
things are getting
pretty tense,
like they're fixin' to, uh, collide.
You know what I mean, Jimmy?
There's a potential,
uh, situation.
I found our access to
the infirmary building,
but I'm gonna need some
time to make it work.
How much time?
Enough for me to find my way up a
20-foot vertical drain pipe without
using a ladder.
I'll probably need to skip PI tomorrow
if I want to get this thing done.
Can't just skip it.
It ain't class.
What if one of the
bulls decide to drop in?
Well, I don't have a choice,
do I?
Once we get through the pipe
below the guards' room,
it will be a whole lot easier.
I can come and go
without using the door,
and with Westmoreland
as a lookout,
we'll have one more
man available for dig.
Westmoreland's gonna
be a problem.
All seven of us can't break
over that wall in 18 minutes.
You said it yourself:
it's impossible.
Listen, man, I'm telling you,
one of us has got to take a hike.
I know.
Mind if I share that with
the rest of the class?
Apparently, College
Boy here did the math.
Figured out that we got
too many clowns in the car.
So, one of us is in here digging,
but his seat ain't guaranteed.
How is this your problem, man?
He doesn't know what
he's talking about.
I'm not gonna dig if
I'm not gonna go.
We need to make a
decision on who gets cut.
Well, I think we can all agree
who that should be. Right?
Oh, pardon me for interrupting.
But, uh...
what's that smell?
It smells a little
like... conspiracy.
We need to get back to work.
Yeah, before you do,
I have an announcement to make.
I've been growing leery of the way
y'all talk, like I'm a lesser man.
So, I bought an
insurance policy.
I called up my guy on the outside,
and I told him about our plan.
And I told him, in all likelihood,
I'll be seeing him next week,
but...
if he don't hear from me five minutes
before the escape, and 20 minutes after,
I told him to call up the warden,
blow the whistle on the whole thing.
So if you all got ideas
about getting rid of me...
I suggest you make other plans.
Son of a bitch has got a
countermove for everything.
Not for this.
Odd men out-- me and you.
What do you mean?
Look who you're
walking with right now.
You should be up there,
calling the shots with
the rest of the suits.
- Yeah. So?
- So?
Scofield is only
here for one reason:
his brother.
And he only needs two things:
the old man's money,
and the mob boss's plane.
He don't need you.
You just happened to be in the
same cell when he got here.
You  and the toilet.
I've done a lot of
work on this thing.
Exactly, and me, too.
Yeah, we're just the damn
laborers on this thing, man.
And the night that Fish
goes into that hole,
you think he wants to carry
all that extra baggage?
'Cause that's all we are.
I don't know about you,
but I'm going.
How  much does he
tell you, anyways?
Or does he keep it
all to himself?
Yeah, he probably tells you,
the less you know, the better, right?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
He tells me everything.
If he tells you everything,
then you don't need him.
Now, we can go by ourselves,
me and you.
Or, you know, you can wait
and see if Scofield really
wants to carry heavy weight.
It's up to you, popi.
Yo, I still waitin'.
What for?
I swiped you that watch, man.
Where's my PI?
That's not gonna happen.
You promised.
I said I'd think about it.
Maybe somewhere down the road.
Yeah. Ain't gonna
hold my breath.
What do you want me to do?
Get somebody! Now!
No, no, no! No, they see a bullet,
they're gonna call the cops.
We don't have a choice, okay?
I'm not gonna let you die.
Find it, find it! Find it!
What?
The bullet--
just find it and dig it out.
- I can't.
- Do it!
Where's Scofield?
There you are.
I just looked for you in your cell.
Couldn't find you anyplace.
I couldn't find your
credit card, either.
You know the one
I'm talking about.
The one your whore wife
trunked in the other day.
She told me all about it.
Maybe whore's too strong.
What do you call a girl who married a
felon to get into the United States?
Why'd she have to come
here for, anyway?
No strip clubs in Whazistan?
- Officer Bellick.
- Captain.
Fine. Do you mind conducting your
inquisitions on your own time, please?
I have a schedule to maintain.
Excuse me, Doctor.
I was just asking Mr.
Scofield about the contraband
he had his stripper wife
trunk in the other day.
But you go ahead.
Your job's more important.
He's had it out for me
since the day I got here.
- Hold still, please.
- Sorry.
I only married her...
so she could get
her green card.
I saw you coming out
of the conjugal room.
That's just business.
You don't have to explain
it to me, Michael.
I know.
But I want to.
D.B.?
Oh,  is that who you is now?
I thought you was just a cowboy.
Take a couple of
steps back, boy.
You know what I
can't understand is,
why somebody like you wants
to get out of here anyway.
How you going to survive, huh?
The world's all different now.
It's scary...
They got computer phones,
boobies made out of silicone.
You wouldn't know what to do.
I don't have to
justify myself to you.
Oh, you're going to have to.
Them old bones just going
to be dragging us down.
Maybe I'll just snap a
few of 'em right now.
Take your best shot.
Hey, break it up down there!
Bow out, cowboy.
I'm not going to warn you no more.
What's up?
Records from the phone in the yard.
James Bagwell. Lives down in Gary.
T-Bag's insurance policy?
Yeah.
My guy's going to lock him up in a
moving van for a couple days until we're
in the clear.
- Moving van?
- Yeah.
Don't worry, he can breathe and all.
We do it all the time.
What about T-Bag?
He's no longer a threat.
Trust me.
You James Bagwell?
Got a delivery for you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You all right?
- Ma'am?
- Yes?
Can I speak with you, please?
Of course.
You stay right here, okay?
Is he going to be okay?
We don't know yet.
He's lost a lot of blood.
I was going to call the police,
but I wanted to speak to you first.
His wound is obviously
the product of a gunshot.
You need to be honest with me.
What was he doing
when he got shot?
He was in the garage,
underneath his car.
He's in surgery right now.
The blood loss has caused his muscle
tissue to suffer from a lack of oxygen.
He's also sustained a fair amount
of damage to his shoulder,
and with a bullet there's always
an increased risk of infection.
So, he's going to
have to be admitted.
Is there anyone you should call?
Any family?
No. It's just me.
All right, well... I'll let you
know as soon as he's in recovery.
Thank you.
Yeah.
- Are you there yet?
- Almost.
You remember, be patient.
Follow his lead.
We want the trifecta today.
Yeah, I'm on it.
It's me.
Yeah. I got some bad news.
Yeah, like what?
The job you ordered went bad.
The guy was a paranoid,
he had a gun...
one thing led to another.
What, he's dead?
Yeah. And, unfortunately...
there was a kid there.
What are you... What are you
talking about? You killed a kid?
It was unintentional.
- It's a kid, man.
- I know, I'm sorry.
SOB used him as a shield.
- A boy or a girl?
- I don't know. Boy.
- How old?
- Four, maybe five.
- Who's here to see me?
- Hell if I know. Some lady.
Baby.
Hi.
You look so beautiful.
I came here cause I have
to tell you something.
What?
I'm pregnant, Fernando.
Pregnant?
With your baby.
I'm going to have your son.
You...  you're going to...
We...
We're going to have a baby?
Oh, yeah, Papi, you hear that?
I'm going to be a dad!
- I'm not finished!
- What, Mami, what?
Okay, Hector...
he asked me to marry him.
What?
- Look, it's crazy, I know.
- Well, tell him no.
Tell him you're having my son.
We're going to be a family.
Fernando... Look,
my mom, she says...
that having a baby is the
hardest job in the whole world.
And it's even harder if
I do this by myself.
But all I know is is
I'm really scared.
I'm really scared
to do this alone.
You're not going to have to.
Well, I haven't
told him no yet.
Wait, wait.
You're not actually considering this.
Oh, baby... I don't know.
I don't know.
Oh, my God, baby, you got to
stop listening to these people.
They're poisoning your brain.
Your hormone things-- they're out of
whack. You're not thinking straight.
This is our child
we're talking about.
I want you to listen to me.
I want you to wait.
I'm going to be out.
Sooner than you think.
You keep on telling me that.
All right, visiting time is up.
Let's go.
Tell me you're going to wait.
Hands off, Sucre!
You're all I got left in the world,
baby. Please.
I love you.
But you'll learn to
love again, right?
Tell me you're going
to tell him no, honey.
I don't know.
I don't know anything any more.
Sucre. Come on.
- The kid's here.
- Perfect.
Follow  him back to the
lawyers and call me back.
Where are you going?
I'll be back in ten minutes.
What do you have to do?
It's complicated.
I can't explain.
But if it works...
you'll see soon enough.
I want to go with you.
I want to see now.
Someone has to stay here.
I need a lookout.
I'm always on lookout.
You're my cellmate.
Who else is going to do it?
I'll be back in
ten minutes, okay?
Okay.
We're all lined up for tomorrow.
Where do you want him?
John?
Tomorrow. Where do you want T-Bag:
in the shop or the shed?
Shh...
I don't care.
You decide.
Thank God. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
She didn't do anything.
She didn't deserve this.
I know.
- Here you go, man.
- Yeah, yeah.
These were seriously
hard to get.
- What you need them for anyway?
- None of your business.
Thank you for
waiting, Theodore.
I don't mean to deny
your time in the yard.
What's this all about?
I, uh...
I'm afraid I have
some terrible news.
You cousin James was shot and
killed in his home yesterday.
His son, James Junior was killed,
as well.
I'm very, very sorry.
What does it mean?
Am I chosen?
Or what?
Often, the Lord appears when you're
in particular need of forgiveness.
Maybe that's what's
happening right now.
John, it's never too late.
If you agree to accept Christ into
your heart and turn from your sin,
he will forgive you and
save you in eternity.
Do you agree?
Revelation chapter three.
Verse 20:
Jesus said, "Behold,
I stand at the door and knock.
If any man hear my
voice and open the door,
I will come into him."
He got to the infirmary
building last night.
Through  the old sewer pipe.
It's the same pipe that runs
under the guards' room.
That's all I know.
That's the little thumb-sucker
that swiped my watch.
Who? Tweener?
Solid gold.
Took it right off my arm.
It was a half hour before
I even noticed it.
Whose was it in
the first place?
I don't care that you stole it.
You can tell me.
Michael Scofield.
What are you looking at?
I'll be right
around the corner.
Westmoreland!
You scared me, boss.
Get back to work.
All right, let's go!
Move it, Scofield.
"As for me, I will call upon God,
and the Lord shall save me.
I cry aloud,
and he'll hear my voice.
He shall hear my voice.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Well, keep an eye on the tier for me,
will you?
When are we getting
out of here exactly?
I need to know the time.
As soon as possible.
"As soon as possible"
is not a specific time.
- You tell Abruzzi the time?
- Yes, because he needs to know.
Why does he need to
know and I don't?
Because he's arranging the plane.
Why the sudden curiosity?
Why would you want to be responsible
for potentially dangerous information?
The less you know, the better.
It's for your own good.
I have to go.
I'll meet you in PI.
Stealing from a guard.
You can get thrown
in the SHU for that,
maybe even add a few
years to your bid.
I don't know...
Don't deny it.
I already know it's true.
Lucky for you,
I got pull some around here.
I can make this sort of thing go away,
like it never even happened.
Mmm.
That's good.
Now...
I'm sure you've
heard the word "rat."
I don't like it.
"Snitch," neither.
Those sort of words aren't
appropriate for what I need from you.
What I need is a
little information.
Like when you're hanging
out with Scofield...
...just come back and
tell me what he said.
I got an extra burger.
But, man, I'm full.
What do you say, kiddo?
You want a cheeseburger...
or do you want to
go to the SHU?
That's my boy.
Hey, honey,
what are you doing here?
I thought you left.
What's wrong?
I, um... I've been thinking.
I think we need
to make a change.
What are you talking about?
Remember when we first got married,
and we thought about moving out west?
Yeah, we were 22.
Well, maybe we should give it a shot.
It's not too late.
I don't understand.
What brought this on?
It's just work.
I'm tired of being on the road
and working for somebody else,
while you sit at home all alone,
night after night.
I want our lives
to be about us.
I do, too, but there's so much to think
about, like the kids and the house.
We got to go.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
Oh.
The crowd has
thinned out in here.
How you doing, Sucre?
Almost got it. Switch me out.
You're up, then Westmoreland.
We got to get through.
Michael's gonna be coming back this way.
- Hello?
- Veronica Donovan?
Who is this?
It, it doesn't matter who I am.
Don't hang up.
I have information that
you may be interested in--
information that will lead to the
exoneration of Lincoln Burrows.
What? What is it?
I can't tell you that now.
Meet me tonight at the Highland
Cafe on Kennedy Avenue.
This isn't a trap. I will tell
you everything you need to know.
Highland Cafe, 8:00 p.m.
All right, that's enough.
- Leave us alone.
- You sure?
Get out of here.
You don't have to do this.
You brought it on yourself.
I'm just an emissary for all the
pain and suffering you caused,
all the families you ruined,
all the kids.
What about Jimmy?
He had nothing to do with this.
You didn't need to kill him.
And what about
his beautiful son?
He had his whole life
in front of him.
You didn't need to kill
a beautiful child.
After all I've done,
maybe I do deserve to die, maybe I do.
But you are no better than me.
But I can be, if I want.
God has given me the
chance to choose.
Maybe I should give
you a chance as well.
Yes, anything,
anything, please.
Please.
Back out.
Of the escape?
Or die.
I would, I...
I wouldn't make it
out there, anyway--
not with my proclivities.
I want you to give
me your word.
You hear me?
I want you to give me your word!
Yeah, you got it, John.
You got it. Come on, you got it.
- Please.
- Swear.
I'm out, I swear!
I swear to God!
I'm out, okay, I sw...
All right. All right!
I have forgiven you.
You just have to pray that the Lord
Jesus Christ will do the same.
Hey, John, you know,
actually, about Jesus...
Say hi to Him for me, will you?
I'm through.
- Keep it up.
- Come on, stomp it.
Bulls.
You got to stall them.
We're not ready.
Hey, boss.
What you doing out here, Linc?
Taking a break.
Got to check the
status in there.
It's all good.
Then you won't mind
me checking it out.
Hey.
What the hell's
your problem, con?
Hey, hey!
Step off or you're going to the SHU!
Get off him!
Thanks.
Well...
we leave tonight.
Where's my brother?
Michael, we got a big problem.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net