Previously on Prison Break...
How does a simple fisherman
know so much about the Company?
You gonna do this or not?
Yes,but once we're out,
I consider you collateral.
Lincoln causes as many
problems as he solves.
He needs to get way,and I
think you can assist him.
I stay one step ahead,and
you get 50 grand.
What happened?
She came up to me just like you said
and offered me a bunch of
cash to talk behind your back.
- So we stick to the plan,right?
- Yeah.
Cool.
I found a passport.
Who's Gary Miller?
I've been working on a
way for us to be together.
James,how-how can I believe you?
How can I believe anything anymore?
We got a way out of this?
We need some kind of
support brace for the tunnel.
Or what?
Or the whole thing
collapses,and we're buried alive.
No more excuses.
Papa's dead because of this Yankee.
I'll kill him myself if i have to, right.
He survived the box.
So what?
The guards went after Scofield.
Scofield won.
He's a folk hero now.
Look,I want Scofield
dead as much as you,
but not at the cost of an uprising.
Mail call.
Who's that?
That's my son.
Bagwell gave the okay.
The coast is clear.
We gotta go.
I didn't think I'd see you again.
Once someone goes into the box,its...
it was a misunderstanding.
They wanted to talk to you
about the helicopters,right?
What helicopters?
you really trying to escape?
I don't know what you're
talking about,and neither do you.
Just so you know,
Bagwell's coming with us.
You were gone.
He had something we needed.
I didn't have a choice.
Fine.
So what's the new plan?
- Did you tell him?
- Yeah.
I am coming with you.
Okay by me.
Everyone hear that?
You hear that,lawman?
But you're staying up here.
Maybe I didn't enunciate myself.
The work downstairs
requires two hands.
Hey.
We need somebody to stay
outside in case Sammy returns.
I thought we couldn't
dig through this stuff.
The bracing's gonna be tricky.
Unless the tunnel gets
the proper support,
it's all going to
come down on our heads.
We should have the
materials for the braces,
but we'll need a a saw
to cut them to size.
And a hammer.
Can you help us out?
Yeah. I can do that.
Two days.
And if not?
Two days
Guillermo should have
everything we need.
You know where he is,right?
I think it's,uh...
it's down this corridor on the left.
Halfway down.
Cell 40.
Down the corridor on the left.
Okeydoke.
Are you lost already,Teodoro?
No.
But you are.
This is my room now.
You're done in here.
If you had gone after Scofield today,
all would have been forgiven.
This is suicide.
Shut up,old man!
I'll take my chances.
Yeah. You think you can run Sona?
You couldn't even run shipments
from one dock to the other,
but I still keep you by my side.
I'll let you walk out of here
out of respect for what you were.
Come on!
Get the hell out of here!
All of you ready to do this?
Until Lechero gets back,
we should start
looking for pieces about
4 feet in length.
I'm running things now!
Anyone got a problem with that?
Come get it!
Good.
First order of business,
A case of rum to the man who
brings me Michael Scofield!
Don't worry
We'll be there with all the cash
Okay? Gracias.
Osberto.
That's who you want to talk to.
This guy on
the up-and-up?
The guy I was running things
into Sona for arranged this,
so it's as up as it's gonna
get for this kind of deal.
So,yes.
Osberto doesn't speak English, though,
so how do you want to work it?
I need to meet with Susan.
I'll take Sofia.
She can translate for me.
Don't worry about it.
So when I meet with Susan,
what do you want me to tell her?
Tell her whatever you
think she wants to hear.
Just buy us enough time
to do our thing,all right?
Home stretch,papi.
Listen,man. I want to
thank you for everything.
Oh,Linc,please.
When we get home,I got your back¡
Whatever you need,
whatever you want.
That won't be necessary.
When I'm back home,I'm a saint.
I'm not even jaywalking.
Osberto. Don't forget.
Osberto.
Scofield steps outside
that tunnel,he's a dead man.
Far as I can tell,we have two options.
We can invite Sammy on the escape...
he can go to hell.
Which brings us to option number two.
You wouldn't last a
second in there with sammy.
Would you?
Then I guess we'll
just have to outsource.
I felt sorry for the guy,
but you don't chicken-foot an Ex-Delta
force and expect to make it out alive.
You're delta force?
Like chuck norris?
Norris? He wouldn't have
made it through boot camp.
Excuse me...
I see you're making friends.
Hey,once you get the hang of
it,this place ain't so rough.
Yeah.
Too bad.
Too bad what?
You were right.
We got a little plan going on.
But,you know,if you're
putting down roots...
no,no.
You were saying...
We're supposed to be
out of here in 48 hours.
Not through Scofield.
You heard the town cried.
College boy's life is
barely worth a case of booze.
Hence our current conversation.
I know how you got
your cherry yesterday,
Daubing your wraps in acetone,
smothering the guy until he
passed out from the fumes.
You do the same thing
to Sammy,and you're in.
Chicken-foot Sammy?
Chicken-foot Sammy.
It's all riding on you,champ.
Thank you.
This shouldn't take long.
What are you getting?
Supplies.
For?
I don't want to get
caught flat-footed again.
You know what that means?
No.
Well,these people
obviously have a plan.
We're gonna need one,too.
Does that plan include
screwing over James?
Is it James or Gary Miller?
Whatever his name is,
there's a part of me that
doesn't want to believe
he works for them...
'cause he's the man I loved,
the man who went to prison for me,
the man who was going to take
me to my first trip to Paris.
I haven't turned my
back to that man.
Do I have your word that
he's gonna be all right?
Yeah.
Now get in.
Do I have your word?!
Yeah,you got my word.
Now get in.
You know I just found out,
That "Sucre" means "Sugar. "
Yeah.
So every time I say your name,
I'm calling you "Sugar. "
Basically.
I like that.
Look,I don't have a
lot of information.
Which,I guess,that's
good news for you,right?
You care to elaborate?
Lincoln isn't cooking anything up.
He's still planning on
exchanging Whistler for LJ.
He hasn't been talking
about running any games.
And did he become an
eagle scout last night,too?
Lady,he got the message.
He knows he doesn't have a
choice,he has to play it straight.
Look,I could have come up here and
made something up
just to get paid,but...
I'm not trying to get
on your bad side either.
You know what?
I believe you.
So,I'll call you if anything comes up.
Whoa,whoa! What am I,
a toothless crack whore?
Sit down.
I keep my promises.
People I work for,they don't
like to deal in greenbacks;
it's just too bulky.
Cashier's check payable to cash.
Same thing.
Half now and half
when you're done.
Keep your ears open,Sugar.
Alex,come on!
Hold it steady!
I am! I am!
I'm gonna need a little help here!
I got it.
I said I got it.
That little piece of metal's
gonna hold all this weight?
All right,let go,let go.
So,how many more are we gonna
need before we get to the top?
20 maybe.
That gets us to no-man's land.
Then what?
Helicopter'd be nice.
Hey,I was supposed to kill you.
Oh,so you're not a fisherman?
They threatened to
come after my family if
I didn't kill you and
jump on that helicopter,
but I didn't.
I'm so grateful.
So what happened to your family?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll find out if
we ever get out of here.
Well,it's a crazy world,isn't it?
We all agree on that.
And we have a lot of work to do.
Where the hell is Lechero?
Is everything set?
Huh?
Yeah,no problemo.
Excuse me,sir.
Do we come to you if we
need the chicken foot?
Tiger pants.
Who you got a beef with?
I don't know his name.
Some Caribbean guy.
Stole my wallet a while back.
Better think long and hard
before you say another word,eh?
He's got this fruity little
mustache and this ugly-ass vest.
Please,I'm beggin' ya.
in the ring.
15 minutes.
I never thought I'd say this,
but I envy you,Brad.
I've wanted to shank that little
calypso kid ever since I first met him.
I'm not a violent guy by nature,
but if a man makes me walk around
in my grunts for two days...
yeah,that's great! Just don't
take too long to finish him off, ok
The sooner he's dead,the
sooner we can get on the escape.
No games. I'm in.
You're in.
No,no,no.
What's wrong?
We got to call off the fight.
No,that's an impossibility.
No,no,no,you don't understand!
There's got to be more
Acetone around here.
No,that's it!
I can't go against
Sammy straight up!
I'm a dead man!
If you don't kill him,
we are all dead.
This isn't the best neighborhood.
I've been in a lot worse.
Just stick close.
Osberto?
Si.
You want to do this?
¿Tiene el dinero?
Yeah,yeah,I got it.
¿Donde esta?
"Where is the money?"
I want to see the product.
"Money first. "
Show me the stuff.
El dinero!
Lincoln,please,
let's get out of here.
Tell him to stop wasting my time.
No.
Tell him.
Oh,my god!
Big?
It's grande?
Si.
Ask him how do i
trigger it by remote.
Boom.
"Dial one-one,send. "
One-one,send?
yeah
Adios.
Buena suerte.
Why didn't you tell me
you were gonna buy a bomb?
You never would
have come otherwise
We need that saw.
You know,uh,I am a fisherman.
I am.
I'm just maybe a little bit
more connected than I've let on.
I think this is gonna work.
Yeah.
You know,I run
charters,just like I said...
I have for years.
Then one day,that
brunette,Gretchen well,
she asked me if I wanted to be
exclusive to her corporation,right?
And,uh,well,with the
money she was offering,
I had a pretty good idea she
wasn't just trawling for salmon.
So you two have history.
Yeah. And she's been
an absolute nightmare
in my life ever since that first job.
Alex,I need a wedge.
Wedge.
Look,I took 'em where
they wanted me to take 'em.
I have to figure out these coordinates
and I have to take them back there.
Quit embarrassing yourself.
What?
We're not two chicks at a
bar you're trying to pick up.
- Unless you need to hear this?
- No.
All right,good.
You work for the Company.
And when you break out of here,
you're gonna do whatever the
Company asks you to do,period.
Well,they're using me just
like they're using you.
Good,I'm glad you shared that with me.
So why don't we go back to work?
How's that sound?
Let those idiots chicken foot
themselves all they want,huh?
But if one of them
tries to use it on us...
you don't have to fight that guy.
It's my farewell tour.
the rest of those pieces are no good.
We're going to need
those tools,Michael.
I guess we'll just have to wait.
That book of yours- it's just a
bunch of coordinates in there,right?
Among other things.
So you wouldn't mind.
It's just a bunch
of,uh,numbers and dates.
"Gate. "
Gate netting company.
That's where I rent my trammels.
"Stampede. "
That's my buddy's cape islander.
And this is important to us how?
It's important because I'm being
accused of being someone I'm not.
And I don't want Scofield ditching
me once it's time to leave...
he's not ditching anybody.
If he could have gotten rid of
anybody,he would have gotten rid of me.
And if he tries to leave
the city he knows that
we're gonna turn him in
before he gets out of the city.
I'm going upstairs to find
Lechero and his equipment.
I'm with Alex.
Do you mind?
Sounds like someone's up there.
If Lechero gets stranded up
there,we're not getting out of here.
So when you think it's safe,or it feels
like it's safe,we got
to go,we got to go up.
we've been talking about
chicken footing Sammy for months.
No one had the courage.
Do you have any paint thinner?
Paint thinner?
Shoe polish,lighter fluid,glue?
There you are,champ.
It's time.
Stomp his face,Brad!
You know,this has all been
one big misunderstanding.
I wasn't talking about Sammy.
It was... that's him.
That's the guy I was talking about.
Yeah,I don't see no "fruity moustache,"
and where's his "ugly-ass vest," Brad?
Don't worry,you stand a real
chance of winning this one.
You cannot just hide out all day.
What else can I do,huh?
I've ruled these men
for a year with blood.
You don't think those men want to take
the head of the man who wore the crown?
Be that as it may,Bellick is
about to lose his head to Sammy.
You may not want to hear
this,but once that happens,
we are both very much
aware that Scofield is gonna
stop getting curious about
where the hell you are.
He's going to come crawling out of
his hole and right into Sammy's arms,
and then he and our
escape are gone forever.
Wait.
We get the tools and
we come straight back.
Come on
You guys want to watch the fight?
You know,chill out.
I'll get you a beer.
You like that?
Stop it!
It's Scofield!
Scofield's in there.
It's locked.
Open the door.
I don't have the combination.
I said... open it now.
We can't. We can't.
Open it now.
I don't have the combination.
Hey,I've got your man out here.
If you don't open the door,
he's the one who's
going to pay the price.
I need him alive!
You saw those guys.
What do you think they've got planned?
All of you is trying my patience.
What do you suggest,Alex?
Let's be ready for them.
Time's up.
You want another one?
Then you better be persuasive.
Michael.
Don't open the door!
He's got a gu...
Are you going to tell
me what it's for?
No.
Because you think I might tell James?
Because you don't need to know.
It's going to be all right.
- How'd it go?
- Good.
I told her what she wanted to
hear,just like you told me.
That it?
Yeah.
Cool.
Listen,I want you to call her up,
tell her you've got some information.
Make sure she picks you up,and
get in the car,all right?
Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Why?
She looks upset.
I'll call you later.
Got something down
here we can use,Michael.
If they come through that door...
you hit 'em right here.
Go ahead,take it.
Go ahead.
It'll puncture the heart.
you were hiding Scofield in your room?
Look at you- the power
make you mad already.
Come along, Norman.
It's cool.
What is so urgent?
Lincoln bought a gun.
I... I asked him what he planned on
doing with it,but he wouldn't answer.
So I just... I just thought
you might want to know.
If anything changes,I'll
get back to you,okay?
You know,the other day
when you and Lincoln
had your little spat
in the lobby and you
all distraught and jilted- went
across the street to the bar,
a cynic might think that was staged.
I'm a cynic,Sugar.
You're high,Sugar.
If it's any comfort,
you guys almost pulled it off.
The Puerto Rican and the gorilla- you
really had me scrambling there for a minute.
Hey,if you don't want my
help,fine,I'm out,okay?
It's a little thing called a tracing
number- on the check I gave you.
Apparently your extensive expertise
in banking failed you that day.
You promptly wired all 25k to
Maricruz Delgado in Chicago at 123
"Please don't hurt me" Lane.
- I swear to god,if
something happens to her...
- if what?!
What,jackass?!
You're going to go back there and
you're going to get me
some real information,
or Maricruz and her head
are going to part ways.
Get out of my car.
Now.
Hey,Blanco.
I got your good buddy Lechero here.
Why don't you give it the secret
knock so he know's you,huh?
The combination.
What makes you think
I have the combination?
Just do what he says.
How many times you gonna
pull that little thing out?
As many times as
I feel necessary.
What,you think it
make you look strong?
All it does is magnify your weakness.
Funny,I'm feeling pretty
secure right about now.
Now,the combination,old man.
We're not asking again.
Sammy!
I'm opening the door.
Michael,do not open the...
Drop 'em!
Drop them,I said!
Now move!
You're escaping with him?
I was gonna tell you
all about this,bredda.
It just never came up,eh?
Take it. It's yours.
The tunnel,the escape
plan,everything.
We can go together.
I'm taking everything you got.
But you ain't going nowhere.
How you finishing up this hole?
Promise me you'll
take Whistler with you.
You making demands on me? Huh?
I understand...
why you're going to kill me,
but he's done nothing wrong.
I'll tell you everything you need
to know,just take him with you.
You need him.
He's the only one who
figured this one out.
Don't you worry,I'll
take care of your friend.
All right.
First,you need to keep building
braces to support the tunnel as you go.
How you do that?
Whistler can show you how.
Look like you just make some wood
squares from these boxes here.
Like I said,
Whistler can show you.
How much further to the surface?
Not far.
Can't be more than ten feet.
Impressive,Blanco.
Too bad you won't
be around to enjoy it.
How long is this going to set us back?
What's gonna set us back
is if the tower guards are
looking at a giant sinkhole
out in no man's land.
Michael?
- We're good.
- Yeah.
We're good.
Back in business.
I'm in.
For what,getting your ass kicked?
I'm in or I shout it from the rooftops.
You're in,champ.
Okay,you need to stay here.
I got to get something,all right?
Don't move.
can you get home from here?
Yeah,I'm two blocks away.
If he doesn't take you,I will.
Here. Use this.
- Thanks.
- Right there.
You know,for all the times you
wanted me to prove I was a fisherman,
I should have been asking
if you were a real engineer.
That could've been one
of us buried down there.
I'll do better next time.
I'm gonna go back down and try
to salvage some of those braces.
Yeah,I'll go with you.
Never gets any easier.
Scofield,visita.
Scofield, you have a visitor.
All the side jobs I do
at Sona for 3 years.
I save all of my money.
It's $173.
If you're really leaving,
it's yours.
Take me with you.
Please?
I don't want to be here anymore.
You don't want any part of this.
You got a plan or are
we back to square one?
I have a plan.
Good,'cause I got something
cooking on the outside.
I ain't walking into a buzzsaw again.
How you dealing with
the animals in here?
Actually,it's starting
to feel like home.
Whistler still pretending
he's a fisherman and all this?
Why?
Sofia found a passport in
one of the apartments he kept.
Name's Gary Miller.
I'm shocked.
Guy's a fraud,Michael.
As far as I know,there
ain't fish in Scottsdale.
Well,if he's not a fisherman...
What is he?
www.tvsubtitles.net