Previously on Prison Break...
The strikes are getting closer.
We got a day, maybe two, tops,
- to get out of this hole.
- Desperate times, desperate measures.
- Michael's reaching out to us.
- We got to get help. A woman named Sheba.
Your brother speaks in riddles, does he?
ISIL. We're gonna get stopped.
Why don't we forget
each other ever existed.
Beauty's not so easily forgotten.
Friends in high places, Bagwell.
I can equip you with a
fully articulate prosthetic.
- Who's behind this?
- Nobody.
- This is Kaniel Outis.
- Okay, but you and I both know
- who Michael Scofield was.
- We've awoken something,
something people are trying
to hide about Michael.
Jacob?
That's game theory. You meet people.
You bring them into your life
until the moment
you need to manipulate the relationship
to your advantage.
You agreed to help him... how?
If I could arrange a blackout.
He knew someone who could get him out.
Someone found my father.
It means the escape is on.
ISIL forces are also bent
on freeing their leader Abu Ramal,
known for his extreme
views and practices.
_
He says Bubble Gum Man sent him.
Someone in the prison he hasn't met,
but gives him gum in
exchange for errands.
He says he's frightened.
Tell him it's all right.
Ask him if he does Tic Tacs.
He can have the whole lot
if he keeps the messages coming.
Thank you, Tic Tac Man.
Tic Tac, Tic Tac, Tic Tacs.
It's a passage from the Suras.
"And Yusef said to the prisoner:
'Remember me in the
presence of your lord.'
"But Satan made him forget,
and Yusef stayed in prison
for several years."
The calligraphy is unusual,
the spacing, the way it's shaped,
like, like spokes on a wheel.
Like the center of Sana'a.
You think his brother sent us a map?
There's a red dot
dotting the "I",
and whatever this is here.
He's trying to give us a location.
A location for what?
The only thing I can think of
is where we're supposed to meet him
when the escape goes down tonight.
Your brother is your business now.
I have to get my family
on a flight tonight
- before the airport shuts down.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up.
We need tickets, too, three of them.
One for me, one for Michael, one for C.
If I'm getting anybody any
tickets it's these kids,
not your mercenary brother.
And how are you going to
do that without any money?
You're holding these kids' freedom
over my head, is that it?
Sheba, you get me those plane tickets,
and I'll pay for every
single one of these kids
to get out of this country.
Something tells me that's
what you want to do anyhow.
Careful.
You're accusing me of having a heart.
Out of my way. Get out of my way.
Hmm? Huh? What, you want to go?
Hey.
Keep it together.
You got to have it together
to keep it together.
One of those hits us now,
- after all this time, I swear to God...
- Nine hours.
Nine hours till we get
out, you understand?
It's 1:00 a.m.
We get through today
and we're on the bricks.
And then what?
It was four years ago.
All of our plans, the
passports, the shop,
everything is probably
under rubble by now.
I got someone on it.
What, the kid you throw planes to?
No.
I'm talking about the only
person I trust in the world
as much as I trust you.
So, this is it, the spot on the map.
The owner says he sold the auto shop
to an American four years ago
and hasn't seen him since.
You know that American
was Michael, right?
Question is what was
he using this place for.
Planning his escape.
It looks like his original exfil point
was at the northern border.
Won't be doing that now.
It's ISIL territory.
Mock-ups, passport photos,
disguises.
But it looks like he just wasn't
planning on getting himself out.
He was getting Abu Ramal out.
This guy's the enemy
of everything that's civilized, Linc.
That brings me to my real question.
Who in the hell are we breaking out?
Is it Michael Scofield
or Kaniel Outis?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
What the hell's going on?
Ramal's men are gonna
institute Sharia law.
And that son of a bitch
himself is gonna enjoy the show.
We just have to keep our
heads down and get through this
- so we can get out tonight.
- _
_
No. No, don't let them take me!
No!
_
- Sorry.
- No!
_
Ramal!
Get back. Just let him go.
What are you doing?
- Stay out of this.
- No.
The escape is tonight.
If you want to get out, you
need me and you need him.
Get to the point.
Let him go, Ramal.
Then I'll do it.
Do not touch him.
Get back, dog!
There will be no killing in
this prison... Understand?
He's tried to contact her before.
Only difference is he
succeeded this time.
It's smart... going through the boy.
Ask a question?
Why are we pulling our
punches with this woman?
I got sent to her house
a couple of days ago,
started spilling blood, but
I'm just supposed to stop
before I start spilling hers.
How's that work?
You'll get used to Poseidon's game.
It's all chess.
It's a performance.
A performance designed to
make Outis reach out to her.
Now all we got to do is listen in,
find out what his plans are.
And she doesn't know it.
She's the one that's
going to lead us to him.
They said I can go in the morning.
Your femoral artery was severed.
That's not something you usually
just get up and walk away from.
Hey, they gave me the okay.
They're the doctors
on this one, not you.
And I'm going full mental
in here, so I'm gonna go.
Okay. How about this?
When you are discharged,
why don't we go up to
your parents' lake house?
I'll just pick you up
with Mike and we'll go.
Mmm.
You don't want to be
in the house, do you?
Somebody comes into your house
and shoots up your husband
and they're still out there.
No.
What?
No, it's just something
you do with your nose
when you're determined.
- With my nose?
- It's subtle.
- I mean, it's really subtle.
- Better be.
The face is amazing.
I mean,
the tiniest detail,
less than a millimeter,
differentiates everything.
An emotion on one person can be...
so troubled
and on another...
so beautiful.
You're not trying to get
somewhere, are you, Mr. Ness?
Yes, actually,
I am.
Hello there.
I come as a compatriot, Sara.
Get out of my way or I'll scream.
Last thing I want.
For your information,
I know about Kaniel Outis.
Tell me what you know.
The day I hit the bricks from Fox River,
someone named Outis,
out of the goodness of their soul,
unsolicited, pays for
this modern prosthesis.
What's that?
A million bucks? Why would anyone
come out of a pocket
for a wretch like me,
a penny, much less a million bucks?
Yeah, if you're coming to me
for answers, I don't have any.
Oh, I went looking
for answers, Doc Sara.
I looked up Outis on the Interwebs.
Whose face comes up but
your dead ex-husband's,
looking very much alive.
Lazarus arisen from the dead.
He's drawing us into
something, isn't he?
He wants something, doesn't he?
Come near me or my family
again, I will kill you.
Better to have me on your side, Sara.
We can figure this out together.
We have all heard the war
outside.
But even if it is just
within these walls,
the law of the land is still in place.
The law of God supersedes
the law of this corrupt land.
We will not be reduced to animals.
Amazing you still trust him.
He will use you for the
escape and he will leave you.
No one's escaping.
Who are you?
A man who knows your friend there
more than anyone in this prison.
I was in solitary with him
- for years.
- Yeah, so was I.
But not in the cell across from him.
He told me about the escape.
- We have to work together.
- No.
Tried to convince me to go with him,
just the two of us.
But I told him no.
I would not leave my brother.
That is the Army in me,
the Christian in me.
He is an opportunist.
He will use whoever he needs.
He has told you something
about the escape. I know he has.
You were in the cell with him. You.
You tell me, so I can help you,
before he uses you to get that devil out
and we are all left here to die.
We need passports, Omar.
You think you can help us?
Hold on. We're gonna trust this guy?
He's the one who stole my
passport in the first place.
It was honest bargaining, friend.
I took nothing. Besides,
your passport is long gone,
somewhere far overseas by now, I bet.
If you want, um, I can have
the forgers make you another.
My own fake passport coming from you?
You have another option?
Quick. I'm leaving the city.
Nowhere is safe anymore.
I need two passports. One for me,
one for my brother, Michael Scofield.
$1,000 U.S. each, deposit.
$1,000 U.S. when you pick them up.
C?
You screw with me and I'll kill you.
I screw you,
I won't be around for you to kill me.
11:00 tonight, Sheba.
Passports will be ready.
That means we're gonna have to split up.
You two get the passports,
and I'll go with our friend
here to the power plant
and kill the lights.
And we get Michael out.
A U.S. State Department
spokesperson said
the capital of Yemen
grows ever closer to collapse
and it's only a matter of time
until Sana'a's fallen to
the hands of ISIL radicals,
with the total collapse
coming as soon as tomorrow.
Hey.
Looking for a smartphone?
Yeah. You, um...
you fix phones, too, right?
Yeah.
I think somebody hacked my cell.
Whoa.
Is there any chance you
can help me figure out who?
_
That Christian guy said
you told him you'd just
take him. No one else.
He's a liar. You don't want anything
- to do with him.
- I don't know. Christian, Army.
- Seems pretty up front to me.
- Did he happen to tell you
about some of the arrests
he and his brother made
- at their security checkpoint?
- No, focused on you.
They had a specialty: women.
Body parts strewn around Yemen.
That's why they're here.
Wearing a cross is one thing.
- Living by it is another.
- All right, okay, sure.
Just promise me I can trust you,
that we're still doing this tonight.
All these years
we've been working together,
you've been able to
trust me the whole time.
Last four years in the
hole, sitting in the dark,
I couldn't even hear
a voice. I don't know.
Maybe something's changed or...
Nothing's changed.
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,
but then he abandoned us.
Ramal is Poseidon's guy,
- not ours. He's an animal.
- I suggest
you watch your mouth. Some
of these guys speak English.
Why are we still getting him out?
We're telling him we're getting
him out. There's a difference.
We got to act like we're
on his side until the moment we're not.
But what if you're acting
like you're on my side
till the moment you're not?
You are getting paranoid.
Yeah, well, four years in the
box is gonna do that to you.
I'm not leaving you behind.
- You're my whip hand.
- I don't know that.
How do I know I'm your whip hand?
- You'll understand later.
- I want to understand now.
Okay?
Get your hands off me.
Answers, now. I'm serious.
Okay.
I said don't touch me!
Okay. Mm.
Mm. Okay, that's fair.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You want the hole again, huh?
No, we're good.
No.
We're good.
We're far from good.
By tomorrow, we won't
have to worry about him.
Keep your head down.
Don't make eye contact with anybody.
A lot of ISIL sympathizers everywhere.
We get our passports, we're out of here.
Understand?
Planning on leaving?
Right when the glorious
revolution is beginning.
I'm not here for political
discussion, just passports.
Money first.
Passports first.
They're empty.
Sheba!
I'm sorry I hit you.
- I can explain.
- Can you explain why
you were going to let that man kill me?
I wouldn't have let him kill you.
You sure seem to be chums
with the head of ISIL, friend.
Didn't know you participated
in these conversations, Ja.
Only when they're interesting.
And they're usually not.
There are people in my government,
believe it or not, who want that man out
for their own convoluted
foreign policy over here.
That's the job Whip and
I were sent here to do.
But for some reason,
we were betrayed.
Which means we're
getting out without Ramal.
And every one of you
is crucial to that plan.
How?
Your whole escape's already wired.
Lights out, you're over the wall.
What do you need a Korean junkie
- like me for?
- Korean genius, you mean.
Getting over that
wall is just the start.
Once that happens,
there are things only you can do.
Back on point: you hit me.
You wanted proof that I
sided with you and not Ramal.
- And splitting my lip does that how?
- Son of a bitch
Kaniel Outis keeps playing, doesn't he?
Where is my watch?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hmm. You don't?
I'm going to break you in half
when I find that watch, you know?
Toss the cell.
It's not here.
Order a lockdown of the whole prison.
No one gets out of their cells
until that watch is found!
_
I told you, Ramal's not
going anywhere. Only we are.
We're gonna be locked in our
box just like the rest of them,
only our box has a way out.
And in two hours when
those lights go black,
we're gonna disappear from
this place like ghosts.
Yeah, all right.
Sheba!
Who are these men you work with?
They're beneath you.
You're beneath me.
It pains me to hurt you,
but a good woman is a humble woman.
Remember that.
Who are these men?
Doesn't matter.
They're leaving.
I am not the bad guy here.
You and I have a history.
How I doted
on you in grade school,
how I waited and I waited.
You did not wait.
You tried to rape me!
Please.
Please. Please untie me...
so I can take your other eye.
Afternoon.
I'm looking for a cell phone
that a woman stole from me.
She looks like this?
No, can't help you.
Can't... or won't?
Sorry. Store policy, that's all.
Hey, what are you doing?
- Just...
- Ow!
- Oh!
- Let's go again.
Have you seen her?
Yes. Yes!
She was here, like, ten minutes ago.
Said her phone was hacked
and wanted to know who did it.
And now she knows, doesn't she?
She baited us.
Dead end.
Any chance Poseidon'll just
- let us kill her?
- It might come to that.
We get out, where are you going?
Back to my couch.
My couch in Seoul.
Where the walls are mine,
the floors are mine,
no one can get to me.
The world stays outside
like it's supposed to.
Calgary.
Canada?
I'm going to be a ski jumper.
You've never seen snow, have you?
That's the point.
Everything in my life
till now in this country...
The heat, the hate, the
skies that never snow.
You talk about the world.
I want to be on the other side of it.
_
Hey, Dad. Hey, Mom.
Hi, son. Yeah, Sara,
- let me, uh...
- Thanks, sir.
Oh, give me one sec. Sorry.
Hello?
Hi. This is Brian at
Jep's. I got this number
when I activated your new phone.
You never came back.
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm going to.
Well, okay, I just want
to let you know that
I figured out who was
hacking your phone.
Who?
You... hacked your own phone.
What are you talking about?
Your thumbprint is your
password, right? Well,
whoever hacked your phone
used your thumbprint, so,
unless you're missing
a thumb, that's you.
I don't know what you're messed up in,
but I'd watch your back...
When you were in the hospital,
the woman who attacked us
came back with her partner.
What?
They tracked me down
using my cell phone,
so I brought it to Jep's
to try and figure out
- who they were working for.
- Whoa, wait. Sara, this has police
- written all over it.
- Police haven't been able to do a thing.
So, what? You went to Jep's Electronics
in some hackneyed attempt
at counter-espionage?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just...
I get you don't know where to turn,
but I got a stake in this, too.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay? This is my wife, my son.
You want to get back at these guys?
The university. I mean,
it has real resources,
their computer sciences department.
The phone's done. It's
gonna stay at Jep's.
So that's your plan... just
bury your head in the sand?
No.
No, I've learned over the years
that's exactly what
you don't do. Thank you.
Which one's this?
The one you accosted in a bathroom.
Oh, that wasn't accostment, honey.
I've learned some things
about who it is we're
apparently both looking for?
But I need to know that you're
willing to go the distance.
I'm made of the distance, honeysuckle.
I am the distance.
Good. Because you're
gonna have a conversation
with Paul Kellerman for me.
Bull. Kellerman's behind this?
And you are gonna get
every shred of information
you can about what's really going on.
15 minutes.
I'm soiling myself
here, just so you know.
Look, I'm just gonna
say one thing, okay?
You're like a brother to me,
like an older brother.
- I'm not much of a brother.
- Sure.
Point is that I had zero,
nobody, till you recruited me.
When you pulled me out of that prison
in the Ozarks, you had integrity.
I know we were doing CIA work, sure,
you know, pulling their people out, but
it was about you and me,
and having each other's back.
And it didn't matter if you
were Ramon Cadena when we did
the Colombian break,
or, you know Asaf...
What was his name?
Whatever. The one in Egypt.
You were still you.
And it's the same with this one.
You know, we trump
you up as Kaniel Outis,
big international terrorist.
It's just a name,
it's just a rap sheet, it's
a way to get you locked up.
Right?
I guess what I'm asking you is did...
did something happen to you
while you were in solitary?
Did you become Kaniel Outis
in there in your head?
Do you now want Ramal out after all?
I already told you Ramal
is out of the picture.
Yeah, you said that,
but one small thing...
We go up through that hole,
and then we skirt above the block.
Goes right above
Ramal's cell, doesn't it?
Knock out a couple tiles,
he joins the escape, doesn't he?
What did you whisper to him
in that moment after the fight?
You whispered something, what was it?
Nine minutes.
How do you know?
He told me at dinner.
He said he would come for us.
It's supposed to be only me,
but you will all be coming.
Open block five.
Everyone out.
Shakedown.
Got it.
Found it, Mustapha. It was
in the emir's coat here.
You trusted the liar, didn't you?
Now, we just pray they
get the lights out.
We got to hurry, man.
We got less than ten minutes
to kill the power.
Don't worry.
With luck, both your friend and my son
will be free within the hour.
Okay, breakers are down.
Now, we just need to
pull the redundancies.
They're down the hall.
I'll stay here and
deal with security. Go.
Okay.
Come on, where are you?
Ah.
Oh, come on.
Oh, when in doubt, go old school.
Let's go.
Get the generators up.
Get these inmates back inside!
Now!
Let's go, let's go!
The weapons, get their weapons.
They are trying to escape without us.
Get to their cell.
Block six. Come on!
You heard them, brother.
- Block six.
- Yes.
Ja, give me your phone.
Come on.
Mount flashlights.
Secure every room.
Shoot only if you have to.
And if you do, shoot to kill.
This way.
A shortcut to block
six, brother, come on!
Get off me, you sick bastard!
It's easier if you don't struggle.
This is how you treat me?
You're going to die now, dog.
Sheba, Sheba, it's me, it's me.
Are you okay?
Linc, talk to me.
Get to the rendezvous, the auto shop.
We ain't gonna make it.
Sheba's busted up real bad.
- What happened?
- Just get to the rendezvous.
We got to be there for Michael, damn it!
Damn. Lockdown.
Extra guards on the roof.
Question is whether they move on.
Quickly! Hurry, hurry!
It's here, this one!
We got problems.
- Guys are trying to get into the cell.
- Problem.
- What's wrong?
- People coming.
Damn it, we got guards up here.
Try and buy us some time.
I'm taking care of it.
No, they're escaping, hurry!
Ah!
No, please! Don't leave us.
Please, we are Christians,
they will kill us! Please!
No, we're still not clear up top.
Make sure they don't get up.
Go!
They're coming, Ja.
- How we doing?
- Not good.
Guards are even closer.
Pull yourself up!
Help, help!
Sid!
Help me out!
Get him up here first.
That's not how this works.
You pull my brother up first.
Hurry, Ramal is coming.
Lend me your hand. I swear I'm gonna...
The kid comes up first!
Step away, step away.
- No!
- Muza, Muza, look at me!
Muza! Muza!
No! No, look at me, brother.
Go, go, go! It's Ramal.
Look at me! Muza!
Hurry. We've got a minute
tops to get out of here.
Get up there, after him.
Drop them!
Put it down!
Do it!
- No!
- Down, now!
- Board spans the gap.
- Blanket covers the wire.
Get out!
What are you doing in this cell?
They're on the roof!
Don't shoot!
I trusted you, Kaniel Outis.
And you lied to me.
By God and my armies of the caliphate,
you will die for it.
Maybe even tomorrow.
Sara...
I'm putting you in
danger by saying this,
but maybe it doesn't
matter because I'll be dead,
and they'll leave you alone.
But I love you.
You see, I loved you.
I never stopped loving you.
This whole lie, it was for you.
Sara, if I... if I do die,
don't let them put Kaniel
Outis on the headstone
because that's never what it was.
Make them put my real name,
the man I have always been.
Michael Scofield.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net