- Where is it ?
- Go to hell.
You did this to yourself.
Sara, if you're listening,
I only hope, by now,
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
- Sara Tancredi.
- You know her well ?
I'd know her a lot better
if you can get my ass moved.
- I'll talk to the warden.
- "Another Chance" and "Safe Haven."
Those are the names
of some of the chapters
in the book they use an AA.
So make no mistake about it.
We will be a family
if it kills us.
That's your map ?
- What happened to your arm ?
- My dad drinks, too.
My tummy hurts.
She needs that medicine.
She can't go two days without it.
Kacee's going into the system now.
Aiding an escaped con.
- Tell her lawyer I'll turn myself in.
- Kacee said you need to run.
If you get busted
or turn yourself in,
Dede won't have either of you.
- Michael, I want for this to be over.
- That makes two of us.
It's just a question of looking at
whatever it is your father gave you.
It's just a key.
If I may, sir, the president...
she could be useful.
Madam President ?
I want you to
come home, Paul.
but not with
those brothers
- running around the country.
- Caroline...
Please, bring
them in, Paul,
and everything can go back
to the way it was.
Agent Kellerman.
Paul, where are you ?
Out in the cold. Remember ?
I'm speaking in
Chicago tonight.
Yeah, well...
Lincoln.
Sara.
It's funny how you only call me
when you need me.
- Maybe "funny" is not the right word.
- All of this can go away, Paul.
- Can it ?
- Yes.
I'm the President
of the United States.
Please just come
back to Chicago
and turn Burrows
and Scofield in.
I promise you that I will make
everything go back
to the way it was.
I have to go.
Just come back, Paul.
I need you.
You actually think
we have a shot ?
It depends on what
your father gave you.
This fell out of his pocket
when I found him.
I don't recognize
the insignia, do you ?
No.
But, uh...
Sara, we've got someone
working with us now.
Good morning, sunshine.
How did you sleep ?
I'll tell you what.
I'll go unlock the kids
and make us all breakfast.
No. I'll get the kids.
- No !
- I insist.
No.
I'll get the kids.
Some hand cream will make them
rope burns feel better.
It won't work.
'Course it will.
Says right here on the bottle :
"Soothes skin irritations
- and..."
- No. This.
It won't work. I've got a job.
The kids have school.
We're all going to get back
to our normal routines
once this little
- adjustment period is over.
- There's someone coming over today.
- Who ?
- This woman, Patty,
- from the Welcome Wagon Committee.
- Call her and cancel.
I don't have her number.
And, if she shows up,
and I don't answer the door,
she's going to know
something's wrong.
Teddy...
Teddy Bear...
you need to go.
If she recognizes you...
I don't want you
to get in trouble.
That's nonsense.
It's no trouble.
No trouble at all.
Wakey wakey, Jones !
Hi, Sara.
What's done is done.
We all want the same thing.
You didn't tell us
you left her to die.
I was scaring her.
I wanna get her cold.
Pull out !
No. No, you left me
in there to drown.
I wonder how long
you can hold your breath.
- Maybe we should find out.
- You need me, and you know it.
Lincoln !
You need me. You need me.
Why ? Why do we need him ? We have
the key. We'll find out what it's for.
I can tell you what
that key's for right now.
It's to a private cigar club.
Where ?
Chicago.
We have to hurry.
We have to hurry, Larry.
I did a bad thing.
God ! I did a very bad thing.
All gas stations :
on 80, 30, 77.
I want Scofield's
and Burrows'pictures
on each and every gas pump.
If they have no fuel,
they can't get anywhere.
- Sir ?
- What ?
We might need to divert
our attention away from Scofield
- and Burrows for a while.
- Why would I do that ?
Because one of the other
escapees just killed a civilian.
Patoshik.
A man fitting his description
was spotted
running from the scene
of a brutal homicide.
Happened in Algoma,
Wisconsin,
less than four hours
from the prison.
Call the field office in Madison,
and have them get some agents
Okay. I'll notify headquarters.
I didn't say headquarters. I said,
are you not following direct orders ?
Oh, I am following
direct orders, sir.
Just not from you anymore.
Everything goes through
headquarters from now on.
May I ?
Yeah.
You heard about Patoshik.
Just now.
Good.
He goes.
Come on, the man is mentally ill.
He doesn't know anything, he's not a...
Patoshik was one of Scofield's
cellmates for a while.
Scofield included him in the escape.
Who knows what he knows ?
- Scofield and Burrows are still out there.
- Don't worry about Scofield and Burrows.
So,
again...
Patoshik goes.
Take care of it.
Hi, are you in
charge of seating ?
- Yeah, can I help you ?
- Agent Paul Kellerman, Secret Service.
I'm transporting a fugitive
to Chicago.
- I need you to clear a car for me.
- A fugitive ?
That's right.
Well, it's just that we're already
near capacity...
You want him to rub elbows
with your other passengers ?
- No, sir.
- Okay.
What's he wanted for ?
Killing people.
- Good Lord.
- Make it happen.
All right, come on,
follow me.
It's gonna be all right.
If you say so.
We use him to get what we need,
then we dump him.
Okay.
I'm sorry you got
involved in this.
The fact that
you're helping us...
it means a lot.
Thank you.
The other riders aren't
in any danger, are they ?
I mean, should I make an
announcement or anything ?
You want pandemonium ?
- No, sir.
- Okay, then no announcements, right ?
Keep everybody out of this car
then everything is jake.
I've done this a million times.
Never had a problem.
Okay, will do.
Let's go.
For all passengers
going to Chicago,
it won't be any stop
till the station
We'll be in Chicago
in about five hours.
Want to get some rest.
You okay ?
Yeah.
Brad.
- You don't look too good.
- I helped you with Sara Tancredi,
and you were supposed
to get me into Ad Seg.
I tried.
But your new warden is...
straight as an arrow.
But I might be able to do you
one better than Ad Seg.
You found Scofield and Burrows
through the Russian girl, right ?
Yeah, Nika. Why ?
And you tracked down Bagwell
by following Susan Hollander.
Yeah.
And I blow my nose with
my right hand and I wipe my ass
with my left.
What of it ?
I've got very powerful people
behind me
that want me to finish my job.
They can push through the quickest
habeas corpus proceedings
the courts have ever seen.
Paperwork's sitting on the right
person's desk as we speak,
setting forth all
the Constitutional violations
in your prosecution.
It's just waiting
to be rubber-stamped.
And what do I have to do ?
You just find those cons.
Only, this time...
you're gonna do it for me...
unofficially,
under the radar,
no paper trail...
I need a junkyard dog
who's willing to do
the ugly things it takes
to bring a con to justice.
Are you my dog, Brad ?
Damn hell, yeah, I am.
This is delicious.
What'd you call it again ?
That, my dear Patty-cake,
is what my auntie back in'Bama
used to call "hobo chicken."
One part chicken, two parts
spice, three part actual hobo.
I know...
fowl isn't part of a...
traditional brunch, per se, but
I have found a
lean meat can act
as an aperitif to...
awaken the pallet
for more subtle flavors and
textures, such as...
Mama mia !
Pumpkin cinnamon breads
with fresh strawberries and cream.
Boy !
Now, how did you two meet ?
Church.
After my, uh...
accident, uh,
I was volunteering
with some other...
amputees.
My parish back home did
an exchange program with
churches all over
this fine country and...
well...
the good Lord just saw fit to plop
my country rump right down
rump right down in the pew
beside my Susie Q.
And you just stole her heart.
I'm a regular one-armed bandit.
A one-armed bandit...
Mrs. Wallace,
Teddy just bought me
a brand-new bike.
It's out in the garage.
Wanna go see ?
Sure.
We have got company.
Oh, that's okay.
No, it's not; it's rude.
Zack knows better.
Isn't that right ?
You do know better, Zack.
You gotta have discipline.
Without a strong
father figure,
a young man might just
end up in prison.
Since you are such a fan
of lame store-bought
blueberry pie,
I am gonna bake you
a real pie...
Hi, my name's Lance
and I'm an addict.
Hi, my name is not Lance,
I'm not an addict.
Michael...
Do you know if there's any way
I can get any water ?
Yeah, I think there's
a bathroom downstairs.
- I'll check.
- Thanks.
It was never personal, Sara.
- War never is.
- Yeah.
Sara !
Sara, back off !
Let him go, Sara.
Sara !
Sara.
You get one of those !
You get one of those.
One.
Calm down.
Down. Get down, right now.
What ?
These three guys said they saw
what looked to be a fight
going on in there.
They didn't, all right ?
Just get the train to Chicago.
Do I need to notify
the police ?
You need to do what I told you
to do. You take the tickets,
I'll watch the fugitive. You guys can
continue to do bong hits,
or whatever you do
back there, okay ?
Now would you guys
mind your own business ?
Everybody clear ?
Great.
Don't interrupt again, please.
Just so we're all clear :
if she tries that again...
You'll do what ?
Just stay on the other side
of the car.
It wasn't personal, Paul.
Yeah.
All ours, Patty Cake
- Ooh ! What're these ?
- Oh, I'm, uh...
gonna do some renovations.
I was just tappin'the sheetrock,
lookin'for the stud.
Looks like you
already found one.
Whoo ! Potty mouth !
Oh !
Me and the girls get together
every Friday
for book club.
You ought to host it this week
and everybody can meet you.
I'll see you then !
Can't wait.
This ain't ever
gonna work here.
Go pack your things.
we're movin'.
Now, hey, if you
don't stop me,
I'm gonna eat this
whole thing by myself.
All right, sweetie,
listen.
I'll make a deal with you.
Remember that merry-go-round
that we saw today ?
You're not gonna get
a chance to ride it,
if you don't eat something.
- Go ahead.
- I don't feel good.
Oh, sweetie.
Okay, come on.
Let's go, all right ?
I got you.
Okay, just hold on.
- Okay, sweet pea ?
- Check, please ?
All right ! Nobody move !
- Hey, Sara ?
- Leave me alone.
How is she ?
Well, she wants to be alone.
So we get what her dad
locked away with that key.
What do we do then ?
I mean... you saw what they did
with the tape we made.
They're gonna bury everything
we put out there.
That's why we're keeping him
close to us.
He's got a lot of connections
in Washington.
So we get to the cigar club,
open her dad's box...
what if the only thing
inside's a bunch of stogies ?
I think it's worth making
the trip to find out.
- Yes ?
- Caroline.
Paul. Where are you ?
I need to know exactly
what you meant
when you said you were gonna
make this right.
- I need specifics.
- Where are you ?
What's that noise ?
I'm on a train.
I'll be in Chicago later today.
But I need to know specifics.
Where are Burrows and Scofield ?
Are they with you ?
Don't worry about them.
- Worry about me.
- Paul,
there are still positions
in my administration
that need to be filled...
including Chief of Staff.
I want that to be you.
When I get to Chicago,
we'll meet.
We'll talk.
All of it.
I just brought enough
to get a sandwich.
I was sitting
right there, okay ?
If you're lying...
Look, my daughter is sick, and
I don't want to spend any more minutes
in here than necessary.
Trust me,
that is all that I have.
What do you got, sweetheart ?
What do you got ?
- You don't want to listen ?!
- Hey,
- hey, calm down, man.
- Shut up !
All right.
Listen to me, you've got
to calm down.
All right, I can help you get
everything that you want.
But you don't want to hurt
anybody else, right ?
Come on.
Look, listen.
Hey. Why don't you go ahead
and lock the door,
and turn the closed sign back,
so everybody thinks that
this place is closed,
all right ?
And then, we can get everybody away
from the window.
- Is that cool with you ?
- Everybody's away from the window, okay ?
Let's move everybody onto
this side of the room.
Get on this side of the room,
everybody.
Let's move to this side of the room
from the window.
- Move !
- Everybody, let's get on this side
of the room, okay ?
This side of the room.
- Yeah.
- Why don't you take my daughter, okay ?
Take her on this side of the room,
so that everybody...
everything is gonna be okay.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Because you're not gonna put your hand
on another person, right ?
Right. We're all good.
Y'all good ?
We're good, right ?
- Hey, Sara ?
- Come on in.
Hey.
I've been sitting
here evaluating.
I, uh...
I jumped bail.
I'm on the run,
and I just tried
to take a man's life.
I'm not using.
Which is actually...
quite an accomplishment.
But three weeks ago,
I was a doctor.
You can get that back...
all of it.
You need to believe that.
You believe that ?
You think you can
get it all back ?
I choose to have faith.
Because without that,
I'm nothing.
It's the only thing
that's keeping me going.
Well...
I got two things
keeping me going.
First, is that I want the people
who killed my dad.
And actually, the second...
ironically, I probably
wouldn't even
say if I hadn't lost him,
but, um...
You should know that...
The first thing they tell you
when you take the job,
is, um,
never to fall in love
with an inmate.
What's going on ?
Roadblock.
Linc !
It's locked.
Hey ! You can't be in here.
- Run the roadblock.
- Man, I can't do that.
Run it !
Bradley Bellick, FBI.
Brad Bellick,
Federal Bureau
of Investigations.
Brad Bellick, FBI.
Special Agent Brad
Bellick, FBI.
Hi, there, I'm Brad Bellick
with the FBI.
I'm an agent with the FBI,
Brad Bellick.
I'm with the Bureau.
I already talked to the cops,
told them all I had to say.
Yeah, well, I'm no local hayseed cop.
I'm federal.
And you're not going to get away
with lying to me.
- I didn't lie to nobody.
- Really ?
"He was just some homeless guy,
hangs around Hancock Square,
hitting up college
kids for change.
He's down there all the time.
if he's not there,
I don't know where
to find him."
That's your statement, right ?
- Pretty much.
- Right. See,
the problem is Charles "Haywire"
Patoshik is a paranoid,
who suffers from
fear of crowds,
who's terrified of strangers.
If he's anywhere,
he's in the middle of nowhere,
keeping to himself,
being a weirdo.
- And ?
- And if you want to get tough...
how about I arrest
you right now
for hindering
a federal investigation ?
Who they going to believe ?
An agent with 15 years on the force
and three
Presidential Citations
or a piece of white trash
with a juvie record ?
I didn't ask him to do it
but in case you haven't noticed,
I ain't exactly broken up
over my dad's death.
Why can't you just leave
this Patoshik guy alone ?
Where is he ?
Or do you want to
get locked up...
right now ?
- Yeah.
- I got a lead on Patoshik.
Where ?
I'm on my way.
Keep him there.
Alone.
Any information on Scofield
and Burrows,
I want to be
notified immediately.
If that works out for you.
They're gonna have cops waiting
for us at the next station.
- We need to jump then.
- And do what ?
Hide under a barrel ?
Linc's right.
Okay, you just put
those in there.
I'm so sorry about all this.
It's okay, sweet pea.
Here's everything
right here, man.
- It's good.
- All right,
everyone in the storage room.
Now.
What ?
Get back there
until the cops show up.
No, no, no, no,
I can't go back there.
- Come on.
- No.
Look, you kept a cool head
this whole time.
Don't get yourself killed now.
You know what ?
Listen to me.
I'm a wanted man.
Okay ?
If the police show up here,
they'll take me back to prison,
and you know what ?
That's fine.
But my little girl right here ?
She's sick.
And she's going
to be left alone.
And I can't let that happen,
so can you please
let us go ?
- Go ! This way.
- Okay.
Go !
All right,
everyone in the back.
Move.
- Not you.
- No !
You're coming with me.
Go on. Move.
Okay, I want you to stay
right here, okay ?
- Go on !
- Hey.
- I think you should let her go, man.
- Take off.
- Last chance.
- You've got the money.
Burglary and assault.
Man, hey, that's change, man,
that's little time.
But this right here...
you will be in prison
for the rest of your life.
- Believe me on that.
- Unless you want
your daughter to see you die,
move.
I'm trying to help you, man !
Sweetie, stay right there.
Oh, no.
Who did this ?
I did.
Thank you.
Haywire !
Don't move !
Run ! Larry ! Run !
Hurry !
Dino, it's Eric.
We've got four jumpers.
Three males
and a female.
Call it in and get us
to the next station.
Do you hear me ?
Get us to the next station.
The men who pushed through
the roadblock are jumping off the train
near mile marker 54,
just south of the
Tedford Bridge.
Please, stop !
Stop where you are.
Freeze !
Don't shoot !
Turn around !
I'm an employee of
the train company.
Dino, it's Eric.
We've got four jumpers.
Three males and a female. Call it in
and get us to the next station.
Let's go. Come on.
They told us to jump and run
and not to look back
or they'd shoot us.
We need to find a car.
- Yeah.
- I got Haywire trapped.
Don't do anything.
Just hold him
until I get there.
No problem.
I got this wingnut treed.
- Caroline.
- Paul, where are you ?
Did you send the police ?
No, of course not.
How did they know
I was on that train ?
Paul, I have no idea.
- I'll let the president know.
- I contact the president directly.
Are Burrows and
Scofield with you ?
I was expecting to
brief the president.
You report to me now.
Paul ?
Where did we spend
my 35th birthday ?
What ?
The restaurant.
Where was it ?
You remember.
Don't be ridiculous.
I have to go.
Do not hang up.
Just get Burrows
and Scofield...
Hey.
Whoever this is...
tell Bill Kim
that he just screwed up...
big-time.
Paul ?
What's all this ?
Some whacko climbs up
to a grain elevator,
people want to watch.
Oh, God, you were supposed
to keep a handle on things.
Do you know what that means ?
I got you Haywire.
What else do you want ?
FBI. He's my chargee.
How you doing, Charles ?
I don't want to go
back to prison.
I don't blame you.
I want to go to Holland.
That's not what I
expected to hear.
But you can't go there, son.
I just...
I just want to go... here.
See ?
I'll tell you what.
You don't have to go to prison.
But you can't go to
Holland, either.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
- no, no.
- It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay. Hey,
you're in a tough spot.
You feel trapped,
you got no options, and...
caught in a situation
where you have no control.
I know how you feel.
I do.
It takes its toll on you,
and all you want to do is run.
But run where ?
I just want to go.
There's a way out.
A way out ?
Of this maze ?
Yeah.
There are private humidors
in the back.
Each member's name
is on their box.
- Any security ?
- A receptionist.
That's it.
I'm not a wanted fugitive.
Give me the key.
I'll do it.
Want to take a walk ?
Yeah.
I know you killed your parents
because they hurt you.
And I know you killed that guy yesterday
because he was hurting Sasha,
but what you did...
was wrong.
You know that.
I just want to go.
You can.
I want to go now.
It's okay.
Sara.
About before.
Me, too.
Yeah.
Synchro: Csivore
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net