Do something, my brother is innocent!
- He's American...
- I can't do anything.
Yes! Back at the crime scene,
- that'll prove...
- I'm a night clerk.
You want someone who can
do something, wait for the consul.
He gets in in the morning.
I'm sorry.
That ain't gonna cut it.
Your brother,
- where do they have him incarcerated?
- Sona.
What?
The worst of the worst are there,
men no other prison will take.
They rioted so badly a year ago,
the guards pulled out,
just left them
to themselves.
A thousand thieves,
rapists, murderers.
The government just stays back,
keeps the perimeter.
To them, Sona's
a one-way street.
What goes in...
never comes out...
unless it's dead.
Subtitles: swsub.com
Somebody wasn't diligent enough
with this guy,
and we need him moved to a facility
that's a little more... moderate.
All right? Thank you.
Alright, the good news
is as of yesterday you're a free man.
- You got nothing to worry about.
- Just my brother.
Right. Well, that's a heck
of a story, you two.
That made the news even down here.
And I understand you also have a son?
LJ... Lincoln Jr.?
He must be ecstatic about your
exoneration.
- Still trying to reach him.
- Tell us where he is. We'll send...
Let me handle that.
Let's just focus on Michael.
Okay, well, good news is
is that much
of what you're saying is
checking out at the crime scene.
The victim did have a service revolver
with U.S. government numbers on it.
And if a weapon was found,
then that lends
real credence to self-defense
as a motive.
Great.
Did they find anything else?
- Like what?
- A bag.
- What was in it?
- A little money.
No, sorry.
- Of course they didn't.
- Yeah, well, whatever the case,
regarding Michael,
I've managed to make a little headway.
I arranged the transfer of your brother
to another facility tomorrow.
- It's a lot safer, it's a lot cleaner.
- Great.
And if this is stacking up
like I think it is,
I'd be pretty confident
the charges will be dropped.
He'd be free?
Well, he'd still face charges
in the U.S.
- But out of there?
- Yes.
Is there...
is there a mess hall here?
Mess hall?
And some water.
I'm dying of thirst. Please.
Please.
There's some water.
Bite me.
- What'd you say?
- I didn't say nothing.
Drink it.
You hear me?
Drink!
Hey, get used to it, man.
I haven't eaten for days.
Come on.
- How are you doing?
- What do you want, Alex?
You're so clever...
Planting the drugs on the boat.
That's a big irony.
Lawman in jail.
You are exactly where
you belong.
No, you're wrong.
And you're gonna help me.
I will have a court date one day,
and you will be there on the stand.
And you'll tell the truth,
that you planted this
and you set this up,
and I'm gonna go home.
That's funny.
I could have sworn you set this up.
I set this up?
I'm in here.
What does the Company want with me?
Why Panama?
What, you think I know
what they wanted?
They had me.
I did what they
asked me to do:
arrest you in Panama
and hand you over.
That's it. That's...
That's old news, huh?
This is the first day
of the rest of our lives.
How about we work together,
help each other out.
Except every time I look at you,
all I can see is the man
who killed my father.
You're on your own.
Sign here to say that once inside,
you're on your own by the law,
you're not protected by the military
in case of an assault.
Any attempt to assist
an inmate trying to escape
will be met
with a lethal response.
Wouldn't dream of it.
So...
Feel like I'm on the wrong side.
- You're on the right side.
- You're not.
- Gonna break me out?
- Too tiring. All that running.
Yeah, well, maybe you should
have lost the cowboy boots.
You scared?
I'm getting you out of here, man.
The Consulate's arranged to transfer you
to a safer facility until the trial...
which is about a month.
- They say you got a good chance.
- When's the transfer?
Tomorrow.
Just... just hold on,
man, one more day.
You know, I keep waiting for you
to mention a certain someone.
- I don't know where she is, man.
- Well, you got to find her.
I will.
She's important
to me, Linc.
If anything happens to Sara...
It's going to be fine, man.
I promise.
I'll see you tomorrow.
All right?
American, right?
I love America.
NBA. Tracy McGrady shooting the
ball in the hoop from downtown.
Whatever you're selling,
I'm not buying.
Selling?
I just want to talk basketball.
Who's your team?
Let's go, blanco.
Orientation.
- I'm not interested.
- It's not for you to decide.
Bring them in.
I hope they haven't been
treating you too poorly.
I should hear of it if you have.
I think as you can tell, Sona
is unlike any other place in the world.
Since the riots of last year,
they left us here to rot.
They figured we would just destroy
ourselves, but instead, we've thrived.
With the canal, Panama is now a breeding
ground for international crime.
27 different nationalities we have here.
But not one gang.
Not one racially-motivated incident.
It's just...
me.
Egalitarianism I believe is the word.
- Did I get that right?
- Right as rain.
That's what practice does for you.
Now, is there anything
you want to tell me?
Any history that you bring to this place
that I should know about?
I don't think you're quite
telling me the truth.
We get the news, man.
You were quite the superstar on CNN.
Man breaks brother out...
and flees to Panama.
But you're not a superstar here!
- You realize that, don't you?
- I'm not going to make waves.
It wouldn't be within your power.
I heard about the two of you.
You two in the hall today.
Now, if you'd like to sort your problems
out, it's very simple here.
A man has a beef with another,
he makes his problem known.
And then we deal with it directly
as men... over there.
Won't be necessary.
You always shake like that?
Or just when you're scared of someone?
I think he gets the message.
We could go...
You and me... right here.
You're a brave man, huh?
You're lucky I've been meditating.
Before, I couldn't take my finger
off the trigger, but now,
now, I have mind control.
Complete control.
Mind...
body...
and soul.
Get out!
He's a waste of our time.
Who would have thought...
a famous person in Sona.
Weak people rally around fame.
They worship it. They're blinded by it.
There are many people of weak character
behind these walls.
Yes, they will follow a man like this,
and they will put him on a pedestal.
He has that charisma, right, mami?
He's no you.
You don't have to pander me, mami.
He's good looking, right?
He's the best looking man
in the prison, right?
Not compared to you.
I told you, mami...
Sara Tancredi... she's an American.
She's missing.
We don't have a report
of anything like that.
But if you do, you call me.
The number's on the back.
- Anything, you call me, alright?
- Will do.
Thank you.
Where'd you get shoes?
It's time to start
earning your rent, here.
- There's no rent, it's prison.
- Keep talking.
It's going up.
Here.
Work time's started right now.
Where?
- Hell no.
- Absolutely not.
One more word from you,
and I will drown you in here,
you understand?
Now, work.
Burn it down in the sewers
when you're done.
- Elliot Pike.
- What do you want?
Well, to be frank, to represent you.
- You're a lawyer?
- Of sorts.
The court already appointed me a lawyer.
Then perhaps I can be
of assistance in a different way.
Somehow I doubt that.
I got a lot of big guns behind me,
Mr. Scofield,
people you might like
to have in your corner
should you ever decide,
say... to break out of here.
Who are you?
We can assist you in every possible way
once you get past that wall.
There's a reason a guy like you,
with your skill set,
was put in here, you know.
This conversation's over.
You should listen to what I have to say.
We're trying to do this the easy way!
What the hell are you doing
taking my stash?
Cough it up, you bitch!
- I didn't do it.
- Where is it?
- It wasn't me.
You know the rules about
extra-curricular fights!
It doesn't happen here.
- He took something that belongs to me.
- He's out of his mind.
It seems pretty easy to get
to the bottom of this... check him.
Check his area.
That's bull.
You're both scumbags.
You and me, man,
we're not done here.
You haven't seen her?
No one like this has checked in?
You're absolutely sure?
Thanks.
Yeah.
Mr. Burrows. Captain Itzuris
at the constable's office.
We found an American woman
matching the description
of your friend, Ms. Tancredi.
Where?
At the morgue.
What's he saying?
That we can't eat.
What are we supposed to eat?
They expect us to forage, like dogs.
I'll die.
I will literally die.
Hang in there, man.
Playing by yourself.
Same old Pretty.
Just not good
at making friends, are you?
We got nothing to say to each other.
On another note,
them big government types
that shook me so hard,
why did they wanted you here?
Was it Sona they was interested in?
I'm wondering.
Want me to get you down here,
in this very county.
What do you think it is?
You think it's Sona?
Who'd be interested in a dump like this?
Runner! Runner!
- Thanks for getting back to me.
- No problem.
The body was fished out of the pond
this morning.
Where?
Calle Sesenta-Seis.
Just west of Avenida Colon.
Sir?
That's the last
place I saw her.
It's not her.
Someone's thrown the glove
down on you.
The gauntlet, right?
Yeah, except we both know
I didn't take those drugs.
I'm not the judge.
I don't deal in the claims
people make.
I just make sure the rules are followed.
And the rules say
all grievances are dealt with
two men in a ring, a fight.
I'll be leaving tomorrow,
so that won't be necessary.
It may not be necessary to you,
but it is to me.
I have a duty
to maintain order here...
an ironclad legal system
that assures that
no one goes independent
with their grievances,
as is so often the case
in other prisons.
Here,
there is a system,
and that system means order.
So whether you agree with it or not
does not matter to me.
There's a larger agenda than yours.
What happens if I refuse?
We'll come for you.
And I can guarantee you that is
an outcome that you will not like.
Tell me something...
do you always set up your fights?
I had nothing to do with it.
And yet the only one
in this prison
who has a problem with me is you.
I'd be glad to see
you go down...
superstar.
Go on, keep going.
You burn it around the corner.
Think you can do me a favor?
Bite me.
I can feed you.
A few weeks ago, I was in your shoes.
Didn't get any food for days.
They'd have let me die,
just like they're gonna let you die.
Get back to the "feed me" part.
Chicken. Man, where'd you get chicken?
That's not chicken.
Want some more?
Then you're gonna have
to run an errand for me.
What kind of errand?
- Dad? It's me.
- LJ.
- Where are you?
- I'm in Panama.
What?
How...
- How'd you get this number?
- I ran into Sara.
The consulate gave her your number.
- Dad, I'm cutting out.
- LJ?
- I can't hear you.
- Dad, do this.
Meet us at the restaurant
in the Garfield Price building,
- at the top.
- Garfield what?
8:30...
Time to fight, blanco.
Best to make your peace with God.
Uno, dos, tres, all right?
What? Even at 10-1?
There's a reason he chose World.
Six consecutive life terms, okay?
I'm just kidding, man.
Tranquilo!
Surely,
it's beneath a man of your status
to be walking around like that
all sticky-like.
Leave him.
What do you propose?
Ablution.
A humble sign of friendship
from a stranger
who's come into your house.
Sorry about that.
Just... half a man down here.
What's your name, norteño?
You can just call me...
"friend."
Go for the kneecap.
You...
You hit it straight on, it'll buckle,
and you'll take the guy
out of commission.
Fighting dirty? That's your secret?
I didn't think there was any such thing
as clean in a place like this.
You know, I'm surprised, Alex.
It almost sounds like you care.
You're my get-out-of-jail-free card.
Just survive.
Kneecap, really hard.
Good luck, man.
God bless, man.
We got a disagreement
between two dogs.
A drug addict and a thief.
And I condone neither.
And I wash my hands of both of them.
But they have an issue,
and we have rules.
And without rules,
we're nothing but savages.
Therefore,
with proper respect for the rules,
this fight is engaged
with only one rule:
no weapons.
Only man versus man,
without augmentation or handicap.
I'm done talking.
I'm not gonna fight!
I don't think
you understand the rules, friend.
Only one man comes out alive.
No weapons!
Rules are rules, remember?
If we don't have them...
we're savages.
Excuse me.
You have no jacket.
I'm just meeting someone.
Give me a break.
Well, this is a nice place.
It requires jackets.
- I don't have a jacket.
- It requires jackets.
Fine.
Excuse me.
You speak English?
How about American?
Can I grab a water, please?
Please, tell me you didn't come
all the way to Panama for the water.
Family.
That's a nice jacket... Sergio.
It's a long story.
Thank you.
You're waiting for someone?
I should have known.
Good-looking ones are always taken.
What happened to your face?
- A cat.
- Cat?
It's a big cat.
You push anything too far into a corner,
and the claws will come out.
- Your timing's all wrong, lady.
- Come on. Hang out.
I'd like to...
but it ain't the right time.
Yes, it is, Lincoln.
We have a lot to discuss.
Specifically, your brother.
I highly suggest you talk to him.
How are we coming with the transfer?
There are some people that want you
to break someone out of there.
Yeah, I know.
Some guy approached me.
I said, "No, thank you."
You gotta stay.
What are you talking about?
His name's James Whistler.
No, Linc, I can't do that again.
Talk.
Dad!
Dad,
I'm so sorry.
They got me and Sara.
Please, do what they want.
Dad, please.
You got a week
to find this Whistler guy.
Get him out of there.
Otherwise, they...
Sara and LJ...
they both die.
www.tvsubtitles.net