Previously on Prison Break.
I didn't kill that man, Michael.
The evidence says you did.
No, I was set up.
Put down your weapon.
I find it incumbent that you see the inside of a prison cell.
I'm looking for someone, guy named Lincoln Burrows.
Man killed the vice-president's brother.
Why do you wanna see Burrows so bad anyhow?
Because he's my brother.
I'm getting you out of here.
Impossible.
Not if you designed the place it isn't.
You've seen the blueprints.
Better that that.
I've got them on me.
You find out who's trying to bury him.
Nobody's trying to bury him.
The evidence was cooked.
There's a lawyer poking around.
Anyone that's a threat is expendable.
Scofield!
Found you a new cellie. Haywire, get in here.
Someone found Fibonacci.
Who was this someone?
Now where is Fibonacci?
I give you that information, I'm a dead man.
Three.
On your feet!
What time is it?
Get up!
What's going on?
Bellick!
Bellick! No!
Bellick! Where are you taking me?!
Bellick! Bellick! No!
No! Bellick, don't!
Bellick, no! I got a month left!
Please! No! Bellick!
Bellick, no!
Bellick, please!
No! No! I got a month left!
Please!
No! Bellick!
Make your peace, Lincoln.
Let's get on with it.
Open 40!
Close 40.
Haywire. You ever thought of breaking out?
What the hell would I do out there?
Not be here.
Halfway houses,
psych visits, meds, checking in with a P.O.,
urine tests, keeping a job...
No.
Why you ask?
This guy was talking about it in the yard yesterday. I didn't know what to say.
Tell officer Bellick.
He'll make life easy for you, if, uh...
If what?
Your tattoos.
What about them?
What are they of?
What are they? Like, some kind of a...
They're just tattoos.
It's candy time, Haywire.
They think I have schizo-affective disorder with bipolar tendencies.
Think you got it?
Whatever.
Ah!
I take the pills, keep the quacks off my back.
Bye, now.
Get out of the way.
You know, maybe they give you those things for a reason.
Yeah.
To keep me dull.
To keep me in their invisible freakin' handcuffs.
Seriously, though, those tattoos, they're beautiful.
You mind if I, you know, look at the whole thing?
I do, actually.
Why?
Yo! Stand clear!
Does there need to be a reason?
Sucre!
I ain't even talking to you, man.
What's the problem?
Nothing I can't handle.
Well, I knew there was a problem.
I could tell by looking at you from across the yard.
Hey, guys, didn't I say there was a problem?
So what's the problem?
You're looking at it.
What? Haywire?
Yep. That's my new cellmate.
That's a problem.
He doesn't sleep.
So, when do you dig?
I don't.
Hey, you and I are in bed now.
You  made me promise.
You said that we were going to get out of here.
You renege now, and I'm going to gut you.
So, you better take care of your business,
or I will take care of you.
Have a nice day.
It's really coming together, isn't it?
Yep.
You  think it'll be done in time?
Well, I figure, we still have the interior alcoves
and pilasters to do, which is no small task.
But, yes, I think so.
Listen, I have to say, I...
I really appreciate all the effort that you put into this.
I wish there was some way I could, you know, pay you or something.
There is one thing you could do for me.
My cellmate.
Ah, the inimitable Charles Patoshick.
Haywire?
Then you know.
Hold it right there.
Officer Bellick is in charge of cell transfers.
You're gonna have to talk to him about that.
I tried, but he seems to think we're a good match.
Has he threatened you?
Who, Haywire or Bellick?
Hmm.
Unfortunately, unless there's some evidence of violence
or sexual predation between cellmates,
those kinds of requests fall on deaf ears around here.
Prison system's a little too crowded for requests based on personality.
It's not exactly Sandals out there.
Warden?
Sorry. Your wife is here.
What?
She's not supposed to be here till 4:00.
Becky, do not let her come in here under any circumstances.
She's not supposed to see this until our anniversary.
I'll be right out.
Hi, sweetheart.
You're early.
Uh... let's go eat.
You're acting funny.
I am?
What's going on in there?
Um... just going over some files.
Becky said you were in a meeting.
This isn't Toledo all over again, is it?
Toledo?
How can you say that?
Then, you won't mind if I look.
Judy...
Warden, I'm not going to be able to cooperate.
I'd get killed if I did.
Johnson's still deciding.
Then, you and I are done.
You should have just told me.
Well, you know how anxious I get when you come around the inmates.
Becky, have a guard escort Johnson back to his cell.
I'll deal with him later. Come on, let's go eat.
What you doing here?
I'm  your attorney.
I'm representing you now.
Hmm.
If that's all right with you.
Last time I saw you, you called me a liar.
Things have changed.
I believe you now.
I got in touch with Crab Simmons's ex-girlfriend Leticia.
She corroborated your story.
Will she testify?
She's missing.
I don't know. I think the Secret Service got to her.
Secret Service?
They've been poking around.
Soon as they show up, she disappears. What do you think happened?
Um... I didn't realize it was that high up, you know.
Do you know what we're up against?
I know it's a lot more than either of us can handle on our own.
Project Justice.
Why have I heard of them?
All they handle is death penalty cases.
There's a guy there, Ben Forsik, I sent him copies of everything I had.
You can go there, tell him what you found.
Maybe we'll get enough to bring him on board.
Okay.
So, uh... how's Sebastian?
What do you mean?
Well, you being here. I mean... is he cool with it?
I haven't talked to him.
The, um...
The engagement's off.
Oh. I'm sorry.
You could at least say that like you mean it.
I do.
God, you always were a lousy liar.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I better get to Project Justice.
Veronica?
Thank you.
I didn't have a whole lot left.
You can thank me when I get you out of here.
Baby, it's me. Are you there?
Hello? Are you there?
Hey, if she is, she obviously don't want to talk to you.
It's Wednesday, babe.
You're gonna come around today, right?
Okay, I got to hang up now.
I got to go back in the block, but
you're gonna be here today, right?
I'm your man, baby, and I love you.
I do.
It's a pattern.
What did you say?
Your-Your tattoo-- it's a pattern.
You're seeing things.
Putting him in with Haywire is a low blow, Deputy.
What? The shrinks cleared Haywire for reentry into gen pop.
Besides, he's so doped up on meds, he's like a kitten these days.
A kitten who murdered both his parents.
Well, all due respect, sir.
If you give Scofield preferential treatment, it'll undermine your credibility.
I know you got a soft spot for the guy because he's got brains in his head,
and he's helping you with that contraption in there,
but the guy's a violent criminal.
He deserves punishment just as much as the rest of these guys.
You have been here long enough to know
that I'm less interested in punishment than I am in rehabilitation.
And sticking him in with Haywire is not rehabilitation in my book.
You delegated authority over gen pop to me, boss.
I know I did.
Then, you either got to let me do my job, or pass it on to somebody else.
Now, Brian, go easy.
There's a reason I'm giving you more and more responsibility.
When I retire, I'm recommending you to take my place.
Don't make me regret it.
All  I'm saying is, take another look at the Scofield situation.
I trust your judgment.
Yes, sir.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, hold up.
This is supposed to be an open visitation. Why are we doing it in here?
Ask your visitor.
What are you doing here? Where's Maricruz?
She's not going to be coming around here anymore.
Is she hurt?
No, no. She's fine, she's fine. She's just, uh...
She's with me now.
She's with you now?
It's a joke, right?
No, she made a decision, man.
She decided she needed stability.
Is she going to get that from you?
Look, look, you can think whatever you want about me. But, uh...
I'm not the one who's in prison.
See,
I actually can do something for her.
And she wanted me to stop by here and talk to you first, you know, in case you got mad...
You just proved my point.
You're a con, and that's all you'll ever be.
Make it quick.
Yeah. He's, uh, right in here.
Take a walk, Choppy.
Scofield.
You're in a restricted area.
I'm doing yard work for P.I. We need some fertilizer.
Why are you in the masonry section?
Oh, by the way, how's the foot?
Don't ever go around me to The Pope again.
Now, move.
You know what, Haywire?
I don't think we're gonna work out.
And, since I was here first, I think you should go.
I crapped myself once in junior high.
It  was during... during P.E.
We were... We were playing badminton,
and I knew I was gonna have to walk past a bunch of the other students to,
you know, get back to the locker room.
And so...
I just started walking.
And I tried to make fun of it, you know, before anyone else did.
So, I turned around behind me, and...
and I said, "Look, I have a tail!"
I just shared a secret with you.
Now, it's your turn.
Want to know what the tattoos mean?
- Yeah.
- Nothing.
Hey, Fish.
Making any progress?
With Sleeping Beauty back there, or with the digging?
Either.
No.
But I know what to do.
Oh, yeah?
Problem is, you don't got the stugots to do it.
Abruzzi, let's go.
See you.
Yeah?
Really?
Well, tell the crazy son of a bitch I said hi.
Wrap it up.
How about Aunt Ruth? She out of the hospital yet?
- Wrap it up.
- Hold on, Ma.
Bite me!
Okay, we got a problem now, man.
Let's handle it, then.
That's what I thought.
Hello?
Maricruz, it's me. Baby, what the hell is going on?
What's the deal with you and Hector?
When were you gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
That Rita Saldana's been visiting you?
- What?!
- Yeah. Hector told me.
Hector told you. Hector told you.
Of course he told you. Baby, that guy's a snake. He's a liar.
Why would he lie?
Well, why would he lie? Because he's been trying to get into your pants
since the minute we started dating, that's why.
You know what?
I don't know what to believe.
Me, Mami, believe me.
Yeah, well I wait by the phone twice a week.
Baby,  where is this coming from?
I don't know.
Look, there's just so many things.
Yesterday, I went to Teresa's house,
and I saw her baby.
Is that what this is about? You think your clock is ticking?
Well, I am going to be 30 in a few years!
Baby, you're 25.
You want to get pregnant? Let's get pregnant right now.
Baby, you know I can't get pregnant till I'm married.
We're gonna get married...
in 16 months.
Yeah, well, Hector says that if something goes wrong in there,
that you could serve your full sentence.
I can't wait ten years.
I can't wait ten years, baby.
I'm going to be out in 16 months.
Okay, well, what if something does happen, huh?
Baby, I can't wait that long.
I can't.
I'm sorry, I got to go.
Hello? Ba... Wait. Hello? Hel...
Even if Leticia Barris turned up again,
her testimony would be worthless.
By and large, most junkies with criminal records don't shine on the stand.
Maybe, but I just found all this out in the past couple of days.
I'm confident that I can find out a whole lot more
now that I'm devoting all my time to the case.
The Secret Service agent who came to visit you when Leticia was in your office--
what did he want?
Nick, please. You've got to understand, Ms. Donovan.
Unless there's new information you can provide for us,
we've already reviewed Mr. Burrows's case thoroughly.
Do you have any new evidence?
No, but I...
But...
that is effectively what you're telling us, right?
I need to clarify here.
Yes, that is what I'm telling you.
But look, Mr. Forsik, you don't need to point out what I don't have.
I'm well aware of that.
I'm here asking for your help
because I don't think an innocent man should be killed for something he didn't do.
And I believe that's what it says on your mission statement in the lobby.
We get thousands of requests for representation.
I'm sure you do.
And I have to decide which cases we're going to devote
our very limited resources to.
I will do all of the legwork, Mr. Forsik.
But since I don't have any experience in death penalty cases,
I'm just asking you to point me in the right direction.
Please.
I'm sorry.
We just don't have the manpower.
Thank you for your time.
She's just leaving now.
Figure it'll take her at least a half hour to get across town in this traffic.
I'm not going to need nearly that much time.
I've turned up quite a bit already.
Hey, have you seen my toothpaste?
It was right here!
Haven't seen it.
I always put it in the same place.
I'm sure it'll turn up.
The tattoos, there's a maze.
Get away from me.
I need to see them. Just... you got to show them to me. It's pulling me in.
I said... get away from me.
Okay.
He's got a maze on his skin.
Yeah, he's got a maze on his skin.
Why?
Why would he do that? Why?
Why has he put a maze on his skin? Um...
I don't... Ow!
How are your contacts in Chemical Lockup?
Depends who's asking.
I need a bottle of drain line root control, sooner than later.
Got weeds growing in your cell?
Just one.
You the one who was looking for me?
Yeah, I wanted to ask you some questions about the Lincoln Burrows case.
Yeah?
I'm Veronica Donovan. I'm representing Lincoln on his appeal.
What about it?
You were the first one to respond
to Lincoln's apartment the night of the murder, right?
That's right.
Look, I'd really appreciate if you could just tell me exactly what you saw.
Dispatch called in with a tip that Burrows was seen running
from the garage where they found Terrence Steadman.
So, we went over to Burrows's place.
We spread out.
Entered he bathroom,
that's where I saw your client washing out the bloody pants.
Police! Hands up!
I don't need to tell you it was Steadman's blood, do I?
In the report that you typed up that night,
you said that you saw Lincoln standing in the bathroom, that's all.
Later, you testified that you saw him washing the pants-- which one is it?
Does it matter?
Did you actually see him washing the pants, or not?
Yes.
He stood up, turned around,
his hands were all wet, looking guilty as hell.
Your testimony factored into his conviction. You know that, right?
You know, lady, if you got any other questions,
just go through the department.
Miss Donovan.
I didn't mean to scare you.
What are you doing here?
Nick Savrinn with Project Justice.
I know who you are, but what are you doing here?
Look, my boss may not think Lincoln's case is worth looking into, but I do.
There's a quicker way to take care of your problem.
There's smarter ways, too.
What stood out for me was that most death penalty cases
take ten years to exhaust all appeals.
Lincoln got there in three.
So, for it to be expedited,
there had to have been some sort of political influence, right?
Well... given that Terrence Steadman is the vice president's brother,
that's not too hard to believe.
How, though? They got to every judge that rejected Lincoln's appeal?
Doesn't take a judge.
All it takes is a little special attention from one of his clerks.
But how Lincoln got fast-tracked doesn't interest me. It's why.
If he was set up, then why?
I think the answer to that might lie in the victim.
What do we know? He was the CEO of EcoField, right?
He was pushing alternative energy.
Successfully pushing alternative energy.
So, oil companies, the Saudis, even our own government...
a lot of people stood to benefit with Steadman out of the picture.
Why'd you wait till now to take up this case?
I thought he did it, like everybody else.
I just hope it's not too late.
Very well may be.
You need to prepare yourself for that.
What about you?
Why death penalty work?
My father did 15 years for a crime he didn't commit.
I know first-hand that when the government gets you in their crosshairs,
you stand very little chance.
That's why.
Now... do you want my help?
- I want back in.
- Too late.
I'll do anything you need. You see these hands?
They're digging machines.
You want to go to China? I'll get you to China.
I'll dig like a psychotic rodent if I have to.
Fish... I gotta be back in.
As of right now, there is no "in."
Van Gogh over there is my new cellmate.
But you're going to do something about it, right?
- You're gonna get rid of him.
- I'll do what's necessary.
You're my boy!
So how you gonna do that?
Well, let's just put it this way--
someone's going to get hurt.
How'd we miss this, guys?
Scofield's father was out of the picture by the time he was born.
Took his mother's maiden name.
All right, Scofield had no priors and a full-time job as an engineer.
Correct.
Then he goes and robs a bank, discharging a gun in the process.
So that in sentencing, he maneuvers his way to Fox River
where his brother's scheduled to die in less than a month.
Obviously, something is up.
All due respect, brothers are incarcerated together all over the country.
It may just be a coincidence.
Move on the younger brother.
Do it preemptively before anything rises up, bites any of us in the ass.
It's a pathway...
where does it lead?
Where are you taking me?
What, are you nuts?
Officer!
I need an officer!
What the hell's the problem down here?
What... son of a bitch!
Open up on 40!
He's got the pathway on his body. It leads somewhere.
Back off, Haywire!
No, look... Look... look at his tattoos. It's a pathway.
Haywire, I said "back off." You want a hot shot?
I'm telling you, look at his...
Back off, man! Get in over here!
Let's go!
It leads to hell!
It's a pathway to hell!
He's taking us all to hell!
So, the gang's all back together again. Well, ain't that swell?
Told you not to go around me to The Pope.
But you just keep making waves, don't you?
- Good to be back, man.
- Good to have you back.
So when do we get started?
Good afternoon, Mr. Scofield.
Hello.
How you feeling today?
We're good.
What happened?
Um, caught an elbow playing basketball.
Uh-huh.
Mind if I take a look?
By all means.
You know you're going to get killed in here, right?
If you're not careful.
I'll make you a bet.
When I get out of here, alive,
I'll take you to dinner.
Lunch? Cup of coffee?
Michael, this, um... this charm act
could be exactly what's getting you into trouble out in the yard.
Lean forward.
All right...
you went to the parking garage,
Terrence Steadman is already dead.
That's right.
You saw that and you ran... took the gun.
- Dumped the gun.
- Where?
Storm drain, Van Buren and Wells.
Nobody ever found it.
All right, well, what do you do after that?
You go back to your apartment?
Yeah.
I was freaking out, trying to figure out what happened.
Then, I saw the bloody pants in the tub.
The cops, they busted in a minute after I got there.
The pants-- the ones with Steadman's blood on them--
first cop on the scene says he saw you washing them in the bathtub.
He's lying.
My hands were wet after splashing water on my face.
Police! Let's see your hands! Hands up!
I never touched those pants.
Which brings us back to the gun,
the one you said you dumped.
It was planted.
It's the only way it could have got there.
Ballistics matched to a slug...
The gun was planted! It was planted!
Just like the pants.
Your fingerprints were all over the gun.
Bo...
Who's Bo?
He's the guy who arranged everything.
Had me come around the night before,
tried a few guns, see which one felt right.
That was the setup right there.
One of those must have been the murder weapon.
That's how they got my fingerprints on the gun.
Had to be.
All right, so this, this... this Bo--
uh, he coerces you into doing this, all to clear a $90,000 debt.
He was going to kill my son.
Well?
A lot of "I didn't do it," and those don't count for much.
Security tape, the one that shows Lincoln pulling the trigger...
- you got it, right?
- Yeah.
Well, if Lincoln's telling the truth, then that tape is lying.
Think we should have a look, decide for ourselves.
You're clear.
If the chemicals can eat through the iron pipes,
how come they can't eat through the toothpaste tube?
It's only when the chemicals are combined that they become a corrosive.
You study chemistry or something?
Not in school.
But what you're doing up there in the infirmary,
what does it got to do with what we're doing here?
Getting through this wall is just the beginning.
There's a whole lot of real estate in between here and the outside walls.
Infirmary's the closest building to those walls...
...and the weakest link in the security chain.
Cool.
I think I've got enough grout out to bust through.
I'm going to need you to make some noise.
Is that the best you can do?
Have some faith, Papi.
Have some faith.
Shut up!
You suck!
Not one more word!
Next inmate that opens his mouth goes in the hole!
We're good.
You okay?
Work.
It's fine.
I got it.
Everything all right?
Couldn't be better.
You want to come in? We just sat down to eat.
No, I just wanted to stop by to tell you in person.
Problem solved.
What's this?
That is a transfer request.
Michael Scofield is getting shipped out tomorrow.
Have a good night.
Transcript: RaceMan
Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net