- I didn't kill that man, Michael.
- The evidence says you did.
- I was set up.
- Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
Put down your weapon!
I find it incumbent that
you see the inside of a prison cell,
Mr. Scofield.
I'm looking for someone...
Guy named Lincoln Burrows.
Why you want to see
Burrows so bad anyhow?
'Cause he's my brother.
- I'm getting you out of here.
- That's impossible.
Not if you designed the place, it isn't.
You one mixed-up cracker,
you know that?
Are we in business?
Now... it's all about timing.
Scofield. You just
as pretty as advertised.
When do we get started?
- I need your help.
- You're asking me to break the law.
I'm asking you to make a mistake.
Forget to lock up.
Come on.
We did it, Mike.
However this plays out...
I have no regrets.
Michael!
Well, if you're watching
this, that means you're safe.
I wish I could be there with you,
but as you know now, I
wouldn't have had much time.
I made my choice.
I don't regret it.
We're free now.
We're free.
_
Freedom has a price.
I died seven years ago.
Left behind a brother...
a wife...
a son.
But the dead talk...
if you listen.
They're there with you...
reaching out...
trying to tell you something.
Because not all deaths are the same.
Some are real.
Some are a story.
Question is...
do you believe the story?
Was the man who died
who you thought he was?
The dead talk...
if you listen.
_
Still tight as...
scales on a snake.
Must have friends in
high places, Bagwell.
How a cesspool like you gets his
walking papers I'll never know.
This cesspool has been a model citizen.
Model citizen.
$71.31.
Laptop.
Pack of gum, three pieces.
How about you keep that?
Whatever you bring in, you bring out.
And one last piece of correspondence.
Something really wrong with
the world when I'm receiving
dozens of letters a
week for guys like you.
Nothing compared to the e-mails.
What is it with you
killers that put the satin
on women's panties anyhow?
Lackaday!
_
Burrows!
How about you step out and pay us
the hundred grand you owe us?
Take that as a no.
Lincoln Burrows...
says no.
Big tough guy...
who made it out of the neighborhood.
And look at you now...
Back to your roots,
the way you've always been.
A small-time crook who
can't pay his debts.
We're gonna find you, you know,
and we're gonna open you up.
Lincolny-linc.
All huffin' and puffin'.
Don't you look at me like I'm trash.
My house is in order. I'm
clear with the government,
the D.O.C. and my God.
Doesn't appear to be the same with you.
Look at you, all backslid.
You're supposed to be going
up in the world as you age,
or did you not get the memo?
You don't get off my deck,
I'm gonna crack your skull.
I wouldn't do that.
Seems fate has deigned
to join us at the hip once again,
despite our mutual contempt.
Have a look-see.
Where'd you get this?
Received it on release
earlier this week.
No return address.
If you're playing me, I'll kill you.
Take a look at that postmark on that.
I may be a sophisti-cat,
but not so sophisticated
as to forge something like that.
Besides...
what angle could I
possibly have in coming here
and telling you that it
looks like your brother
might just be alive?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
It's impossible.
That's what I thought.
Why'd he send it to you?
Again, what I thought.
And then I gave the
words another look-see.
Maybe that's the answer.
"By your hand
you shall know the
glories of your Progeny
and our world will be
made right forevermore."
Hell if I know what that means.
But just like that
envelope's addressed to me,
those words are addressed
to me. Got to be!
Get out.
I'm trying to work with you here.
Is there any possible way
your brother could've survived?
My brother's dead.
Th-Then who sent this? And why?
Get out.
Least let me take my
rightful correspondence.
Oh, I made a copy, Burrows.
I knew you'd be the same
obstinate son of a beyotch
you always been, but I'd
hoped you'd seen the light.
But you are what you is
and you is what you are.
Still, I'm telling you...
fate has got us joined
at the hip somehow.
Where you in from?
Chicago.
Love Chicago.
- There you go.
- Thanks, man.
I didn't think
I was ever gonna see you again.
You didn't come to the wedding.
I mean, I figured I... I get it...
He hates me for marrying someone
other than his brother, but...
I haven't been in a good place, Sara.
My brain, it's... it's been a mess.
That's why I didn't show up.
And... I didn't want my
nephew to see me like that.
But now it's impossible to stay away.
Someone's got a sick sense of humor.
I know you want it to be true.
Losing a brother...
The massive hole that
leaves in your life.
Like the same massive
hole losing a husband is.
Maybe.
Lincoln Burrows?
Jacob.
I haven't seen you in what,
three, four years?
- Yeah.
- Uncle Lincoln!
Hey-hey! Buddy!
Oh...
so good to see you.
Did you bring me any sunken treasures?
Sunken treasures?
Oh. The dive shop.
- Panama.
- Yeah, I've been telling him stories
about being down there before
we came back to the States.
You've become kind of like
a mythological hero to
him. Let me get some beers.
- I want to know what you been up to. Okay.
- Sure, man. Yeah.
Come here.
I want you to go wash up, okay?
And then you can catch
up with your uncle.
He hasn't just mythologized you.
He mythologizes Michael, too.
It's like someone thinking
he was born to a god,
a god he's never met...
and who isn't here.
And who never will be again.
I can be pragmatic.
Michael was sick.
He was terminally sick,
and he died.
Sara...
how do you explain that?
It's Photoshop, Linc,
or something.
You got to consider the source.
This came from T-Bag.
I know you want it to be true.
I want it to be true.
How about a date tonight, model citizen?
A little well-earned love
after a long time at sea.
Jeh... boop.
Miss Dorothy.
E-mailing her undying love
from Aurora, Illinois.
I-eesh.
How about this one?
"Love Cannon Alonzo in Champaign."
Ooh. Hop on that just on the name alone.
- _
- What the hell?
Prosthetic research?
Smart girl, your Sara.
She's right.
I'm just desperate to see your face.
My life's been a mess
ever since you left.
Fallen back into my old ways.
Something you wouldn't tolerate.
But I got good in me, Michael.
I got good in me.
It'd just be nice if
you were here to... help me find it.
So... yeah.
"Ogygia."
Telling me where you are.
There's only one way to find out.
Theodore Bagwell.
And you're Dr. Whitcombe,
the man who invited me
to this mystery meeting
at 9:30 at night when the
rest of the building's closed.
I know what you've done.
That's why I don't want to be
seen associating with your sort.
Just want to know why I'm here, and...
if this has anything to do
with that special envelope
I received in the prison.
I know nothing about an envelope.
I can only tell you my work.
Targeted muscle reinnervation.
Using the brain to manipulate prosthesis
as it were a natural limb.
But as with any cutting-edge work,
funding is not easy to find, and yet,
incredibly, I got the grant
in the form of a
considerable anonymous grant
on one condition...
The first recipient of my procedure...
is you.
I can equip you
with a fully articulate prosthetic,
operationally indistinguishable
from a real hand.
All of this because
of an anonymous donor?
Someone seems to have
plans for both of us.
I've reserved an
operational lab for Monday
if you decide you are interested.
It's your hand, ultimately.
By your hand,
you shall know glories of your progeny.
What's that?
Nothing, Doc.
Come on, Michael.
You must have left me something.
Come on!
Come on.
What's going on?
Oh, my God, what happened?
I'm not sure. I'm gonna call
the police.
Hello?
I dug up Michael's
grave. He's not in it.
He... What?
Sara, someone just tried to kill me.
They've been watching.
They've been watching,
- probably for...
- Who tried to kill you?
It started at the airport. I...
There was a... a red sedan.
It started following me.
Then they... they... they swapped
down to a...
What was it? A pickup.
What color was the pickup?
Black.
Why?
Sara?
Jacob?
- Yeah.
- Behind one of
the pictures on the brick wall,
there's a hole, and there's
- a gun in it. I need you to get it.
- What?!
Right now! Right now!
Someone's coming for us!
A gun? What do you mean, a gun?
Mike?
9-1-1. What is your emergency?
I have an armed intruder in the house.
I need you to send people right away.
I don't have time. Please, come.
- Mike?
- Sara?
What's going on, Sara?
Hey.
- Mom?
- Come here.
Sara? Sara!
It's just me. There's
no one else in the house.
- What do you want?
- Get in the tub.
Who's here, Mom? What do they want?
I don't know, baby.
Okay, listen to me, if anyone comes
through that door, you don't move, okay?
I will put this through them,
and you will not be harmed.
You understand? Good boy.
Jacob?
Mom.
Go get every towel you can find.
Right now, right now.
Please, Jacob.
Okay. I think it got an artery.
Stay with me. I want you
to look at me, all right?
Don't close your eyes and
don't go to sleep, all right?
I'm gonna need you to stay with me.
I need an ambulance!
- How is he?
- The shot almost completely
severed his femoral artery so
they're trying to stabilize him.
And him?
He's seven.
How you doing, Mikey?
Something's happening, isn't it?
First, you come
and that person came in our house.
It has something to do with
my real father, doesn't it?
Why do you say that?
Because I can see it in her face.
I'm gonna need to talk to your uncle.
I'm gonna be right over there
where you can see me. Okay?
What's going on?
We've awoken something.
Something people are trying
to hide about Michael.
Your brother's dead, Lincoln.
Or is he dead? Where is the body?
Then why did he leave?
If he's been out there
for all of these years,
why did he abandon his own son?
You know I'm right.
It wouldn't be like this if
something wasn't happening.
- It wouldn't, but...
- Let's fight back.
I don't know who we're fighting.
Let's go to Yemen and find out.
To Yemen? I have a son, Lincoln.
My husband's in the ER. Right?
Look, leaving them is exactly
the wrong thing for me to do right now.
Ma'am. He's ready to see you.
One second.
I'll do it.
I'll go to Yemen.
You don't know a damn thing about Yemen.
I'll find someone who does.
See ya, Mikey.
_
I envy you.
You changed your life around.
A man gets tired of
living a profligate life.
So I took up jihad. Real jihad,
not that madness that
you see on the news.
War within.
The spiritual struggle
to clean up your act.
Finding and serving God.
That's good, man.
The world needs it, Linc.
I mean we're, uh, we're small here
but we do what we can
to help the peace efforts
in the Middle East.
Working on anti-radicalization
campaigns here at home.
Like I said, the struggle.
That's why I'm here.
If I needed to get to Yemen,
that something you could help me with?
I thought he was dead.
So did everyone.
But Ogygia?
I mean, that's for heavy hitters,
political prisoners.
In Yemen, it doesn't come any worse.
I mean, do you know what it
would take to stage a death?
Not to mention keeping
a man who is not dead
under the radar for seven years.
Some very powerful players.
Sayed, what do you make
of this mosque right here?
Aksa Mosque. It's one of
the main ones in Sana'a.
- It's very distinct.
- Ah.
Sightlines seem pretty consistent
with what it would probably be
from the prison to the mosque.
Now, you ask me, that photo's legit.
Then that's the
building my brother's in.
Easiest way to find out is
to call the prison and ask.
Mafi Michael Scofield.
Shukran.
There's no Michael Scofield.
Punch up an image from the Internet.
Michael Scofield.
Send it to the prison.
Maybe he's under a different name.
Listen, Linc,
I got to say something, man.
Man, you got to slow your roll.
Yemen is in a civil war.
They're really close to collapse.
It's no place for a white
man with an American passport,
no command of Arabic, to
just show up on a whim.
And yet, apparently, my brother did.
Got a picture. Your
brother's intake photo
from the Fox River Penitentiary.
Here's his DMV photo
and here's a photo from
his old workplace Web site.
It's not him.
None of them are.
Someone's erasing him from history.
- Lincoln, where are you going?
- Hotel, to grab my stuff,
- then the airport.
- Hey, listen.
You're not going to Yemen.
- Stop me.
- You won't make it three days.
We need to go through
the proper channels.
The proper channels?
Someone's erasing his existence.
Who does that? Who has that ability?
I'm telling you, Michael's caught
in the middle of something big.
What if he's not caught in the middle?
What are you saying?
Michael has never been anyone's sucker.
He's always been in control. Always.
You saying he faked his own death?
I'm saying you need to look
at all of the possibilities
before you walk into a war zone.
I wasn't sure you'd come.
Sometimes a man has
to surrender to fate.
See what it has in store for him.
We'll need to put you under.
No, no, no. I don't do
general anesthetic, compadre.
It's mandatory for a
procedure like this.
You'll forgive me
if I have a problem lying unconscious
before a man with sharp
items at his disposal.
It cannot be done without
a general anesthetic.
Oh, I've done it before, friend.
And look what it got you.
You do anything untoward to
me while I'm under and I'll...
You are the last man I'd run afoul of.
- Okay?
- Mm.
Oh, fate, you mysterious bitch.
Why you doing this to me?
Hi. Dry cleaning. Nice jacket.
Thank you, sir.
Have a good day.
What the hell was that for?
Sucre, what the hell are you doing here?
C-Note told me what's going on.
He tell you to talk me out of it?
No. I'm coming with you.
You're not coming.
Michael's my best friend. If he's alive,
if he's in trouble, I want to help.
Don't you have a job or something?
Yeah, on a tramp. Not great work,
but hey, I'm an ex-con, right?
Tramp?
Yeah, I've been riding her for a while.
What are you, a pimp?
What? No. No, no, no.
A tramp is a freelance cargo ship.
We go to Hong Kong, Spain, Buenos Aires,
basically wherever the boss tells us.
Corrupt son of a bitch.
Well, I suggest you
get back on that tramp,
- 'cause you're not coming.
- I'm telling you,
- I can help!
- Listen to me, this is the Middle East.
Lots has changed. I'm an
international hitter now.
A raconteur.
I don't think that means
what you think it means.
Don't speak to me like I don't
know French, I know French.
And I'm brown, that's something.
I'll fit in better over there
than you will, snowflake.
I decided I was wrong when I said
you would be dead inside of three days.
You go over there, you'll
be dead inside of one.
But with me, we have
people at the mosque
that have worked over there,
people with legal connections
that can get us inside of that prison.
Hold on. You're not
saying he gets to go.
He's not any browner than I am.
_
Huh?
No?
I managed to pick up a little Arabic
while I was serving in Iraq.
This is the final boarding
call for Flight 39
to JFK, connecting to Yemen.
This is the final boarding...
Listen, man.
There's gonna be a time
when I'm gonna need you.
You better find him.
And you better call me when you do.
I will.
You really got contacts?
Contacts with contacts.
Could just follow 'em into the bathroom,
ragdoll him in one of stalls
and be done with it.
Then we'd have a body to deal with.
And we want him utterly
and irrevocably gone from this world.
Where no amount of digging
will bring him back.
_
We're the only ones
coming into the place.
Yeah, the country's falling apart.
Everyone wants out.
Who's that contact again?
A woman named Sheba.
Our handler.
She helps us track
Americans that come in
to fight the jihad fight.
Welcome to the civil war.
Mr. Franklin,
Ms. Sheba sent me to collect you.
As-salaam alaikum.
Wa alaikum as-salaam.
Uh, this way, gentlemen. Follow me.
_
Yemen very dangerous.
You never know who's
enemies, who's friends.
Everyone scratching each other's backs.
ISIL is starting to attack the city.
They have been building up
out in the desert for months.
If they... take the city,
they will kill all the secularists,
install Sharia law.
Huh. You know.
You don't seem worried.
I scratch backs, too, my friend.
No, no, no, no. This isn't right.
Hey, wait a minute,
this-this isn't the address.
- I get cigarettes.
- No, no, you don't.
You take us straight to
the address right now!
I-I get cigarettes.
Linc, this is a setup.
Grab your bag now.
_
Greetings from the U.S.
prison system, bitches.
What is it?
Someone set us up.
Come quickly.
Or we'll all be dead!
Go, go. She's one of us.
Come on, grab your
bag. Come on, let's go!
How did you find us?
A contact at the airport saw you
get into the wrong taxi.
You're lucky I found you.
This is very radicalized neighborhood.
Whoever set you up couldn't
have set you up in a worse way.
Throw your phones out the window.
I don't want anyone tracking us.
Do it!
Sheba, this is Lincoln.
Lincoln... Sheba.
You've been made whole, Mr. Bagwell.
You're free to go.
Not till you tell me
what you've put in me.
You feel an unease, do you?
I'd venture that's what's
always been in you since birth.
Your soul. I just put
the hardware into you.
You're the thing that runs it.
- Who's behind...
- Nobody!
Nobody's behind this.
What does that mean?
I got a single word. That's it.
Just... my benefactors ID'd
themselves by a single word.
Outis.
I looked it up.
It's Greek for "nobody."
That's who your
benefactor is, Mr. Bagwell.
Nobody.
_
Okay.
Who's this?
Omar has connections in Ogygia Prison.
He says he can arrange a visit.
That mean Michael's in there?
There's apparently an American
in there matching
your brother's description.
There's just one thing.
Arranging such a visit
is hard. Very difficult.
- Comes at a price.
- Money's not a problem.
Not money.
Your passport.
My passport?
What, did...
- you want to hold it?
- No. Straight trade.
Visit for your passport.
Uh, U.S. passport is like gold here.
A few changes, and it can
be a ticket to freedom.
Don't do it, Linc.
Mm-mm.
I know it is not ideal, but...
ideals as of right now
are history in Yemen.
You cannot get out of the country
without a passport.
Don't do it.
Inshallah...
you will see your brother soon.
I told myself I'd never
step foot in another prison.
As long as we walk out of it.
_
There's no Michael Scofield.
It was a scam to get my passport.
Omar is one of my
most trusted operators.
Listen, lady. Trust doesn't seem to mean
a whole lot in this country.
Give me a second, okay?
I'll figure out a way
to work this thing out.
An image.
Right? The one that they sent to you?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Do you have it?
Look.
There.
Kaniel Outis.
Yes, Kaniel Outis. Is he here?
He says, yes, the man
in the picture is here
and we can see him, but only
'cause we're dealing with Sheba.
Why did you say that name?
Because of my brother's jacket.
Thought you were on the
right side of God on this.
Sheba. No, hey, hey. Sheba...
Hey. Kaniel Outis
is a big-time terrorist.
They got him in here for murder.
He's been working with ISIL
trying to take down the government.
Come on, C.
You know that's not Michael.
Well, whoever he is...
...we're about to meet him.
What was my father like?
My real father.
Michael Scofield...
...was like a storm.
Grab the camera.
I want to prove he's alive.
He was beautiful
and frightening
and mysterious.
And he would show up in your life
out of the clear blue sky
and then he would
disappear just as quickly.
But storms, they can come back.
Can't they?
Mm-hmm.
Question is, if they come back,
is it the same storm,
or has something changed?
Michael.
New tats.
What do you mean, new?
We're gonna get you out of here.
My name isn't Michael.
And I don't know who you are.
Sorry.
_
Michael.
Michael, talk to me. Michael...
Mike.
Mike! What are you doing, damn it?!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net