Hey, man, look at the sad sack
I found moping around the lobby.
- Hey.
- Hey, there, Walt.
- How you doing, buddy?
- Good.
Listen, I'm sorry to drop in on you
out of the blue.
- No, no, no.
- If it's a bad time, I could--
No. I'm just kind of settling into the new
digs here. What do you think?
It is very nice.
- Yeah. Congratulations again.
- Yeah.
- We're all very proud of you.
- Oh, well, thanks.
My days of chasing dirt-balls is over.
But I'll tell you what, being a boss...
...own kind of grind,
you know what I'm saying?
Steve, would you mind if.... I've gotta
run something by Hank, if it's all right.
Yeah. Yeah, hey, somebody's
gotta go chase the bad guys.
- Walt, it's a pleasure seeing you again.
- Thanks again, Steve.
- Appreciate it.
- Sure.
Hey. Look at that.
Jesus, Walt.
- That's nice. Let me see that.
- Yeah.
Wow, that's beautiful.
- Was it a birthday present?
- Yeah.
Well, I mean, not really.
I bought it for myself.
- Hey, well, have a seat.
- Thanks.
New car, new watch.
Good for you.
With all the curveballs
that were thrown at you this year...
...you deserve to treat yourself.
I mean, as long as you got
the money to spend, that is.
So how's Sky?
Actually, she went to work
this morning.
She wanted to.
She said she needed to, you know,
keep her mind occupied, and....
- That's good. Great, actually.
- Yeah.
I mean, as long as you're all right
with her being on her own and stuff.
Yeah, well, you know,
I'm right there with her most of the time.
And Mariano kind of keeps an eye
on her when I'm not, so....
- Good.
- Yeah.
And what about the whole idea
of talking to somebody?
You know, Marie goes off about Dave
like he's a rock star shrink, you know?
They come in like zombies, out
like larks, you know what I'm saying?
That's great.
Actually, she already found someone.
Yeah. Peter....
I don't know why I'm drawing a blank
on his last name. Peter....
Anyway, he's out in Rio Rancho.
He's supposed to be top-notch.
Good, good. I'm glad you're on it. That's
not something you wanna let fester.
No. No, you don't. You don't.
Hank, I just....
I wanted to thank you and Marie
for watching the kids.
No, it's-- It really is--
No, it's nice of you...
...and I'd like to come by tonight
and see them, if that's all right.
Of course. What do you mean?
You don't have to ask that.
It's great having them.
They're great kids.
I appreciate that.
I do.
Something else
on your mind there, Walt?
Walt, feel free to, you know....
Skyler doesn't love me anymore.
And I don't know what to do, Hank.
I don't.
She....
She says that I'm a bad influence
on the kids...
...and that I'm not....
- Not good for them.
- Jeez, Walt.
No.
She thinks I'm a bad father.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I mean, Sky and you
got your issues...
...but that there, that's.... That's....
I mean, I'm no....
I'm not an expert on parenting or
anything, but from where I'm sitting...
...I just don't see it, you know?
I mean, I....
I think you're great with the kids.
You're a provider,
a role model, you know?
Hell, the guts you showed
going toe-to-toe with cancer...
...that alone, that's an inspiration
to me, you know?
- No, I've made mistakes, you know?
- Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Listen, I'm gonna get a coffee.
You want a coffee?
- Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
- I'm gonna have a cup of coffee.
I'm gonna give you a moment
to just get it together there.
You want cream and sugar?
Yeah, yeah. Hank, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
That-- Cup of coffee, right?
All right.
Just take a moment. Take a moment.
You know, you two
are really great together.
Take it from me, buddy,
it's always darkest just before the dawn.
Yeah.
What is this place? What is this place?
What are we doing here?
- Get me the table.
- I can't be here.
My daughter, my little girl,
she's gonna be home soon.
What? What are you doing?
- Mike, Mike, Mike....
- Shut up!
Give me her phone.
All right, Lydia.
My friends here don't know you
like I do...
...so they are very kindly
giving you one last chance.
There's your script. Study it.
In about 30 seconds, I'm gonna dial
Agent Schrader on your line here...
...and you're gonna pass along
this information...
...and then we'll see what we see.
But here are the rules:
If you yell for help, try to give the man
some kind of coded message...
...or otherwise tip him off...
...I am gonna pull out my pistol
and shoot you in the head.
Same goes for panicking,
breaking down into tears.
Remember how you like to do that?
If it happens this time,
I am going to pull my pistol out...
...and I am going to shoot you
in the head.
Look at me, not at them.
Lydia, look at me.
If you make Schrader suspicious
in any way...
...any way at all,
tell me what's gonna happen next.
- You'll pull out your gun and shoot me.
- And where will I shoot you?
- In the head.
- In the head. That's right.
And it's a pistol, not a gun.
I'm expecting precision here.
We up and running?
Yeah. Computer's set.
Okay, Lydia.
If you ever needed to give
the performance of a lifetime...
...it's now.
You're up.
ASAC's office.
Hi. Lydia Rodarte-Quayle
calling for Agent Schrader.
I'm sorry. What's this regarding?
Madrigal Electromotive.
Lydia Rodarte Quayle
...
Hold, please.
Hank, Lydia Rodarte-Quayle
on line one.
Hank Schrader.
How can I help you, Ms. Quayle?
Well, this is kind of an odd....
It's just that I was in our warehouse,
supervising a shipment of chemicals...
...when I noticed a device on the bottom
of one of our barrels of methylamine.
- A device?
- Yeah. I guess you'd call it that. I mean...
...I'm certainly no expert,
but it looks to me like some kind of a....
A tracking device or a GPS.
So I was just wondering
if maybe your people put it there.
Not that it's any of my business, but
the last thing I wanna do is interfere...
...with a law enforcement operation
or a sting...
...or whatever you call it.
So, I don't know...
...maybe you could
give me some guidance?
Well, I'll tell you what.
Set that barrel aside for me,
if you would...
...and I'll look into it
and get back to you.
And in the meantime,
mum's the word, all right?
Yeah. All right. Sure thing.
Okay, great.
Thanks for the call, Ms. Quayle.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Gomey, come here, would you?
- Yeah?
- Hey, man.
You know anything about GPS trackers
on a methylamine barrel?
Madrigal Houston, I'm talking about.
Nope. Nobody from my team
planted anything. Why?
Oh, I don't know. I figured as much.
All right. Thanks.
I know what you're thinking,
but I didn't do it.
- I'm telling you, I didn't plant that thing.
- Shut up.
And there you have it, like I said.
All right. So now what?
It's not the DEA's, so Schrader's
probably thinking some crew planted it...
...looking for a weak spot
to pull a heist.
He's gonna send a team
over to that warehouse.
He's gonna wire it out the wazoo.
Bugs, cameras, the whole nine yards.
So the warehouse is too hot.
Her supply is useless to us now.
It depends on how fast Schrader
can get his guys there.
We're 900 miles closer, after all.
I say we keep listening,
suss out how much time we have.
If it's at least 12 hours,
then we head down there...
...use her security code
to gain access...
...and we take every barrel we can.
U-Haul can only take six or seven
before the suspension gives out.
It's a stopgap. But right now,
it's the best we can do.
Well, what about her?
You two drive the barrels back tonight.
I'll deal with her.
No! No, no, no.
You're making a mistake.
This was not me!
I swear to God I didn't do it!
I don't know.
Sounds like she's telling the truth to me.
She has a gun to her head, kid.
Everyone sounds like Meryl Streep
with a gun to their head.
I'm sorry, Jesse.
You're the one who wanted
to put it up to a vote.
It's two against one.
No. No! You can't kill me! Come on!
I swear I didn't do anything!
Janice, give me Doughty
in the Houston office, will you?
You got it.
Hank Schrader for Mr. Doughty.
He's on the line.
Hey, Erol. Please tell me you guys
didn't do something as lamebrained...
...as put a GPS tracker on the outside
of a barrel of methylamine.
One earmarked for the
Madrigal warehouse in Houston?
Who's asking?
Did someone find them?
Jesus. Are you shitting me?
Since when do you put a GPS tracker...
- ...on the outside of a barrel?
- We didn't have time to go in...
...with hazard suits, Hank.
They were about to ship.
We epoxied them to the bottom.
They were well-hidden.
Oh, really? Well, not well-hidden
enough. How many barrels you tag?
All of them. All the ones
headed to the warehouse, anyway.
Christ. All right. Well, sit tight.
Let me figure out how to play this.
Next time, a little communication first,
all right?
- Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
- Asshole.
Aside-- Aside from the fact...
...that we almost killed this woman,
all of those barrels are already marked.
We solve the problem we can.
This has not changed the equation
one iota for her.
Oh, come on! You are not seriously
still considering killing me?
I saved you! If it weren't for me,
we'd all be in jail right now.
I hate to say it, but she's right, Mike.
She saved our asses
by finding that thing.
She is saving herself.
She's a loose cannon.
I am telling you, she will turn a gun or
a badge on us the first chance she gets.
The woman put a hit out on me.
Seriously?
Wait. A hit? What? Like the mafia?
Yeah, like the mafia.
Hey! You still need methylamine,
don't you? Right?
You wanna talk methylamine?
Then tell your partner to stop
threatening me, and let's talk.
Talk about what? You heard.
You can't even get us a single barrel.
Who said anything about barrels?
I'm talking about an ocean
of the stuff.
Just give him a minute, would you?
Trust him.
"Trust him."
Okay. So, let's hear it.
Not without a guarantee that once
I tell you how to get what you want...
- ...I won't be killed anyway.
- Fine. You have my word.
- Not good enough.
- Look, lady--
- Do you have children?
- That has nothing to do with this.
It's not a trick question.
Why don't you just answer it?
Yes, I have children. So what?
You think that somehow
because we're both parents...
...that I won't let my partner
do what's necessary?
- Swear on their lives.
- Oh, what?
Swear on your children's lives
that I won't be harmed.
Otherwise, how can I trust you?
Look, you're a smart businesswoman.
You understand the concept
of leverage.
- Please don't patronize me. I hate that.
- You have none.
But trust has to work both ways, Lydia.
Is it true that you put a hit out on Mike?
- Yes.
- Why?
I was scared.
- Of Mike?
- Not at first.
There are men who used to work
with Gus Fring in custody now.
Nine of them. They know everything
about me. Everything.
Some of them even know about you,
assuming you're the master chemist...
...they're always talking about.
And if it's these nine
that you're worried about...
- ...why put the hit on Mike?
- I had no choice.
I'm not going to prison and have my
daughter raised in a group home.
Do you have any idea
what those places are like?
I gave him a list of names...
...but instead of handling it,
he's protecting them.
So I hired someone else.
At that point, there was no option...
...but to add Mike to the list.
This ocean of methylamine...
...that you claim
you can get your hands on...
...how much are we
talking about, literally?
How does 24,000 gallons sound?
Once a week, on a Wednesday, a freight
train leaves the Port of Long Beach...
...loaded with industrial chemicals.
There's always at least one tanker car
full of methylamine...
...which we import from
a manufacturer in Guangzhou.
The train travels east
through Arizona...
...stops at a rail yard
outside Flagstaff...
...where it gets broken down and rebuilt.
But the methylamine always moves on...
...destined for our pesticide concerns
in Texas and Oklahoma.
Which means that it passes
right through your home state.
There's a remote three-mile stretch
here in McKinley County.
That's where you do it.
That's where we do what exactly?
Get your methylamine.
- Like, rob it? Like Jesse James?
- You want the stuff?
I'm offering you enough
to fill a swimming pool.
You are offering us a quick trip
to prison. That's what I'm hearing.
Stopping a train, post 9/11?
You have any idea how many alarms
that'll set off between here and D.C.?
None, if you do it right here.
If a freight train is stopped in transit...
...anywhere other than
the usual yards or depots...
...absolutely, a signal will alarm
the FRA and the TSA Surface Division...
...at the Department of Homeland
Security. But what you don't know...
...and I do, because my job requires me
to keep track of my buyers' shipments...
...this is dark territory.
- What's that?
- Train-speak for an area of no contact.
It's a dead zone.
No automated supervision system,
no alarms, no contact with control.
What about cell phones?
- Crew could just call the cops.
- No cellular either.
I'm telling you, it's the perfect place.
You'd have time enough
to stop the train...
...siphon off as much methylamine
as you can carry...
- ...get away before the police are called.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Assuming we can stop
a moving train...
...how do we know we have the right
one? And which tanker car is which?
I can't believe that they would
advertise their contents.
Once the train gets rebuilt in Flagstaff...
...a final manifest gets uploaded
to my company's server.
I'll have it for you sometime
between midnight and 2 a.m.
That'll give you at least
six hours of lead time.
Keep in mind, I'm taking a huge risk
supplying this information.
I expect to be paid.
We can talk percentages later.
You know what this means, don't you?
We've gotta off the crew.
How do you figure?
If we don't, the engineer's
gonna call the cops...
...as soon as he gets out of the
dead zone. It's only three miles long.
- We're way out in the boonies.
- I don't care if it's in the Gobi Desert.
Once they get word,
the FBI and Homeland Security...
...are gonna swoop down with choppers
on us so fast, it'll make our heads spin.
And there is no hiding
in that open country.
- How many in the crew?
- Just two.
- An engineer and a conductor.
- Assuming there are no security guards.
No guards. It's not like
we're carrying nuclear warheads.
Wait. Two guys.
Can't we just tie them up or something?
And then what? Even if we wear a mask,
we're leaving two witnesses behind.
Bottom line, I have done this
long enough to know...
...that there are
two kinds of heists:
Those where the guys
get away with it...
...and those that leave witnesses.
Give me a break.
You guys were gonna murder me.
I thought you were professionals.
Can you say "ASAC"?
"ASAC." Can you say that?
Say, "ASAC Schrader."
If those turn out to be her first words,
I will beat you with my shoe.
- Don't listen to him, Holly.
- I'm just telling it like it is, babe.
Boss man. I'm the boss man.
Say, "Boss man."
Am I the boss man? I'm the boss.
Hey, that better be something from
a boob instead of some fake soy crap.
- Yeah, yeah.
- My little girl...
- Your little girl.
- ...deserves the real McCoy.
- No. See?
- Okay.
She doesn't want it.
No, she wants me.
She wants me.
Yeah, my little girl,
because I'm not giving her back.
Yeah, I know.
What about Emo McGee?
Has he come out
of his room today?
Barely.
When he does, he barely talks.
Yeah, well, what do you expect,
you know?
His parents treat him
like he's a baby there.
Flynn, do you want me to heat up
some of that lasagne...
...to hold you over till dinner?
No.
Hey, I picked up Heat on Blu-ray.
Wanna watch it with me later?
No. And you can keep
talking about me now.
Well, if no one else is gonna
offer an opinion, I will.
We do it the old-fashioned way.
We hit skid row, the Crystal Palace,
all the halfway houses...
...scrounge up about a dozen skells,
put them to work smurfing cold pills.
You mean switch back
to a pseudo cook.
You're the chemist. Admittedly,
it's gonna cut down on our output.
Like a factor of four or five.
It also means
that we will eat $80,000...
...we just invested
in our new lab equipment...
...which is only good for a P2P cook.
You know, I don't have to do
the math to know...
...that we'd be making
a fraction of the profit.
And making less money
is better than making nothing.
Oh, yeah, Mike?
Well, why don't you tell us why?
Why is making nothing
not an option?
- Walter--
- Let me tell you why.
It's because of your nine guys
in lockup, right?
You broke it, you pay for it. And we've
talked about this plenty already.
Well, maybe we better
talk about it a little more...
...because what it sounds like you're
telling me, Mike, is that from now on...
...we have no choice
but to do this piddling pseudo cook...
...so that we can pay back
your guys.
Or else what? Or else they're gonna
rat on us, and we end up in prison.
Yeah? And it sounds like
what you're telling me, Walter...
...is that you wanna do this heist...
...even if it means killing
a couple of innocent men.
That what you want?
You know, I don't know why you insist
on putting words in my mouth here.
What if we can rip off that train,
and no one ever knows it got robbed?
Maybe.
Just maybe.
It'll come from that direction.
Seven seventy-five.
Eight hundred.
Eight fourteen.
Wait a minute.
It's perfect. Yeah, we do it here.
We do it right here.
How are we looking, Mike?
All clear.
Copy that.
Go down, go down.
You got it. That's good, Fernando.
Hey.
- This one.
- Right.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- What's your name again?
- Todd.
Todd, on the day, are you gonna be able
to make this climb?
Yes, sir. I'll be ready.
All right.
- You mind if I ask you a question?
- No. Go ahead.
Well, I get why we want the tank
for the methylamine.
But why this other one for the water?
Well....
Jesse, it's your idea.
You wanna fill him in?
It's all about the weight, yo.
The tanker we're gonna hit gets weighed
when it gets loaded in Long Beach...
...and then again
when it's unloaded in Texas.
If the weights don't match...
...the train company's
gonna know it got robbed.
Okay.
Boosting methylamine from a train
is, like, a major rap.
The point is, no one other than us can
ever know that this robbery went down.
Nobody. You got it?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
With all that said,
the whole thing relies on us...
...replacing the weight of methylamine
we steal with the same weight in water.
So they'll never know
we hit them. Cool.
Aqueous methylamine is water-based,
yet it weighs slightly less than water.
We will be removing a thousand gallons
of methylamine from the tanker car...
...but replacing it with about nine-tenths
of that volume in water...
...which comes to 900.24 gallons.
Actually, Jesse,
let's make that an even 920...
...to account for spillage
and whatever will remain in the hose.
- Yeah.
- How we doing, by the way?
- Eight fifty. We're almost there.
- All right.
Won't they figure they got robbed,
getting watered-down methylamine?
Well, out of 24,000 gallons...
...it'll only amount to about
four percent dilution, so....
But, yes, you're right.
They will notice.
At which point, they will blame China...
...for sending
a marginally weaker batch.
Damn, you guys thought
of everything.
Flynn.
Flynn, open the door.
Just come out and talk to me.
I'm staying. That's all I have to say.
- What's going on?
- You got what you wanted, that's what.
Congratulations.
It's me. Open up.
Come on, Junior.
I'm not gonna ask twice.
What?
You know what.
Are you seriously kicking me out
of my own house?
Are you seriously doing that?
We are not kicking you
out of anywhere, son.
We love you. And this is your house
as much as it is ours.
But your mom and I need some time
alone, and you know that.
- We explained that to you.
- You haven't explained jack shit.
You want me out?
Explain to me why.
Why do I have to go
to Uncle Hank's?
Give me the exact reason
or I'm not going anywhere.
This is not gonna be a debate.
What's going on?
Why can't anybody tell me anything?
I want one good reason.
Because we're your parents
and you're our child.
That's reason enough.
Now, please, do as I ask.
Now.
It'll pass. He'll understand.
Don't start, Walt.
I won't change my mind about you.
Ever.
Well, I don't accept that.
You're my wife.
I'm not your wife, I'm your hostage.
But since you insist
on keeping me imprisoned...
...I'll make you a deal.
I will launder your money,
I'll keep your secrets...
...but the kids will stay
at Hank and Marie's...
...where they have
a chance of being safe.
I think you've seen too many movies.
Our children are not in danger.
Just a couple of days ago...
...you told me that a man
held a gun to your head.
You said it like it was a point of pride.
There's nothing you can say
that'll convince me...
...there won't come a day
that somebody will knock on that door...
...looking to harm you or me
or all of us.
And when that day comes,
the children cannot be here.
You agree to that...
...and I will be whatever kind of partner
you want me to be.
Okay.
By the way...
...you're visiting a therapist
from Rio Rancho. Peter.
Last name is up to you.
Out burying bodies?
Robbing a train.
- Yeah?
- It's me.
I've got it.
Okay, Mr. White, everything's set.
Hey, Wallace! Up ahead!
Stop the train now!
Stop!
Stop the train!
Now. Go, go, go.
Jesus. Thank God you guys
weren't asleep at the switch.
It'd be like pancake city out here.
Man.
Hey, you believe this?
I mean, shit fire
and save the matches.
Talk about bum luck.
Hey, man, I'm sorry to
put you guys out like this.
What's the trouble with it?
No clue. I was just driving
down the road.
All of a sudden, the old cow
just bellied up and died on me.
Either one of you guys know about
engines? Oh, of course you do.
That's why they call you
an engineer, right?
- All right.
- Think it's....
Think it's in there or something.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Probably a pretty good bet.
When was the last time
you changed the oil?
I don't know, man. I just drive it.
- Now. Go, go, go.
- We're on.
- Good?
- Yeah.
Go!
It looks good up here.
Now, hold up. There it is.
I think this is the one.
- We good?
- Yeah.
Hey, you wanna get in there,
give it a whirl?
All right, let me give it a try.
- Ready?
- Ready.
- Nothing?
- Try again.
- Nothing.
- All right.
Maybe if we all pushed?
All right. It's worth a try.
Any other ideas,
you just shout them out.
Not at the moment, I don't.
You coming?
So far, so good.
Give me a status.
We're at 300 gallons and counting.
Water is going....
Now.
Water's going in now.
We're going with water now.
- Good?
- Yeah.
All right.
One, two, three.
You did remember
to put it in neutral, right?
Yeah, man. Give me a little credit.
You sure you're not out of gas?
I got a full tank here.
Yeah, this doesn't make any sense.
Everything looks good.
Why don't we just keep going over it?
There's gotta be
something loose somewhere.
Damn, buddy. Picked a hell of a place
to break down.
I know, right? Crazy.
Hey, you know anything about engines?
Not a whole lot. I can push you off
the tracks at least.
Gee, I wouldn't want you
to mess up your ride.
- I'll go slow. Won't get a scratch.
- You'll screw up your nice shiny bumper.
Hey. We're running late because of you.
The man said it was no problem.
Come on already.
And thank you, by the way.
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely, pal. Thanks.
Jesus. Walter, we've got
a Good Samaritan on the scene.
You pull your guys
off that train right now.
We're not done yet.
The track is clear, Walter.
I said get out of there.
- Thank you, mister. Much obliged.
- Glad we could work that out for you.
- Yeah, no problem.
- You want a ride into town?
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
Walter, they are back in the locomotive.
If you do not abort right now,
you are gonna get us all busted.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Mr. White!
Hey!
Hold it! Hold it steady!
Now!
Close it off! Close it off!
Todd! Get off! Get off!
Yeah, bitch!
- We did it.
- Oh, yeah!
Oh, my....
- Okay, okay. Nice job.
- Yeah!
No! No! No!
No.