Mummy?
Mummy.
Wake up! Wake up!
Mummy!
- Wake up.
Help me, please.
I'm on a plane. Everyone's asleep.
Help me.
Hello.
My name is Jim Moriarty.
Welcome to the final problem.
You know I could arrest you.
- What for?
- Wearing a dress like that.
Would you like me to take it off?
Then I'd really have to press charges.
Press away.
- Isn't that how they got started?
Who?
Adam and Eve.
Oh, them.
And that turned out okay.
You think so?
I thought it was supposed to be
the beginning of all human misery.
Now, what was all that about arresting me?
Well, maybe not arresting you.
- No?
- I could just keep you
under close watch.
- Very close?
Uh-huh.
Shame, I was looking forward
to putting myself
into the hands of the authorities.
- You were?
- Fingerprinting.
Being searched.
Thoroughly.
Mycroft.
Why don't you come out and show yourself?
I don't have time for this.
We have time, brother dear.
All the time in the world.
Mycroft.
Who are you?
You know who.
Impossible.
- Nothing's impossible.
You of all people know that.
Coming to get you.
- There's an east wind coming, Mycroft.
You can't have got out! You can't!
- No use, Mycroft.
There's no defense and nowhere to hide.
Sherlock.
Help me.
Experiment complete.
Conclusion,
I have a sister.
This was you? All of this was you?
Conclusion two.
My sister, Eurus, apparently,
has been incarcerated from an early age
in a secure institution
controlled by my brother.
Hey, bro.
Why would you do this...
This pantomime? Why?
Conclusion three.
You are terrified of her.
You have no idea
what you're dealing with. None at all.
New information, she's out.
That's not possible.
It's more than possible,
she was John's therapist.
Shot me during a session.
- Only with a tranquilizer.
- Mmm.
Still had 10 minutes to go.
Well, we'll see about a refund.
Right, you two,
Wiggins has got your money by the gate,
- don't spend it all in one crack den.
Oh, I hope we didn't spoil
your enjoyment of the movie.
You're just leaving?
Oh, we're not staying here,
Eurus is coming and, uh,
someone's disabled all your security.
Sleep well!
Dr. Watson, why would he do that to me?
- That was insane.
- Uh, yes.
Well, someone convinced him
that you wouldn't tell the truth
unless you were actually wetting yourself.
"Someone"?
Probably me.
So that's it, is it? You're just going.
Well, don't worry.
There's a place for people like you,
the desperate, the terrified,
the ones with nowhere else to run.
What place?
221 B Baker Street.
See you in the morning.
If there's a queue, join it.
For God's sake,
this is not one of your idiot cases.
You might wanna close that window.
There is an east wind coming.
You have to sit in the chair.
They won't talk to you
unless you sit in the chair,
it's the rules.
- I'm not a client.
- Then get out.
She's not gonna stay there, is she?
- Would you like a cup of tea?
- Thank you.
The kettle's over there.
So what happens now?
Are you going to make deductions?
You're gonna tell the truth, Mycroft,
pure and simple.
Who was it said, "Truth is rarely pure
and never simple"?
I don't know and I don't care.
So there were three of us.
I know that now.
You, me...
And Eurus.
A sister I can't remember.
Interesting name, Eurus.
It's Greek, isn't it?
Mmm, yeah, uh, literally,
the god of the east wind.
Yes.
"The east wind is coming, Sherlock."
- You used that to scare me.
- No.
You turned my sister into a ghost story.
Of course I didn't.
- I monitored you.
- You what?
Memories can resurface.
Wounds can reopen.
The roads we walk have demons beneath.
And yours have been waiting
for a very long time.
I never bullied you.
I used, at discrete intervals,
potential trigger words to update myself
as to your mental condition.
I was looking after you.
Why can't I remember her?
- This is a private matter.
- John stays.
This is family.
That's why he stays!
So there were three Holmes kids.
What was the age gap?
Seven years between myself and Sherlock,
one year between Sherlock and Eurus.
Middle child. Explains a lot.
So, did she have it too?
- Have what?
- The deduction thing.
"The deduction thing"?
- Yes.
- More than you can know.
Enlighten me.
- You realize I'm the smart one.
- As you never cease to announce.
But Eurus, she was incandescent, even then.
Our abilities were
professionally assessed more than once.
I was remarkable.
But Eurus was described as an
era-defining genius beyond Newton.
Then why don't I remember her?
You do remember her, in a way.
Every choice you've ever made,
every path you've ever taken,
the man you are today,
is your memory of Eurus.
She was different from the beginning.
She knew things
she should never have known,
as if she were somehow aware of truths
beyond the normal scope.
You look funny grown up.
- What's wrong?
- Sorry.
The memories are disturbing.
What do you mean? Examples.
They found her with a knife once.
She seemed to be cutting herself.
Mother and Father were terrified.
They thought it was a suicide attempt.
But when I asked Eurus
what she was doing, she said...
I wanted to see how my muscles worked.
Jesus!
So I asked her if she felt pain.
And she said...
Which one's pain?
Then what happened?
Musgrave.
The ancestral home
where there was always honey for tea.
And Sherlock played
among the funny gravestones.
Funny how?
Come on, you lot.
They weren't real.
The dates were all wrong,
an architectural joke
which fascinated Sherlock.
♪ Who will find me?
♪ Deep down below the old beech tree
♪ Help...
- Help, succor me now,
- the east winds blow.
- East winds blow.
♪ ...east winds blow ♪
- Sixteen by six.
♪ Brother
And under we go.
- You're starting to remember.
- Fragments.
Redbeard!
Redbeard?
He was my dog.
Eurus took Redbeard and locked him up
somewhere no one could find him.
Redbeard!
And she refused to say where he was.
She'd only repeat that song.
Her little ritual.
- Redbeard!
- We begged and begged her
to tell us where he was.
She said...
The song is the answer.
But the song made no sense.
♪ Brother,
And under we go ♪
What happened to Redbeard?
We never found him.
But she started calling him
"drowned Redbeard,"
so we made our assumptions.
Sherlock was traumatized.
Natural, I suppose. He was,
in the early days, an emotional child.
But after that he was different,
as though he'd changed.
Never spoke of it again.
In time, he seemed to forget
that Eurus had ever even existed.
How could he forget?
She was living in the same house.
No.
They took her away.
Why?
You don't lock up a child
because a dog goes missing.
Quite so.
It was what happened
immediately afterwards.
She knows where he is.
We can't make her tell us.
We can't make her do anything!
After that, our sister
had to be taken away.
Where?
Oh, some suitable place,
or so everyone thought.
Not suitable enough, however.
- She died there.
- How?
She started another fire,
one which she did not survive.
This is a lie.
Yes.
It is also a kindness.
This is the story I told our parents
to spare them further pain
and to account for the absence
of an identifiable body.
And no doubt to prevent
their further interference.
That too, of course.
The depth of Eurus's psychosis
and the extent of her abilities
couldn't hope to be contained
in any ordinary institution.
Uncle Rudi took care of things.
Where is she, Mycroft?
Where is our sister?
There's a place called Sherrinford,
an island.
It's a secure and very secret installation
whose sole purpose is to contain
what we call "The Uncontainables."
- The demons beneath the road,
this is where we trap them.
Sherrinford is more than a prison,
or an asylum.
It is a fortress
built to keep the rest of the world safe
from what is inside it.
Heaven may be a fantasy
for the credulous and the afraid.
But I can give you
a map reference for hell.
That's where our sister has been
since early childhood.
She hasn't left, not for a single day.
Whoever you both met,
it can't have been her.
♪ I that am lost
Oh, who will find me?
♪ Deep down below the old beech tree
♪ Help, succor me now
The east winds blow
♪ Sixteen by six, brother
And under we go ♪
- Keep back.
- Keep as still as you can.
- What is it?
It's a drone.
Yeah, I can see that.
What's it carrying?
What's that silver thing
on top of it, Mycroft?
It's a DX-707.
I've authorized the purchase
of quite a number of these.
Colloquially it is known
as the "patience grenade."
"Patience"?
- The motion sensor is activated.
If any of us move,
the grenade will detonate.
- How powerful?
- It'll certainly destroy
this flat and kill anyone in it.
Assuming walls of reasonable strength,
your neighbors should be safe,
but as it's landed on the floor,
I am moved to wonder
if the cafe below is open.
It's Sunday morning,
- so it's closed.
- What about Mrs. Hudson?
Going by her usual routine,
I estimate she
has another two minutes left.
She keeps her vacuum cleaner
at the back of the flat.
So?
So, safer there,
when she's putting it away.
But we have to move eventually.
We should do it when she's safest.
When the vacuum stops,
we give her eight seconds
to get to the back of the flat.
She's fast when she's cleaning.
Then we move.
What's the trigger response time?
Once we're mobile,
how long before detonation?
We have a maximum of three seconds
to vacate the blast radius.
John and I will take the windows,
you take the stairs.
Help get Mrs. Hudson out, too.
- Me?
- You're closer.
You're faster.
Speed differential won't be
as critical as the distance.
Yes. Agreed.
She's further away.
She's moving to the back.
I estimate we have a minute left.
Is a phone call possible?
Phone call?
John has a daughter.
He may wish to say goodbye.
I'm sorry, Dr. Watson,
any movement will set off
the grenade. I hope you understand.
Oscar Wilde.
- What?
- He said, "The truth is rarely pure
"and never simple."
It's from The Importance of Being Earnest.
We did it in school.
So did we, now I recall.
I was Lady Bracknell.
Yeah. You were great.
You really think so?
Yes, I really do.
Well, it's good to know.
I've always wondered.
Good luck, boys.
Three, two, one.
Go!
And now the Shipping Forecast,
issued by the Met Office...
...on behalf of the Maritime and
Coastguard Agency at 0505...
Go on, son, get it up.
Better out than in.
Is it always like this?
Nah!
Thank God!
Usually it's much worse.
I might go and work in a bank.
- Is that a helicopter?
Nah. Not in this weather.
Malin, Sherrinford.
- Sherrinford.
- You hear that?
Sherrinford.
I never heard that one before.
"Sherrinford."
Forget you ever heard it.
What?
Sometimes when we're out in these waters
we get that message.
Just forget about it.
- Yeah, but we've never... It's never...
- Shh.
Who the hell are you?
- My name's Sherlock Holmes.
- The detective.
The pirate.
Golf, whisky, x-ray,
this is a restricted area.
Repeat, restricted area.
You are off course. Are you receiving?
Golf, whisky, x-ray, you are off course.
Are you receiving?
Yeah, receiving you.
This is a distress call. Repeat,
distress call, we're in trouble here.
Golf, whisky, x-ray,
what is your situation?
Golf, whisky, x-ray? Where are you now?
We're headed for the rocks.
We 're going to hit!
- Governor to the control room.
- Lockdown in progress.
Lockdown in progress.
Please proceed to designated red stations.
Hold it! Wait, wait, wait!
In the sand!
I need to speak to Mycroft.
He's in hospital,
there was an explosion.
Put me through to the hospital.
He's not conscious.
He's severely injured.
No one is even confident
he's going to pull through.
Where is his brother?
Where's Sherlock Holmes?
Missing.
No, he's not. He's here.
Sir, we found two more from the boat.
He stole our boat!
Him and another fella, with guns!
Where did you find 'em?
North side of the island, sir.
Holding cell, now!
Right, sir.
Lockdown in progress.
This is a mistake! I'm the victim here!
This man stole my boat. He's a pirate.
- Yeah, I really am.
- Please, sit down.
I don't even know who he is!
He's Dr. John Watson, formerly of the
5th Northumberland Fusiliers.
What are you doing here?
It's a hospital. Any work?
It's not a hospital.
I want eyes on Eurus Holmes.
Go straight to the special unit,
deploy green and yellow shift
on my authority.
- Sir.
I'm sparing your blushes because
we're supposed to be on the same side,
and frankly, this is embarrassing.
Oh. Doing a cavity search?
The true art of disguise,
according to your famous friend,
is not being looked at.
But I am looking at you,
aren't I, Mr. Holmes?
- Yes, you are.
But that is sort of the point, isn't it?
See, you should've been looking
at the guy you just gave your pass to.
That's the trouble with uniforms
and name badges,
people stop looking at faces.
You'd be better off with clown outfits.
At least they'd be satirically irrelevant.
Oh, you'll find the real landers
on the north shore,
tied up with two others.
- Two others?
- Mmm.
Well, it was trial-and-error.
We had to find the right waistband.
This is insane.
- This is unnecessary.
- No, your security is compromised,
and we don't know who to trust.
And that justifies dressing up?
Yes, it does!
It justifies dressing up
or any damn thing I say it does.
Now, listen to me.
For your own physical safety, do not speak.
Do not indulge in any non-verbal signal
suggestive of internal thought.
If the safety of my sister is compromised,
if the security of my sister is compromised,
if the incarceration of my sister
is compromised,
in short, if I find any indication
my sister has left this island
at any time, I swear to you, you will not!
- Say thank you to Dr. Watson.
- Why?
He talked me out of Lady Bracknell.
This could have been very different.
Are you in?
Just arriving at the secure unit.
Explain.
Door opening.
Prison within a prison.
Eurus must be allowed
the strict minimum of human interaction.
- Why?
- Since you're determined to meet her,
you're about to find out.
Eyes on Eurus Holmes.
Governor's orders.
Answer yes or no.
Has there ever been,
against my express instructions,
any attempt at a psychiatric
evaluation of Eurus Holmes?
- Yes.
- I presume the tapes are in my office.
- Your office?
- Cast your mind back.
It used to be yours.
- You haven't been down here before,
have you?
Silence of the Lambs, basically.
- You what?
- Keep your distance.
Stay at least three feet away
from the glass and all that.
- Why the headphones?
- She doesn't stop playing.
Sometimes for weeks.
Beaufiful.
- It kills you in the end.
- Aye.
Still beautiful, though.
- Door closing.
Why am I here?
Why do you think you're here?
No one ever tells me.
- Am I being punished?
- Were you bad?
There's no such thing as bad.
- Well, not good.
- Good and bad are fairy tales.
We have evolved to attach
an emotional significance
to what is nothing more
than the survival strategy
of the pack animal.
We are conditioned
to invest divinity in utility.
Good isn't really good,
evil isn't really wrong,
and bottoms aren't really pretty.
You are a prisoner of your own meat.
Why aren't you?
- I'm too clever.
Did you bring it?
Sorry?
My hair band.
Did you bring it like I asked?
I'm not one of the...
I... I don't work here.
My special hair band.
I'm not one of your doctors.
The one I made you steal from Mummy.
It was the last thing
I said to you, remember?
The day they took me away.
No.
No?
We've spoken since then.
You came around to my flat
a few weeks back.
You pretended to be a woman
called Faith Smith.
We had chips.
Does this mean
you didn't bring my hair band?
How did you manage
to get out of this place?
How did you do that?
Easy. Look at me.
I am looking at you.
You can't see it, can you?
You try and try, but you just can't see,
- you can't look.
- See what?
What do you think?
Beautiful.
- You 're not looking at it.
- I meant your playing.
Oh, the music.
I never know if it's beautiful or not.
Only if it's right.
Often they're the same thing.
If they're not always the same thing,
what's the point in beauty?
Look at the violin.
I need to know how you escaped.
It's a Stradivarius.
It's a gift.
- Who from?
- Me.
Why?
You play, don't you?
How did you know?
How did I know?
I taught you, don't you remember?
How can you not remember that?
Eurus, I don't remember you at all.
Interesting.
Mycroft told me
you'd rewritten your memories.
He didn't tell me
you'd written me out completely.
What do you mean, "rewritten"?
You still don't know about Redbeard,
do you?
Oh.
This is going to be such a good day.
She smiles at you when you come home.
Everyone we sent in there...
- Like a reflex.
-...it's hard to describe,
- it's like she...
- Recruited them.
Smiling is advertising.
Enslaved them.
She's been capable of that
since she was five.
She's an adult now.
- I warned you. I ordered you.
She's clinically unique. We had to try.
At what cost?
Happiness is a pop song.
Sadness is a poem.
What cost?
Tell me the worst thing that has happened.
She kept suggesting to Dr. Taylor
that he should kill his family.
And?
He said it was like an ear worm,
- couldn't get her out of his head.
- And?
- He left.
Killed himself.
And?
His family.
You're going to cry.
It's okay if you cry.
I don't need to cry.
I can help you cry.
Play for me.
I need to know how you got out of here.
You know already. Look at me.
Look and play.
No, not Bach. You clearly
don't understand it. Play you.
Me?
You.
Oh, have you had sex?
- Why do you ask?
- The music. I've had sex.
How?
One of the nurses got careless.
I liked it. Messy, though.
People are so breakable.
I take it he didn't consent.
- He?
- She?
Afraid I didn't notice
in the heat of the moment.
And afterwards... Well!
You couldn't really tell.
Is that vibrato or is your hand shaking?
I warned you explicitly.
No one was to talk to her alone.
- You spoke to her.
- I know what I'm doing.
You even brought her a visitor
on Christmas Day.
- I took a calculated risk.
- You gave her a Christmas present.
Remember her Christmas present?
I am aware of the dangers Eurus poses
and equipped to deal with them.
What dangers?
Eurus doesn't just talk to people.
She reprograms them.
Anyone who spends time with her
is automatically compromised.
I'm only trying to help you.
We can help each other.
Helping someone is the best way
you can help yourself.
I don't trust you.
So clearly, you remember me.
I remember everything, every single thing.
You just need a big enough hard drive.
- Sherlock.
- Not now.
- Vatican cameos.
- In a minute.
Let's continue. Did they tell you
to keep three feet from the glass?
- Yes.
- Be naughty, step closer.
- Why?
- Do it.
Step closer.
Tell me what you remember.
You, me and Mycroft.
Mycroft was quite clever.
He could understand things
if you went a bit slow, but you...
You were my favorite.
Why was I your favorite?
Because I could make you laugh.
I loved it when you laughed.
Once I made you laugh all night.
I thought you were going to burst.
I was so happy.
Then Mummy and Daddy
had to stop me, of course.
- Why?
- Well...
Turns out I'd got it wrong.
Apparently, you were screaming.
Why was I screaming?
Redbeard.
- I remember Redbeard.
- Do you, now?
Tell me what I don't know.
Touch the glass.
I put my trust in you.
My implicit trust,
as governor of this institute.
It's obvious when it all started.
Well, she was never the same
after that Christmas.
It's as if you woke her up.
That is entirely beside the point.
You had your orders and failed to act...
- Listen to the tape.
- Sorry?
Do it now. Listen.
- My sister's methods...
- Just listen.
You have no idea how I could help.
Bring me your wife. I want to meet her.
I don't need your help.
Redbeard was my dog.
I know what happened to Redbeard.
Oh, Sherlock.
You know nothing.
Touch the glass
and I'll tell you the truth.
I'll touch it too if you're scared.
I can fix her for you and then
I'll give you her straight back.
Good as new, I promise.
That's all?
What you're proposing is not...
It's not right.
Yeah, everyone who went in there
got affected.
- Enslaved, you said?
- Yes.
- One after the other?
- Dr. Watson, I think...
- Shut up.
Do you trust your wife?
One question.
That's your voice, isn't it?
Do you trust her?
You've got to stop saying these things.
If Eurus has enslaved you,
then who exactly
is in charge of this prisoner?
It's completely inappropriate.
I'm sorry.
- No.
- Very, very sorry.
You think it's a trick.
You look so...
Unsure. You're not used
to being unsure, are you?
- It's more common than you'd think.
- Look at you.
A man who sees through everything
is exactly the man who doesn't notice...
...when there's nothing to see through.
Do you see how it was done?
I know you like explanations.
Signs, you suspended the signs.
And my voice? Throat mic.
- Puts me through the speakers.
Don't you think it's clever?
- Simple, but clever.
- Transparent.
Well, you do keep asking me
how I got out of here.
Like this.
Get in here, all of you!
Stop me killing him.
No, no, stop me in a minute.
Red alert! Red Alert!
Big red bouncy Red Alert!
- Dr. Watson.
- Klingons attacking lower decks.
Also, cowboys in black hats.
Darth Vader. Don't be alarmed.
I'm here now, I'm here now.
Did you miss me? Did you miss me?
Miss me? Miss me? Miss me? Miss me?
Miss me? Miss me? Miss me? Miss me...
♪ I want to break free
♪ I want to break free from your lies
♪ You're so self-satisfied
I don't need you
♪ I've got to break free
♪ God knows
♪ God knows I want to break free
♪ I've fallen in... ♪
- Mr. Moriarty.
- Big G.
Big G means governor. Street speak.
I'm a bit down with the kids, you know.
I'm relatable that way.
Do you like my boys?
This one's got more stamina,
but he's less caring in the afterglow.
This way, please.
Smell all that insane criminality.
- Do you have cannibals here?
- Yes.
- How many?
- Three.
That's good.
People leave their bodies to science.
I think cannibals would be
so much more grateful.
Oh, isn't that sweet?
Maybe you should sit down.
I wrote my own version of the Nativity
when I was a child.
The Hungry Donkey.
It was a bit gory.
But if you're gonna put a baby in a manger,
you're asking for trouble.
- You know what this place is, of course.
- Of course.
So, am I under arrest again?
You remain a person of interest,
but until you commit
a verifiable crime, you are,
I regret, at liberty.
- Then why am I here?
- You are a Christmas present.
Ah! How do you want me?
There is, in this facility,
a prisoner whose intellectual abilities
are of occasional use
to the British government.
What, for, like, really difficult sums,
long division, that sort of thing?
She predicted the exact dates
of the last three terrorist attacks
on the British mainland
after an hour on Twitter.
That sort of thing.
In return, however, she requires treats.
- Last year it was a violin.
- This year?
Five minutes unsupervised conversation...
with you.
Me?
With me?
She has noted your interest
in the activities of my little brother.
So...
What's she got to do with Sherlock Holmes?
Whatever you're about to tell me,
I already know it's gonna be awesome!
I'm your Christmas present.
So what's mine?
Redbeard.
No...
How are you?
Bit of a lump.
True that, but you have your uses.
You see your sister?
- Yes.
- How was that?
Family is always difficult.
Is this an occasion for banter?
- Hmm. Case in point.
Are we phoning someone?
Apparently.
- What's he doing here?
- As he is told.
Eurus is in control.
Help me, please.
I'm on a plane. Everyone's asleep.
Help me.
Hello.
My name 's Jim Moriarty.
Welcome to the final problem.
- It's okay, he's dead.
- He doesn't sound dead.
This is a recorded announcement.
Please say hello
to some very old friends of mine.
Hello? I can hear you talking.
Please help me.
I'm on a plane and it's going to crash.
- What is this? We can't do this.
- Do shut up, dear.
- Is someone there?
- Is this supposed to be a game?
- Be quiet.
- Please help me.
Oh, hello, erm...
Try... Try to stay calm, just...
Tell me what your name is.
I'm not supposed to tell my name
to strangers.
Of course not, very good, but...
I'll tell you mine, my name is...
Hello?
Oh, dear. We seem to have lost
the connection.
How have you done this?
How is any of this possible?
You put me in here, Mycroft.
You brought me my treats.
What treats?
Clever Eurus! You go, girl!
How can that be Moriarty?
Oh, he recorded lots of little messages
for me before he died.
Loved it.
Did you know
his brother was a station master?
I think he was always jealous.
The girl. Where is she?
Can I talk to her again?
Poor little thing.
Alone in the sky on a great, big plane
with nowhere to land.
But where in the world is she?
It's a clever little puzzle.
If you want to apply yourself to it,
I can re-connect you, but first...
That's my wife.
That's my wife!
Oh, God, that's my wife.
I'm going to shoot the governor's wife.
Please, no.
Please, help her.
In about a minute...
Bang! Dead.
Please don't do that.
Well, you can stop me.
- How?
- There's a gun in the hatch. Take it.
You want to save the governor's wife?
Choose either Dr. Watson
or Mycroft to kill the governor.
Oh... Oh, God.
You can 't do it, Sherlock. If you do it,
it won 't count. I'll kill her anyway.
It has to be your brother or your friend.
You have to do this.
Eurus will kill her.
Doesn't appear we have a choice.
Right, then.
Countdown starting...
- How long?
- No, no, no.
The countdown is for me.
Withholding the precise deadline,
I'm gonna apply the emotional pressure
more evenly where possible.
Please give me an explicit verbal
indication of your anxiety levels.
I can't always read them
from your behavior.
I can't do this.
Can't, it's murder.
This is not murder.
This is saving my wife.
I'm particularly focused
on internal conflicts
where strategising round
a largely intuitive moral code
appears to create
a counter-intuitive result.
I will not kill.
I will not have blood on my hands.
Yes, very good, thank you.
Killing my wife is what you're doing.
No.
Okay, fine.
John.
Dr. Watson, are you married?
- I was.
- What happened?
She died.
What would you give to get her back?
I mean, if you could, if it was possible.
What would you do to save her?
Eurus will kill me.
Please save my wife.
There will, I'm afraid, be regular prompts
to create an atmosphere of urgency.
Tick-tock...
Tick, tick, tick. Tick, tick, tick...
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
What's your name?
- David.
- Are you sure about this, David?
Of course I'm bloody sure.
Nearly there.
Right, do you want to pray or anything?
With Eurus Holmes in the world,
who the hell would I pray to?
You are a good man,
and you are doing a good thing.
So are you.
I'll spend the rest of my life
telling myself that.
Please...
- Oh, God.
I know that you are scared,
but you should also be very proud.
Just do it.
Be quick.
Tick, tick, tick. Tick, tick, tick.
This is very good, Dr. Watson.
I should have fitted you
with a cardiograph.
- Good bye, David.
Tack, tock, tock, tock.
Tick, tick, tick...
Please...
I can't. Sorry, I can't do it.
Fine, it's all right.
Stop! No, no, stop.
I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- I'm so sorry.
Remember me.
- No!
You all right?
Interesting.
All right, there you go.
You got what you wanted.
And he's dead.
- Dead or alive,
it really wasn't very interesting,
but you three, you three,
were wonderful.
Thank you.
You see, what you did,
Dr. Watson, specifically,
because of your moral code,
because you don't want blood
on your hands,
- two people are dead instead of one.
- Not two people.
Yes. Sorry. Hang on.
- Oh!
What advantage
did your moral code grant you?
Is it not, in the end, selfish
to keep one's hands clean
at the expense of another's life?
You didn't have to kill her!
The condition of her survival was that
you or Mycroft had to kill her husband.
This is an experiment.
There will be rigor.
Sherlock, pick up the gun.
It's your turn next.
When I tell you to use it, and I will,
remember what happened this time.
What if I don't want a gun?
Oh, the gun is intended as a mercy.
- For whom?
- You.
- How so?
- If someone else had to die,
would you really want to do it
with your bare hands?
Would waste valuable time.
Probably just take it.
There's only one bullet left.
You will only need one.
But you will need it.
Please... Go through.
There's a few tasks for you
and a girl on a plane
who's getting very, very scared.
- Treats?
- Yes.
You know, a violin.
In exchange for?
She's very clever.
I'm beginning to think you're not.
Come on, now! All aboard.
She must be redecorating.
Is that allowed?
She's literally taken over the asylum.
We have more to worry about
than her choice of colour scheme.
Barely dry. Recent.
That's for our benefit.
As a motivator to your
continued cooperation,
I'm now reconnecting you.
Fasten your seat belts.
It's gonna be a bumpy night.
- Are you still there?
- Yes. Hello.
Hello, we're still here.
- Can you hear us?
- Yes.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I just need you to tell me where you are.
Outside, is it day or night?
Night.
That certainly narrows it down
to half the planet.
What kind of a plane are you on?
I don't know.
- Is it big or small?
- Big.
Lots of people on it?
Lots and lots, but they're all asleep.
I can't wake them up.
Where did you take off from?
And the driver's asleep.
No, I understand, but...
Where did you come from?
Where did the plane take off?
My nan's.
And where are you going?
- Home.
- No. I mean, what airport?
Enough for now! Time to play a new game.
Look on the table in front of you.
Open the envelope if you want
to speak to the girl again.
Earn yourself some phone time!
- This is inhuman. This is insane.
- Mycroft, we know.
Six months ago, a man called Evans
was murdered, unsolved, except by me.
He was shot from a distance
of 300 meters with this rifle.
Now, if the police had any brains,
they'd realize there are three suspects,
all brothers. Nathan Garrideb,
Alex Garrideb and Howard Garrideb.
All these photos are up-to-date,
but which one
pulled the trigger, Sherlock?
Which one?
What's this?
We're supposed to solve this,
- based on what?
- This, this is all we get.
Please make use of your friend, Sherlock.
I want to see you interact with
people that you're close to.
Also, you may have to choose
which one to keep.
What do you make of it?
Am I being asked to prove my usefulness?
Yes, I should think you are.
I will not be manipulated like this.
Fine. John.
John!
Yeah, I think I've seen one of these.
It's a... Buffalo gun.
I'd say 1940s. Old-fashioned sight.
No crosshairs.
Glasses, glasses.
Nathan wears glasses.
Evans was shot from 300 metres.
Kickback from a gun with this caliber...
...would be massive.
No cuts, no scarring.
Not Nathan then. Who's next?
Well done, Dr. Watson!
How useful you are.
Do you have a suspicion
we're being made to compete?
No, we're not competing. There's a plane
in the air that's gonna crash.
So what we're doing is actually
trying to save a little girl.
Today we have to be soldiers, Mycroft.
Soldiers. And that means
to hell with what happens to us.
Your priorities do you credit.
No, my priorities just got a woman killed.
Now, as I understand it, Sherlock,
you try to repress your emotions
to refine your reasoning.
I'd like to see how that works.
So if you don't mind,
I'm going to apply some context
to your deductions.
Oh, dear God!
Two of the Garridebs
work here as orderlies,
so getting the third along
really wasn't too difficult.
Once you bring in your verdict,
let me know,
- and justice will be done.
justice.
- What will you do with them?
- Early release.
You'll drop them into the sea.
Sink or swim.
- They're tied up.
- Exactly! Now there is context.
Please continue with your deductions.
I'm now focussing on the difference
to your mental capacity
a specified consequence can make.
Why should we bother?
What if we're disinclined
to play your games, little sister?
I have, if you remember,
provided you with some motivation.
We're getting through the clouds.
Like cotton wool.
Oh, that's nice.
Try to tell me more about the plane.
Why won't my mummy wake up?
So it's got to be one of the other two.
Now, Howard...
Howard is a lifelong drunk.
Pallor of his skin,
terrible gin blossoms on his red nose.
And terror notwithstanding,
a bad case of the DTs.
There's no way he could have taken
that shot from 300 meters away.
So that leaves us with Alex.
Indentations on the temple suggests
he habitually wears glasses.
Frown line suggests a lifetime of peering.
He's short-sighted, or he was.
His recent laser surgery
has done the trick.
- Laser surgery?
- Look at his clothes.
He's made an effort.
That's very good.
Excellent. Suddenly he sees himself
in quite a different light,
now that he's dumped the specs.
Even has a spray tan.
But he's clearly not used to his new
personal grooming ritual.
That could be told by the state
of his fingernails
and the fact that there's hair
growing in his ears.
So it is a superficial job, then.
But he got his eyes fixed,
his hands were steady.
He pulled the trigger, he killed Evans.
Are you ready to condemn the prisoner?
- Sherlock, we can't do this.
- Plane, remember?
Sherlock, are you ready?
- Alex.
- Say it.
Condemn him.
Condemn him in the knowledge of
what will happen to the man you name.
I condemn Alex Garrideb.
Mind the gap.
Congratulations, you got the right one.
Now, go through the door.
You dropped the other two, why?
- Interesting.
- Why?
Does it really make a difference,
killing the innocent
instead of the guilty? Let's see.
The train has left the station.
No.
That felt pretty much the same.
John, don't let her distract you.
- Distract me...
- Soldiers today.
- One more minute on the phone.
Frightened, I'm really frightened.
It's okay, don't worry,
I don't have very long with you.
So I just need you to tell me
what you can see outside the plane.
just the sea. I can see the sea.
- Are there ships on it?
- No ships.
I can see lights in the distance.
- Is it a city?
- I think so.
She's about to fly over a city
in a pilotless plane.
- We'll have to talk her through it.
- Through what?
- Hello, are you still there?
- Still here, just give us a minute.
Getting the plane away from any
mainland, any populated areas.
- It has to crash in the sea.
- What about the girl?
Well, obviously, Dr. Watson,
she's the one who is going to crash it.
No. We can help her land it.
And if we fail, she crashes into a city.
How many will die then?
How are we gonna get her to do that?
I'm afraid we're going to have to
give her hope.
Is there really no one there
that can help you?
Have you really, really checked?
Everyone 's asleep.
Won't you help me?
We're going to do everything that we can.
I'm scared. I'm really scared.
- It's all right, I...
Now, back to the matter in hand.
Coffin.
Problem, someone is about to die.
It will be, as I understand it,
a tragedy. So many days not lived.
So many words unsaid.
Etcetera, etcetera. Etcetera, etcetera.
Yes, yes, yes. And this, I presume,
will be their coffin.
Whose coffin, Sherlock?
Please, start your deductions.
I will apply some context in a moment.
Well, allowing for the entirely
pointless courtesy of headroom,
I'd say this coffin is intended
for someone of about 5'4".
- Makes it more likely to be a woman.
- Not a child.
A child's coffin would be more expensive.
This is in the lower price range,
although still,
best available in that bracket.
That was a lonely night on Google.
This is a practical and informed choice.
Balance of probability suggests that
this is for an unmarried woman
distant from her close relatives.
That much is suggested
by the economy of choice.
Acquainted with the process of death,
but unsentimental about
the necessity of disposal.
- Also the lining of the coffin...
- Yes, very good, Sherlock,
or we could just look
at the name on the lid.
Only it isn't a name.
So, it's for somebody who loves somebody.
It's for somebody who loves Sherlock.
This is all about you. Everything here.
So, who loves you?
I'm assuming it's not a long list.
- Irene Adler.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Look at the coffin.
Unmarried, practical about death.
Alone.
- Molly.
- Molly Hooper.
She's perfectly safe for the moment.
Her flat is rigged to explode
in approximately three minutes,
unless I hear the release code
from her lips.
I'm calling her on your phone, Sherlock.
- Make her say it.
- Say what?
Obvious, Sherly.
- No.
- Yes.
Oh, one important restriction.
You're not allowed to mention in any way
at all that her life is in danger.
You may not, at any point, suggest
that there is any form of crisis.
If you do, I will end this session
and her life. Are we clear?
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock, tick-tock...
What's she doing?
She's making tea.
Yes, but why isn't she answering her phone?
You never answer your phone.
Yes, but it's me calling.
Hi, this is Molly
at the dead center of town.
Leave a message.
Okay, okay.
Just one more time.
Come on, Molly, pick up.
Just bloody pick up.
Hello, Sherlock.
Is this urgent, because
I'm not having a good day.
Molly, I just want you to do
something very easy for me
and not ask why.
Oh, God, is this one of your stupid games?
No, it's not a game.
I need you to help me.
- But I'm not at the lab.
- It's not about that.
Well, quickly then.
Sherlock...
What is it? What do you want?
Tick-tock, tick-tock...
Molly, please, without asking why,
just say these words.
What words?
"I love you."
- Leave me alone.
- Molly, no,
please, no, don't hang up.
Do not hang up.
Calmly, Sherlock,
or I will finish her right now.
Why you doing this to me?
Why are you making fun of me?
Please, I swear,
you just have to listen to me.
Softer, Sherlock.
Molly, this is for a case.
It's a sort of experiment.
I'm not an experiment, Sherlock.
No, I know you're not an experiment.
You're my friend.
We're friends. But...
Please, just say those words for me.
Please don't do this.
Just... just don't do it.
It's very important. I can't say why.
But I promise you, it is.
I can't say that.
I can't... I can't say that to you.
Of course you can. Why can't you?
- You know why.
- No, I don't know why.
Of course you do.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock...
Please, just say it.
I can 't.
- Not to you.
- Why?
Because... Because it's true.
Because it's true, Sherlock.
It's always been true.
If it's true, just say it anyway.
- You bastard.
- Say it anyway.
You say it. Go on.
You say it first.
- What?
- Say it.
Say it like you mean it.
Final 30 seconds.
I...
I love you.
Molly.
Molly, please.
I love you.
- Sherlock, however hard that was...
- Eurus, I won. I won.
Come on, play fair. The girl
on the plane. I need to talk to her.
I won. I saved Molly Hooper.
Saved her?
From what? Oh, do be sensible.
There were no explosives
in her little house.
Why would I be so clumsy?
You didn't win. You lost.
Look what you did to her.
Look what you did to yourself.
All those complicated little emotions.
I lost count.
Emotional context, Sherlock.
It destroys you every time.
Now please, pull yourself together.
I need you at peak efficiency.
The next one isn't going to be so easy.
In your own time.
Sherlock.
No. No!
Look, I know this is difficult
and I know you're being tortured.
But you have got to keep it together.
This isn't torture. This is vivisection.
We're experiencing science
from the perspective of lab rats.
- Soldiers.
Tick-tock. Tickets, please.
Hey, sis, don't mean to complain,
but this one's empty.
What happened?
Did you run out of ideas?
It's not empty, Sherlock.
You've still got the gun, haven't you?
I told you you'd need it, because
only two can play the next game.
just two of you go on from here.
Your choice.
It's make-your-mind-up time.
Whose help do you need the most?
John or Mycroft?
It's an elimination round.
You choose one and kill the other.
You have to choose family or friend.
Mycroft or John Watson.
Tick, tick, tick...
- Eurus, enough!
- Not yet, I think, but nearly.
Remember, there's a plane in the sky
and it's not going to land.
- Well...
- Well what?
We're not actually
going to discuss this, are we?
I'm sorry, Dr. Watson.
You are a fine man in many respects.
Make your goodbyes and shoot him.
- Shoot him.
- What?
Shoot Dr. Watson.
There's no questioning who has to
continue from here. It's us.
You and me.
Whatever lies ahead
requires brain power, Sherlock.
Not sentiment.
Don't prolong his agony. Shoot him.
Do I get a say in this?
Today we are soldiers.
Soldiers die for their country.
I regret, Dr. Watson,
that privilege is now yours.
Shit. He's right.
He is, in fact, right.
Make it swift.
No need to prolong his agony.
Get it over with,
and we can get to work.
God!
I should have expected this.
Pathetic. You always were the slow one.
The idiot.
That's why I've always despised you.
You shame us all.
You shame the family name.
Now, for once in your life,
do the right thing.
Put this stupid little man
out of all our misery.
- Shoot him.
- Stop it.
Look at him. What is he?
Nothing more than a distraction,
a little scrap of ordinariness
for you to impress,
to dazzle with your cleverness.
- You'll find another.
- Please, for God's sake, just stop it.
- Why?
- Because on balance,
even your Lady Bracknell
was more convincing.
Ignore everything he just said,
he's being kind.
He's trying to make it easy
for me to kill him.
Which is why this is going to be
so much harder.
You said you liked my Lady Bracknell.
- Sherlock, don't.
- It isn't your decision, Dr. Watson.
Not in the face, though. Please.
I promised my brain to the Royal Society.
Where would you suggest?
Well, I suppose there is a heart
somewhere inside me.
I don't imagine it's much of a target,
but why don't we try for that?
I won't allow this.
This is my fault.
- Moriarty.
Her Christmas treat.
Five minutes' conversation
with Jim Moriarty five years ago.
What did they discuss?
Five minutes' conversation,
unsupervised.
Goodbye, brother mine.
No flowers.
By request.
Jim Moriarty thought
you'd make this choice.
He was so excited.
And here we are, the end of the line.
Holmes killing Holmes.
This is where I get off.
Five minutes.
It took her just five minutes
to do all of this to us.
Well, not on my watch.
What are you doing?
A moment ago, a brave man
asked to be remembered.
I'm remembering the governor.
Ten...
No, no, Sherlock.
Nine...
- Eight.
- You can't.
- Seven.
- You don't know about Redbeard yet.
- Six.
- Sherlock!
- Five.
- Sherlock, stop that at once!
Four.
Three.
Two...
Hello?
Hello, are you still there?
Yes. Yeah, no, I'm still here. I'm here.
You went away. You said you'd help me
and you went away.
Yes, I know. Well, I'm sorry about that.
We must have got cut off.
How long was I away?
Hours. Hours and hours.
- Why don't grown-ups tell the truth?
- No, I... I am telling the truth.
You can trust me.
- Where did you go?
- I'm not completely sure.
Um, now, I'll tell you what.
You've got to be really,
really brave for me.
Can you go to the front of the plane?
Can you do that?
- The front?
- Yes. That's right. The front.
- You mean where the driver is?
- Yes, that's it.
Okay, I'm going.
- Are you there yet?
- Yeah, I'm here.
John?
- Yeah.
Where are you?
I don't know. I've just woken up.
I'm in another cell. I just spoke
to the girl on the plane again.
- We've been out for hours.
- What, she still up there?
Yes. The plane will keep flying
until it runs out of fuel.
- Is Mycroft with you?
- I have no idea.
I can hardly see anything.
Mycroft? Mycroft?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
All right. Well, just keep exploring.
Tell me anything you can
about where you are.
The walls are rough.
They're rock, I guess.
- What are you standing on?
- Uh, stone, I think.
But listen,
there's about two feet of water.
Chains.
Yeah, my feet are chained up.
I can feel something.
Bones, Sherlock.
- There are bones in here.
- What kind of bones?
Uh, I don't know, small.
Redbeard.
Who's Redbeard?
Oh, hello. Are you at the front
of the plane now?
Yeah, I still can't wake the driver up.
That's all right. What can you see now?
I can see a river.
There's a big wheel.
All right. Well, you and I are gonna
have to drive this plane together.
Just you and me.
- We are?
- Yeah, there's nothing to it.
We just need to get in touch
with some people on the ground.
Now, um, can you see anything
that looks like a radio?
No.
That's all right. Keep looking.
We've got plenty of time.
- What's wrong?
- The whole plane's shaking.
- It's just turbulence.
There's nothing to worry about.
My ears hurt.
Does the river
look like it's getting closer?
- A little bit.
- All right, then.
That means you're nearly home.
Sherlock?
I'm in a well.
That's where I am.
I'm in the bottom of a well.
Why would there be a well in Sherrinford?
Why is there a draft?
Walls don't contract
after you've painted them.
Not real ones.
I'm home. Musgrave Hall.
Me and Jim Moriarty,
we got on like a house on fire,
which reminded me of home.
Yeah, it's just an old building.
I don't care.
The plane. Tell me about the plane, now!
Sweet Jim. He was never
very interested in being alive.
Especially if he could make
more trouble being dead.
Yep. Still not interested. The plane!
You knew he'd take his revenge.
His revenge, apparently, is me.
Eurus, let me speak
to the little girl on the plane
and I'll play any game you like.
First, find Redbeard.
I'm letting the water in now.
You don't want me to drown
another one of your pets, do you?
At long last, Sherlock Holmes, it's time
to solve the Musgrave Ritual.
Your very first case,
and the final problem.
- Bye-bye.
-  Sherlock!
♪ I that am lost
Oh, who will find me?
Sherlock!
♪ Deep down below
the old beech tree
♪ Help, succor me now
The east winds blow
John. John?
Can you hear me? John!
Help me. Help me, please.
Sherlock!
John?
- Yeah, it's flooding.
- The well is flooding.
Try as long as possible not to drown.
What?
I'm going to find you. I am finding you.
Well, hurry up, please,
because I don't have long.
It's leaning over.
The whole plane!
♪ Oh, who will find me?
♪ Deep down below the old beech tree
Three...
Eurus, you said the answer is in the song,
but I went through the song,
line by line, all those years ago,
and I found nothing.
I couldn't find anything.
There... There was a beech tree
in the grounds
and I dug, I dug,
and dug, and dug, and dug.
Sixteen feet by 6, 16 yards, 16 metres,
and I found nothing.
No one!
Sherlock?
Oh, it was a clever little puzzle.
Wasn't it?
So why couldn't you work it out, Sherlock?
Sherlock?
There's something you need to know.
Emotional context.
And here it comes.
Sherlock? The bones I found...
Yes? They're dog's bones, that's Redbeard.
Mycroft's been lying to you, to both of us.
They're not dog's bones.
Remember Daddy's allergy?
What was he allergic to?
What would he never let you have
all those times you begged?
Well, he'd never let you have a dog.
Come on, Redbeard!
Your funny little memory, Sherlock.
You were upset,
so you told yourself a better story.
But we never had a dog.
Victor.
Now it's coming.
Victor Trevor.
We played pirates.
I was Yellowbeard and he was...
He was Redbeard.
You were inseparable.
But I wanted to play, too.
Oh, God.
What...
What did you do?
♪ I that am lost
♪ Oh, who will find me?
♪ Deep down below
♪ The old beech tree ♪
- Please, let me out.
Please, someone, help me. Please!
Come on, Redbeard!
Victor.
Deep water, Sherlock,
all your life, in all your dreams.
Deep waters.
You killed him.
You killed my best friend.
I never had a best friend.
I had no one.
Play with me, Sherlock.
Play with me.
No one.
Okay.
Okay, let's play.
Hello, are you there?
I need your help.
I'm trying to solve a puzzle.
But what about the plane?
The puzzle will save the plane.
The wrong dates.
She used the wrong dates
from the gravestones
as the key to the cipher,
and the cipher was the song.
Is this strictly relevant?
Yes, it is.
I'll be with you in a minute.
The lights are getting closer.
Hush, now. Working.
Let's number the words of the song.
Then rearrange the numbered words
to match the sequence on the gravestones...
"I am lost.
"Help me, brother.
"Save my life
"before my doom.
"I am lost
"without your love. Save my soul.
"Seek my room."
Oh, God!
We're going to crash!
We're going to die!
I think it's time
you told me your real name.
I'm not allowed
to tell my name to strangers.
But I'm not a stranger, am I?
I'm your brother.
I'm here, Eurus.
You're playing with me, Sherlock.
We're playing the game.
The game. Yes, I get it now.
The song was never a set of directions.
I'm in the plane. I'm going to crash.
And you're going to save me.
Look how brilliant you are.
Your mind has created the perfect metaphor.
You're high above us, all alone in the sky,
and you understand everything
except how to land.
Now, I'm just an idiot.
But I'm on the ground.
- I can bring you home.
- No.
No, no.
- It's too late.
- No, it's not.
It's not too late.
Every time I close my eyes,
I'm on the plane.
I'm lost.
Lost in the sky, and...
No one can hear me.
Open your eyes.
I'm here.
You're not lost any more.
Now...
You... You just...
You just went the wrong way
last time, that's all.
This time, get it right.
Tell me how to save my friend.
Eurus.
Help me save John Watson.
- Help.
We just spoke to your brother.
- How is he?
- He's a bit shaken up, that's all.
She didn't hurt him.
She just locked him in her old cell.
What goes around, comes around.
Give me a moment, boys.
Um...
Mycroft, make sure he's looked after.
He's not as strong as he thinks he is.
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
Thanks, Greg.
Pete, the helicopter ready?
Let's move her, then.
Is that him, sir?
- Sherlock Holmes?
- A fan, are you?
Well, he's a great man, sir.
No, he's better than that.
He's a good one.
- You okay?
- I said I'd bring her home.
I can't, can I?
Well, you gave her
what she was looking for.
Context.
Is that good?
It's not good, it's not bad. It's...
It is what it is.
Alive! For all these years?
How is that even possible?
What Uncle Rudi began,
I thought it best to continue.
I'm not asking how you did it, idiot boy!
I'm asking, how could you?
I was trying to be kind.
Kind?
You've told us that our daughter was dead.
Better that
than tell you what she had become.
I'm sorry.
Whatever she became,
whatever she is now, Mycroft,
she remains our daughter.
And my sister.
Then you should have done better.
He did his best.
Then he's very limited.
Where is she?
Back in Sherrinford, secure this time.
People have died.
Without doubt, she will kill again
if she has the opportunity.
There's no possibility
she'll ever be able to leave.
When can we see her?
There's no point.
How dare you say that!
She won't talk.
She won't communicate
with anyone in any way.
She has passed beyond our view.
There are no words
that can reach her now.
Sherlock?
Well?
You were always the grownup.
What do we do now?
Uh, yeah.
I think you better get round here.
- P.S.
I know you two.
And if I'm gone,
I know what you could become.
Because I know who you really are.
A junkie who solves crimes to get high.
And the doctor who never
came home from the war.
Will you listen to me?
Who you really are, it doesn't matter.
It's all about the legend,
the stories,
the adventures.
There is a last refuge for the desperate,
the unloved,
the persecuted.
There is a final court of appeal
for everyone.
When life gets too strange,
too impossible,
too frightening,
there is always one last hope.
When all else fails, there are two men
sitting, arguing in a scruffy flat,
like they've always been there
and they always will.
The best and wisest men
I have ever known,
my Baker Street boys,
Sherlock Holmes and Dr. Watson.