(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(PANTING)
(ANIMAL GROWLING, MAN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(GROWLING AND SCREAMING CONTINUE)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, hello.
Are you all right?
What is it, dear? Are you lost?
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
(CROWS CAWING)
(PANTING)
- Well, that was tedious!
- You went on the Tube like that?
None of the cabs would take me.
Nothing?
- Military coup in Uganda...
- Hmm.
Hmm. Another photo of you with the...
(GROANS)
Oh, um, Cabinet re-shuffle...
Nothing of importance! Oh, God!
John, I need some. Get me some!
- No.
- Get me some!
No! Cold turkey. We agreed.
No matter what.
Anyway, you've paid everyone off,
remember?
No one within a two-mile radius
will sell you any.
- Stupid idea! Whose idea was that?
- (CLEARS THROAT)
Mrs. Hudson!
Look, Sherlock,
you're doing really well.
Don't give up now!
Tell me where they are. Please. Tell me.
- Please.
- Can't help, sorry.
I'll let you know
next week's lottery numbers.
Oh, it was worth a try.
- Yoo-hoo!
- My secret supply.
What have you done
with my secret supply?
- Hey?
- Cigarettes!
What have you done with them?
Where are they?
You know you never let me
touch your things.
(CHUCKLING) Oh!
Chance would be a fine thing.
- I thought you weren't my housekeeper?
- I'm not.
(SHERLOCK GRUNTS)
How about a nice cuppa? And
perhaps you could put away your harpoon.
I need something stronger than tea.
Perhaps 7% stronger.
- (GASPS)
- You've been to see Mr. Chatterjee again.
- Pardon?
- Sandwich shop. That's a new dress,
but there's flour on the sleeve.
You wouldn't dress like that for baking.
- Sherlock.
- Thumbnail, tiny traces of foil.
Been at the scratch-cards again.
We all know where that leads, don't we?
(INHALES DEEPLY) Mmm, Casbah Nights.
Pretty racy for first thing on
a Monday morning, wouldn't you agree?
I've written a little blog
on the identification of perfumes.
It's on the website.
You should look it up!
- Please!
- I wouldn't pin your hopes
on that cruise with Mr. Chatterjee.
He's got a wife in Doncaster
- that nobody knows about.
- Sherlock!
Well, nobody except me.
I don't know what you're talking about,
I really don't!
(DOOR SLAMMING)
What the bloody hell was all that about?
(SIGHS) You don't understand.
Go after her and apologise.
- Apologise?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, John, I envy you so much.
- You envy me?
- Your mind.
It's so placid, straightforward,
barely used.
Mine's like an engine,
racing out of control.
A rocket tearing itself to pieces,
trapped on the launch pad.
- I need a case!
- You've just solved one!
By harpooning a dead pig, apparently.
Ah! That was this morning!
When's the next one?
Nothing on the website?
"Dear Mr. Sherlock Holmes,
I can't find Bluebell anywhere."
"Please, please, please, can you help?"
- Bluebell?
- A rabbit, John!
- Oh.
- Ah, but there's more.
Before Bluebell disappeared,
it turned luminous.
"Like a fairy!"
according to little Kirsty.
Then the next morning,
Bluebell was gone!
Hutch still locked,
no sign of a forced entry.
What am I saying? This is brilliant.
Phone Lestrade,
- tell him there's an escaped rabbit.
- You're serious?
- It's this or Cluedo.
- No.
- We are never playing that again.
- Why not?
Because it's not actually possible
for the victim to have done it,
- Sherlock, that's why.
- It was the only possible solution.
- It's not in the rules.
- Well, then the rules are wrong!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Single ring.
- Maximum pressure,
just under the half-second.
BOTH: Client!
REPORTER: Dartmoor. It's always been
a place of myth and legend.
But is there something else
lurking out here?
Something very real?
Because Dartmoor is also home
to one of the government's
most secretive operations,
the Chemical and Biological
Weapons Research Centre,
which is said to be even more
sensitive than Porton Down.
Since the end of the Second World War,
there have been persistent stories
about the Baskerville experiments.
Genetic mutations.
Animals grown for the battlefield
There are many who believe
that within this compound,
in the heart of this ancient wilderness,
there are horrors beyond imagining.
But the real question is
are a{{ of them still inside?
I was just a kid.
It was on the moor; it was dark,
but I know what I saw.
I know what killed my father.
(SIGHS)
- What did you see?
- Oh, I... I was just about to say.
Yes, in a TV interview.
I prefer to do my own editing.
Yes.
Sorry, yes, of course.
Excuse me. (BLOWING NOSE)
- In your own time.
- But quite quickly.
- Do you know Dartmoor, Mr. Holmes?
- No.
It's an amazing place.
It's like nowhere else,
it's sort of bleak but beautiful.
Hmm. Not interested, moving on.
We used to go for walks after
my Mum died, my Dad and me.
Every evening we'd go out onto the moor.
Yes, good, skipping to the night that
your dad was violently killed.
Where did that happen?
There's a place, it's a sort of
local landmark called Dewer's Hollow.
That's an ancient name for the Devil.
SQ?
Did you see the Devil that night?
Yes.
(SCREAMING)
HENRY: It was huge.
Coal black fur with red eyes.
(ANIMAL GROWLING)
It got him. Tore at him, tore him apart.
I can't remember anything else,
they found me the next morning
just wandering on the moor.
My Dad's body was never found.
JOHN: Hmm.
Red eyes, coal black fur.
Enormous. Some sort of dog, wolf?
Or a genetic experiment?
- Are you laughing at me, Mr. Holmes?
- Why, are you joking?
My Dad was always going on about the
things they were doing at Baskerville.
About the type of monsters
they were breeding there.
People used to laugh at him.
At least the TV people
took me seriously.
- I assume did wonders for Devon tourism.
- Yeah... (SIGHS)
Henry, whatever did happen
to your father,
it was 20 years ago.
Why come to us now?
I'm not sure you can help me, Mr. Holmes,
since you find it all so funny!
- Because of what happened last night.
- Why? What happened last night?
- How... How did you know?
- I didn't know, I noticed.
Came up from Devon on the first
available train this morning.
You had a disappointing breakfast
and a cup of black coffee.
The girl in the seat across
the aisle fancied you.
Although you were initially keen,
you've now changed your mind.
You are, however, extremely anxious
to have your first cigarette of the day.
Sit down, Mr. Knight.
And do please smoke, I'd be delighted.
(JOHN SIGHS)
- How on earth did you notice all that?
- It's not important...
Punched-out holes
where your ticket's been checked.
- Not now, Sherlock.
- Oh, please?
- I've been cooped up in here for ages.
- You're just showing off.
Of course. I am a show-off.
That's what we do.
Train napkin you used
to mop up the spilled coffee,
strength of the stain shows
that you didn't take milk.
There are traces of ketchup on it and
round your lips and on your sleeve.
Cooked breakfast. Or the nearest
thing those trains can manage,
- probably a sandwich.
- How did you know it was disappointing?
Is there any other type
of breakfast on a train?
The girl,
female handwriting's quite distinctive,
wrote her phone number down
on the napkin.
I can tell from the angle she wrote at
that she was sat across from you
on the other side of the aisle.
Later, after she'd got off, I imagine,
you used the napkin to
mop up your spilled coffee,
accidentally smudging the numbers.
You've been over the last four digits
yourself with another pen
so you wanted to keep the number.
Just now, though, you used the napkin
to blow your nose. Maybe
you're not that into her after all.
Then there's the nicotine stains
on your fingers,
your shaking fingers. I know the signs.
No chance to smoke one on the train,
no time to roll one
before you got a cab here.
It's just after 9:15, you're desperate.
The first train from Exeter to London
leaves at 5:46 a.m.
You got the first one possible,
so something important
must have happened last night.
Am I wrong?
(INHALES) No. You're right.
You're... You're completely,
exactly right.
- Bloody hell, I heard you were quick.
- It's my job. Now shut up and smoke!
(JOHN CLEARING THROAT)
Henry, your parents both died
and you were, what, seven years old?
I know, but...
(INHALING DEEPLY)
That must be quite a trauma.
Have you ever thought that maybe
you invented this story, this...
(IN HALING)
...to account for it?
- That's what Dr. Mortimer says.
- Who?
- His therapist.
- My therapist.
Obviously.
Louise Mortimer.
She's the reason
I came back to Dartmoor.
She thinks I have to face my demons.
And what happened when you went back
to Dewer's Hollow last night, Henry?
You went there
on the advice of your therapist
and now you're consulting a detective.
What did you see
that changed everything?
It's a strange place, the Hollow.
Makes you feel so cold inside,
so afraid.
(SIGHS) Yes, if I wanted poetry,
I'd read John's emails
to his girlfriends, much funnier.
- What did you see?
- (SIGHING)
Footprints.
On the exact spot where
I saw my father torn apart.
- A man's or a woman's?
- Neither.
- They were...
- Is that it? Nothing else?
- Footprints. Is that all?
- Yes, but they were...
No, sorry, Dr. Mortimer wins, childhood
trauma masked by an invented memory.
Boring! Goodbye, Mr. Knight.
Thank you for smoking.
But what about the footprints?
Oh, well, they're probably pawprints,
could be anything, therefore nothing.
Off to Devon with you.
Have a cream tea on me.
Mr. Holmes, they were the footprints
of a gigantic hound!
- Say that again?
- I found footprints, they were...
No, no, no, your exact words.
Repeat your exact words
from a moment ago,
exactly as you said them.
Mr. Holmes,
they were the footprints
of a gigantic hound.
- I'll take the case.
- Sorry, what?
Thank you for bringing this
to my attention, it's very promising.
No, no, no. Sorry, what?
A minute ago footprints were boring,
now they've very promising?
It's got nothing to do with footprints.
As ever, John, you weren't listening.
- Baskerville, ever heard of it?
- Vaguely. It's very hush-hush.
- Sounds like a good place to start.
- Ah, you'll come down, then?
No, I can't leave London
at the moment, far too busy.
But don't worry,
I'm putting my best man onto it.
Always rely on John to
send me all the relevant data,
as he never understands
a word of it himself.
What are you talking about, you're busy?
You don't have a case.
- A minute ago you were complaining...
- Bluebell, John! I've got Bluebell.
The case of the vanishing
glow-in-the-dark rabbit.
- NATO's in uproar.
- Oh, sorry. You're not coming, then?
Oh! Okay.
Okay.
I don't need those any more,
I'm going to Dartmoor.
You go on ahead, Henry,
we'll follow later.
Sorry, so you are coming?
Twenty-year-old disappearance?
A monstrous hound?
I wouldn't miss this for the world!
(MRS HUDSON SHOUTING)
Oh! Looks like Mrs. Hudson finally
got to the wife in Doncaster.
Hmm. Wait till she finds out
about the one in Islamabad.
Paddington Station, please.
There's Baskerville.
Uh, that's Grimpen village.
So that must be...
Yes, Dewer's Hollow.
- What's that?
- Hmm?
A minefield?
Technically, Baskerville's an army base,
so I guess they've always been keen
- to keep people out.
- Clearly.
(TOUR GUIDE TALKING, IN DISTINCT)
All right. Three tours a day.
Tell your friends. Tell anyone!
Don't be strangers and remember,
stay away from the moor at night,
- if you value your lives! Take care.
- (TOURISTS LAUGHING)
It's cold.
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(HEN RY SIGHS)
That part doesn't change.
What does?
Oh, there's something else. It's a word.
(EXHALES)
Liberty.
- Liberty?
- There's another word.
In. I-N.
"Liberty In."
What do you think it means?
Eh, sorry we couldn't do
a double room for you boys.
That's fine. We're not...
- There you go.
- Oh, ta. I'll just get your change.
Ta.
(TILL BEEPING)
(COINS CLINKING)
Well, there you go.
I couldn't help noticing, on the map
of the moor, a skull and crossbones?
Oh, that.
- Pirates?
- Eh, no, no.
The Great Grimpen Minefield,
they call it.
- Oh, right.
- It's not what you think.
It's the Baskerville testing site.
It's been going for 80-odd years.
I'm not sure anyone really
knows what's there any more.
- Explosives?
- Oh, not just explosives.
Break into that place
and if you're lucky
you just get blown up, so they say.
In case you're planning
a nice wee stroll.
Ta, I'll remember.
Aye. No, it buggers up tourism a bit,
so thank God for the demon hound!
- Did you see that show? The documentary?
- Quite recently, yeah.
God bless Henry Knight
and his monster from hell.
- You ever seen it? The Hound?
- Me? No, no.
Eh, Fletcher has.
He runs the walks, the monster walks,
for the tourists, you know?
He's seen it.
That's handy. For trade.
I'm just saying
we've been rushed off our feet, Billy.
Yeah, lots of monster hunters.
Doesn't take much these days.
One mention on Twitter and woomph!
- We're out of WKD.
- All right.
What with the monster
and the ruddy prisoner,
I don't know how we
sleep nights, do you, Gary?
- Like a baby.
- That's not true. He's a snorer.
- Hey! Shh.
- Is yours a snorer?
Got any crisps?
FLETCHER: Yeah. No.
All right? All right. Take care.
Mind if I join you?
It's not true, is it? You haven't
actually seen this Hound thing?
- You from the papers?
- No. Nothing like that just curious.
- Have you seen it?
- Maybe.
- Got any proof?
- Why would I tell you if I did?
- Excuse me.
- I called Henry...
- Bet's off, John. Sorry.
- What?
- Bet?
- My plan needs darkness.
We've got another
half an hour of light...
Wait, wait. What bet?
Oh, I bet John here 50 quid that you
couldn't prove you'd seen the Hound
Yeah, the guys in the pub
said you could.
(CHUCKLES) Well, you're going to
lose your money, mate.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I seen it. Only about a month ago.
Up at the Hollow. It was foggy, mind.
Couldn't make much out.
- I see. No witnesses, I suppose?
- No, but...
- Never are.
- No, wait.
- There.
- (LAUGHS)
Is that it?
It's not exactly proof, is it?
- Sorry, John. I win.
- Wait, wait! That's not all.
People don't like going up there,
you know. To the Hollow.
- Gives them a bad sort of feeling.
- Ooh, is it haunted?
- Is that supposed to convince me?
- Nah, don't be stupid!
Nothing like that. But I reckon
there is something out there.
Something from Baskerville. Escaped
- A clone? A super-dog?
- Maybe.
God knows what they've been
spraying on us all these years.
Or putting in the water. I wouldn't
trust them as far as I could spit.
Is that the best you've got?
I had a mate once
who worked for the MOD.
One weekend we were meant to
go fishing, but he never showed up.
Well, not till late. When he did,
he was white as a sheet.
I can see him now.
"I've seen things today, Fletch," he
said, "I ain't never want to see again.
"Terrible things."
He'd been sent to some secret
army place. Porton Down, maybe?
Maybe Baskerville? Or somewhere else.
In the labs there,
the really secret labs,
he said he'd seen... terrible things.
Rats as big as dogs, he said.
And dogs, dogs the size of horses.
Uh, we did say 50?
Mmm. Ta.
(ANIMALS CALLING)
GUARD: Pass, please?
Thank you.
We got ID for Baskerville? How?
SHERLOCK: It's not specific
to this place. It's my brother's.
Access all areas. I, um...
acquired it ages ago, just in case.
(BEEPS)
- Brilliant.
- What's the matter?
- We'll get caught.
- No, we won't. Well, not just yet.
Caught in five minutes.
"Oh, hi! We just thought"
"we'd come and have a wander round
your top-secret weapons base."
"Really? Great! Come in,
kettle's just boiled."
That's if we don't get shot.
- Here you are.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Straight through, sir.
JOHN: Mycroft's name
literally opens doors.
SHERLOCK: I've told you. He practically
is the British Government.
I reckon we've got about 20 minutes
before they realise something's wrong.
- What is it? Are we in trouble?
- "Are we in trouble, sir?"
- Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
- You were expecting us?
Your ID showed up straight away,
Mr. Holmes.
Corporal Lyons. Security.
- Is there something wrong, sir?
- Well, I hope not, Corporal. I hope not.
It's just we don't get inspected here,
you see, sir. It just doesn't happen.
Never heard of a spot check?
Captain John Watson.
Fifth Northumberland Fusiliers
Sir! Major Barrymore
won't be pleased, sir.
He'll want to see you both.
I'm afraid we won't have time for that.
We'll need the full tour.
Right away. Carry on.
- That's an order, Corporal.
- Yes, sir.
(BEEPS)
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
- Nice touch.
- Haven't pulled rank in ages.
- Enjoy it?
- Oh, yeah.
(BEEPS)
(SCREECHING)
How many animals do you keep down here?
Lots, sir.
Any ever escape?
They'd have to know
how to use that lift, sir.
We're not breeding them that clever.
Unless they have help.
Ah. And you are?
I'm sorry, Dr. Frankland, I'm just
showing these gentlemen around.
Ah, new faces! How nice.
Careful you don't get stuck here,
though. I only came to fix a tap.
(CHUCKLES)
How far down does that lift go?
- Quite a way, sir.
- Mmm-hmm.
And what's down there?
Well, we have to keep the bins
somewhere, sir.
This way, please, gentlemen.
JOHN: So what exactly is it
that you do here?
LYONS: I thought you'd know, sir.
This being an inspection.
Well, I'm not an expert, am I?
Everything from stem cell research
to trying to cure the common cold, sir.
- But mostly weaponry?
- Of one sort or another, yes.
- Biological, chemical...
- One war ends, another begins, sir.
New enemies to fight.
We have to be prepared.
(BEEPING)
(SCREECHING)
Okay, Michael.
Let's try Halo 3 next time.
- Dr. Stapleton.
- Stapleton.
Yes.
Who's this?
Priority ultra, ma'am.
Orders from on high.
- An inspection.
- Really?
We're to be accorded
every courtesy, Dr. Stapleton.
What's your role at Baskerville?
(LAUGHS)
Accorded every courtesy,
isn't that the idea?
I'm not free to say. Official Secrets.
Oh, you most certainly are free.
And I suggest you remain that way.
I have a lot of fingers
in a lot of pies.
I like to mix things up.
Genes, mostly.
Now and again, actual fingers.
- Stapleton, I knew I knew your name.
- I doubt it.
People say there's
no such thing as coincidence.
What dull lives they must lead.
Have you been talking to my daughter?
Why did Bluebell have to die,
Dr. Stapleton?
- The rabbit?
- Disappeared from inside a locked hutch,
- which was always suggestive.
- The rabbit?
Clearly an inside job.
- Oh, you reckon?
- Why?
Because it glowed in the dark?
I have absolutely no idea
what you're talking about.
Who are you?
(ALARM SOUNDING)
Well, I think we've seen enough
for now, Corporal. Thank you so much.
- That's it?
- That's it. It's this way, isn't it?
Just a minute!
Did we break into a military base
to investigate a rabbit?
(DOOR BEEPING)
(PHONES RINGING)
(TEXT ALERT CHIMES)
Huh. 23 minutes. Mycroft's getting slow
(DOOR BEEPING)
Hello. Again.
- Uh, Major, this is...
- Bloody outrageous!
Why wasn't I told?
Major Barrymore, is it?
Yes. Well. Good.
Very good. We're very impressed.
- Aren't we, Mr. Holmes?
- Deeply. Hugely.
The whole point of Baskerville
was to eliminate
- this kind of bureaucratic nonsense!
- I'm so sorry, Major.
- Inspections...
- New policy.
You can't remain unmonitored forever.
Goodness knows what you'd get up to.
- Keep walking.
- Sir!
(ALARM BLARING)
- ID unauthorised, sir!
- What?
- I've just had the call.
- Is that right? Who are you?
Look, there's obviously
been some kind of mistake.
Clearly not Mycroft Holmes.
Computer error, Major.
It'll all have to go in the report.
- What the hell's going on?
- It's all right, Major.
- I know exactly who these gentlemen are.
- You do?
Yeah. I'm getting a little slow
on faces,
but Mr. Holmes here isn't someone
I expected to show up in this place.
- Ah, well...
- Good to see you again, Mycroft.
I had the honour of meeting Mr. Holmes
at the WHO conference in...
Brussels, was it?
- Vienna.
- Vienna. That's it.
This is Mr. Mycroft Holmes, Major.
There's obviously been a mistake.
- On your head be it, Dr. Frankland.
- (LAUGHS)
- I'll show them out, Corporal.
- Very well, sir.
- Thank you.
- This is about Henry Knight, isn't it?
I thought so.
I knew he wanted help but...
I didn't realise he was going to
contact Sherlock Holmes.
Don't worry, I know who you really are.
I'm never off your website.
Thought you'd be wearing the hat,
though.
That wasn't my hat.
- I hardly recognise him without the hat.
- It wasn't my hat.
- I love the blog, too, Dr. Watson.
- Oh, cheers.
The Pink thing! And that one
about the Aluminium Crutch!
You know Henry Knight?
Well, I knew his dad better.
He had all sorts of
mad theories about this place.
Still, he was a good friend.
Listen, I can't really talk now.
Here's my cell number.
If I can help, with Henry,
give me a call.
I never did ask, Dr. Frankland.
What exactly is it that you do here?
Mr. Holmes, I would love to tell you,
but then of course
I'd have to kill you. (LAUGHS)
That would be
tremendously ambitious of you.
Tell me about Dr. Stapleton.
I never speak ill of a colleague.
But you'd speak well of one,
which you're clearly omitting to do.
I do seem to be, don't I?
- I'll be in touch.
- Any time.
- 50?
What was all that about the rabbit?
Oh, please.
Can we not do this this time?
- Do what?
- You being all mysterious with your...
cheekbones, and turning
your coat collar up so you look cool.
- I don't do that.
- Yeah, you do.
So, the email from Kirsty,
the missing luminous rabbit...
Kirsty Stapleton, whose mother
specialises in genetic manipulation.
She made her daughter's rabbit
glow in the dark?
Probably a fluorescent gene.
Removed and spliced into the specimen,
simple enough these days.
So...
So we know that Dr. Stapleton performs
secret genetic experiments on animals.
The question is has she been working
on something deadlier than a rabbit?
To be fair, that is quite a wide field.
(DOOR OPENS)
- Hi. Come in. Come in.
- Hi.
This is, uh...
Are you, um... rich?
- Yeah.
- Right.
It's a couple of words.
That's what I keep seeing.
- "Liberty."
- Liberty?
"Liberty" and...
"In-"
It's just that.
- Are you finished?
- Mmm.
Mean anything to you?
"Liberty in death",
isn't that the expression?
- Mmm.
- The only true freedom?
(SIGHS)
- What now, then?
- Sherlock's got a plan.
- Yes.
- Right.
We take you back out onto the moor.
- Okay.
- And see if anything attacks you.
- What?
- That should bring things to a head.
At night?
- You want me to go out there at night?
- That's your plan?
- (LAUGHS) Brilliant.
- Do you have any better ideas?
- That's not a plan.
- If there is a monster out there, John,
there's only one thing to do,
find out where it lives.
(ANIMAL SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING)
(RUSTLING)
(BIRD CALLING)
Sher.
(READING MORSE CODE)
U-M-Q-R-A. UMQRA?
(WHISPERING) Sherlock.
JOHN: Sherlock.
(WHISPERING) Sherlock!
SHERLOCK: Met a friend of yours.
- What?
- Dr. Frankland.
Oh, right. Bob, yeah.
He seems pretty concerned about you.
He's a worrier. Bless him.
He's been very kind to me
since I came back.
- He knew your father?
- Yeah.
But he works at Baskerville. Didn't your
dad have a problem with that?
Well, mates are mates, aren't they?
I mean, look at you and John.
What about us?
Well, I mean,
he's a pretty straightforward bloke
and you...
They agreed never to talk about work,
Uncle Bob and my dad.
Dewer's Hollow.
(WHISPERING) Sherlock?
(RYTHMIC, SOFT CLANKING)
(CLANKING CONTINUES)
(CHUCKLES)
(METAL CLANKING SOFTLY)
(HOWLING)
(GROWLING)
(PANTING)
HENRY: Oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God...
Did you see it?
- Did you hear that?
- We saw it! We saw it.
No. I didn't see anything.
What? What are you talking about?
I didn't see anything!
Look, he must have seen it!
I saw it. He must have.
He must have. I...
Why? Why? Why would he say that?
It-it-it was there. It was.
Henry? Henry, I need you to sit down.
- Try and relax, please.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm going to give you something
to help you sleep.
- All right?
- This is good news, John.
It's... it's... it's good.
I'm not crazy.
There is a Hound. There is...
And Sherlock, he saw it too.
No matter what he says. He saw it.
Well, he is in a pretty bad way.
He's manic.
Totally convinced there's some
mutant super-dog roaming the moors.
And there isn't, though, is there?
'Cause if people knew how to make
a mutant super-dog, we'd know.
They'd be for sale.
I mean, that's how it works.
Listen, on the moor,
I saw someone signalling.
Morse. I guess it's Morse.
Doesn't seem to make much sense.
U-M-Q-R-A. Does that mean anything?
So, okay. What have we got?
We know there's footprints,
'cause Henry found them.
So did the tour guide.
But we all heard something.
Maybe we should just
look for whoever's got a big dog.
- Henry's right.
- What?
I saw it, too.
- I saw it, too, John.
- Just... just a minute. You saw what?
- A hound.
Out there in the Hollow.
A gigantic hound!
Um...
Look, Sherlock.
We have to be rational about this. Okay?
Now, you, of all people, can't just...
Let's just stick to what we know, yes?
Stick to the facts.
Once you've ruled out the impossible,
whatever remains,
however improbable, must be true.
What does that mean?
Huh.
Look at me, I'm afraid, John.
Afraid.
Sherlock...
I've always been able
to keep myself distant.
Divorce myself from feelings.
But, look, you see?
My body's betraying me.
Interesting, yes? Emotions.
The grit on the lens,
the fly in the ointment!
Yeah, all right, Spock.
Just take it easy.
You've been pretty wired lately.
You know you have.
I think you've just gone out there
and got yourself a bit worked up.
Worked up?
- It was dark and scary...
- Me?
There's nothing wrong with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Sherlock?
- Sherlock?
- There is nothing wrong with me!
Do you understand?
You want me to prove it, yes?
We're looking for a dog, yes?
A great big dog.
That's your brilliant theory.
Cherchez le chien!
Good. Excellent. Yes!
Where shall we start?
How about them?
The sentimental widow and her son,
the unemployed fisherman?
- The answer's yes.
- Yes?
She's got a West Highland terrier
called Whisky.
- Not exactly what we're looking for.
- Sherlock, for God's sake.
Look at the jumper he's wearing,
hardly worn.
Clearly he's uncomfortable in it.
Maybe it's because of the material,
more likely the hideous pattern.
Suggests it's a present.
Probably Christmas.
So, he wants into his Mother's good
books. Why? Almost certainly money.
He's treating her to a meal,
but his own portion is small.
That means he wants to impress her,
but he's trying to economise
on his own food.
- Well, maybe he's just not hungry.
- No. Small plate. A starter.
He's practically licked it clean.
She's nearly finished her pavlova.
If she'd treated him,
he'd have had as much as he wanted.
He's hungry, all right.
And not well off.
You can tell that from
the state of his cuffs and shoes.
"How do you know she's his mother?"
Who else would give him
a Christmas present like that?
Well, it could be an aunt or an
older sister, but mother's more likely.
Now, he was a fisherman.
The scarring pattern on his hands
is very distinctive, fish-hooks.
They're all quite old now,
which suggests he's been unemployed
for some time.
Not much industry
in this part of the world,
so he's turned
to his widowed mother for help.
"Widowed?" Yes! Obviously.
She's got a man's wedding ring
on a chain around her neck,
clearly her late husband's
and too big for her finger.
She's well-dressed
but her jewellery's cheap.
She could afford better,
but she's kept it. Sentimental.
Now, the dog.
Tiny little hairs all over the leg
from where it gets a little bit
too friendly.
But no hairs above the knee,
suggesting it's a small dog,
probably a terrier. In fact, it is
a West Highland terrier called Whisky.
"How the hell do you know that,
Sherlock?"
Because she was on the same train
as us and I heard her calling its name.
And that's not cheating,
that's listening.
I use my senses, John,
unlike some people.
So, you see, I am fine.
In fact, I've never been better.
So just leave me alone.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Why would you listen to me?
I'm just your friend.
- I don't have friends.
- No.
I wonder why? (CLEARS THROAT)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
WOMAN: Oh, Mr. Selden!
You've done it again!
SELDEN: Oh.
I keep catching it with me belt.
Oh, God. Oh...
Sh...
(TEXT ALERT CHIMES)
SQ?
Oh, you're a bad man.
(BARKING)
Morning!
(ROARING, WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(GUN COCKS)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
- (LAUGHING) No, I mean...
- What is it?
Um, more wine, Doctor?
- You trying to get me drunk, Doctor?
- The thought never occurred.
Because a while ago,
I thought you were chatting me up.
Oh! Where did I go wrong?
When you started asking me
about my patients.
No, you see, I am one of
Henry's oldest friends.
Yeah, and he's one of my patients,
so I can't talk about him.
Though he has told me about
all his oldest friends.
Which one are you?
- A new one?
- (BOTH SCOFF)
Okay, what about his father?
He wasn't one of your patients.
Wasn't he some sort of
conspiracy nutter, theorist?
- You're only a nutter if you're wrong.
- Hmm.
- Was he wrong?
- I should think so.
But he got fixated on
Baskerville, didn't he?
With what they were doing in there.
Couldn't Henry have gone the same way?
Started imagining a hound?
Why do you think I'm going to
talk about this?
(LAUGHS) Because I think
you're worried about him.
And because I am a doctor, too,
and because I have
another friend who...
might be having the same problem.
- Dr. Watson!
- Hi.
Hello.
How's the investigation going?
- Hello.
- What investigation?
Didn't you know?
Don't you read the blog?
- Sherlock Holmes!
- Sherlock who?
(SCOFFS) Private detective.
- This is his PA.
- PA?
- Well, live-in PA.
- Perfect.
- Live-in.
- Uh, this is Dr. Mortimer.
Henry's therapist.
Oh, hello. Bob Frankland.
Listen, tell Sherlock I've been
keeping an eye on Stapleton.
Any time he wants a little chat...
All right?
(LAUGHS)
- Oh.
- Ah.
Why don't you buy him a drink?
I think he likes you.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Morning! Oh, how are you feeling?
I'm... I didn't sleep very well.
That's a shame.
Shall I make you some coffee?
Oh, look. You've got damp.
Listen.
Last night...
Why did you say
you hadn't seen anything?
I mean, I only saw the Hound
for a minute but...
- Hound.
- What?
Why do you call it a hound?
Why a hound?
- Why? What do you mean?
- It's odd, isn't it?
Strange choice of words, archaic.
That's why I took the case.
"Mr. Holmes, they were
the footprints of a gigantic hound."
Why say "hound"?
- I don't know, I've never...
- Actually, let's skip the coffee.
You, uh, getting anywhere
with that Morse Code?
- No.
- U-M-Q-R-A, wasn't it?
- UMQRA.
- Nothing.
- UMQ...
- Look, forget it.
I thought I was onto something,
I wasn't.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
How about Louise Mortimer?
Did you get anywhere with her?
- No.
- Too bad.
Did you get any information?
Hmm. You're being funny now?
Thought it might break the ice a bit.
Funny doesn't suit you.
I'd stick to ice.
- John...
- It's fine.
No, wait. What happened last night,
something happened to me,
something I've not really
experienced before.
Yes, you said. Fear.
"Sherlock Holmes got scared," you said.
No, no, no. It was more than that, John.
It was doubt. I felt doubt.
Always been able to trust my senses,
the evidence of my own eyes,
until last night.
You can't actually believe that
you saw some kind of monster?
No, I can't believe that.
But I did see it.
So the question is how? How?
Yes.
Yeah, right, good.
So, you got something to go on, then?
Good luck with that.
Listen, what I said before, John,
I meant it.
I don't have friends.
I've just got one.
Right.
John?
John!
- You are amazing! You are fantastic!
- Yes, all right.
You don't have to overdo it.
You've never been the most
luminous of people
but as a conductor of light,
you are unbeatable.
- Cheers.
- What?
Some people who aren't geniuses
have an amazing ability
to stimulate it in others.
Hang on, you were saying sorry
a minute ago, don't spoil it.
Go on. What have I done
that's so bloody stimulating?
Yeah?
What if it's not a word?
What if it is individual letters?
- You think it's an acronym?
- Absolutely no idea.
What the hell are you doing here?
Oh, nice to see you, too.
I'm on holiday, would you believe?
No. I wouldn't.
- Hello, John.
- Greg.
I heard you were in the area.
What are you up to?
You after this Hound of Hell,
like on the telly?
I'm waiting for an explanation,
Inspector. Why are you here?
I've told you, I'm on holiday.
You're brown as a nut. You're clearly
just back from your holidays.
Maybe I fancied another one.
- Oh, this is Mycroft, isn't it?
- Now, look...
Of course it is.
One mention of Baskerville
and he sends down my handler
to spy on me, incognito.
Is that why you're
calling yourself Greg?
- That's his name.
- Is it?
Yes, if you'd ever bothered to find out.
Look, I'm not your handler.
And I don't just do
what your brother tells me
Actually, you could be
just the man we want.
- Why?
- I've not been idle, Sherlock.
I think I might have
found something. Here.
Didn't know if it was relevant,
it's starting to look like it might be.
That is an awful lot of meat
for a vegetarian restaurant.
- Excellent.
- A nice, scary inspector
from Scotland Yard
who can put in a few calls
might come in very handy.
Shop!
- What's this?
- Coffee. I made coffee.
- You never make coffee.
- I just did. Don't you want it?
You don't have to keep apologising.
Thanks.
Mmm, I don't take sugar.
LESTRADE:
These records go back nearly two months.
That's nice. It's good.
Was that when you had the idea?
After the TV show went out?
It's me. It was me.
I'm sorry, Gary, I couldn't help it.
I had a bacon sandwich at Cal's wedding
and one thing just led to another.
Nice try.
Look, we were just trying to give
things a bit of a boost, you know?
A great big dog run wild up on the moor,
it was heaven sent.
It was like us having our own
Loch Ness Monster.
- Where do you keep it?
- There's an old mine shaft.
It's not too far.
He was all right there.
- Was?
- (SIGHING)
We couldn't control the bloody thing!
It was vicious.
And then a month ago,
Billy took him to the vet
- and, you know...
- It's dead?
- Put down.
- Yeah.
No choice. So it's over.
- It was just a joke, you know?
- Yeah. Hilarious.
You've nearly driven
a man out of his mind.
You know he's actually pleased
you're here? Secretly pleased.
Is he? That's nice.
I suppose he likes having
all the same faces back together.
- Appeals to his... his...
- Asperger's?
So, you believe them
about having the dog destroyed?
- No reason not to.
- Well, hopefully there's no harm done.
Not quite sure what
I'd charge them with anyway.
I'll have a word with the local force.
Right, that's that, then.
Catch you later. I'm enjoying this!
It's nice to get London
out of your lungs.
So that was their dog
that people saw out on the moor?
- Looks like it.
- But that wasn't what you saw.
- That wasn't just an ordinary dog.
- No.
It was immense, had burning red eyes
and it was glowing, John,
its whole body was glowing.
(GASPS)
I've got a theory, but I need to get
back into Baskerville to test it.
JOHN: How? You can't pull off
the ID trick again.
SHERLOCK: Might not have to.
Hello, brother dear. How are you?
(SCREECHING)
Afternoon, sir, if you could turn
the engine off. Thank you.
SHERLOCK: I need to see Major Barrymore
as soon as we get inside.
- Right.
- Which means you'll have to start
- the search for the Hound.
- Okay.
In the labs. Stapleton's first.
Could be dangerous.
Oh, you know I'd love to. I'd love to
give you unlimited access to this place.
- Why not?
- It's a simple enough request, Major.
I've never heard of anything so bizarre.
You're to give me 24 hours.
It's what I've negotiated.
Not a second more.
I may have to comply with this order
but I don't have to like it.
I don't know what the hell
you expect to find here, anyway.
- Perhaps the truth.
- About what?
Oh, I see!
The big coat should have told me.
You're one of the conspiracy lot,
aren't you? Well, then, go ahead.
Seek them out. The monsters,
the death rays, the aliens.
Have you got any of those?
Oh, just wondering.
A couple. Crash-landed here in the '60s.
We call them Abbott and Costello.
Good luck, Mr. Holmes.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, God!
(MOANING)
(BEEPS)
Oh!
Ow!
(ALARM BLARING)
Come on.
(ALARM STOPS)
What the...
Hello?
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(cum KING)
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
- (BEEPING)
- No, come on. Come on.
(BEEPING)
(SPEED-DIALLING NUMBER)
(PHONE RINGING, JOHN PANTING)
No, you've...
Don't be ridiculous. Pick up. Damn it!
Right.
(SCRURRYING)
Okay.
(GROWLING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(VICIOUS SNARLING)
(PANTING)
(LOW GROWLING)
(MOBILE RINGING)
(WHISPERING)
It's here. It's in here with me!
- SHERLOCK: Where are you?
- Get me out, Sherlock.
You've got to get me out. The big lab.
The first lab that we saw.
- (GROWLING)
- Oh!
- John? John?
- Now, Sherlock. Please.
- A ll right. I'll find you. Keep talking.
- I daren't, it'll hear me.
Keep talking. What are you seeing?
- John?
- Yes, I'm here.
What' can you see?
I don't know. I don't know,
but I can hear it, though.
- (GROWLING)
- Did you hear that?
Stay calm. Stay calm. Can you see it?
- Can you see it?
- No. I...
(GROWLING)
I can see it.
It's here.
It's here!
- Are you all right? John?
- Jesus Christ! It was the Hound!
Sherlock. It was here.
I swear it, Sherlock. It must...
It must...
Did you see it? You must have!
- It's all right. It's okay now.
- No, it's not!
It's not okay! I saw it, I was wrong.
- Hmm. Let's not jump to conclusions.
- What?
- What did you see?
- I told you, I saw the Hound.
'Huge? R I ed eye 7 Yes! 5'
- Glowing?
- Yeah.
- No.
- What?
I made up the bit about glowing.
You saw what you expected to see
because I told you.
You have been drugged.
We have all been drugged.
- Drugged?
- Can you walk?
Of course I can walk.
Come on, then.
It's time to lay this ghost.
Oh, back again?
- What's on your mind this time?
- Murder, Dr. Stapleton.
Refined, cold-blooded murder.
Will you tell little Kirsty
what happened to Bluebell or shall I?
- Okay, what do you want?
- Can I borrow your microscope?
Are you sure you're okay?
You look very peaky.
No, I'm all right.
It was the GFP gene from a jellyfish,
in case you're interested.
- What?
- In the rabbits.
Hmm. Great news.
Aequorea Victoria,
if you really want to know.
- Why?
"Why not?"
We don't ask questions like that here.
It isn't done.
It was a mix-up, anyway.
My daughter ended up
with one of the lab specimens,
so poor Bluebell had to go.
- Your compassion's overwhelming.
- I know. I hate myself sometimes.
So, come on, then, you can trust me,
I'm a doctor, what else have you got
hidden away up here?
(SIGHS) Listen, if you can imagine it,
someone is probably doing it somewhere.
Of course they are.
- Cloning?
- Yes, of course!
Dolly the sheep, remember?
- Human cloning?
- Why not?
And what about animals? Not sheep.
- Big animals.
- Size isn't a problem. Not at all.
The only limits are ethics and the law.
And both those things can be
very flexible.
But not here, not at Baskerville.
- It's not there!
- JOHN: Jesus!
Nothing there!
It doesn't make any sense.
- What were you expecting to find?
- A drug, of course! It has to be a drug.
A hallucinogenic or a deliriant
of some kind.
There's no trace of anything
in the sugar.
- Sugar?
- The sugar, yes.
It's a simple process of elimination.
I saw the Hound, saw it as my
imagination expected me to see it.
A genetically engineered monster.
But I knew I couldn't believe
the evidence of my own eyes,
so there were
seven possible reasons for it,
the most possible being narcotics.
Henry Knight, he saw it, too.
But you didn't, John. You didn't see it.
Now, we have eaten and drunk exactly
the same things since we got to Grimpen,
apart from one thing!
You don't take sugar in your coffee.
I see. So...
I took it from Henry's kitchen.
His sugar.
- But it's perfectly all right.
- But maybe it's not a drug.
No, it has to be a drug.
How did it get into our systems? How?
There must be something. Something...
Something...
Something buried deep. Get out.
- What?
- Get out.
- I need to go to my mind palace.
- Your what?
He's not going to be doing much
talking for a while, we may as well go.
- His what?
- Oh, his mind palace.
It's a memory technique.
A sort of mental map.
You plot a map with a location.
It doesn't have to be a real place.
And then you deposit memories there.
Theoretically,
you can never forget anything.
All you have to do
is find your way back to it.
So this imaginary location
could be anything, a house or a street?
- Yeah.
- But he said palace.
- He said it was a palace.
- Yeah, well, he would, wouldn't he?
(BELL TOLLING)
(BARKING)
You ain't nothing...
MALE VOICE: H.O.U.N.D.
(HOWLING)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(SOBBING)
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I am so...
I am so sorry. I am so sorry.
(BEEPS)
- John?
- Yeah, I'm on it.
Project H.0.U.N.D.
I must have read about it.
Stored it away.
Experiment in the CIA facility
in Liberty, Indiana.
H-O-U-N-D.
(BEEPING)
That's as far as my access goes,
I'm afraid.
There must be an override. A password.
I imagine so,
but that'd be Major Barrymore's.
Password. Password. Password.
He'd have sat here
when he thought it up.
- Describe him to me.
- You've seen him.
- But describe him.
- He's a bloody martinet. A throwback.
The sort they'd have sent into Suez.
Good. Excellent. Old-fashioned.
A traditionalist.
Not the sort of man that uses
children's names as a password.
He loves his job. Proud of it.
And this is work-related.
So, what's at eye level?
Books. Jane's Defence Weekly.
Bound copies. Hannibal,
Wellington. Rommel. Churchill's
History of the English-Speaking Peoples,
all four volumes.
Churchill. He's fond of Churchill.
Copy of The Downing Street Years,
one, two, three, four, five separate
biographies of Thatcher.
Mid-1980s, at a guess. Father and son.
Barrymore senior? Medals.
- Distinguished service order?
- That date, I'd say Falklands veteran.
Right, so Thatcher's looking
more likely a bet than Churchill.
So that's the password?
No! With a man like Major Barrymore,
only first-name terms would do.
(BEEPING)
"H.O.U.N.D."
Jesus!
Project H.0.U.N.D. A new deliriant drug
which rendered its users
incredibly suggestible.
They wanted to use it
as an anti-personnel weapon
to totally disorientate the enemy
using fear and stimulus.
But they shut it down
and hid it away in 1986.
Because of what it did to the subjects
they tested it on?
And what they did to others.
Prolonged exposure drove them insane.
Made them almost
uncontrollably aggressive.
So, someone's been doing it again?
Carrying on the experiments?
Attempting to refine it, perhaps.
For the last 20 years.
- Who?
- Those names mean anything to you?
No. Not a thing.
(SIGHS) Five principal scientists,
20 years ago.
Maybe our friend's somewhere
in the back of the picture.
Somebody who was old enough to be there
at the time of the experiments in 1986.
Maybe somebody who says "cell phone"
because of time spent in America.
- You remember, John?
- Mmm-hmm.
Here's my cell number.
Gave us his number
in case we needed him.
Oh, my God. Bob Frankland.
But Bob doesn't even work on it.
I mean, he's a virologist.
- This was chemical warfare.
- That's where he started, though.
And he's never lost the certainty,
the obsession
that that drug really could work.
Nice of him to give us his number.
Let's arrange a little meeting.
(MOBILE RINGING)
- Hello?
- (WOMAN SOBBING)
- Who's this?
- You've got to find Henry.
It's Louise Mortimer.
Louise, what's wrong?
Henry was remembering, then...
He tried... He's got a gun,
he went for the gun and tried to...
What?
He's gone! You've got to stop him.
I don't know what he might do.
- Where are you?
- His house, I'm okay. I'm okay.
Right. Stay there,
we'll get someone to you. Okay?
- Henry?
- He's attacked her.
Gone? There's only one place he'll
go to, back to where it all started.
Lestrade, get to the Hollow.
Dewer's Hollow, now! And bring a gun.
(ANIMAL SCREECHING)
I'm sorry.
So sorry, Dad.
(COCKING GUN)
- Oh, Henry, no! No!
- Get back, Dad! Get away from me!
- Easy, Henry. Easy. just relax.
- I know what I am.
- I know what I tried to do!
- Just put the gun down. It's okay.
- No! No! I know what I am!
- Yes. I'm sure you do, Henry.
It's all been explained to you,
hasn't it?
- Explained very carefully.
- What?
Someone needed to keep you quiet.
Needed to keep you as a child,
to reassert the dream
that you'd both clung on to
because you had started to remember.
Remember now, Henry. You've got to
remember what happened here
when you were a little boy.
I thought it had got my dad. The Hound.
I thought... Oh, Jesus!
I don't know any more!
- I don't!
- No, Henry! Henry!
Henry, remember, "Liberty, In."
Two words.
Two words a frightened little boy
saw here 20 years ago.
You'd started to piece things together,
remember what really happened
here that night.
It wasn't an animal, was it, Henry?
Not a monster.
A man.
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
You couldn't cope.
You were just a child
So you rationalised it
into something very different.
And then you started to remember,
so you had to be stopped.
Driven out of your mind so that no one
would believe a word that you said.
Sherlock!
Okay. It's okay, mate.
But we saw it! The Hound.
Last night. We did!
There was a dog, Henry.
Leaving footprints, scaring witnesses.
But it was nothing more
than an ordinary dog.
We both saw it. Saw it as our
drugged minds wanted us to see it.
Fear and stimulus.
That's how it works.
But there never was any monster.
(HOWLING)
Sherlock?
- No! No, no, no, no, no!
- Henry...
Sherlock!
- No, no, no, no, no, no'
- Henry?
(GROWLING)
Sherlock?
Are you seeing this? He is not drugged,
Sherlock. So what's that?
- What is it?
- All right! It's still there!
But it's just a dog, Henry.
It's nothing more than an ordinary dog!
My God!
(GROWLING)
Oh, Christ!
(RASPING BREATHING)
No! No!
(DOG GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
It's not you.
It's not you!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
- The fog.
- What?
It's the fog!
The drug, it's in the fog!
Aerosol dispersant,
that's what it said in those records.
Project H.0.U.N.D. It's the fog.
A chemical minefield.
(GROWLING)
For God's sake, kill it! Kill it!
(FIRING)
(WHIMPERS)
Look at it, Henry.
- No, no, no.
- Come on, look at it!
It's just... You bastard.
You bastard!
Twenty years! Twenty yea rs of my life
making no sense.
Why didn't you just kill me?
Because dead men get listened to.
He needed to do more than kill you.
He had to discredit every word
you ever said about your father.
And he had the means right at his feet.
A chemical minefield!
Pressure pads in the ground,
dosing you up every time
that you came back here.
Murder weapon, scene of the crime,
all at once.
(LAUGHING) Oh, this case, Henry!
- Thank you, it's been brilliant.
- Sherlock.
What?
Timing.
- Not good?
- No, no, it's okay.
It's fine, because this means...
This means that my dad was right.
He'd found something out, hadn't he?
And that's why you killed him,
because he was right!
And he'd found you
right in the middle of an experiment.
(GROWLING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Frankland!
- Frankland!
- Keep running.
Keep back!
It's no use, Frankland!
Come on!
(MINE BEEPING)
(EXHALES)
Hmm.
Thanks, Billy.
So they didn't have it put down, then?
The dog.
Obviously. Suppose they just
couldn't bring themselves to do it.
I see.
No, you don't.
- No, I don't. Sentiment?
- Sentiment.
Mmm, listen, what happened to me
in the lab?
- Do you want some sauce with that?
- I hadn't been to the Hollows.
How come I heard those things in there?
Fear and stimulus, you said.
You must've been dosed
with it elsewhere.
When you went to the lab, maybe.
You saw those pipes.
Pretty ancient, leaky as a sieve.
And they were carrying the gas, so...
- Um, ketchup, was it, or brown?
- Hang on.
You thought it was in the sugar.
You were convinced it was in the sugar.
Better get going, actually.
There's a train that leaves
in half an hour, so if you want...
Oh, God. It was you.
You locked me in that bloody lab!
I had to. It was an experiment.
- An experiment?
- Shh.
I was terrified, Sherlock.
I was scared to death!
I thought the drug was in the sugar
so I put the sugar in your coffee.
Then I arranged everything
with Major Barrymore.
It was all totally scientific,
laboratory conditions. Well, literally.
(RECORDING OF GROWLING PLAYING)
It's in here with me.
SHERLOCK: All right. Keep talking.
I'll find you.
- Keep talking.
- I daren't, it'll hear me.
Tell me what you're seeing.
(RECORDING OF GROWLING PLAYING)
I don't know but I can hear it, though.
I knew what effect it had had
on a superior mind,
so I needed to try it
on an average one.
You know what I mean.
But it wasn't in the sugar.
No, well, I wasn't to know you'd
already been exposed to the gas.
- So you got it wrong.
- No.
You were wrong. It wasn't in the sugar.
You got it wrong.
A bit.
Won't happen again.
Any long-term effects?
None at all. You'll be fine
once you've excreted it. We all will.
Think I might have
ta ken ca re of that already
- Where are you going?
- Won't be a minute.
Got to see a man about a dog.
All right. Let him go.