LADY SMALLWOOD: Mr. Magnussen, please
state your full name for the record.
MAGNUSSEN: Charles Augustus Magnussen.
Mr. Magnussen, how would you describe
your influence over the Prime Minister?
MAGNUSSEN: The British Prime Minister?
Any of the British Prime Ministers
you have known.
I've never had the slightest influence
over any of them.
Why would I?
I notice you've had seven meetings
at Downing Street this year.
Why?
MAGNUSSEN: Because I was invited.
Can you recall
the subjects under discussion?
Not without being more indiscreet
than I believe is appropriate.
Do you think it right
that a newspaper proprietor,
a private individual and,
in fact, a foreign national
should have such regular access
to our Prime Minister?
I don't think it's wrong
that a private individual
should accept an invitation.
However, you have my sincere apologies
for being foreign.
That's not what I meant.
That is not in any way...
Mr. Magnussen, can you recall an occasion
when your remarks could have
influenced government policy?
Or the Prime Minister's thinking
in any way?
MAGNUSSEN: No.
Are you sure?
(BEEPING)
I have an excellent memory.
MAN: Your car is waiting outside
in the front, thank you.
See you tomorrow.
- May I join you?
- I don't think it's appropriate.
- It isn't?
- Mr. Magnussen, outside the enquiry
we can have no contact,
no communication at all.
Please don't do that.
In 1982, your husband corresponded
with Helen Katherine Driscoll.
That was before I knew him.
The letters were lively, loving,
some would say explicit,
and currently in my possession.
Will you please move your hand?
"I long, my darling,
to know the touch of your body."
I know what was in the letters.
She was 15.
She looked older.
Oh, she looked delicious.
We have photographs, too.
The ones she sent him.
Yum yum.
He was unaware of her age.
He met her only once
before the letters began.
When he discovered the truth,
he stopped immediately.
Those are the facts.
Facts are for history books,
I work in news.
Your hand is sweating.
Always, I'm afraid. I have a condition.
It's disgusting.
Ah. I'm used to it.
The whole world is wet to my touch.
I will call someone,
I will have you removed.
What is that?
(SNIFFING)
Claire-de-la-lune?
Bit young for you, isn't it?
You want to hit me now?
Could you, still?
You're an old lady now.
Perhaps you should settle
for calling someone.
Well, call him.
No? Because now there are consequences.
I have the letters
and therefore, I have you.
This is blackmail.
Of course it isn't blackmail.
This is... ownership.
You do not own me.
Claire-de-la-lune.
It never tastes like it smells,
does it?
Lady Smallwood's bill is on me.
See to it.
Yes, Mr. Magnussen.
(SHUDDERING)
(GASPING) Oh, God!
You all right, ma'am?
Fine. Yes.
Magnussen.
No one stands up to him.
No one dares, no one even tries.
There isn't a man or woman in England
capable of stopping
that disgusting creature.
- Ma'am?
- Turn the car around.
We're going back into town. Turn round.
Where are we going, ma'am?
Baker Street.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(CONTINUOUS GUNFIRE)
Seen a lot of injuries, then?
Violent deaths?
JOHN: Enough for a lifetime.
- Want to see some more?
- JOHN: Oh, God, yes.
(BANGING ON DOOR, GASPING)
The game is on.
(BANGING CONTINUES)
I know it's early.
Really, I'm sorry. (SOBBING)
- Is that Kate?
- Yeah, it's Kate.
Going to invite her in?
Uh, sorry, yes.
Do you want to come in, Kate?
- (SOBBING)
- MARY: Hey!
Sorry.
- There you go.
- It's Isaac.
- Ah, your husband?
- Son.
Son, yeah.
He's gone missing again.
- Didn't come home last night.
- (SIGHS)
- The usual.
- He's the drugs one, yeah?
Yeah, nicely put, John.
Well, is it Sherlock Holmes you want?
Because I've not seen him in ages.
- About a month.
- Who's Sherlock Holmes?
See? That does happen.
There's a place they all go to,
him and his friends.
They all... do whatever they do.
Shoot up, whatever you call it.
Where is he?
It's a house. It's a dump,
I mean, it's practically falling down.
No, the address.
Where exactly?
- Seriously?
- Why not?
She's not going to the police,
someone's got to get him.
- Why you?
- Being neighbourly.
Since when?
(CHUCKLING)
Since now. Since this exact minute.
- Why are you being so...
- What?
Oh, I don't know.
What's the matter with you?
There is nothing the matter with me!
Imagine I said that without shouting.
I'm trying.
No, you can't come, you're pregnant.
You can't go, I'm pregnant.
(METAL CLANGING)
(LAUGHING) What is that?
- It's a tyre lever.
- Why?
Because there were loads of
smackheads in there
and one of them might need help
with a tyre.
If there's any trouble,
just go, I'll be fine.
Wait, John. John, John, John...
It is a tiny bit sexy.
Yeah, I know.
JOHN: (KNOCKING) Hello?
- What do you want?
- Excuse me.
Hey, you can't come in here.
I'm looking for a friend.
A very specific friend.
I'm not just browsing.
MAN: You gotta go.
No one's allowed here.
(CLEARS THROAT) Isaac Whitney,
you seen him?
I'm asking you
if you've seen Isaac Whitney
and now you're showing me a knife.
Is it a clue?
You doing a mime?
Go. Or I'll cut you.
Ooh, not from there.
Let me help.
Now, concentrate. Isaac Whitney.
Okay, you asked for it.
(GROANING)
Right, are you concentrating yet?
- You broke my arm.
- No, I sprained it.
It feels squishy.
Is it supposed to feel squishy?
- Feel that.
- Yeah, it's a sprain.
I'm a doctor,
I know how to sprain people.
Now, where is Isaac Whitney?
I don't know.
Maybe upstairs.
There you go. Wasn't that easy?
No, it was really sore.
Mental, you are.
No, just used to a better class
of criminal.
(MAN COUGHING)
Isaac? Isaac Whitney?
(TIN CAN CLATTERING)
(SOFTLY) Isaac?
(ISAAC GROANING)
Hello, mate. Sit up for me?
Sit up.
- ISAAC: Dr. Watson?
- Yep.
Where am I?
Arse-end of the universe
with the scum of the Earth. Look at me?
Have you come for me?
Do you think
I know a lot of people here?
Hey, you all right?
Oh, hello, John.
Didn't expect to see you here.
Come for me, too?
- Hello, Isaac.
- Mrs. Watson, can I...
Can I get in, please?
Yes, of course, get in.
- Where's John?
- They're having a fight.
Who is?
- For God's sakes, John. I'm on a case.
- A month, that's all it took.
- One!
- I'm working.
Sherlock Holmes in a drug den,
how is that going to look?
- I'm undercover.
- No, you're not.
Well, I'm not now!
In, both of you, quickly.
Please, can I come?
I think I got a broken arm.
- No, go away.
- No, let him.
- Why?
- Yeah, just get in. It's a sprain.
Anyone else? I mean, we're taking
everybody home, are we?
- All right, Shezza?
- Shezza?
I was undercover.
Seriously, Shezza, though?
We're not going home,
we're going to Barts.
- I'm calling Molly.
- Why?
Because Sherlock Holmes
needs to pee in a jar.
Well, is he clean?
Clean?
How dare you throw away
the beautiful gifts you were born with?
And how dare you betray
the love of your friends!
Say you're sorry.
Sorry your engagement's over.
Though I'm fairly grateful
for the lack of a ring.
Stop it.
Just stop it.
If you were anywhere
near this kind of thing again
you could have called,
you could have talked to me.
Oh, please, do relax.
This is all for a case.
A ca... What kind of case
would need you doing this?
I might as well ask you
why you've started cycling to work?
No, we're not playing this game.
Quite recently, I'd say,
you're very determined about it.
- Not interested.
- I am. Ow!
Oh, sorry, you moved,
but it is just a sprain.
- Yeah, somebody hit me.
- Huh?
Yeah, just some guy.
Yeah, it was probably just an addict
in need of a fix.
Yes, I think in a way it was.
- Is it his shirt?
- I'm sorry?
Well, it's the creases, innit?
The two creases down the front?
It's been recently folded
but it's not new.
You must have dressed in a hurry
this morning.
So all your shirts
might be kept like that.
But why?
Maybe 'cause you cycle
to work every morning,
shower when you get there
and then dress in the clothes
you brought with you.
You keep your shirts folded,
ready to pack.
- Not bad.
- And I further deduce...
you've only started recently
because you've got a bit of chafing.
No, he's always walked like that.
Remind me, what's your name again?
- They call me The Wig.
- No, they don't.
- Well, they call me Wiggy.
- Nope.
Bill. Bill Wiggins.
Nice observational skills, Billy.
(PHONE CHIMING)
Ah, finally!
- Finally what?
- Good news?
Oh, excellent news, the best.
There's every chance that my drug habit
might hit the newspapers.
The game is on.
Excuse me for a second.
SHERLOCK: You've heard of
Charles Augustus Magnussen, of course?
Yeah, owns some newspapers.
Ones I don't read.
Hang on. Weren't there other people?
Mary's taking the boys home,
I'm taking you. We did discuss it.
People were talking, none of them me,
I must have filtered.
- I noticed.
- Had to filter a load of witless babble,
I've had Mrs. Hudson
on semi-permanent mute.
(SIGHS) What is my brother doing here?
So I'll just pay, then, shall I?
He's straightened the knocker.
He always corrects it. He's OCD.
Doesn't even know he's doing it.
- Why did you do that?
- Do what?
JOHN: Nothing.
Well, then, Sherlock, back on the sauce?
What are you doing here?
- I phoned him.
- The siren call of old habits.
How very like Uncle Rudy,
though in many ways, cross dressing
would've been a wiser path for you.
- You phoned him?
- Course I bloody phoned him.
Course he bloody did.
Now, save me a little time.
Where should we be looking?
- We?
- ANDERSON: Mr. Holmes?
For God's sake!
- Anderson?
- Sorry Sherlock, it's for your own good.
Oh, that's him, isn't it?
He's said to be taller.
Some members of your little fan club,
to be polite.
They're entirely trustworthy.
Even willing to search through
the toxic waste dump
that you were pleased to call a flat.
You're a celebrity these days, Sherlock.
You can't afford a drug habit.
I do not have a drug habit.
Hey, what happened to my chair?
It was blocking my view to the kitchen.
Well, it's good to be missed.
Yeah, you were gone,
I saw an opportunity.
No, you saw the kitchen.
What have you found so far?
Clearly nothing.
There's nothing to find.
Your bedroom door is shut,
you haven't been home all night.
So, why would a man who has never
knowingly closed the door
without the direct orders of his mother
bother to do so on this occasion?
Okay, stop! Just stop!
- Point made.
- Jesus, Sherlock.
I'll have to phone our parents,
of course, in Oklahoma.
Won't be the first time
that your substance abuse
has wreaked havoc
with their line dancing.
This is not what you think,
this is for a case.
What case could possibly justify this?
Magnussen.
Charles Augustus Magnussen.
That name you think
you may have just heard,
you were mistaken.
If you ever mention hearing that name
in this room, in this context,
I guarantee you on behalf
of the British Security Services
that materials will be found
on your computer hard drives
resulting in your
immediate incarceration.
Don't reply, just look frightened
and scuttle.
I hope I won't have to
threaten you as well.
Well, I think we both find
that embarrassing.
- Magnussen is not your business.
- Oh, you mean he's yours?
You may consider him
under my protection.
I consider you under his thumb.
If you go against Magnussen,
then you will find yourself
going against me.
Okay, I'll let you know if I notice.
Erm... What was I going to say?
Oh, yeah. Bye-bye.
Unwise, brother mine.
(GROANING)
- Brother mine...
- (CRACKING)
Don't appal me when I'm high.
Mycroft, don't say another word,
just go. He could snap you in two
and right now,
I'm slightly worried that he might.
Don't speak, just leave.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Uh, Magnussen?
- What time is it?
- About 8:00.
(SIGHS) I'll be meeting him
in three hours. I need a bath.
- It's for a case, you said.
- Yep.
- What sort of case?
- Too big and dangerous
for any sane individual
to get involved in.
- You're trying to put me off?
- God, no.
I'm trying to recruit you.
And stay out of my bedroom.
Oh, John, hi.
- How are you?
- Janine?
Sorry, not dressed.
Has everybody gone? I heard shouting.
Yes, they're gone.
God, look at the time, I'll be late.
Sounded like an argument.
- Was it Mike?
- Mike?
Mike, yeah, his brother, Mike?
They're always fighting.
Mycroft?
- Do people actually call him that?
- Yeah.
Oh, could you be a love
and put some coffee on?
- Sure, right, yeah.
- Thanks.
Ooh, how is Mary?
How's married life?
She's fine, we're both fine. Yep.
Oh, it's over there now.
- Where's Sherl?
- Sherl.
(CLEARS THROAT)
He's just having a bath.
I'm sure he'll be out in a minute.
Oh, well, like he ever is!
Yeah.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR) Morning!
(BOTH CHATTING AND LAUGHING)
- (JANINE LAUGHING)
- SHERLOCK: Morning.
(SHERLOCK CHUCKLING, JANINE EXCLAIMING)
So, she's just a guest but you've
probably got some questions.
Yeah, one or two, pretty much.
Naturally.
You have a girlfriend?
Yes, I have.
Now, Magnussen.
Magnussen is like a shark.
That's the only way I can describe him.
Have you ever been to the shark tank
at the London Aquarium, John?
Stood up close to the glass, those...
floating, flat faces, those dead eyes?
That's what he is.
I've dealt with murderers, psychopaths,
terrorists, serial killers.
None of them can turn my stomach
like Charles Augustus Magnussen.
Yes, you have.
- Sorry, what?
- You have a girlfriend?
What? Yes, I'm going out with Janine.
I thought that was fairly obvious.
Yes. Well, yes... (CLEARS THROAT)
But I mean, you...
You are in a relationship?
- Yes, I am.
- You and Janine?
Hmm. Yes, me and Janine.
Care to elaborate?
Well, we're in a good place, it's, um,
very affirming.
- You got that from a book.
- Everyone got that from a book.
Okay, you two bad boys,
behave yourselves.
You, Sherl, you're going to have to
tell me where you were last night.
- Working.
- Working?
Of course. I'm the only one
who really knows what you're like.
- Remember?
- Don't you go letting on.
JANINE: I might just, actually.
I haven't told Mary about this,
I kind of wanted to surprise her.
Yeah, I think you probably will.
But we should have you two
over for dinner
- really soon.
- Yeah.
My place, though, not the scuzz dump.
Great, yeah. Dinner! Yeah.
Oh, I'd better dash.
- It was brilliant to see you.
- You, too.
Have a lovely day. Call me later.
I might do. I might call you.
Unless I meet someone prettier.
Solve me a crime, Sherlock Holmes.
You know Magnussen as a newspaper owner
but he is so much more than that.
He uses his power and wealth
to gain information.
The more he acquires,
the greater his wealth and power.
And I'm not exaggerating when I say
that he knows
the critical pressure point
on every person of note or influence
in the whole of the Western world
and probably beyond.
He is the Napoleon of blackmail.
And he has created
an unassailable architecture
of forbidden knowledge.
Its name is Appledore.
- Dinner.
- Sorry, what, dinner?
Me and Mary coming for dinner
with wine and...
sitting.
Seriously? I've just told you
that the Western world
is run from this house
and you want to talk about dinner?
Fine, talk about the house.
It is the greatest repository
of sensitive and dangerous information
anywhere in the world.
The Alexandrian library
of secrets and scandals.
And none of it is on a computer.
He's smart. Computers can be hacked.
It's all on hard copy in vaults
underneath that house.
And as long as it is,
the personal freedom of anyone
you've ever met is a fantasy.
(KNOCKING) Yoo-hoo.
Oh, that was the doorbell.
Couldn't you hear it?
It's in the fridge. It kept ringing.
- Oh, that's not a fault, Sherlock.
- Who is it?
Mr. Holmes says you can go right up.
(BEEPING)
(SIGHS) Go ahead.
Sir?
Can I have a moment?
He's fine.
Look, I...
Right, I should probably tell you...
Okay, I... That...
- And...
- (METAL CLANGING)
Doesn't mean I'm not pleased to see you.
I can vouch for this man,
he is a doctor.
If you know who I am,
then you know who he is.
Don't you, Mr. Magnussen?
I understood we were meeting
at your office.
This is my office.
Well, it is now.
SHERLOCK: Mr. Magnussen,
I have been asked to intercede with you
by Lady Elizabeth Smallwood
on the matter of her husband's letters.
Some time ago you put pressure on her
concerning those letters.
She would like those letters back.
Obviously the letters no longer have
any practical use to you
so with that in mind...
(CHUCKLING)
Something I said?
No, no. I was reading.
There's rather a lot.
Redbeard.
Sorry. Sorry, you were
probably talking?
I... (CLEARS THROAT)
I was trying to explain that
I have been asked to act on behalf...
- Bathroom?
- Along from the kitchen, sir.
MAGNUSSEN: Okay.
I've been asked to negotiate
the return of those letters.
I'm aware you do not
make copies of sensitive documents...
Is it like the rest of the flat?
- Sir?
- The bathroom?
- Yes, sir.
- Maybe not, then.
Am I acceptable to you
as an intermediary?
Lady Elizabeth Smallwood.
I like her.
Mr. Magnussen, am I acceptable to you
as an intermediary?
She's English with a spine.
Best thing about the English...
You're so domesticated.
Always standing around, apologising.
Keeping your little heads down.
(UNZIPPING TROUSERS)
You can do what you like here,
no one's ever going to stop you.
(URINATING)
A nation of herbivores.
I've interests
all over the world but, uh,
everything starts in England.
If it works here...
(ZIPPING TROUSERS)
...I'd try it in a real country.
The United Kingdom, eh?
Petri dish to the Western world.
Tell Lady Elizabeth
I might need those for later, so...
I'm keeping them.
Goodbye.
Anyway... (CHUCKLING)
...they're funny.
Jesus!
Did you notice
the one extraordinary thing he did?
There was a moment
that kind of stuck in the mind, yeah.
Exactly. When he showed us the letters.
Okay.
So, he's brought the letters to London.
So no matter what he says,
he's ready to make a deal.
Now, Magnussen only makes a deal
once he's established
a person's weaknesses,
the "pressure point", he calls it.
So, clearly he believes I'm
a drug addict and no serious threat.
And of course,
because he's in town tonight,
the letters will be in his safe,
in his London office,
while he's out to dinner with the
Marketing Group of Great Britain
- from 7:00 till 10:00.
- How do you know his schedule?
Because I do. Right, I'll see you
tonight. I've got some shopping to do.
- What's tonight?
- I'll text instructions.
I'll text you if I'm available.
SHERLOCK: You are, I checked!
- Don't bring a gun.
- Why would I bring a gun?
Or a knife or a tyre lever, probably
best not to do any arm-spraining
but we'll see how the night goes.
You're just assuming I'm coming along?
Time you got out of the house, John.
You've put on seven pounds
since you got married
and the cycling isn't doing it.
It's actually four pounds.
Mary and I think seven. See you later.
NEWSREADER:
And breaking news now,
John Garvie, MP, has been arrested today
on charges of corruption.
This follows an investigation into
information acquired...
Magnussen's office is on the top floor,
just below his private flat.
There are 14 layers of security
between us and him...
(BEEPING)
...two of which aren't even
legal in this country.
Want to know how
we're going to break in?
- Is that what we're doing?
- Of course it's what we're doing.
Magnussen's private lift, goes straight
to his penthouse and office.
Only he uses it and only his key card
calls the lift.
Anyone else even tries,
security is automatically informed.
Standard key card for the building.
Nicked it yesterday.
Only gets us as far as the canteen.
Here we go, then.
If I was to use this card
on that lift now,
- what happens?
- (ALARM BEEPING)
The alarms would go off
and you'd be dragged away by security.
Exactly.
You're taken to a small room somewhere,
your head kicked in.
- Do we really need so much colour?
- It passes the time.
But if I do this... If you press
a key card against your mobile phone
for long enough, it corrupts the
magnetic strip, the card stops working.
It's a common problem, never put
your key card with your phone.
What happens if I use the card now?
(BEEPING)
It still doesn't work.
But it doesn't read as
the wrong card now.
It registers as corrupted.
But if it's corrupted, how do they
know it's not Magnussen?
Oh.
Would they risk dragging him off?
Probably not.
So what do they do?
What do they have to do?
Check if it's him or not.
There's a camera at eye height
to the right of the door.
(BEEPING)
A live picture of the card user
is relayed directly to Magnussen's
personal staff in his office,
the only people trusted
to make a positive ID.
At this hour, almost certainly his PA.
So, how does that help us?
Human error. I've been shopping.
Here we go, then.
(BEEP)
You realise you don't exactly
look like Magnussen?
Which, in this case,
is a considerable advantage.
(BEEPING)
Sherlock, you complete loon,
what are you doing?
- Hang on, is that...
- Hi, Janine.
Go on, let me in.
I can't, you know I can't.
Don't be silly.
Don't make me do it out here, not...
in front of everyone.
Do what in front of everyone?
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
(BEEP)
You see? As long as there's people,
there's always a weak spot.
- That was Janine.
- Yes, of course it was Janine,
she's Magnussen's PA,
that's the whole point.
Did you just get engaged
to break into an office?
Yeah. Stroke of luck
meeting her at your wedding.
You can take some of the credit.
Je... Jesus, Sherlock, she loves you.
Yes. Like I said, human error.
What are you going to do?
Well, not actually marry her, obviously.
There's only so far you can go.
So what will you tell her?
Well, I'll tell her that our entire
relationship was a ruse
to break into her boss's office.
I imagine she'll want to stop seeing me
at that point
but you're the expert on women.
So, where did she go?
That's a bit rude.
I just proposed to her.
Sherlock.
Did she faint?
Do they really do that?
It's a blow to the head.
She's breathing.
- Janine.
- (MURMURS)
Another in here.
Security.
JOHN: Does he need help?
Ex-con, white supremacist
by the tattoos, so who cares?
Stick with Janine.
Janine, focus on my voice now.
Can you hear me?
(WHISPERS) Hey!
They must still be here.
(WHISPERING) So is Magnussen,
his seat's still warm,
he should be at dinner
but he's still in the building.
- Upstairs.
- We should call the police.
During our own burglary? You're really
not a natural at this, are you?
(SIGHS)
- No, wait, shh...
- (BEEPS)
(INHALES)
Perfume. Not Janine's.
Claire-de-la-lune. Why do I know it?
Mary wears it.
No, not Mary, somebody else.
JOHN: Sherlock!
MAGNUSSEN: Coming here?
What... What would your husband think?
He... Your lovely husband.
He's honourable.
- What would he say to you now?
- (COCKING GUN)
(STAMMERING)
MAGNUSSEN: You're doing this to protect
him from the truth?
What is this obsession here
with honesty?
Additionally,
if you're going to commit murder,
you might consider
changing your perfume,
Lady Smallwood.
(GASPS)
Sorry, who?
That's not Lady Smallwood, Mr. Holmes.
- Is John with you?
- He's, um...
Is John here?
He's downstairs.
So, what do you do now?
Kill us both?
Mary, whatever he's got on you,
let me help.
Oh, Sherlock, if you take one more step,
I swear I will kill you.
No, Mrs. Watson,
you won't.
(GUN FIRING)
I'm sorry, Sherlock.
Truly I am.
Mary.
(ALARM BLARING)
It's not like it is in the movies.
There's not a great big spurt of blood
and you go flying backwards.
The impact isn't spread
over a wide area,
it's tightly focused so there's little
or no energy transfer.
You stay still and the
bullet pushes through.
You're almost certainly going to die,
so we need to focus.
(GASPS)
I said focus!
It's all well and clever
having a mind palace
but you've only three seconds
of consciousness left to use it.
So come on, what's going to kill you?
- Blood loss.
- Exactly.
So, it's all about one thing now,
forwards or backwards.
You need to decide which way
you're going to fall.
- One hole or two?
- Sorry?
Is the bullet still inside you
or is there an exit wound?
It will depend on the gun.
That one, I think.
Or that one.
Oh, for God's sake, Sherlock,
it doesn't matter about the gun,
don't be stupid.
You always were so stupid.
Such a disappointment.
I'm not stupid.
You're a very stupid little boy.
Mummy and Daddy are very cross,
because it doesn't matter
about the gun.
Why not?
You saw the whole room
when you entered it.
What was directly behind you
when you were murdered?
Not been murdered yet.
Balance of probability, little brother.
If the bullet had passed through you,
what would you have heard?
The mirror shattering.
You didn't, therefore...
The bullet's still inside me.
ANDERSON: So we need
to take him down backwards.
I agree.
Sherlock, you need to fall on your back.
ANDERSON: Right now the bullet
is the cork in a bottle.
The bullet itself is blocking
most of the blood flow.
But any pressure or impact on
the entrance wound could dislodge it.
Plus, on your back,
gravity is working for us.
Fall now.
What is that? What's happening?
You're going into shock. It's the next
thing that's going to kill you.
- What do I do?
- Don't go into shock, obviously.
Must be something in this
ridiculous memory palace
of yours that can calm you down.
(ECHOING)
Find it.
The east wind is coming, Sherlock.
It's coming to get you. (ECHOING)
Pain containment.
Hello, Redbeard.
Here, boy. Come on, come to me.
It's okay, it's all right.
Come on, it's me. It's me, come on.
Come on.
Good boy, clever boy.
Hello, Redbeard.
They're putting me down, too, now.
It's no fun, is it? Redbeard.
(DOG BARKING)
MOLLY: Without the shock,
you're going to feel the pain.
There's a hole ripped through you.
Massive internal bleeding.
You have to control the pain.
(SCREAMS) Control, control, control.
You.
You never felt pain, did you?
Why did you never feel pain?
You always feel it, Sherlock.
But you don't have to fear it!
(GROANING)
Pain.
Heartbreak.
Loss.
Death.
It's all good.
Sherlock? Sherlock, can you hear me?
- What happened?
- He got shot.
Jesus.
Sherlock! Oh my...
Who shot him?
WOMAN: (ON PHONE)
Emergency, which service do you require?
♪ It's raining, it's pouring
♪ It's raining, I'm crying
♪ Sherlock is dying ♪
We're losing you. Sherlock!
Come on, Sherlock.
Just die, why can't you?
One little push
and off you pop.
(FLATLINE TONE DRONING)
You're going to love being dead,
Sherlock. No one ever bothers you.
Mrs. Hudson will cry.
And Mummy and Daddy will cry.
And the women will cry and John will cry
buckets and buckets.
It's him that I worry about the most.
That wife...
You're letting him down, Sherlock.
John Watson is definitely in danger.
(GROANS)
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, you're not getting better, are you?
Was it something I said, huh?
Sherlock!
(BEEPS)
(GROANS)
(BEEP)
(BEEPS)
(HEARTBEAT MONITOR BEEPING)
- Mary.
- Hey.
He's only bloody woken up.
- He's pulled through.
- Really?
- Yeah, you...
- Seriously?
...Mrs. Watson. You're in big trouble.
Really, why?
His first word when he woke up?
Mary.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
(SIGHS)
MARY: You don't tell him.
Sherlock!
You don't tell John.
MAGNUSSEN: Bad girl.
Bad, bad girl.
Look at me.
And tell me you're
not going to tell him.
I'm buying a cottage.
I made a lot of money
out of you, Mister.
Nothing hits the spot
like revenge with profits.
You didn't give these stories
to Magnussen, did you?
God no. One of his rivals,
- he was spittin'.
- Hmm.
Sherlock Holmes, you are a backstabbing,
heartless, manipulative bastard.
You, as it turns out,
are a grasping, opportunistic,
publicity-hungry, tabloid whore.
- So we're good, then?
- Yeah, of course.
Where's the cottage?
Sussex Downs.
- Oh, nice.
- It's gorgeous.
There's beehives
but I'm getting rid of those.
(GASPING)
Oh, it hurts, does it?
Might want to restart your morphine.
I might have fiddled with the taps.
How much more revenge
are you going to need?
Just the occasional top-up.
Dream come true for you, this place.
They actually attach the drugs to you.
Not good for working.
You won't be working
for a while, Sherl.
You lied to me.
You lied and lied.
I exploited the fact of our connection.
- When?
- Hmm?
Just once would have been nice.
Oh.
I was waiting till we got married.
That was never going to happen.
Got to go.
I'm not supposed to keep you talking.
And also,
I have an interview with The One Show
and I haven't made it up yet.
Oh.
Just one thing.
You shouldn't have lied to me.
I know what kind of man you are.
We could have been friends.
I'll give your love to John and Mary.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(HUFFING)
MARY: You don't tell him.
You don't tell John.
So...
you're Mary Watson.
Who are you?
(WHISPERS) Mary Watson.
JOHN: I don't know how much sense
you'll get out of him.
He's drugged up,
so he's pretty much babbling.
Oh, they won't let
you use that in here, you know.
No, I'm not going to use the phone,
I just want to take a video.
Hmm.
Oh, Jesus.
So where would he go?
Well, Christ knows.
Try finding Sherlock in London.
LESTRADE: He's got
three known bolt-holes.
Parliament Hill, Camden Lock
and Dagmar Court.
Five known bolt-holes.
There's the blind greenhouse
in Kew Gardens
and the leaning tomb
in Hampstead Cemetery.
Just a spare bedroom.
Well, my bedroom.
We agreed he needs the space.
Behind the clock face of Big Ben.
I think he was probably joking.
No, I don't think so.
Leinster Gardens, that's his
number one bolt-hole.
It's top, top secret.
He only knows about it
because he stalked him one night.
- Followed.
- Followed, yeah.
He knew who shot him.
The bullet wound was here,
so he was facing whoever it was.
So why not tell us?
Because he's tracking
them down himself...
Or protecting them.
Protecting the shooter, why?
Well, protecting someone, then.
But why would he care?
He's Sherlock, who would
he bother protecting?
Call me if you hear anything,
don't hold out on me, John.
- Call me, okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, right.
Okay, goodnight, then.
Bye, then.
John, need a cuppa?
Mrs. Hudson, why does Sherlock think
that I'll be moving back in here?
Oh, yes, he's put your
chair back again, hasn't he?
That's nice. Looks much better.
John, what's wrong? Tell me.
- John.
- (MOBILE VIBRATING)
That's your phone, isn't it?
It's Sherlock, John. It's Sherlock.
John, you have to answer it!
(MOBILE VIBRATING)
- Spare any change, love?
- No.
Oh, come on, love,
don't be like all the rest.
Rule one of looking for Sherlock Holmes,
he finds you.
You're working for Sherlock now.
Keeps me off the streets, innit?
Well, no.
(MOBILE RINGING)
Where are you?
SHERLOCK: Can't you see me?
What am I looking for?
The lie, the lie of Leinster Gardens
hidden in plain sight.
Hardlyanyone notices, people live
here foryears and never see it
but if you are what I think you are,
it'll take you less than a minute.
The houses, Mary. Look at the houses.
How did you know I'd come here?
Well, I knew you'd talk to the people
no one else would bother with.
(SCOFFS) I thought I was being clever.
You're always clever, Mary,
I was relying on that.
I planted the information
for you to find.
Ohhh!
30 seconds.
What am I looking at?
No doorknobs, no letterbox,
painted windows.
23 and24 Leinster Gardens.
The empty houses.
They were demolished years ago
to make way for the London Underground.
Vents for the old steam trains.
Only the very front section of the house
remains, it's just a facade.
Remind you of anyone, Mary?
A facade.
Sorry, I never could resist
a touch of drama.
Do come in. It's a little cramped.
MARY: Do you own this place?
SHERLOCK: Mmm. I won it in a card game
with the Clarence House cannibal.
Nearly cost me my kidneys
but fortunately, I had a straight flush.
Quite a gambler, that woman.
What do you want, Sherlock?
Mary Morstan was stillborn
in October, 1972.
Her gravestone is in Chiswick Cemetery,
where five years ago,
you acquired her name and date of birth
and thereafter, her identity.
That's why you don't have friends
from before that date.
Need to work on your half
of the church, Mary.
Looking a bit thin.
Oh, orphan's lot.
Friends, that's all I have.
It's an old enough technique,
known to the kinds of people
who could recognise
a skip code on sight.
At first I thought it was just a Bible
thing, you know, spam, but it's not.
It's a skip code.
And extraordinarily retentive memories.
How can you not remember which room?
You remember everything.
- I have to delete something!
- 207.
You were very slow.
How good a shot are you?
How badly do you want to find out?
If I die here, my body
will be found in a building
with your face
projected on the front of it,
even Scotland Yard could
getsomewhere with that.
I want to know how good you are.
Go on, show me.
The doctor's wife must be
a little bit bored by now.
(GUN CLICKING)
May I see?
(SCOFFS) A dummy?
Well, I suppose that was
a fairly obvious trick.
And yet, over a distance of six feet
you failed to make a kill shot.
Enough to hospitalise me,
not enough to kill me.
That wasn't a miss.
That was surgery.
- I'll take the case.
- What case?
Yours.
Why didn't you come to me
in the first place?
Because John can't ever know
that I lied to him.
It would break him
and I would lose him forever
and Sherlock, I will never
let that happen.
Please.
Understand.
There is nothing in this world
I would not do to stop that happening.
Sorry.
Not that obvious a trick.
Oh.
(GASPING)
Now, talk
and sort it out and do it quickly.
(HARK! THEHERALDANGELSSING
PLAYING ON STEREO)
MYCROFT: Oh, dear God. It's only 2:00.
It's been Christmas Day
for at least a week now.
How can it only be 2:00? I am in agony.
MRS. HOLMES: Mikey, is this your laptop?
Upon which depends
the security of the free world, yes.
And you've got potatoes on it.
Well, you shouldn't leave it
lying around, if it's so important.
Why are we doing this? We never do this.
We are here because Sherlock is home
from hospital
and we are all very happy.
Am I happy, too? I haven't checked.
Behave, Mike.
Mycroft is the name you gave me,
if you could possibly struggle
all the way to the end.
Mrs. Holmes.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Not absolutely sure why you're here.
I invited him.
I'm his protégé, Mrs. Holmes.
When he dies,
I get all his stuff and his job.
- Nope.
- Oh. Well, I'll help out a bit.
Closer.
If he does get murdered or something.
Probably stop talking now.
Okay.
Lovely when you bring
your friends round.
Stop it, you.
Somebody has put a bullet in my boy
and if I ever find out who,
I shall turn absolutely monstrous.
Ah, this was for Mary.
I'll be back in a minute.
Ah, Mary.
There you are. Cup of tea.
Now, if Father starts making
little humming noises,
just give him a little poke,
that usually does it.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
- Did you write this?
Oh, that silly old thing.
You mustn't read that.
Mathematics does seem
terribly fatuous now.
Now, no humming, you!
Complete flake, my wife,
but happens to be a genius.
She was a mathematician?
Gave it all up for children.
I could never bear to argue with her.
I'm something of a moron myself.
But she's...
unbelievably hot.
(LAUGHING) Oh, my God.
You're the sane one, aren't you?
Aren't you?
(DOOR OPENING)
Oh, sorry. I just...
Oh. Do you two need a moment?
If you don't mind.
No, of course not. I'll go see if I can
help with something or another.
Those two.
They all right?
Well, you know,
they've had their ups and downs.
Baker Street. Now.
John.
Mary.
Oh, Sherlock.
Oh, good gracious, you look terrible.
Get me some morphine from your kitchen,
I've run out.
I don't have any morphine.
Then what exactly is the point of you?
What is going on?
Bloody good question.
The Watsons are about to have
a domestic and fairly quickly, I hope,
because we've got work to do.
No, I have a better question.
Is everyone I have ever met
a psychopath?
Yes.
SHERLOCK: Good that we've settled that.
- Now...
- Shut up!
And stay shut up.
Because this is not funny.
Not this time.
- I didn't say it was funny.
- You...
What have I ever done?
Hmm?
My whole life, to deserve you?
Everything.
Sherlock, I told you,
shut up.
No, I mean it, seriously. Everything.
Everything you've ever done
is what you did.
Sherlock, one more word
and you will not need morphine.
You were a doctor who went to war.
You're a man who couldn't stay
in the suburbs for more than a month
without storming a crack den
and beating up a junkie.
Your best friend is a sociopath
who solves crimes
as an alternative to getting high.
That's me, by the way. Hello.
Even the landlady used to run
a drug cartel.
It was my husband's cartel.
I was just typing.
And exotic dancing.
Sherlock Holmes,
if you've been YouTubing...
John, you are addicted
to a certain lifestyle.
You're abnormally attracted to
dangerous situations and people,
so is it truly such a surprise
that the woman you fall in love with
conforms to that pattern?
But she wasn't supposed to be like that.
Why is she like that?
Because you chose her.
Why is everything always...
- my fault!
- Ooh, the neighbours.
John, listen. Be calm and answer me.
What is she?
- My lying wife?
- No, what is she?
And the woman who's carrying my child
who has lied to me
since the day I met her?
SHERLOCK: No, not in this flat,
not in this room.
Right here, right now, what is she?
Okay.
Your way.
Always your way.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SNIFFS)
Sit.
Why?
Because that's where they sit.
The people who come in here
with their stories.
The clients.
That's all you are now, Mary.
You're a client.
This is where you sit and talk
and this is where we sit and listen.
Then we decide if we want you or not.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So you're okay?
Oh! Are we doing conversation today?
It really is Christmas.
(SCOFFS) Now?
Seriously? Months of silence
and we're going to do this now?
A-G-R-A. What's that?
MARY: Uh...
My initials.
Everything about who I was is on there.
If you love me,
don't read it in front of me.
Why?
Because you won't love me
when you've finished.
And I don't want to see that happen.
(JOHN SIGHS)
How much do you know already?
By your skill set, you are or were
an intelligence agent.
Your accent is currently English
but I suspect you are not.
You're on the run from something.
You've used your skills to disappear.
Magnussen knows your secret,
which is why you were going to kill him
and I assume you befriended Janine
in order to get close to him.
Oh, you can talk.
Oh, look at you two.
You should have got married.
The stuff Magnussen has on me,
I would go to prison
for the rest of my life.
So you were just going to kill him?
People like Magnussen should be killed.
That's why there are people like me.
Perfect!
So that's what you were?
An assassin? How could I not see that?
You did see that.
And you married me.
Because he's right.
It's what you like.
So, Mary...
Any documents that Magnussen has
concerning yourself, you want...
extracted and returned.
Why would you help me?
Because you saved my life.
Sorry, sorry, what?
When I happened on you and Magnussen,
you had a problem.
More specifically, you had a witness.
MAGNUSSEN: What do you do now?
Kill the both of us?
SHERLOCK: This solution,
of course, was simple.
Kill us both and leave.
However,
sentiment got the better of you.
SHERLOCK: One precisely calculated shot
to incapacitate me
in the hope that it would bide you
more time to negotiate my silence.
Of course, you couldn't shoot Magnussen.
On the night that both of us
broke into the building
your own husband
would become a suspect so...
SHERLOCK: You calculated
that Magnussen would use the fact
of your involvement
rather than sharing the information
with the police, as is his MO.
And then you left the way you came.
- Have I missed anything?
- How did she save your life?
- She phoned the ambulance.
- I phoned the ambulance.
She phoned first.
(MOBILE BEEPING)
WOMAN: Emergency, which service
do you require?
You didn't find me
for another five minutes.
Left to you, I would have died.
The average arrival time
for a London ambulance is...
MEDIC: Did somebody call an ambulance?
SHERLOCK: Eight minutes.
Did you bring any morphine?
I asked on the phone.
- We were told there was a shooting.
- There was, last week.
But I believe I'm bleeding internally.
My pulse is very erratic.
You may need to restart my heart.
- Whoa.
- John... John.
John, Magnussen is all that matters now.
You can trust Mary.
- She saved my life.
- She shot you.
Uh, mixed messages,
I grant you. That is a...
- (GROANING)
- Sherlock... Sherlock. Take him.
- Got him?
- MEDIC: Yeah.
(SHERLOCK GROANING)
So, have you read it?
- Would you come here a moment?
- No. Tell me, have you?
Just come here.
No, I'm fine.
I've thought long and hard about
what I want to say to you.
These are prepared words, Mary.
- I've chosen these words with care.
- Okay...
(CLEARS THROAT)
The problems of your past
are your business.
The problems of your future
are my privilege.
That's all I have to say,
that's all I need to know.
(CLEARING THROAT) No, I didn't read it.
You don't even know my name.
- Is Mary Watson good enough for you?
- Yes.
- Oh, my God, yes.
- Then it's good enough for me, too.
(TEARFULLY) Oh...
All this does not mean that I'm not
still basically pissed off with you.
I know, I know.
(WHISPERING) I am very pissed off
and it will come out now and then.
I know, I know, I know.
You can mow the sodding lawn
from now on.
- I do mow the lawn.
- I do it loads.
You really don't.
- I choose the baby's name.
- Not a chance.
JOHN: Okay.
I'm glad you've given up
on the Magnussen business.
Are you?
I'm still curious, though.
It's hardly your usual kind of puzzle.
Why do you hate him?
Because he attacks
people who are different
and preys on their secrets.
Why don't you?
He never causes too much damage
to anyone important.
He's far too intelligent for that.
He's a businessman, that's all.
And occasionally useful to us.
A necessary evil.
Not a dragon for you to slay.
A dragon-slayer.
- Is that what you think of me?
- No.
It's what you think of yourself.
Are you two smoking?
- No!
- It was Mycroft.
I have, by the way,
a job offer
I should like you to decline.
- I decline your kind offer.
- I shall pass on your regrets.
- What was it?
- MI6.
They want to place you back
into Eastern Europe.
An undercover assignment
that will prove fatal to you
in, I think, about six months.
Then why don't you want me to take it?
It's tempting but on balance, you have
more utility closer to home.
(SCOFFING) Utility.
How do I have utility?
Here be dragons.
(COUGHS) This isn't agreeing with me.
I'm going in.
You need low tar.
You still smoke like a beginner.
Also...
- your loss would break my heart.
- (COUGHING)
What the hell
am I supposed to say to that?
- Merry Christmas?
- You hate Christmas.
Yes.
Perhaps there was something
in the punch.
Clearly. Go and have some more.
MARY: So you realise
that Sherlock got us
out here to see
his mum and dad for a reason?
His lovely mum and dad.
Fine example of married life,
I get that.
That is the thing with Sherlock.
It's always the unexpected.
Oi... Oi...
Mary? Jesus Christ, Mary?
Sit down. Mary, can you hear me?
Don't drink Mary's tea.
SHERLOCK: Oh, or the punch.
JOHN: Sherlock?
Did you just drug my pregnant wife?
Don't worry.
Wiggins is an excellent chemist.
I calculated your wife's dose meself.
Won't affect the little one.
I'll keep an eye on her.
He'll monitor their recovery.
It's more or less his day job.
What the hell have you done?
Deal with the Devil.
MAGNUSSEN: Shouldn't you be in hospital?
I am in hospital. This is the canteen.
- Is it?
- In my opinion, yes.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I've been thinking about you.
Really?
I want to see Appledore.
Where you keep all the secrets,
all the files,
everything you've got on everyone.
I want you to invite me.
What makes you think
I'd be so careless?
Oh, I think you're a lot more careless
than you let on.
Am I?
It's the dead-eye stare
that gives it away.
Except it's not dead-eyed, is it?
You're reading.
Portable Appledore.
How does it work?
Built-in flash drive?
4G wireless?
They're just ordinary spectacles.
Yes, they are.
You underestimate me, Mr. Holmes.
Impress me, then.
Show me Appledore.
Everything's available for a price.
- You making me an offer?
- A Christmas present.
Then what are you giving me
for Christmas, Mr. Holmes?
My brother.
Jesus.
Sherlock, please tell me
you haven't just gone out of your mind.
I'd rather keep you guessing.
- (HELICOPTER HOVERING)
- Ah! There's our lift.
- Coming?
- Where?
- Want your wife to be safe?
- Yeah, of course I do.
Good, because this is going to be
incredibly dangerous.
One false move and we'll have
betrayed the security
of the United Kingdom and be imprisoned
for high treason.
Magnussen is quite simply the most
dangerous man we've ever encountered
and the odds are comprehensively
stacked against us.
But it's Christmas.
I feel the same.
Oh, you mean it's actually Christmas.
Did you bring your gun as I suggested?
Why would I bring my gun
to your parents' house
for Christmas dinner?
- Is it in your coat?
- Yes.
- Off we go, then.
- Where are we going?
Appledore.
(ELEVATOR BEEPS)
I would offer you a drink
but it's very rare and expensive.
(SIGHS)
Oh. It was you.
MAGNUSSEN: Yes, of course.
Very hard to find
a pressure point on you, Mr. Holmes.
SHERLOCK: Hmm.
The drugs thing I never believed
for a moment.
Anyway, you wouldn't care
if it was exposed, would you?
But look how you care about John Watson.
Your damsel in distress.
JOHN: You...
put me in a fire for leverage?
Oh, I'd never let you burn, Dr. Watson.
I had people standing by.
I am not a murderer.
Unlike your wife.
Let me explain how leverage works,
Dr. Watson.
For those who understand these things,
Mycroft Holmes is the most powerful man
in the country.
Well, apart from me.
Mycroft's pressure point is his
junkie detective brother Sherlock.
Sherlock's pressure point
is his best friend John Watson.
John Watson's pressure point
is his wife.
I own John Watson's wife,
I own Mycroft.
He's what I'm getting for Christmas.
It's an exchange, not a gift.
Forgive me but...
- I already seem to have it.
- It's password protected.
In return for the password, you will
give me any material in your possession
pertaining to the woman
I know as Mary Watson.
Oh, she's bad, that one.
So many dead people.
- You should see what I've seen.
- I don't need to see it.
Well, you might enjoy it, though.
I enjoy it.
Then, why don't you show us?
Show you Appledore?
The secret vaults?
Is that what you want?
I want everything you've got on Mary.
(CHUCKLING)
You know,
I honestly expected something good.
Oh, I think you'll find
the contents of that laptop...
Include the GPS locator.
By now your brother
will have noticed the theft
and Security Services
will be converging on this house.
Having arrived, they'll find
top secret information in my hands.
And they'll have every justification
to search my vaults.
They will discover further information
of this kind, then I'll be imprisoned.
You will be exonerated.
Restored to your smelly little apartment
to solve crimes
with Mr. and Mrs. Psychopath.
Mycroft has been looking
for this opportunity for a long time.
He'll be a very, very proud big brother.
The fact that you know it's going
to happen isn't going to stop it.
Then why am I smiling?
Ask me.
Why are you smiling?
Because Sherlock Holmes has made
one enormous mistake
which will destroy the lives
of everyone he loves
and everything he holds dear.
Let me show you the Appledore vaults.
The entrance to my vaults.
This is where I keep you all.
JOHN: Okay.
So where are the vaults, then?
Vaults? What vaults?
There are no vaults
beneath this building.
They're all in here.
The Appledore vaults
are my mind palace.
You know about mind palaces,
don't you, Sherlock?
How to store information
so you never forget it,
by picturing it.
I just sit here, I close my eyes
and down I go to my vaults.
I can go anywhere inside my vaults.
My memories.
I'll look at the files on Mrs. Watson.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(HUMMING)
Oh, this is one of my favourites.
Oh, it's so exciting.
(CHUCKLING)
All those whackjobs for the CIA.
Ooh! She's gone a bit freelance now.
Bad girl.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, she's so wicked.
I can really see why you like her.
You see?
(CLEARING THROAT)
So there are no documents,
you don't actually have anything here?
Oh, sometimes I send out for something
if I really need it but
- mostly I just remember it all.
- I don't understand.
- You should have that on a t-shirt.
- You just remember it all?
It's all about knowledge.
Everything is.
Knowing is owning.
But if you just know it,
then you don't have proof.
Proof? What would I need proof for?
I'm in news, you moron.
I don't have to prove it,
I just have to print it.
Speaking of news, you will both be
heavily featured tomorrow.
Trying to sell state secrets to me.
(TUTTING)
Let's go outside.
They'll be here shortly.
Can't wait to see you arrested.
Sherlock, do we have a plan?
Sherlock?
MAGNUSSEN:
They're taking their time, aren't they?
- I still don't understand.
- And there's the back of the t-shirt.
You just know things.
How does that work?
I just so love
your little soldier face.
I'd like to punch it.
Bring it over here a minute.
Come on, for Mary. Bring me your face.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Lean forward a bit
and stick your face out.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Please.
Now, can I flick it?
Can I flick your face?
(CHUCKLING) Oh, I just love doing this.
I could do it all day.
It works like this, John.
I know who Mary hurt and killed.
I know where to find people
who hate her.
I know where they live.
I know their phone numbers.
All in my mind palace. All of it.
I could phone them right now
and tear your whole life down.
And I will.
Unless you let me flick your face.
This is what I do to people.
This is what I do to whole countries.
Just because I know.
Can I do your eye now?
See if you can keep it open. Hmm?
(CHUCKLING)
Come on, for Mary. Keep it open.
JOHN: Sherlock...
SHERLOCK: Let him, I'm sorry. Just...
let him.
Hmm? Come on, eye open.
(MAGNUSSEN LAUGHING)
It's difficult, isn't it?
Janine managed it once.
She makes the funniest noises.
(INDISTINCT VOICES ON RADIO)
Sherlock Holmes and John Watson,
stand away from that man.
Here we go, Mr. Holmes.
To clarify, Appledore's vaults
only exist in your mind?
Nowhere else. Just there.
They're not real. They never have been.
MYCROFT:
Sherlock Holmes and John Watson.
- Step away.
- It's fine.
- They're harmless.
- MAN: Target not armed.
- Sherlock, what do we do?
- Nothing.
There's nothing to be done.
Oh, I'm not a villain.
I have no evil plan.
I'm a businessman, acquiring assets.
You happen to be one of them.
Sorry. No chance for you
to be a hero this time, Mr. Holmes.
MYCROFT:
Sherlock Holmes and John Watson,
stand away from that man. Do it now.
Oh, do your research.
I'm not a hero.
I'm a high-functioning sociopath.
Merry Christmas!
- (GUNSHOT)
- MAN: Man down. Man down.
Get away from me, John! Stay well back.
- Christ, Sherlock!
- Don't fire.
MYCROFT:
Do not fire on Sherlock Holmes.
Do not fire!
JOHN: Oh, Christ, Sherlock.
Give my love to Mary.
Tell her she's safe now.
Oh, Sherlock.
What have you done?
MYCROFT:
As my colleague is fond of remarking,
this country sometimes needs
a blunt instrument.
Equally, it sometimes needs a dagger.
A scalpel, wielded with precision
and without remorse.
There will always come a time
when we need Sherlock Holmes.
If this is some expression
of familial sentiment...
Don't be absurd.
I am not given to outbursts
of brotherly compassion.
You know what happened to the other one.
In any event, there is no prison
in which we could incarcerate Sherlock
without causing a riot on a daily basis.
The alternative, however,
would require your approval.
Hardly merciful, Mr. Holmes.
MYCROFT: Regrettably, Lady Smallwood,
my brother is a murderer.
SHERLOCK: You will look after him
for me, won't you?
Oh!
Don't worry, I'll keep him in trouble.
That's my girl.
Since this is likely to be the last
conversation I'll have with John Watson,
would you mind if we took a moment?
So here we are. (CLEARS THROAT)
- William Sherlock Scott Holmes.
- Sorry?
That's the whole of it.
If you're looking for baby names.
(CHUCKLING) No, we've had a scan.
We're pretty sure it's a girl.
Oh... Okay.
Yeah...
You know,
I can't think of a single thing to say.
No, neither can I.
- The game is over.
- The game is never over, John.
But there may be some new players now.
That's okay.
The east wind takes us all in the end.
What's that?
It's a story my brother told me
when we were kids.
The east wind, this terrifying force
that lays waste to all in its path.
Seeks out the unworthy
and plucks them from the Earth.
- That was generally me.
- Nice.
He was a rubbish big brother.
(CLEARING THROAT)
So what about you, then?
Where are you actually going now?
Oh, some undercover work
in Eastern Europe.
- For how long?
- Six months,
my brother estimates.
He's never wrong.
And then what?
Who knows?
John, there's something...
I should say, I've meant to
say always and I never have.
Since it's unlikely
we'll ever meet again,
I might as well say it now.
Sherlock is actually a girl's name.
- It's not.
- It was worth a try.
We're not naming our daughter after you.
I think it could work.
To the very best of times, John.
- (MEN CHEERING)
- COMMENTATOR: This one's good...
Alexander comes in for a tackle...
- ALL: Oh!
- Oh, he missed it!
MAN: Oi, what's wrong the telly?
Something wrong with the telly, mate.
MAN 2: Get it working!
- MAN: Who's that?
- (DISTORTED VOICE) Did you miss me?
Did you miss me?
Did you miss me? Did you miss me?
- Did you miss me?
- How is this possible?
We don't know.
But it's on every screen in the country,
- every screen simultaneously.
- Has the Prime Minister been told?
And Mycroft?
But that's not possible.
That is simply not possible.
What's happened?
MAN: Sir? It's your brother.
- Mycroft.
- Hello, little brother.
- How's the exile going?
- I've only been gone four minutes.
Well, I certainly hope
you've learnt your lesson.
As it turns out, you're needed.
Oh, for God's sake, make up your mind.
Who needs me this time?
(DISTORTED) Did you miss me?
Did you miss me? Did you miss me?
Did you miss me?
- Did you miss me?
- England.
But he's dead. I mean, you told me
he was dead, Moriarty.
Absolutely. He blew his own brains out.
So how can he be back?
(SIGHING) Well, if he is,
he'd better wrap up warm.
There's an east wind coming.
Miss me?