My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell,
I have been released from prison
and returned home
with only one goal...
to save my city,
but things have changed.
Instead of operating
outside the law,
I am now working
alongside the police.
I am no longer inmate 4587.
I am once more...
The Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
There's always gonna
be another Dante.
There's always gonna be a
logical reason to compromise,
but I'm not doing
that anymore.
- Walking way is not the answer.
- Well, I'm not walking away.
I'm gonna call
my own shots.
I went to go check
your midterm results online,
and I didn't come across any test results
because you didn't take the exams.
- Why?
- Because I got expelled.
So you found this place
by watching that documentary?
Vigilantes were
the death of Star City,
and they got exactly
what they deserved.
We now have
unfettered access
to the Archer Program's
entire security interface.
Let's find those bombs.
- Heading home soon?
- Not quite yet.
I'll see you
in the morning.
What's it say?
Nothing.
Just some punk kid
pulling a prank.
You ever get in
trouble with your parents?
Uh, yeah.
All the time. Why?
Because William doesn't
need pancakes.
William needs to tell us
why he got expelled
and why he's been
lying to us.
- After pancakes or...
- no.
OK.
- Ready to talk?
- About what?
Why you got
expelled.
Come on, will.
You know you can talk
to us about
anything. Please.
It's not a big deal.
I just got into a fight.
I thought you'd be
proud of me.
I went for the nose
just like you told me.
When did you tell him
to go for the nose?
That was over
a year ago,
and it was a lesson in self-defense,
thank you.
Buddy, it's not like
you to get into a fight.
Why do you guys
even care?
Every time that we spoke,
you're telling me
how much you love
your school,
about your new friends
and your classes.
What am I missing here?
Maybe you should have
asked how I felt for once,
but you don't ask other
people for their opinions.
You decide everything
on your own
just like you decided
to go to prison
rather than take care
of your family!
I don't think
that's fair, but OK.
William, you got
expelled,
and, young man, you
need to understand
that in life you have to
accept responsibility
for your actions.
Yeah? I'm over this.
W-William. Hey.
William, we're not
done here.
That went well.
Damn it! Still no luck
figuring out
where Felicity planted
those bombs.
Well, I'm pretty sure
hitting that thing harder's
not gonna make it
work better.
Makes me feel
better, though.
The Archer Program's
supposed to see everything,
but what good's that when
there's nothing to see?
About damn time.
Your algorithm
kind of sucks.
Ah. Nice to see you, too.
Give it to me.
Archer's not helping us,
and that means
Blackstar's our only lead
on finding those bombs.
You guys have any luck
tracking her down?
Uh-uh. I spent the last few
days searching the entire city,
but she knows
how to be a ghost.
Pretty easy to do with
the way the city is now.
OK. My algorithm
isn't the problem.
The Archer Program was designed
to monitor The Glades,
but Star City is
10 times the size
with half the technological
infrastructure.
So less eyes covering
a larger area.
Even if that's
the case,
that bomb plan
was massive.
We should have
found something.
Well, not if the bombs haven't
been positioned yet.
I mean,
maybe Felicity stockpiled them
somewhere
off the grid,
somewhere no one would
ever think to look.
I think
I might know a place.
This is definitely
off the grid.
God.
I used to think this place was so cool.
I can't believe
it's still standing.
I can't believe my dad
used to call this home.
Yeah. Well, no one's called
this home for quite some time.
Someone's been here.
Unh!
Someone's
still here.
I told you this
wouldn't end well.
What's that, some
A.R.G.U.S. fan mail?
No, not exactly.
Oh. This is some I know what
you did last summer creepiness.
- You want me to run a DNA trace?
- No. Already on top of that.
Besides, that's not the reason
why I called you in here.
How's the search
for Dante coming?
Good. We were able to backtrace
the number Diaz called.
It belongs to Dante's contact in Egypt,
a guy by the name of Virgil.
If we're able to bring him in,
we'll have Dante.
Fantastic!
And we would have you to thank for it.
Excellent work,
Curtis.
Too bad I might not be
around for my victory lap.
What are we talking
about here?
There's no good way
to say this,
but I've been offered a job at the
kohler humanitarian institute in D.C.
I would be able to create
tech that would be able
to help people
all over the world.
Curtis, I know you're not happy
with the ghost initiative,
but I was hoping that
we could get past that.
Besides, the work you're doing
right here at A.R.G.U.S.
is already helping people
all over the world.
I know you
believe that, John.
I'm just not sure
that I do.
The key is to maintain
eye contact.
Your assailant's gonna
focus on your weakness.
In this case,
it's that injury.
So you draw them in,
and as soon as they're
close enough, strike.
Yeah! That's very good.
Eh, you're a natural.
Thanks for teaching me,
aunt Dinah.
It's so cool learning how to
kick ass from the Black Canary.
Keep kicking the crap
out of that shield,
and captain Drake's gonna
have to deputize you, too.
How about you keep practicing
your kicks in your room?
- OK.
- Good job.
Nice work, Zoe.
I saw the way
you looked
when Zoe mentioned
the Black Canary.
You still adjusting
to being outed?
Well, it was one thing when all
the people in our inner Circle
knew about my
secret identity,
but now
everybody knows,
the cops at SCPD,
everybody.
I don't know. Maybe
I'm just worried
people are gonna
treat me differently
now that
the secret's out.
Yeah. Well,
maybe it's a good idea that me and the team
are gonna be hanging out
at the SCPD for now
in case I got to
crack some heads.
Oh. Thanks.
Hey. Ever since you
became captain,
you've been busting your ass to
earn their trust and respect,
so you keep doing
what you're doing
and don't sweat the haters
because they're gonna hate
like... whoever
left me this.
- When did you get this?
- Last night.
Figured it was some
punk-ass pranking me
for working with you
and the SCPD.
- Oh, damn.
- What, did you get one, too?
And so did Laurel.
We've been trying to track down who did it.
We thought maybe it was about
a case we worked together,
but if you're
getting them, too...
who knows who his
next target is?
Ohh!
Get back!
What the hell?
I can't move.
Oh. Stop! Please
just stop.
I'll give you
anything you want.
Why are you
doing this?
Wow! This is
a lot of blood.
I thought kullens was
in jail for helping Diaz.
Yeah.
Well, apparently, he had a very good lawyer
because he got out
a month ago.
Any chance this connects
with the two body drops
we were looking at
last week?
Kullens did have his throat slit,
same as the other two.
I mean, the only difference
is that kullens
was the only victim to leave
behind one of these notes.
Look familiar?
I spoke to the families
of the other victims,
and they did get
notes, as well.
- They just didn't turn them in.
- Right.
This is turning out to be one
hell of a first day on the job.
Yeah. Look at us,
working together again,
being targeted
by a homicidal maniac.
Feels like a Monday.
What about Laurel?
You said that she
got a note, too.
She did, but she's fine.
She's at a conference in D.C. all week.
OK. So wait.
You, me, Laurel, Rene all got notes.
- Curtis and Oliver didn't.
- Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm definitely not
feeling fomo over it.
Well, we already know
this killer's
not only targeting
people on the team.
Kullens was against
vigilantes,
and we didn't even know
the other two victims.
There has to be
a connection.
We just... Be patient,
and we'll find it.
Maybe this will help.
- Kullens' autopsy report.
- Thank you.
Tox screen is clear.
No defensive wounds.
So he didn't fight back.
This M.O. feels
very familiar.
When I was undercover
in Central City,
the guys in homicide were
chasing after a serial killer
with a very similar
pattern...
throat slash and victims
who didn't fight back.
I'm gonna give
captain Singh a call.
Wakey, wakey, money bags.
Unh!
Touch me, I'll bite
your hand off.
Almost makes me forget
that you're nothing
but a pampered girl
from The Glades
playing vigilante
dress-up.
What do you want?
The access codes
to Archer.
Go to hell.
Well, let's try this
another way.
Wait! Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
The access codes now.
Keep your mouth
shut, William.
So that's your name.
All right, William.
What the hell are you even doing here?
Funny. I was just about
to ask you the same thing.
Ooh. Is that
a backbone I'm seeing?
Even if we give you the codes,
you're just gonna kill us
just like you killed Felicity and just like
you're gonna kill the rest of the city,
so what is the point
in talking?
Someone is trying to blow up the city,
but it's not me,
and I sure as hell
didn't kill Felicity.
Then who did?
I've been thinking
about what you said,
about wanting to do
something different.
OK. Suddenly, I'm getting nervous
about where this is going.
No need.
Just talked with Lyla,
and we both agree
that, Curtis, we cannot afford
to lose a talent like yours,
so A.R.G.U.S. wants
to make you
the head of its science
and technology division.
You want me in charge
of the entire division?
The entire division.
You'll be shaping the future
of A.R.G.U.S., Curtis,
and you can make all the
decisions just like you wanted.
- I don't know what to say.
- Say you'll do it, man.
Just stay here
in Star City.
You can keep working
with the team.
I think it's the best
of both worlds.
Think about it.
Captain Singh, thank you
for getting back to me.
I'd have done it sooner,
but some new metahuman freak
sent a bunch of Central
City's finest to the hospital
before the flash and his
team were able to stop them,
not that there's anything
wrong with metahumans.
No disrespect
intended, Dinah.
Well, none taken. Heh.
And here I was just starting
to feel like I had a handle
on this whole captain thing.
Do you remember when
blockbuster and his gang
tried to expand
their operations
from bludhaven
to Central City?
And almost started a turf war with
all the major crime families?
- Yeah.
- But it didn't,
all because one
undercover cop
had the balls and the brains
to infiltrate their ranks
and prevent
a citywide bloodbath.
If anyone knows
how to win
hearts and minds,
Dinah, it's you.
You just have to
have faith in yourself.
I certainly do.
So about that case file.
Your father is gonna make
his famous chili tonight.
Does he really think making
dinner is gonna solve everything?
I mean, it's his chili
we're talking about.
I'm pretty sure it
could solve world peace.
- Let me see that.
- It's impossible.
Actually, solving
a Rubik's Cube is a lot
like running
an algorithm.
In fact, my favorite
pattern is a cube
within a cube.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah.
The Green Arrow has
entered through the front door.
Heh heh heh.
- The Green Arrow?
- You know, I thought I'd give
the security system
a little personality.
Hey, buddy.
Help me unpack
these bags.
I'm good.
I'm gonna give you two
a moment alone.
Give me those.
Thank you.
William,
I understand why you were mad at me before.
You have every right
to be mad at me, OK?
You're a tough kid.
And I forget sometimes
that you are just a kid...
That's lived in 4 different
cities over the past 2 years.
That's tough.
One of the many reasons
why Felicity and I think that
you should come back here
and live with us.
Warning, warning.
Unidentified person at the front door.
Did you...
Mr. and Mrs. Clayton?
What are you doing here?
Our grandson called us.
OK. I apologize.
I understand and appreciate
why after everything
that's happened
you two might
be worried,
but we can assure you that...
that going forward
things will be better
and more stable, OK?
- They will be...
- Right.
Because we're taking
him with us.
We're filing a suit
for guardianship.
No. You can't do that.
William, we need to speak
with your grandparents alone.
Oliver, it's
an open-and-shut case.
You're a convicted felon.
You were absent
for most of his life,
and then once you
showed up... heh...
he's kidnapped,
he's sent into hiding from a mob boss.
I'm his father, frank.
By blood maybe,
but you are not fit
to be William's guardian,
either of you.
We should have done
this a long time ago.
Yes, dear.
It's what Samantha would
have wanted for him.
William is my son.
Felicity treats
and cares
for him like a son,
and nobody...
Is gonna take him
away from us.
No one.
Are you OK?
I hate tranqs.
Where are the others?
Hey, you!
Where are our friends?
They're
with Blackstar.
Hey. She's got
questions to ask.
What about us?
I already know everything
I need to know about you,
and you guys should have
stayed out of this.
Wait. I recognize you.
You know him?
And so do you.
You're Connor hawke,
John Diggle's son.
Thank you, Dinah.
Call me if you
need anything, OK?
All right.
Can I speak with you
for a moment?
Why? Sounds like you got
to go save the city again.
William, get over here
and sit down.
What?
Your grandparents are trying
to take you away from me.
There is no chance
that that's gonna happen,
but I cannot... I cannot
have you phoning for backup
every time that you're
mad at me.
It's the only thing
that got you to listen!
You think I'm
not listening?
I have heard and felt
every single terrible thing that you've
said to me since you've been back!
Come on. I'm... I'm
trying my best.
That's the problem because
whenever you're around,
things always
get worse!
You want to give me
a normal life?
Yes! That's all I've
ever tried to do!
That's why i...
that why I've asked you
to come back here and live
with Felicity and I.
That isn't a normal life!
I want to go live with my grandparents!
Eight murders over the
course of 2 months.
And this is definitely the
same guy we're dealing with?
Yeah. Analysis of the wound
confirms the same angle of entry
in all the murders here
and in Central City.
The question is why pack up
and bring the fun here?
Yeah. That really is the missing
piece of the puzzle, isn't it?
Doesn't seem to be
any obvious connection
between the victims.
Actually,
maybe there is.
They all had elevated levels
of magnesium in their blood.
But their tox screens
came back clear.
Well, that's because increased
magnesium alone isn't a red flag,
but if you combine that with
decreased levels of red blood cells,
then you have a drug
called mivacurium.
It's a neuromuscular
blocking agent.
Captain Singh said it looked like
the victims had been immobilized.
It's because they
had been drugged.
Mivacurium is
extremely rare.
In fact, there's only been one
shipment in the past month
to Star City to a condemned
house in The Glades
addressed to a John Doe.
- Hey, don't, Curtis.
- Why not?
What if someone spots
that thing flying around?
Might as well have
a freaking neon sign
that says, "hey, murderer.
We're here."
You were saying, Rene?
Curtis, Rene,
you take upstairs.
Me and Dinah will
secure down here.
Split up? What? Have you guys
never seen a horror movie before?
Wait, Rene!
Rene.
Don't sneak up
on me like that!
Sorry. What was that?
Our psycho was
at slabside?
Hyah!
Unh!
You should have
listened to me.
- Dinah.
- Dinah, where are you?
Dinah, I need you to copy.
Can you hear me?
Dinah, where are you?
- Oh!
- Oh, my god.
Dinah. Have to stop
the bleeding.
We have to call
an ambulance.
They won't get here
in time.
You're gonna
be fine. D!
It's too deep.
- There's nothing I can do.
- What?!
Maybe there's something
I can do.
I've been working
on a new prototype...
mid-Infrared lasers that might
be able to cauterize the wound.
- Might or will?
- I don't know,
but the only way to bond the
cut is by burning it first.
- I've never tested it, though!
- Do it! Do it!
OK.
- Tell me when.
- When.
OK. Done.
There's a pulse.
You did it.
Be strong, Dinah.
I take it by the way that
you're treating the chili
that your talk
didn't go so well.
He wants to go live
with his grandparents.
- And you think that's...
- I think it's ridiculous
because we're his family and
we are what's best for him!
Well, we've all grown
and changed a lot
since you got out
of slabside,
and I've been thinking
that maybe you and I
need to think more about
what William needs.
You need to tell me...
If you honestly believe that he
would be better off away from us.
I think that now
that you're working
with the SCPD
and Team Arrow again
that we don't exactly provide
a life of normalcy and...
I just want to be a better father
for him than my father was for me.
You already are by giving him
the life that he deserves...
Even if it breaks
our hearts.
If you didn't kill
Felicity, then who did?
No one. Felicity's
still alive.
How do you know that?
I just do.
It's why I need Archer...
to find Felicity.
Don't listen to her.
She's a liar.
She'll say
anything to...
you didn't need
to do that.
No, but I enjoyed it.
Now... how about
those codes?
Only after you tell me why
you're looking for Felicity.
Let's just say
we owe each other.
What I don't get
is you.
You're no hero wannabe
like the rest of them.
You're obviously
well off,
enough to not slum
around Star City.
So what are you
getting out of this?
Honestly...
I don't know.
Closure maybe,
to ask Felicity
why she disappeared
from my life
only to contact me now
out of the blue.
What, did you guys
date or something?
God, no. I'm gay,
and she's my mom.
Stepmom.
Oliver Queen is
your father?
Did you get anything
out of them?
You're supposed to be
watching the others.
Unh! Agh!
Hyaaah!
- Brace yourself.
- What?
Aah!
Roy!
- Ugh!
- Drop the bow.
You first.
I called the ambulance.
They're on their way.
They'll be here
any minute.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- D., d., relax.
Help's on the way.
You don't have to talk.
Oliver. Ohh. Oliver.
Oliver.
What the hell?
Slabside.
We found a uniform upstairs in the closet.
This guy must have been
in prison with Oliver.
So all of this,
the notes, the murders...
It's about Oliver.
Mmm. Sure beats our suppers in hope Springs,
hey, William?
Except when we
ate there,
I could actually
see my food.
Yeah. I'm sure they're working on
getting the power back on soon.
This storm is crazy.
I thought my chili
was your favorite, bud.
- It's too spicy.
- What are you talking about?
It's perfect.
It's absolutely delicious.
In fact, I will have seconds if you
could pass me some more, please.
I can't.
Felicity...
I can't really move.
I can't either.
What's that sound?
Dad, what's going on?
Don't worry, Oliver.
It's me.
I'm just really happy
to see you guys again.
It's so nice
to meet you, William.
I'm Stanley Dover.
I'm your dad's
best friend.
Stanley, don't hurt
my son.
Hurt him?
I don't want to hurt any of you.
I... I just need
to talk.
That's why I gave you
the medicine...
so you would
listen to me.
What kind
of medicine?
Don't worry. Its effects
are temporary.
I used to take this stuff all
the time when I was a kid.
My dad was a doctor.
Said you want to talk,
Stanley.
What do you want
to talk about?
I just have to
warn you
because those people,
they don't understand you like I do.
You can't believe anything
that they say.
Which people?
The people that call
themselves your friends.
I've been sending
them warnings,
but they haven't
listened.
Warnings?
What kind of warnings?
Like, notes?
Yeah.
You're the Star City
slayer.
Don't call me that.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Oliver, I'm sorry.
I just really
hate that name.
Look. No tricks
this time, OK?
I just really need
you to listen to me.
OK. All right, Stanley,
but this is between us...
So I need you to let
my wife and son go.
I can't because there's people
out there that want to hurt you,
who want to hurt
all of you.
If you knew the things that
I had to do to protect you.
But I know that you would
do the same thing for me.
I... I like that you're
working with the police.
Not everybody does.
There's people out there
that are saying
bad things about you.
They want to hurt you.
Like that councilman
that works with Diaz.
Some people don't
deserve to live.
Come on, Stanley.
My teammates
would never hurt me.
But they're still
bad for you,
worse even because they
don't understand you,
they don't understand
you like I do,
and I only had time
to correct one of them.
"Correct" them?
The police captain.
The Black Canary.
What did you
do to her?
It doesn't matter
because we're
together now,
and we can go somewhere new
and be a new team!
But I don't know about her
because I don't think
that she's been listening.
All right,
she's... she's listening.
Just a little scared,
all right?
Sure. I used to be scared
when my dad
gave me medicine.
He gave me medicine
whenever I was bad
or I didn't listen,
and so when
I couldn't move
and when I had to listen,
then he would correct me.
Your dad used to
hurt you?
He was just doing what he
thought was right for me.
My mother thought so, too.
My older brother,
he tried to protect me,
tried to take
my punishments for me,
but it only made it worse.
One day...
I couldn't take it anymore,
and I gave my parents
some medicine.
I corrected them.
Everybody's got to get back
at their parents sometimes,
right, William?
Right, buddy?
Stanley,
you said your brother.
Where's your brother now?
When he found out
what I did for him,
he got upset.
I don't know why.
He wanted to send me
to arkham asylum,
so I had to give him
some medicine, too.
I needed to correct him.
You killed
your own brother?
I didn't have a choice.
If he just listened
to me,
then I wouldn't have
had to do it,
and none of this
would have happened...
But I'm starting to think
that you're not listening
to me either, Oliver.
I can tell!
And you should have...
you should have apologized to me
for being mean to me
at slabside,
but you haven't,
so I'm starting to think
that you're just like
everybody else
and you don't deserve
my... my protection.
I'm sorry that you feel
that way, Stanley.
You're exactly like your father, Stanley.
You're wrong.
I'm nothing like him.
You're right,
you're right.
You're worse.
You're
the Star City slayer.
I told you
I hate that name!
William.
Agh!
Are you all right?
We are now.
Hey. Dinah's
in surgery now.
Doctors say
she'll be fine,
although they're not too
sure about her Voice yet.
Dover's been picked
up by SCPD.
They're transferring him
back to slabside tomorrow.
How many times
has he done this?
At least 3 that we know of.
It always involves some
older brother figure,
someone he admires.
Stanley starts off
by killing those he thinks
are bad for them
and not just enemies
but friends, as well.
Tries to impress them,
tries to endear himself,
and when that doesn't work,
they become his next target.
You guys OK, though?
So far, so good.
If there's any trace
of the drugs left in our system,
the doctors will find it
in the gallons of blood
they just siphoned from us.
I'm gonna go check on William
and get him discharged.
This is A.R.G.U.S.
we have to go.
Actually, John, uh...
You are taking
the position in D.C.
Look. I know that A.R.G.U.S.
does a lot of good,
but I'll never agree with
them on how they do it.
You have to do
what's right for you,
but I am gonna
miss you, Curtis.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Sorry I didn't tell you.
Just with everything going on...
eh, Rene already
gave you up.
I was kind hoping
more for "boo-hoo.
"I'll miss you so much.
You're my other half
I'll never replace."
Yeah, but I'm really
happy that you're
finally doing
what you want.
I think it's time
you do the same.
- Yeah.
- I talked to my lawyer.
They're gonna draw up
some legal documents.
I'm signing over sole
ownership of helix to you.
You don't have to
do that.
I want to.
Helix was your idea,
and I love working
with you,
but it feels like
you're struggling
to find
your purpose, too.
Yeah.
Maybe this is it.
Maybe this is how Felicity
Smoak will change the world.
Well, you are right.
I am really
gonna miss you.
Hey.
Are we going home?
Well, that depends.
Do you want to go home?
What do you mean?
I mean you were right
that I never asked you
what you wanted.
So I'm asking now.
Would you like
to come home
and live with us?
Or do you want to go and
live with your grandparents?
I just want a normal life.
I want that
for you, too.
I thought I could...
Provide that
for you...
Especially since,
um, you know,
I've been unmasked.
After what happened tonight,
I see that, um...
Normal may never be
a real possibility.
I don't want you to stop
being a hero.
I know the city needs you.
I just think
for at least now,
it might be better for me
to be in Central City.
OK.
Then that's what
we'll do.
It gets really cold there
in the winter,
so I'm gonna send you,
like, 3 coats
and mitts and a hat.
You're definitely
gonna need a hat.
Ohh.
I'll miss you so much.
I'm gonna
miss you, too.
Listen here,
young man.
Wherever you are,
I'm always gonna be your dad.
So we'll talk
all the time... ahem...
and I promise to
come and visit
whenever it's cool
with you
and with your
grandparents.
You just have to
promise that you...
you will call me...
if you need anything, anything,
you will call me, OK?
- I will.
- You have a home
with the two of us
in Star City forever.
I love you, William.
I love you, too, dad.
Hi. Dr. Schwartz,
is everything OK?
Oh, good.
I thought it was gonna be one of those calls
where you say,
"everything spread to the liver," and...
I'm what?
You can't win this.
Drop
the damn knife.
Come on!
Don't give me a reason to pull this trigger.
You're not gonna
shoot me.
You sure about that?
Yeah...
Because my name
is Mia Smoak.
I'm Felicity's daughter
and your sister.
Greg, move your head.