My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest
of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
I killed him. The police officer.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you were
overdosed on Mirakuru;
you didn't remember, and I was hoping
that you never would.
This city still needs saving,
and that is my vision
for this company.
Yes, I am your boss now.
I can quit, which is what
I just did.
I thought that I could
be me and the Arrow, but I can't.
Say it's never going
to work out between us.
Say you never loved me.
Say--
I told you as soon
as we talked,
it would be over.
You changed your mind.
I just decided
I want more out of life.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Cupid, stupid.
[Arrow releases]
In the last five minutes,
SCPD has had over 200 reports
of masked men
attacking the city.
[Tires squealing]
[All shrieking and screaming]
It's 3.8 miles to the bridge.
3.8 miles and a dozen
Mirakuru soldiers to stop.
Stop? We're already late!
Stop!
Everybody get back inside.
Isaac Stanzler.
Looks like the two of you
got the same taste in outfits.
I thought
he was in custody.
Yeah.
Corrections was transporting him
to Iron Heights
when he got
pin-cushioned.
By who?
Your guess is
as good as mine.
But whoever it was
went to a lot of trouble.
Dressing him up
and dumping him like this?
I'd say our doer's definitely trying
to get your attention.
Well, he's got it.
Any leads yet?
No. The only
physical evidence
other than
the body is this.
Shaped like a spade.
What's that all about?
I don't know.
I'll look into it.
I'm not your mother
or your wife or your maid.
Okay, all right,
you don't like me, I get it.
At least you're perceptive.
I thought
that last week,
we did the whole
candle meditation thing,
- and maybe we had a moment.
- Moment's over.
You can celebrate
by doing your own laundry.
Yeah.
What?
I--[Sighs]
I don't know how.
Where you going?
Waller just called.
New Intel on this
Li Kuan Hui
the Triad's
interested in. Mm-mmm.
What?
My contact is
down at the docks.
A gaijin would stick out
like neon down there.
Gaijin?
It'll be fine.
I'll only be gone an hour.
What am I
supposed to do?
Your laundry.
Apparently.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
What are you doing? You were supposed
to be at the press conference
20...minutes...ago.
[Grunts]
Oh, God. I have a type.
You know Richard Branson
works out twice a day?
He told me it gives him 20 additional
hours of productivity a week.
I'm sorry, I can't hear
a word you're saying
when you're doing...
That.
[Grunts]
Sorry. What's up?
The announcement?
There's a gajillion
reporters and city notables
waiting for you.
Oh, ha. Well, this will
be interesting. Ha!
BTW, are you free for
dinner tomorrow night?
What?
I have a dinner with the CEO
of a Nevada mining concern.
They own mineral
rights, which are imperative
to the cogeneration
project.
Oh, and I fit into this how?
Ahh, the CEO is boring.
His wife, even more boring.
If I'm forced
to go solo on this,
I'll end up slicing my wrists open
with a butter knife.
Well, I don't think
a butter knife is going to...
Do the job.
Oh, there will be steak knives there,
too. Dangerous.
Well, I'm sure you have
a dozen other employees
that would be better suited
as your anti-boring wing woman.
- Hundreds, actually.
- Oh.
But you are the one I bought
this dress for.
This dress...
costs more than my apartment.
Yeah, it's couture.
Which I'm pretty
sure is French for expensive.
Ohh.
So, dinner?
Purely platonic.
There is nothing platonic
about couture.
Ah, fine. I'll have
my assistant return it.
No, all right, I'll go!
I'll go.
But only so I can
wear this dress.
Of course.
You and I are going
to be best friends.
[Door opens]
Hey.
Last time I saw
a spade that lethal,
it broke up a pretty
good royal flush I was holding.
Hand-soldered out
of high-carbon steel.
Where'd you find it?
Isaac Stanzler's chest.
Ted Grant's
psycho sidekick.
Was murdered while being
transferred by the SCPD.
By an arrow.
Think this is the same
archer that killed Sara?
No. That one
was different.
These bodies were
staged, dressed up to look like--
Copycat archer.
Guess all that positive publicity
you've been getting has a downside.
Well, whatever
the reason, we need to find him.
I would like Felicity to do
a work-up on all of this ASAP.
Copy.
Felicity's a little busy
right now.
Doing what?
Ray: A few months ago,
I made a promise
to help revitalize
Starling City.
But I knew I couldn't
do it alone.
I needed help.
A lot of help.
From people who are even
more intelligent
and dedicated than I am.
All of us are working
very hard with one goal in mind--
to save our city.
But to do so,
Queen Consolidated
needs to be something else.
[Oliver hammering]
You ok?
I'm--I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
Look at this.
What's that, a note?
It's an address.
15 Baron Street,
apartment Seven.
Nobody's home.
These are all articles
about the Arrow.
This isn't just a copycat;
This is a fan.
From the looks of it,
a pretty dedicated one.
And this isn't a spade.
It's a heart.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Woman: It's you.
I can't believe
it's really you.
Did you like your present?
Do you mean Isaac Stanzler,
the man you killed?
I see the way
you take care of your city.
Makes me wonder...
Who takes care of you?
I want to help you--
to fight with you,
to kill for you.
Mr. Stanzler
was just the first.
[Cell phone beeps]
He might be the second.
I thought we could
punish this one together.
I'm going
to find you.
Well, that's the idea.
But you'd better hurry,
I don't think
he's got very long.
♪ Arrow 3x07 ♪
Draw Back Your Bow
Original Air Date on November 19, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oliver: Roy.
I was just researching
cheap booze for Thea's club.
You know, it wasn't you
who killed that officer.
I keep telling myself that,
but it's not working.
Every single time
I put on that mask,
I feel like a fraud.
You--[Sighs]
You have to give this time.
[Sighs]
If you want to talk about it--
I don't.
I appreciate
the offer, though.
I'm fine. Really.
[Footsteps]
Oh, sorry,
am I interrupting?
I was just leaving.
I got to help Thea
get the club ready
for the opening.
Oliver:
What's up?
I got an idea
on your not-so-secret
but very crazy admirer's
hostage.
Who is it?
Joe Gravano,
local mob boss, wanted for 39
counts of murder,
racketeering,
and drug smuggling.
One of the most heavily
protected men in Starling City.
Not anymore.
What's "N.P.P.?"
I don't know.
I can definitely
find out.
Where are we with
the cell phone from her apartment?
Crazy pants
encrypted the SIM card.
I can crack it, but it's going
to take some time.
[Sighs] Which we don't have,
neither does he.
I need 100% of your focus
on finding Gravano.
And I will work round the clock on it,
except for tonight.
Why?
Ray Palmer
invited me to dinner.
Oh.
Not dinner-dinner,
like a date.
It's a work dinner,
but since dinner
is a meal you can technically
only eat at night,
I need the night off.
That ok?
Do what you want.
[Speaking Japanese]
Nothing?
He's not
answering his cell.
Just relax.
I'm sure he's fine.
He said it would
only be an hour.
That was
nine hours ago.
If he's going
to be late,
he always calls.
He said his contact
was down at the docks, right?
I will go down
and check it out.
No, I'll go.
Um...
No offense,
but you're just...
Maseo's wife.
And you just
a billionaire
who doesn't know how to use
laundry machine.
Do you have someone
who can watch Akio for a few hours?
[Music playing,
records scratching]
Great, uh,
thank you.
You were terrific.
Auditions are over.
Thanks for coming, guys.
Hey, peace out.
Wait, what are you doing?
Auditions are not over.
Trust me, I'm saving
you from wasting your day here.
I don't need saving
from anyone,
and if you're really as good
as you say you are,
then you can just wait in line
and prove it like everyone else.
- I don't audition.
- Then you don't work.
For me or for my club.
So...the exit's that way.
Later, Princess.
I got her.
The user registered
to the encrypted SIM card,
Carrie Cutter,
she's former SCPD.
She was the first woman
SWAT team member.
I've seen her
before.
Well, she's not unpretty
for a whacko,
if you're into the whole
red-headed vixen-type thing.
She was a police officer, that
might be why she looks familiar.
No, she left the force once year
before you got back from the island.
But there's another
very good reason
she looks familiar.
Why was she at the crime scene
at Ted Grant's gym?
I don't know,
but it's not just there.
Apparently stalking
isn't her only hobby, either.
She's a member
of a gardening group, too.
Which explains
the whole N.P.P. thing.
What N.P.P. thing?
The bag in the Gravano
hostage photo.
N.P.P., it's an acronym--
stands for nitrogen, phosphate, potash.
It's the chemical formula
for fertilizer.
So what if she's keeping Gravano
in a greenhouse?
Yeah.
The closest one to her apartment
is Sherwood Florist,
7884 Hauser.
Have Roy gear up
and meet me there.
Ok.
Roy...
Find Gravano.
I'll take care of Cutter.
Got it.
[Arrow releases]
Hiya.
Arsenal, there's
no sign of Cutter.
Arsenal.
Arsenal!
Hello, lover.
If you hurt him...
I didn't touch him,
boyfriend.
I'm a one-guy woman.
But I am a little disappointed
you brought your wing man.
Tonight's not about him.
It's about us.
Together against the world.
Just like
we were meant to be.
There is no "We."
We're more like one soul,
you're right.
You and I are more alike
than you think.
Carrie, listen to me.
You're not well.
If I'm out of my mind,
it's because that's what love is.
Our own little
slice of insanity.
Make a wish.
Mine's already come true--
for the two of us
to be together forever.
Please help me. Don't
leave me with this psycho!
- Quiet!
- You don't want to do this.
Sure I do.
Oh, I wouldn't do that.
That rope's laced
with a trip wire that's hooked up
to a little thing
on his chest that goes, "Boom!"
So what do you
want, then?!
Not much.
Just...You.
Never going
to happen.
Such a party pooper.
[Groaning]
[Beeping]
I never thought
I'd be happy to see you!
Roy. Hey!
Why don't you go home, man?
It's been a long night.
She took me out.
It shouldn't have happened.
[Sighs] You're not
at your best.
I'm fine.
Looks like you weren't
the only person that Carrie stalked.
She was put
on limited duty
after becoming obsessed
with her partner.
The department sent
her to St. Walker's for a psych eval.
She quit the force
a little bit after.
- Where's Felicity?
- She's working tonight.
She said she told you.
Yes, she did.
Oliver, you ok?
I know this can't be easy,
with Felicity spending
so much time with Palmer.
I'm fine.
Where you going?
The psychiatrist
that SCPD sent Cutter to.
- You need back up?
- No.
I've got it.
Hey.
Like what you've done
to the place.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, yeah, I was just in the neighborhood.
Thought I would stop by
and check out your new sign.
Oh, yeah.
Phew.
[Chuckles]
Wow, that's a nice dress.
Yeah, it's
really, really,
really nice.
Ray lent it to me
for a work dinner.
Yeah, some...work dinner.
- You and Ray.
- Mm-hmm.
Doesn't seem that platonic.
Actually, it has Oliver
twisted up in knots.
Well, Oliver
made his choice.
We both know that
was the wrong choice.
And did Oliver
say that?
Oh, yeah, because Oliver's just great
at expressing his emotions.
He would rather go ten rounds
with the League of Assassins
than ever say that.
But this thing
with you and Palmer,
it's, um, it's messing
with his head, Felicity,
and...that's really dangerous.
I told you, there is no
me and Palmer.
But if there were,
and if Oliver had
a problem with it,
then Oliver should be the one
to say something.
Ok.
Good night.
- Dr. Pressnall--
- Oh, my god!
I'm not here
to hurt you.
What do you want?!
To talk about
Carrie Cutter.
I can't.
Doctor-patient privilege.
Just please, get out!
Your patient killed a man,
kidnapped another,
and I'm trying to stop her before
she hurts anyone else.
To do that, I need
to understand her.
[Exhales]
Please.
I can only diagnose her.
Attachment disorder,
the inability to form
real, lasting relationships.
They push everyone away,
and fixate
on a single person.
Someone they feel mirrors
their emotional state.
How do I stop her?
Give her the connection
that she craves--
honesty, sincerity...
If you lie to her,
she'll know.
Thank you.
If you'll permit
a professional observation...
you could use
a little therapy yourself.
What gives you
that impression?
You mean,
apart from the mask
and the Robin Hood costume?
Oliver: Shouldn't we
get out and look around
or, I don't know,
something?
In this place,
at this hour?
That's a very efficient way
to get yourself killed.
Feel free.
[Chuckles]
Thank you.
That's...
We'll wait, then.
"Gaijin."
What?
Maseo called me that
before he left,
and I looked it up, but it wasn't in my
Chinese dictionary.
Because
it's Japanese.
It means
"foreigner."
Outsider.
You.
It means you, too.
You're Japanese,
living in Hong Kong.
Sorry.
Why did you
leave Japan?
It wasn't safe
for us there.
Why?
We upset some
very powerful,
very dangerous men.
Who?
You ask a lot
of questions.
That's what
your husband says.
Who's that?
Shu gang.
Rivals of the Triad.
They control this port.
So they know what
happened to Maseo.
I don't know.
Only one way
to find out.
[Speaking Chinese]
Hey, I don't want
any trouble!
[Speaking Chinese]
[Footsteps]
What happened
to the thing?
Wow.
You are
ridiculous.
Um...
Which I mean
in a...good way.
That's...not creepy.
[Clears throat]
You look beautiful.
I think it's the dress.
The dress is actually
missing something.
Oh, no, I forgot
to do up the zipper again?
I always do that.
Oh, no, I can't wear that.
I'm not even sure
I'm supposed to be looking at it.
Well, I had to put down
a $10,000 security deposit
just to borrow it
for the evening,
so one of us should wear it.
And diamonds aren't
really my thing, so.
I appreciate it,
but I think I would
feel strange wearing
a million dollar necklace.
Oh, don't worry.
It's not worth
a million dollars.
Ahh.
I think it was
actually appraised
for $10 million.
So...
There you go.
That's better.
Where you been?
You don't call,
you don't write.
Carrie: I've been
busy, busy, busy.
[Chuckles]
You look good.
Business before pleasure.
First I located
every crime scene
the Arrow's been spotted at
in the past six months.
Now the magic part--
I created
an algorithm, calculated the
average amount of time
it takes the Arrow
to reach a crime scene,
triangulated that
by the distance to said scene...
[Beeping]
Genius, right?
I wonder why no one
thought to do it before.
Now obviously, I can't pinpoint
the exact block,
but, uh, there's no doubt
your guy hangs his hat
or his hoodie
somewhere in this area.
And you're sure
about this?
Statistical correlations
do not lie.
Now...
What was this about pleasure?
Mmm.
[Groans]
Shh.
I'm sorry.
I'm spoken for.
How'd it go
with Cutter's shrink?
Oof. There's a reason
I'm not in therapy.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Detective.
Quentin: Your new girlfriend
just put another
heart-shaped arrow
in the neck of one
of her old CIs.
Oliver:
Who was he?
Kirby Bates. Some kind
of computer expert
holed up in a flop house
north of Amsterdam.
Did a five year bit
in Iron Heights
for stealing a couple of million
credit card pin numbers.
What did Bates do for her?
I don't know.
Everything here
is smashed to pieces.
But smart money says,
whatever Carrie Cutter's planning next,
you're not going
to like it.
[Sighs] Thanks,
Detective.
We need Felicity here.
Oliver, she's still
at dinner with--
I don't care where she
is! We need her here.
You mean, you need her to be
any place where Ray Palmer isn't.
It's not the time,
Diggle.
Oliver, you're in the field
without your head on straight.
I think this is
exactly the time.
I've got it
handled.
Doesn't look that way to me.
What do you
want me to say?
Yes, it bothers me
that she is out to
dinner with Palmer.
Yes, it bothers me that apparently
she is just moving on with her life,
but I made a decision!
She did, too.
And--
I just...I want her
to be happy.
If that were true...
You'd be with her, man.
- Where you going?
- Flop house on Amsterdam.
They're long gone by now.
Maybe she didn't
get that far!
[All grunting and groaning]
I'm here looking
for my husband.
Thin beard, long hair,
Japanese.
Don't know any Japanese.
Try again.
[Speaking Chinese]
I don't know anything!
A.R.G.U.S.
Does that mean
something to you?
I don't know anything!
Except...
Three men, this A.R.G.U.S.,
they work for them.
Worked.
What
do you mean?
They're all dead.
Killed by Triad,
a few hours ago.
Thank you.
Ah, Mr. Gardner.
Ray Palmer.
- Good.
- Mrs. Gardner.
This is Felicity Smoak,
vice president
of Palmer Technologies.
- Hello.
- Pleasure.
Thank you for sitting
down with us tonight.
Well, I'm always happy
to enjoy a good meal.
And I'm very impressed
with your background.
But I have no plans
of selling my Nevada Holding.
The night
is still young.
Shall we sit down?
We have a lot to discuss.
Thank you.
As you said,
the night is young.
[Cell phone
vibrates]
But I don't like to talk business
until at least the entrée.
[Dance music playing]
[Record scratches]
Maybe the DJ
got confused
and he thinks
he's at a rave.
I think my ears
are bleeding.
Excuse me,
I'm sorry, I--
You're fired.
What about the rest
of the night?
I think
my Spotify playlist
is a better option
than you right now.
Whatever.
Need some help?
Just when I thought
the night couldn't get any worse.
Thought I'd swing
by, see what kind of trainwreck
this would be.
Oh, did I say trainwreck?
Because this is...
Pow!
You know, I'm glad
you're enjoying yourself.
Yeah. I think
I'm the only one.
Oh, I just remembered--
I own a bar.
Half the gate and guaranteed gigs
four times a week.
Two times a week.
Three.
Fine.
Just get these
people dancing.
♪ I gotta stay ♪
[Dance music playing]
[All cheering]
Obviously, the progeneration
of certain minerals
can't be accounted for by simple
elemental cohesion.
I am so sorry. I had to help
a co-worker with a thing.
I had to have them take
the steak knives away.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Gardner, did Ray have
a chance to tell you
about his plans for your mineral
deposits in Nevada?
Uh, no, Miss Smoak,
as I mentioned,
I'm not
interested in selling.
Please,
call me Felicity.
And I don't blame you
for not wanting to sell Ray your mine.
Because you don't know
what his plans are.
The thing about Ray is,
he's not...
businessman.
Businessmen
make deals.
They make money.
What Ray is, is...
something else
entirely.
Perhaps you can
enlighten us.
He inspires.
Ray isn't interested
in making money.
He's interested in making
the world a better place.
So if Ray wants your mine,
believe me,
it's because he's going to put it
to the kind of use
that's going
to make you proud.
[Cell phone beeps]
Yeah?
John: I spoke
with Felicity.
I got her to remote
access that laptop.
The last thing Cutter
was looking at was a map.
And Oliver, Verdant
was marked on it.
Felicity was also able to retrieve
Cutter's phone signal from the laptop.
Ok, patch me through,
and then get upstairs
and do not take your eyes off of Thea,
do you understand?
Copy that.
[Dance music playing,
crowd cheering]
♪ Fire up, get loud,
another round of shots ♪
♪ turn down for what ♪
One Cupid's kiss.
♪ Turn down for what ♪
Delicious.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
Oliver: It's me.
I have to admit,
I didn't think a club would be
your kind of scene.
You're always
surprising me.
I'm not there.
Why don't I believe you?
You want to meet me, fine.
I will meet you anywhere
but that club.
So you're
asking me out.
Where do you want
to meet, Carrie?
I know a place.
Our special spot. [Laughs]
But you listen
to me, lover.
I've been burned before.
And if you're
playing me,
I promise you, I'll come back here
and kill everyone in this place.
[Thunder]
Dig, you there?
And me.
Me being Felicity.
What's your 20?
Subway stop
downtown.
Why did Cutter
have you meet her there?
Because this is
where I saved her.
Hello, lover.
I'm not your lover.
Well, maybe not yet,
but after one night with me,
that'll all change.
I promise.
Carrie, I'm here
to help you,
because
you're not well.
Don't ever say that again.
You sound like that shrink
that they sent me to.
I spoke to her.
You talked to that psycho?
She just wanted me
to take pills,
pills, pills.
She thinks that love
is a disease.
But it's not.
Love is the cure.
Well, I'm not the man
you think I am.
You're a hero...
Who saved me.
I understand
that you're hurting.
And I know
what it's like
to want someone...
but not be able
to be with them.
How you wish things
can be different, but they can't.
I can't be with you.
I can't be with anyone.
I have to be alone.
Carrie: No, you don't.
You're a liar!
I don't want
to hurt you!
You already have.
[Both grunting]
[Groaning and gasping]
It's over, Carrie.
I guess it's true
what they say--
you only hurt
the ones you love.
[Grunts]
[Beeping]
Oliver? Get him back.
Oliver!
[Both grunting]
Sorry.
But if I can't
have you--
Carrie, think about this!
I didn't want it
to end this way.
I guess I don't
handle rejection very well.
You don't have to do this.
[Train horn honking]
I do.
But at least this way,
we can be together.
For eternity.
I knew you loved me.
Well, it's done.
Lyla said Cutter's
even nuttier
than the last woman they had in
the Suicide Squad.
You sure this was
a good idea,
handing her over
to Waller?
Iron Heights
isn't right for her.
At least, on the squad,
she can make a difference.
Lyla is preparing
a late dinner,
if you want to join.
No.
No, I'm good, thank you.
Listen, Oliver...
Felicity heard what
you said to Cutter.
About being alone.
If her reaction
was any indication,
she does not
want to be.
You got to tell her
how you feel
before it's too late.
[Exhales]
It's just food
for thought.
What do I tell him?
How do I tell my son
his father is dead?
Where have you two been?
What's going on?
You're home.
I was so worried.
I know. I'm sorry.
I should have called.
Waller changed my orders
and brought me in.
We were
on lockdown tonight
because three agents
got killed.
Gross!
Akio, get over here.
Pretty good
gate tonight.
You're never going to let me
forget this, are you?
You have to admit,
I did save your ass.
God, your modesty, it's--
it's so refreshing.
You know, you're really cute when
you're sarcastic.
[Chuckles]
Half the gate, as agreed.
Keep the money.
My grand reopening
gift to you.
See you next week.
Aha. I thought I might
find you here.
I thought I'd get a jump on that
server encryption
you asked for.
Trying to, you know,
make up for ruining
the deal tonight.
Your definition of ruin
is vastly different from mine.
Gardner's going to sell.
That's amazing!
It's all thanks to you.
[Chuckles]
But really, I should be
thanking you.
I mean, not just
for the new job,
but for this amazing,
expensive necklace.
[Chuckles]
You have to take it
back, don't you?
Yeah, kind of do.
Here, let me help you.
Hmm. Thank you.
You know, Felicity Smoak,
you're different
from anyone I've ever met.
And you deserve all those
things, and more.
I'm--I'm sorry, I, um...
I meant to keep tonight
platonic. ahh...
I should go.
Um, Ray?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ok.
Are you ok?
Not really.
What about you?
Come on.
Where we going?
For something
we both need.
[Knock on door]
Hi.
I know it's late, but, um--
Hey, that was
the invitation.
Something
smells good.
Thank you. Hi.
Come on in.
Yep, I just sent the notarized
transfer of ownership
to Gardner's attorney.
Now listen, I want to get a jump
on the mining operations immediately.
Let me know as soon as the first
of the Dwarf Star alloy is extracted.
Thanks.
[Exhales]
[Beeping]
[Beeps]
Whoever you are, back off!
Ahh.
Sorry to do this to you,
but you have
something I need.
See, that's the thing
about our work...
It always comes back
to haunt you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man