My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
But to the rest
of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
My name is Amanda Waller,
Mr. Queen.
Welcome
to Hong Kong.
Amanda Waller
wants you working for her.
She will have her way.
You're Felicity Smoak.
I know a guy who might
be interested in hiring someone
with your expertise.
Apparently there's another
bidder for the company.
- Who?
- Ray Palmer.
What are you
doing here?
No! No! Sara!
Sara!
No! No!
[Sobbing]
Please!
Felicity,
all I'm trying to do
is make things
easier on you.
By having me
completely
reconfigure
our phone system?
Do you even know
how difficult it is
to ping a clone off a hacked
transband multiplex?
No, but only because you
weren't speaking English just now.
Sara?
I didn't know
where else to take her.
Felicity: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Oh.
What happened?
I couldn't...
I couldn't
leave her.
Felicity: We have to--
call--we can...
take her
to the hospital!
Ollie. Ollie,
it's not fair!
We just got her
back, it's not fair!
Come here...
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
We'll take
our position here.
Who's your target?
I don't have a target--
you do.
What?
Might have escaped
your notice,
but Amanda Waller
doesn't have a sense of humor.
Oh, really?
Then why'd she drag
me off of Lian Yu
and bring me all
the way to Hong Kong
- to become her hit man?
- To become her operative.
Obviously she needs you
for something
or she wouldn't be threatening
my family to assure your compliance.
The target will be entering
our line any moment.
The target will walk 10 paces
through the roof garden
and arrive at his hotel suite.
That's your window.
I see it.
Now.
Tommy?
♪ Arrow 3x02 ♪
Sara
Original Air Date on October 14, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You know, Sara used
to have a stuffed animal.
It was this old,
worn out shark
that she got
from the Starling Aquarium.
Every time something awful
would happen to her,
I would always find her holding
that stupid little shark
close to her chest.
And now that my sister's dead,
again the only thing
that I can think about
is finding that dumb
stuffed animal
and putting it in her arms.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
Hey, whoever
did this,
I'm going
to find them.
We're going to.
When I thought that Sara
died on "The Gambit,"
the only thing
that I could do
was scream at the ocean.
I had so much anger and rage,
and I didn't know
what to do with it.
But I do now.
And I'm going
to help you catch
whoever it is that did this.
You're already helping.
Laurel...
You told us
where to look.
I'm just supposed
to sit here and wait?
No. Now you take
care of yourself
and your family.
Your father is
going to need you.
Telling him now,
it would kill him.
At least now if we wait until
we catch whoever did this,
it'll be easier on him.
Ok.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
But I know that a bar is the last
place I should be.
[Dialing]
[Exhales]
Come on, pick up.
Thea: You've reached Thea.
Leave a message.
Thea, it's Oliver.
Um...
I know you're still
traveling,
but I just,
I could really...
I'd really like
to hear your voice.
So please call me back.
What'd we get off
the cameras?
Place is
a drug haven.
They've all
either been disabled
or paint-balled
by local dealers.
Where are you going?
Where it
happened.
[Horns honking in distance]
Felicity told me.
[Sighs]
You ok?
Killer stood there,
loose gravel
on the rooftop.
- Oliver...
- Sara was here.
Scuff marks
back to the edge.
You don't have to do this
right now, man.
It's the only thing
that I can do.
Listen, I get it.
Military training.
Stay on task.
Your friend gets shot,
you just keep fighting.
- But Oliver...
- I'm fine.
Well, I'm here
for you just the same.
Listen, Sara was
my friend, too.
And if you think you're going after
the person who did this solo,
you couldn't possibly
be more wrong.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Yeah?
Detective Lance called,
he says it's important.
Do you think
he knows about Sara?
[Sighs]
[Voice disguised]
What is it, Detective?
You ok? You look like someone peed
in your cornflakes.
That kind of day, huh?
What's going on?
Another archer
in town.
Dropping bodies.
- Seen this guy's work before?
- I might have.
You know where
SCPD's finest might find him?
- Who's the victim?
- John Burke.
Some corporate
financier from Qurac.
Seems like he wandered into
the wrong part of town
tonight looking
for a little local "entertainment."
He ended up with an
arrow in his chest.
Hey.
You watch your back,
all right? Whoever this guy is...
He's a killer.
Her hands are so small.
I never noticed before.
She was always so strong
and brave. [Sniffs]
I always envisioned her
as this sort of
Amazonian warrior.
Invincible.
Something I could
never be.
I was so jealous.
[Sniffs]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Hi. I know I was
supposed to come into work today.
I--the--I'm sorry.
There's been a death
in the family.
Thank you.
You have any idea what other archer
could have done this?
[Exhales]
There aren't that many of us.
Maybe 10 that I know of,
and most of them are in
the League of Assassins.
Oliver,
you don't think...
No. No.
They don't
target their own.
- What'd you find out?
- He hit again.
An abandoned warehouse
on the corner of Third and Lemire.
Ninth floor. The victim was a construction
foreman, Tim Kaufman.
Security cameras
can't get an angle.
- Who's that?
- Just some low level dealers
that set up shop
in abandoned warehouses.
Doesn't look like
much of an archer to me.
- He might be a witness.
- Diggle: Where do you want me?
Will Lyla give you access
to A.R.G.U.S.'s database?
To find out who did this, Lyla
will give us access to A.R.G.U.S.
I need a list of everyone
on their radar--
assassins and mercenaries
who use a bow.
I'm on it.
What?
Uh, Thea hasn't
called back yet.
You didn't
eliminate the target!
That's not a target,
that's my best friend!
Why am I pointing a gun
at my best friend?
Is this
some sort of test?
Yes. One you failed!
Good. Flunk me.
You think it's a coincidence
your friend just happened
to show up in Hong Kong?
- He's here looking for you!
- What?
When you logged into your email,
it set off an account alert.
Dead men don't check
their email, Oliver.
Oh, so this is
my fault?
Waller needs you.
She can't let you be compromised
by some rich kid flashing
your picture all over Hong Kong.
Whether you're the one
who pulls the trigger or not,
she wants Tommy Merlyn
off the board.
That is a cobalt
encrypted workstation.
You better not be
using it to Tweet.
I was--I was,
um, actually just...
Accessing an FBI database?
What...
Roy, why are you
looking for Thea?
Because I don't think she is where
she says she is.
Why would she lie?
Roy, Oliver needs to see this.
No. This is my fault.
He's going to kill me.
- What if she's in trouble?
- What if she's not?
What if she just
needs space?
She's had five months
and thousands
of miles of space.
Oliver needs to see this.
[Exhales]
You need to show it to him.
[Sighs]
[Cell phone vibrates]
You have got to be kidding me.
What--where
are you going?
There's someone
I need to kill.
[Elevator dings]
Did you do it to make a point?
Because I get it.
Loud and clear.
You are rich.
You are impulsive.
And frankly, you are
the creepiest form of stalker
that I have ever
had to deal with,
and believe me when
I'm telling you that that is saying a lot,
And--what are you doing
to our old offices?
Hi. I'll be right back.
You like it? Yeah,
I'm just trying
to liven up
the place a bit.
I'm hosting
an event tonight.
A pledge drive of sorts.
Got to make
an impression, right?
Now, what can I do for you?
You can stop.
You can stop sending me flowers,
and you can stop
texting me and calling me
and emailing me,
because I spam them, anyway.
Oh, is "spam" a verb now?
Because I am never,
ever, ever going to work for you.
Actually, you already do.
Only because you
bought the store that I work at!
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did!
My boss just called
and told me that you did.
Well, he's wrong--kind of.
I bought the holding company
which owns and operates
all 20,000 Tech Village stores.
But I guess either way,
yes, I am your boss now.
So you can either
work for me here
in a big office
with a big salary,
or... you can work
for me there,
in that awful uniform.
Or... I can quit.
Which is what
I just did.
[Scoffs] You know,
most girls would be flattered that
I spent $1.2 billion to hire them.
Even if I do have a fairly genius plan
for rebranding the stores.
In case you haven't noticed,
I am not most girls.
And I don't
need this. Or you.
Or any of this.
Felicity, I--I piss people
off on a daily basis.
It's part of business,
and, well,
being the smartest guy
in any given room.
I own that. So I have enough experience
with people being angry with me
to know when they're really angry
at something else.
You right now are not
angry at me.
What's your something else?
[Inhales, exhales]
Oh, money won't
fix this problem.
Money won't solve
most problems.
Not the ones that matter.
But talking helps.
I know we barely
know each other...
I'm going
to leave now.
Listen, whatever
happened, I'm sorry.
It helps to remember that...
It gets better.
[Elevator dings]
[Both grunt]
Someone was murdered here.
Tell me what you saw.
I saw nothing.
[Groaning]
There was
a black face mask,
like a--like
a hockey mask.
Now, please, man--
Diggle, are you at A.R.G.U.S.?
I've got something.
Yeah, I'm here.
I got a list of archers
20-long, man.
How many of them
wear masks?
Only one.
Simon Lacroix.
Mercenary.
Goes by "Komodo."
Send Felicity
everything.
Yep.
Oliver, I'm opening up
the file now.
Laurel: Is that him?
Simon Lacroix. Born in
Saint-Sophie, Quebec.
Raised by a single mom.
Terrible credit score.
Oh, and wanted
for murder in seven countries.
- I need his location.
- One minute.
Put him on speaker.
Ok, indexing all active burner
cell phones within the city limits.
There's got to be
10,000 phones.
Yes, but how many
are making calls to dear old mom
in Saint-Sophie, Quebec?
I got him.
He's on the move.
[Tires squealing]
I found Lacroix.
I need to see
what's happening.
Ok. Blowing up
street camera feed.
[Motor revving]
[Tires squealing]
Come on, Ollie.
- Get up.
- Oliver?
Are you ok?
Oliver?
[Sirens]
[Revving engine]
He got away.
I had him, Diggle.
The way you look,
he almost had you.
Where's Roy?
He's out canvassing.
Tell me about
the driver of the car.
His name is Erlich Kelso. He just
got out of Starling General--
And where are we with Lacroix?
He ditched his burner.
I'm searching the city
for any calls made to Quebec.
We used that to track him once;
He's not going to let it happen again.
All right, so why don't we stop
searching for Lacroix
and start searching
for his target?
Because there must be a connection
with his victims.
Already on it.
I mean, what if we just--
we go to a local morgue
and we find a body
that looks like Tommy's?
At the Hong Kong morgue?
You've got a better chance
of winning the lottery
and trying to pay Waller off.
I am not going
to assassinate my best friend,
- do you understand?
- There has to be another way.
There is.
But it involves
Amanda Waller
finding someone else
to execute your friend.
No, not you, Dad.
Look, I'm already in Hong Kong.
No! No, I didn't tell you
I was taking the jet
because I knew you would
freak out like this.
No, I don't know how long, ok?
It doesn't matter.
Listen, if Oliver is still alive,
if he is still here--
[grunts]
Look, why don't you just go back
to banging your Pilates instructor, ok?
I'll just be here searching
for my best friend.
[Gasps]
I'm sorry, miss.
You can't go in there.
Laurel Lance. I'm with the district
attorney's office.
Erlich Kelso
is a witness
of my ongoing
investigation.
- Mr. Kelso's under protective custody.
- Not from me.
And if you have
a problem with that,
you can call
your captain.
Tell him his
daughter says hello.
Who are you?
I work in the DA's office.
I already
told the police,
I don't know
anything.
I still have to ask you
a few questions.
- Why isn't this working?
- It is.
It's running an NSA
algorithm aggregating
the victims' personal
information using
every government database
known, and unknown.
Well, it's taking too long.
Sara's killer is still out there,
which means that every minute that
we waste down here--
I know! You don't
need to tell me
as if I don't already know.
You're right.
And I apologize.
I just need your A game
right now, Felicity.
I don't have it!
My friend--our friend--
was shot with arrows
and fell off of a rooftop.
Her body is upstairs
right above us in a freezer
because we don't know
what to do with it--
with her.
So I am so sorry, Oliver,
if I have feelings, but maybe
if you did, too, we...
Sorry. That was mean.
But this is Sara
we're talking about.
Your Sara.
How can you stand there
being so cold
and rational?
'Cause I don't have the luxury
of falling to pieces.
Everyone's looking to me
to handle things,
to make the right
decisions.
Everyone
is looking to me...
to lead.
If I grieve,
nobody else gets to.
You're still
a human being, Oliver.
You're allowed to have feelings.
I know sometimes
that it's easier
to live under that hood.
I'm not.
Earlier today,
I was looking at Sara,
I realized something.
One of these days
it's going to be me.
And this...[Sighs]
This life that
I've chosen...
It only ends one way.
So that's it?
You're just going
to spend your life
hiding down here
in this cave,
waiting to die?
I'm sorry.
I'm not going
to wait with you,
because if there's one thing that
today has taught me,
is that life is precious.
And I want so much more
in mine than this.
[Sighs]
Let's start
with the obvious.
Why would someone
want to kill you?
I have no idea.
This whole thing,
it's insane.
Mr. Kelso, despite
what you may have heard,
homicides at the hands
of a stranger
are incredibly rare.
Imagine how rare homicides
by bow and arrow are.
Yeah, the guy
was a sicko.
And you're a liar.
- I'm the victim here.
- You're also a witness--
my witness. And you better
give me something useful,
otherwise you're going to be
facing an obstruction charge.
You know, I think I want
to talk to your boss,
because you can't
treat people like this.
Oh, really, you want
to talk to my boss?
- Ohh!
- How's your arm feeling?!
What are you doing?!
John Burke and Tim Kaufman,
they were also shot by
with arrows.
And they're too dead
to tell me why.
Can't.
- Ohh!
- Burke and Kaufman!
What do the two of them
have to do with you?
We were all
working on a deal!
But nobody was supposed
to know about it.
Ohh! Ohh.
What kind of deal?
To build
an oil pipe line.
For Amertek. It's--
Thea: You've reached Thea.
Leave a message.
Hey, Thea, it's me. Again.
And... I don't know
if you're getting these messages,
but I would really
like to talk to you.
So please, just...
call me back.
Bye.
Lyla has multiple teams trying to get
an angle on Lacroix.
[Sighs]
Where's Felicity?
Hmm.
She needed some air.
And what do you
need, Oliver?
I just need Thea
to call me back.
That's not going
to happen.
Why? What do you mean?
It was during the siege.
We were going to run away together,
but I couldn't leave
without helping you fight.
And when I came back,
she was gone.
I didn't say anything
because this is my fault.
She knew I was lying
to her the entire time.
I'm sorry I didn't
say anything about the letter.
I know that
I should have.
Ok.
Felicity, I really
need to talk to you,
so please, can you...
Call me back as soon as you get this.
Laurel! Baby,
are you all right?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Baby, a guy just
got skewered right in front of you.
I hope
you're not fine.
And what the hell were you
doing here in the first place?
The district attorney's office--
Did not send you.
You lied to my officers
and now what,
you're just going
to stand there
and you're going
to lie to me?
I needed to talk to him.
It was important.
Look, sweetie,
I know you want to help,
but you don't need to take these
kind of risks, you understand?
Pretty sure your sister's
got that covered
for the both of you.
Yeah.
Go home. We got this.
Ok?
[Cell phone vibrates]
I've got something.
Meet me at Verdant.
Amertek Industries.
It's an oil company
based in Starling City.
Ok. Now that
I've consolidated
all of Lacroix's
victim's records,
I can run the algorithm,
scan the data
and see who received
money from Amertek.
- How long does that take?
- Not long.
Three to Kelso, one more to Burke,
two more to Kaufman.
All from a subsidiary
from Amertek in Qurac,
which just happens to be the largest
untapped oil field on the planet.
Yeah. Looks like Amertek was trying
to strike an oil deal.
And some paid Lacroix
to stop it.
None of this explains
how Sara was involved.
Sara once told me
she worked in Qurac.
And by "worked," I mean she killed
people for the League.
You're saying she might have brought
her work home with her.
Who authorized the payments?
A board member of Amertek
called Tom Weston.
He's Lacroix's next target.
What's his location?
You will not believe
where he's headed.
[Sighs]
Where do you think
you're going?
- I'm coming with you.
- Absolutely not.
Oliver, the only reason why you know
where to find him is because--
You were reckless. And Lacroix
almost put an arrow in you.
Let me handle this.
Don't you dare tell me
to stay put and think that I'll listen!
You know me better than that.
Sara was trained by some
of the greatest killers in human history.
Lacroix put her down.
So what do you think
he's going to do to you?
I don't care about anything
except for getting him.
- And I will.
- You couldn't before!
I won't let him
escape again.
I promise.
I won't let him
escape again.
[Indistinct chatter]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Ray Palmer.
Thank you. Thank you all
for coming out tonight.
Given all that has
befallen this city,
it's easy for us to lose hope--
to hide in our castles
and be thankful that our
ledges are in the black.
Well, we, the city's most affluent
businessmen and women
hold its future in our hands.
Tonight, I'm making a pledge.
I will give away
half of my net worth
to the benefit of our home.
And this will be my salary
for the year.
So tonight, I invite you all
to join me in this investment.
Not just with your money,
but with your ingenuity,
and most importantly,
your time.
The city is my home,
but it's yours, too.
So help make Star City
our future.
[All screaming]
[Both grunting]
So you're the Arrow.
I thought
you'd be taller.
It's over.
Lower your bow and live.
We both know
that's not going to happen.
- Who hired you?!
- Who's she?
You don't want
to do this.
Yes, I do!
Killing him
won't bring her back.
I know it won't bring
her back, she's dead!
I have stood where
you are right now;
where you're so consumed
with rage you can
hardly breathe,
and you think that
taking revenge
will make it better,
but Laurel... it won't.
It only makes it worse.
No, he murdered Sara!
Who's Sara?
My sister, you son of a bitch!
Two nights ago,
you put an arrow in her chest.
Two nights ago
I was drunk
in Bludhaven.
- You're lying.
- I'm proud of my work.
I wouldn't deny it.
Even with a gun in your face?
Laurel, you need to stop
and listen to him.
No.
No, he killed my sister.
Laurel, Sara
wouldn't want--
Don't you dare tell me
that this isn't what
Sara would have wanted!
Don't you tell me
to think of her,
because I am
thinking of her!
Laurel, if you pull
that trigger--
[clicking]
[Sirens]
You took the bullets
out of the gun!
We have to go.
Lacroix's alibi
checks out.
Two murders in
Bludhaven, same MO.
Same night
Sara was killed.
I almost killed Lacroix.
The only thing that
matters is you didn't.
Laurel...
the trail's
run cold.
I'm going to find
whoever did this.
I will.
But I don't know when.
Your father
deserves to know.
[Inhales, exhales]
[Indistinct chatter]
Lance: Hey, listen.
I got some word on the boy.
Yeah, some stuff's come through.
I don't know. Yeah.
It looks pretty good.
Lacroix, with an "x."
Yeah. I don't know, the guy's French
or something,
why you asking--
Oh, hold on, hold on.
I got to call you back.
Laurel, baby, what's wrong?
Hold on.
What is it?
Just tell me.
Tell me, what is it?
It's about last night.
At the hospital.
I lied to you.
And you deserve to know
the truth, and--
[beeping]
Sorry, sweetheart.
Damn thing goes off every hour
if I don't take my pills.
Laurel, what do you know?
You looked like you were
in the middle
of telling me something.
I just wanted
to say that...
That I'm really sorry.
I know that I should
have told you the truth,
I just...
I just got to--
Hey, I'm your dad.
I forgive you.
Come here.
I always forgive you.
[Exhales]
It's all right.
She can rest now.
She's home.
It's a Jewish custom.
I know she wasn't,
but it feels right.
Laurel.
No, this isn't right.
This isn't--
It--she doesn't even
get a fresh grave?
It's so perverse.
She deserves a proper burial.
She's earned it.
No, it's not fair.
No one will ever
really know who she was.
Oliver, it's not fair.
It's not fair!
Laurel, we'll know.
I know this doesn't
count for much,
but me and Lyla,
we're naming the baby Sara.
We will never forget.
Thank you.
[Sobbing]
[Grunting]
How did I--
what the hell
is going on here?
Where am I?
[Groaning]
Please, please don't--
please don't hurt me.
Just--just
let me go, please.
I promise, I--I won't
tell anybody about this.
Would a fisherman throw his
prized catch back into the sea?
[Scoffs] What
are you talking about?
Look, whoever you are,
you really don't
want to do this.
Do you have any idea who
I am? Who my father is?!
You're Thomas Merlyn.
You've been looking
for Oliver Queen.
How--how do you--
how do you know that?
A simple hack of a missing
billionaire's email account.
I knew somebody would come
looking for him,
but I thought it would be
his... mother.
His sister.
But you, the son
of the CEO of Merlyn Global.
Jackpot.
My friend,
you are going to make me
a very rich man.
So Oliver didn't...
[Gasping]
He isn't...
Oliver Queen is dead.
He's rotting at the bottom
of the ocean.
And you will, too,
if your father doesn't
pay that ransom.
[Siren] I'm in here,
please help! Help!
Police! Hong Kong police!
- It's ok.
- Thank you!
You're going home.
You're safe now.
I'm going to catch
whoever killed her.
I know you are.
And until you do,
I'm back on the team.
What about
your family?
Sara is family,
Oliver.
Just like you,
man.
So now what?
Now I got to go get Thea.
It's long past time
she came home.
["Courage or The Fall"
by Civil Twilight playing]
John.
I don't want
to die down here.
So don't, Oliver.
♪ Man wasn't made
to live alone ♪
♪ that's why I have
my enemies ♪
♪ whenever I close my eyes ♪
♪ you're all I can see ♪
♪ every man needs a savior ♪
♪ every savior needs his task ♪
♪ but which one am I ♪
♪ the man or the one
behind the mask ♪
♪ what comes first ♪
♪ the courage or the fall ♪
Hey.
Hi.
You changed your mind?
I just decided I want
more out of life.
[All grunting,
hitting sticks]
Well done.
Thanks, Dad.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man