Oliver:
My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years I was
stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
to bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
The Oliver you lost might not be
the one they found.
When you were stuck
on that island,
plotting your grand plan
to save the city,
I don't think you stopped
to consider the effect
it would have on
the people in your life.
You're wrong.
Not being able
to tell my family the truth,
it doesn't hurt anyone worse
than it hurts me.
I made you a promise.
I couldn't keep it.
After being granted the miracle
of having my child returned to me,
that you seem to have
no interest in telling me the truth.
You got to let
me in, Ollie.
someone in.
[Vibrating, beep]
Hello?
Hi. Mom said I'm
supposed to remind you
to pick her up
for lunch.
Was I supposed to have
lunch with her today?
She said she left you
like 5 messages.
Just bite the bullet and have
a Cobb salad with the woman.
You know, Thea, sometimes
it's difficult to remember
which one of you
is my mother.
Mrs. Queen,
all I'm asking for
is a chance to sit down and
discuss our proposal. Hmm?
If that's all it is, then I can
save us both the time.
It's rejected.
I see.
May I ask why?
Do I really need
to answer that, Mr. Copani?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm meeting my son
for lunch.
[Tires squeal]
Get down!
[Groans]
Mom? Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm--I'm--
are you sure?
I'm fine.
You're sure you're fine?
Call 9-1-1!
[Horns honking]
[Tires squeal]
[Siren in distance]
♪ Arrow 1x07 ♪
Muse of Fire
Original Air Date on November 28, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hi.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did you reach Walter?
No. I'm sorry.
As I was telling
your mother and sister,
the CAT-Scan showed
a grade two concussion.
She can go home so long
as someone stays with her
just to make sure
there are no after effects.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have left you.
I thought you were fine.
What did you think you
were doing anyway?
Yeah, I wanted to get
the license plate
of the guy who took
a shot at you.
Well, that was foolish.
Yeah.
So did you get
the license plate?
No. He got away.
Maybe you should spend a little
less time trying to be a hero.
You're obviously
not very good at it.
That's cute.
I wasn't trying to be.
You left her on
the street, alone and hurt.
In the street.
To get a license plate?
You don't believe me?
I love you.
Mom loves you.
But it's getting hard when you
won't be truthful with us.
Detectives.
Do you have any leads
on the shooter?
Not yet.
Did you get a good look at him?
No. He was wearing
a helmet.
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
My head of security
is on his way.
I want to make sure there are
men outside my mother's door.
She needs to be protected.
Well, you know
your family's
at the tippy-toppy
of the my list of priorities,
but the guy that
she was with was connected,
mobbed up to
the eyeballs connected.
She wasn't
the target.
And you're welcome.
♪ You are my only escape
[knock on door]
♪ You are the reason
that I wake ♪
Technically
I did get here
like 10 seconds
before this guy.
Keep the change.
So, Tommy, what brings
you by so late?
Well, I assumed,
rightly,
that you would be at home
working tonight,
and I also assumed
that you might be hungry.
Also rightly.
I don't know.
This is a mushroom
and olive pizza from Mario's.
[Scoffs] That is
damn good pie.
All right, what do
you have to offer?
Spicy tuna on crispy rice
from Toro's.
Ohh.
Damn you, Merlyn.
I hope Sushi was
all you had in mind.
Uh, actually, there was something
that I wanted to ask you.
And what's that?
Will you go out with me?
Like on a date.
You brought me dinner
to ask me to dinner?
Well, I also did throw you
a really big charity gala.
See, I thought you threw it
for the hundreds
of people it would benefit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hundreds of people.
Plus one more.
Tommy.
Laurel, I get it.
Okay, this is all happening for us
in the wrong order.
You know, first we're friends
for many years,
and then briefly
we are friends with benefits,
extremely excellent
benefits.
And now I am just
hoping that we can be two people
sitting at the same restaurant
at the same table
at the same time.
See, when I see it
like that,
it doesn't sound
so scary, does it?
Oliver, your mom
was nearly killed.
I think you can take
a day off from training.
My mother wasn't
the target.
This man was.
Paul Copani.
He was trying to close a deal
with her when they were shot at.
Copani works for
Bertinelli Construction
and Frank Bertinelli.
The mob boss?
I did some digging.
Copani isn't the first member
of Bertinelli's crew who's been hit.
You did some digging?
[Sighs] Bertinelli
has a lot of enemies.
The best way to figure out who's
trying to target his organization
is to get inside of it.
So let me get
this right, Oliver.
Your mother's shot
at, nearly killed,
and the way you
process this emotionally
is by going undercover
with the mob.
I'm not trying to process
anything emotionally.
Yeah, well, maybe
that's your problem, man.
You ever
thought about
just being there
for your family?
I tried that today
with Thea.
She told me I wasn't
being honest with her,
and she's right.
I can't very well
explain to her
that I left our mother alone and
bleeding on the pavement
because I'm fast enough to
almost run down the attacker.
But what I can do
is protect my family.
And, Diggle, when I found out
who this guy is,
he's a dead man.
Speedy.
Where you going?
Clubbing. Which is
difficult to do
when you're in a house and
not in an actual club.
I have to go out tonight.
I thought you'd be
watching mom.
I spent the whole day
with her.
I thought you were
taking the night shift.
I'm sorry, but this thing,
it's important.
You know, sometimes, Ollie,
I just don't get you.
And by sometimes,
I mean ever.
You're actually not the first
person to say that to me today.
Why am I not surprised?
Oh, nice dress.
Where you headed?
Upstairs.
Apparently.
Long story.
Hey, I heard about your
mom. Is she all right?
She's resting upstairs.
More shaken up than anything.
I got to run to this
business thing,
but I do appreciate
you stopping by.
It's no problem. Just so long as
your mom's all right.
Yeah.
Hey, one more thing.
Mainly because I don't
want you to find this
out from someone else,
that someone else
especially being Laurel.
We're going to dinner.
As in a date.
That's...that's good.
Laurel deserves
someone special,
and so do you.
Thanks, man.
I gotta run to this thing.
All right. Absolutely.
I'll catch you later.
Oh, and, Tommy,
if you hurt her,
I'll snap your neck.
I'm just kidding.
[Doorbell rings]
Mr. Bertinelli.
Call me Frank.
Ahh. Call me Oliver.
Thank you for agreeing
to meet me at my home.
My father used
to say that living rooms
make the best
conference rooms.
Oh, I'm gonna steal that.
Nick Salvati,
my associate.
How do you do?
Let's have a drink.
So what are you
in the mood for?
We could watch
reality housewife cooking show
or cop docs.
It's where doctors
run around fighting crime
when they're not
all sleeping with each other.
[Laughs]
Whatever you want,
sweetheart.
You're the one who's
given up your evening out.
Oh, it's not like
there's anybody else
who could be staying
with you.
[Gasps] Oh, wait,
yes, there is.
Don't be too harsh
on your brother.
Why not?
I mean, aren't you
getting sick of his lies?
Thea, everyone has secrets.
We all have things that
we want to keep to ourselves.
I just don't get him
sometimes.
I know.
[Sighs]
You know, being in that hospital
and seeing Dr. Lamb again,
it made me remember the day
that Oliver came home.
It was Dr. Lamb
that told me
that the Oliver we'd lost
might not be the Oliver
that they'd found.
I think it's easy
to forget,
but he lived apart
from civilization for 5 years.
So what, he gets like
a free pass?
No. No, no, no,
not at all.
I...
I just think we need
to stop judging him
for the Oliver he was
and start accepting him
for the Oliver that he is.
So, Oliver,
I'll be honest with you.
I was surprised
to hear from you.
It was my impression
from the local news
that you weren't going to be
involved with your family's business.
Well, apparently
there were a few catch phrases
that I missed
while I was away for 5 years.
One of them being
"mainstream media."
[Laughs]
The press never gets
anything right.
[Cell phone rings]
Oh, I know a thing
or two about that.
So, Oliver, I'll be blunt.
Mm-hmm.
I want the contract
to build Queen Consolidated's
new Applied Sciences Division.
And I am inclined
to give it to you.
Your mother wasn't
quite so enthusiastic.
How is she, by the way?
She's recuperating
at home. Thank you.
What a terrible thing
that happened.
And, Frank, I was
very sorry to hear
about what happened
to Paul Copani.
Paul was a good friend.
He was a good man.
Yeah. The violence
in this city.
You know, sometimes
I wonder why I stay.
I've had
the same thought.
So why did you come back?
After that island, you could have
settled anywhere in the world.
Because starling
city is my home.
[Speaking Italian]
No matter which way
you go or turn,
you always end up
at home.
Oliver, this is
my daughter Helena.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm heading out.
All right.
Take one of the guys
with you.
I can take care
of myself.
I wasn't asking,
sweetie.
Frank, that meeting
you requested.
They can do it.
Now.
I can come back
another time.
No, no, no.
Just, uh.
Just excuse us for
a moment, would you?
Thank you.
Oliver Queen.
The rich man's
Lindsay Lohan.
Look, um...
I've got to go
to this other meeting,
but I need someone
to take him to dinner.
So you pimp out
your daughter.
No. I ask her to help me
close a business deal.
A reminder that
the family business is dying
and that we need
this contract,
and Oliver Queen
can give it to us.
Please, Sweet Pea.
For us.
For me. Hmm?
That's my girl.
Oliver, I'm so sorry.
Something has come up.
But Helena would love
to take you to dinner
and discuss the deal
further.
Oh. I was hoping
to speak with you.
Well, as you speak
for your family,
my daughter also speaks
for ours.
It's...It's really
not necessary.
It would be my pleasure.
Sure.
I look forward
to working together.
[Groans]
[Car door closes]
Thank you for coming.
Anything for a friend.
[Speaking Chinese]
We're not responsible
for the attacks on your people.
These attacks
on my business
are my family's
life blood.
They stop now,
or I'm coming for you.
What does the Triad
have to gain by provoking you now?
Well, no one ever credited
the Triad with rational thinking?
If not them, then who?
Whoever it is, when I
find out who's behind this,
there will be blood.
Sounds like Bertinelli's
ready to put the screws
to everyone who pays him
protection money.
Yeah, well, 3 of his best
earners have been murdered.
He's gotta make up the cash
somewhere.
Whoever is pruning
the family tree
is using bullets
instead of arrows.
So you do think
it's one of the other families.
No.
Then who?
Well, according to
the coroner's reports,
none of the vics
took a clean shot.
Half the bullets missed.
Our killer's not a pro.
That's not stopping him
from pulling that trigger.
That's up to us.
Or this is gonna blow up
into an all-out mob war.
You are an angel,
Helena.
So beautiful.
Well, we are gonna take good
care of both of you tonight.
You'll tell your father
hello from us?
Of course, Mr. Russo.
I'll give you a minute.
Thank you.
I heard about
your mother's accident.
Is he gonna be okay?
She's gonna be fine.
Thanks.
I'm glad.
So, why would you want to go
into business with my father?
You know who he is
and how he made his money.
You don't approve of your
family's enterprises?
We share a name,
and that name defines us
whether we want it to or not.
You've already made judgments
about me,
just like I've already
made judgments about you.
Right. I'm the rich man's
Lindsay Lohan.
[Sighs] Sorry.
That's okay.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Yeah.
I know it must have been
hell for you,
alone on that island
for 5 years, but I'm...
But what?
But was there ever a day
when you were just...
Happy to be away
from everything?
No pressure from your family,
no need to be the person
everyone else expects you to be.
Was there ever a day when--
when I didn't feel lost
and I felt...free?
More than one.
And, uh...
Those are the days
that I miss.
Whew!
Ohh...[Laughs]
What, is it too spicy
for you, Merlyn?
No. No, not really.
I'm just, um,
I'm just crying because
I was thinking of
a Hallmark commercial
I saw earlier today,
featuring a sick kitty.
It was very emotional.
[Both laugh]
Will there be anything else?
No. Thank you.
Yeah.
Thanks for letting me
take you to dinner.
Well, thank you for
letting me choose Indian.
You know, I read this article
by a film critic once,
who said if he could have
one wish,
it would be to watch his favorite
movie again for the first time.
I kind of wish
that was us.
So you want dinner
and a movie.
No.
I wish we had just met
and that all this
was just beginning
and there wasn't so much
of me I wish you'd forget.
Well, keep saying
nice things like that
and maybe next time
I'll let you choose the restaurant.
Mr. Merlyn...
Yeah?
I'm sorry, I'm afraid
you credit card has been declined.
Did you swipe it
a few times?
You know, sometimes
those things can be a little glitchy.
I did, and, um,
I'm afraid the credit card company
wants me to confiscate it.
Thank you.
People are always asking me,
what did I miss the most?
[Takes deep breath]
Air conditioning.
Satellite radio.
Tagliet--uh--ta--
tagliatelle?
Mm.
Right.
But those are the answers
that I give people
because those are the answers
they're expecting.
Why can't you
just be truthful?
I don't know how truthful
I can be.
You've been through
a crucible,
and it changed you.
How can it not?
That's beautiful.
Your cross.
It's a gift.
From my fiance.
Fiance.
Mm.
I didn't know
you were engaged.
I'm not.
Anymore.
He died.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
That was my crucible.
Boy, it's nice to...
It's really nice to be with someone
that I can be myself with.
It's nice to be with someone
who knows how hard it can be.
[Cell phone vibrates]
I'm really sorry.
It's okay. Take it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's Diggle.
Something came up.
You gotta get out of there
and call me back.
Helena, I have to go. There's
something that I have to do.
It's about my mother,
otherwise I would, uh,
I would stay.
And I would like that.
[Laughs]
My father would kill me
if I let you pay.
I have a confession.
I didn't want to go out
with you tonight.
That makes two of us.
I'm really glad that I did.
Hmm.
Oliver.
Be careful with my father.
[Knock on door]
Thea, you don't need
to knock, sweetheart.
What about me?
I hope you don't mind.
Thea let me in.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see how
your recovery was going?
Well, surely someone
of your means has a telephone.
I like to see someone
when I have something
important to talk about.
We used to be friends,
Moira.
I still remember that time.
You, me, and Robert.
Which is why I came by.
You are a vital part
of Starling City's future.
Robert feared that future.
He lost his conviction.
It's been my experience
that when someone
has a brush with death
like you experienced today,
even their deepest held
convictions can change.
Have they?
No.
You didn't have to say it.
I can see that they haven't.
What happened?
Yeah, it's what's
about to happen.
Bertinelli's enforcer
Nick Salvati--
yeah. We drank a scotch
together.
He seems like a real
stand-up mobster.
Yeah, well, he's been
paying visits to everyone
who owes the mob
protection money.
Diggle, I'm trying to figure out
who took a shot at my mother,
not take on all
of organized crime.
Well, listen, Oliver,
Salvati and his goons
have already put 4 people
in the hospital tonight,
and if somebody
doesn't stop them,
the poor bastard who owns
Russo's is gonna be next.
Wait, wait. Russo's?
It's at the corner
of Adams and--
I know where it is, Diggle.
I'm here right now.
What?
I was having dinner
with Bertinelli's daughter.
Oliver, you're supposed to be
going undercover, not speed dating.
I didn't have a choice.
Yeah, well, uh,
I've seen her on the web.
You made quite the sacrifice.
Salvati's here.
I'm sorry, we're closed.
Oh, Mr. Salvati.
Buona sera.
I have some fresh-made
lasagna.
We're not here
for food, Mr. Russo.
Your payment's due.
I already made
my payment this month.
You need to pay again.
Please. I can't afford to make
another payment if I'm going to--
Going to what?
Restock your bar?
Break his fingers.
Leave him alone!
Break hers, too.
No! Don't touch her!
I don't understand.
Why is she targeting her family?
I don't know. And here I thought
you had parental issues.
It's not a joke, Diggle.
Oliver, you're not falling
for this girl, are you?
Because I know you can't be
that crazy.
Helena Bertinelli
shot at your mother.
She also murdered 4 men
in cold blood.
She has to have reasons
for what she's doing.
Reasons?
Since when do you care
about the bad guys' reasons?
Oh, she I the bad guy,
Oliver.
She's the killer. And whatever's
going on in your head,
you better get it
straight, man.
Any attempt on his right hand
is gonna send your girlfriend's
father on the warpath.
I know what I'm doing.
Now I know how your family feels
when you lie to them.
Is this the only angle
you got?
The Russos chintzed out a bit
on their security package.
Somebody is in the wings
with a gun shooting at these guys.
What do you got
from earlier?
Yeah.
You mean before the shooting?
A business dinner, a birthday dinner,
a couple of blind dates.
Any guests of the Chinese
persuasion?
Humor me.
Why?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a second. What was that?
Help yourself.
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
[Knock on door]
Detective.
Is everything okay?
Your, um, your buddy
with the arrows
was at Russo's last night.
And I was there earlier
with a date.
So...what?
You think I'm
the hood guy again?
No.
Your date.
Helena Bertinelli.
If I were you,
I'd stay away from her.
Her family's bad news
on a good day.
Why the sudden concern
for my well-being?
A few weeks ago
I made a mistake.
I almost got you killed.
And you felt like
you owed me one?
If I did, as far as I'm concerned,
this clears the books.
[Clacking]
[Grunting]
Can I talk to you?
Dad!
In case
you haven't noticed,
I'm a little occupied
at the moment.
I just talked
to the accountant.
He said my accounts
were frozen.
He said my credit cards
were all canceled.
I pay Sandy a king's ransom
each year in fees, Tommy.
When it comes to money,
if he says it's so, it's so.
Do you think this is a joke?
No.
You are.
Although I must say,
your chronic irresponsibility
and terminal laziness
has lost its humor.
Hmm.
You're wondering why now.
The better question is,
why not sooner?
It's...
It's my trust fund.
Which is comprised
of my money.
Oh, excuse me.
Was comprised.
[Indistinct song playing]
Helena.
How did you
find me here?
I followed you
from your house.
Your fiance?
Yeah.
You said that losing him
was your own crucible.
That it changed you.
You didn't say how.
When you love someone
as much as I loved him,
with all of your heart,
and you can't just
turn that emotion off
when they're taken from you.
You still feel things
as deeply.
And if it can't be love
that you feel, then...
then it becomes hate.
Hate for who?
Oliver...
you should stay away
from me.
Helena?
[Vehicle approaches]
[Brakes squeal]
Get in.
My father is going
to kill you for this.
I've been wanting
to do that for years.
Spoiled bitch.
I knew it was someone
from the inside
waging war against
your father and me.
I just never thought
it'd be this inside.
You dropped this
at Russo's.
You're smarter than I
gave you credit for, Nicky.
You're not.
Hey!
You're a businessman, right?
So let's talk business.
I can offer you a lot
of money if you let us go.
This isn't about money,
Richie Rich.
This is about loyalty.
He's got nothing to do
with any of this.
Then what the hell
is it about?
My father had Michael murdered.
[Laughs]
Of course he did.
He didn't want you
to know the truth.
Your rat of a fiance
was gathering evidence.
He was talking
to the friggin' FBI.
The love of your life
was going to destroy
your father.
You're wrong.
Uhh.
I found a laptop
in Michael's bag, Helena.
Everything that could
send your father and me to prison
for the rest of our lives
was on it.
That computer--
was mine.
Michael wasn't the one
talking to the FBI.
I was.
You?
My father is a monster.
He doesn't care who he hurts
to keep his money and power,
and I wanted it to stop.
Well, then it's your fault
Michael's dead.
Not your father
for ordering the hit
or me for carrying it out.
Yours.
You shot Michael.
In the chest,
so he knew it was me.
Just...
like...
this.
Uhh!
[Choking]
You're gonna burn in hell
for what you've done.
It'll be worth it.
Uhh!
Get up!
Helena...
I didn't have a choice,
Oliver.
No one can know my secret.
CSU didn't find
any usable prints
except for the 3 victims.
One of them had
a GSW to the chest.
So who broke the necks of Salvati
and his buddy?
Look, it's been a while
since the Hood broke anyone's neck.
And I didn't see
any arrows laying around.
We better pray that
Frank Bertinelli blames
the Hood for this.
'Cause if he thinks
it's the Triad,
Starling City is ground
zero to World War III.
[Knock on door]
You okay?
I spoke to my dad
today.
I bet that was fun.
He explained to me what happened
with my credit card yesterday.
And my checking account,
my savings account,
my brokerage account,
my stock portfolio.
He cut me off completely.
What?
My car got repossessed.
That was fun.
Oh, and I have to move out
of my apartment by
the end of the month.
You are gonna be fine,
Tommy.
In fact, you are
gonna be great.
Merlyn money or not.
And you know,
I have a mushroom
and olive Mario pizza
in my refrigerator
waiting to be eaten.
I suppose it's already
paid for, right?
Exactly.
♪ Oh, no, I've
said too much ♪
[Song continues indistinctly]
When did you get back?
Just now.
I'm so happy to see you.
[Chuckles]
But did you come home only
because you heard I was hurt?
No. I was already on my way
when Thea called.
I actually came home
because I miss my wife.
Ohh.
Walter: It's okay.
Is she all right?
Walter's home.
She's gonna be fine.
Look, I'm sorry
if I was a bitch
with you earlier.
There were a few times.
Could you be more
specific?
Don't push it.
Don't worry.
You weren't a bitch.
At the hospital you were a little...
A little bit.
Look, I'm just
worried about you.
You seem really lonely.
And we all have
our secrets, Ollie.
Clearly you have yours.
And it's fine if you don't
want to share them with us,
but I just really think
you should share them
with someone.
[Sighs]
I'd ask how you
got in here,
but the Starling City
vigilante comes and goes
as he pleases, doesn't he?
How'd you know?
I saw you fight.
And I saw your eyes.
That island changed you
in ways
that only someone like me
could understand.
No.
What you're doing
right now,
I know that if feels
like justice, but it's not.
It's revenge.
Sometimes revenge
is justice.
Your father killed
your fiance.
And what did your
father do to you?
Isn't the man in the hood
fighting to set things right?
Why is your vendetta
more valid than mine?
We're the same,
you and I.
No, we're not.
[Scoffs]
Hiding in plain sight.
Concealing our anger
with smiles and lies.
Don't lie to me,
Oliver.
You feel the same
as I do, I know it.
Why are you crying?
[Music playing]
I don't know.
Maybe it's because
I have been alone
in my hate for so long.
I feel--
It feels so good
to tell the truth.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==