Previously, on "Arrow"...
That woman running around in black
leather tonight, that wasn't Sara.
Sure it was. Who else would it be?
That's why I'm talking to you.
Who are we running from?
His name is Ra's al Ghul,
and he's marked me
and my family for death.
I heard a rumor you were leaving town.
Happy to say that those rumors were false.
[Speaking Arabic]
Ra's is going to come for me,
and he will learn the truth about Sara.
Then he will come for Thea.
That's why I have to kill him.
You couldn't before.
This time, I will have you to train me.
[Groaning]
Dinah Laurel Lance...
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
[Grunting]
[Groaning and gasping]
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying to take my place?
* Arrow 3x13 * Canaries
Original Air Date on February 11, 2015
sync & corrected by elderman / resynced to LOL by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Your job, apparently.
I told you that I didn't want you out here.
And I told you that it
wasn't your call to make!
Will you think for a second
about what it would do
to your father if
something happened to you?
What you're doing is selfish.
Fighting for your city isn't selfish.
It's what a hero would do.
You're not a hero.
Maybe it's best if we stay
out of each other's way.
How did it go out there?
We ran into Laurel.
Again.
Diggle, how could you
sign off on her doing this?
Oliver, you might not notice,
but she's not exactly lobbying
for anyone's permission.
She has yours.
Well, not at first, but she can
definitely hold her own out there.
You have a visitor.
Or as I like to call him, your new BFF.
I see things are still
running smoothly down here.
What do you want?
[Sighs] It's been weeks since your return.
I thought it past time we spoke.
Nanda Parbat is remote,
but I wouldn't delude
yourself into thinking
that Ra's al Ghul missed
your televised return
to Starling City.
Your point, Malcolm?
We can't merely wait
for Ra's to mobilize his forces.
It's time to bring Thea into the fold.
She's not ready to know my secret.
I disagree.
But in any case,
if we have to protect Thea
and to defeat the League,
the three of us need to join forces.
But I don't see how we can do that
if she is still to believe that her brother
is a reformed playboy
and failed businessman.
John: Oliver, I told you before,
if Thea finds out you've been
lying to her all this time,
you will lose her... forever.
Oliver: How's Tatsu?
She'll be better when
we're far away from here.
Your bow. If you want anything else,
take it quickly. We're
leaving in five minutes.
We're not coming back.
Oh, we can't just run.
Waller knows I tried to steal the virus
to get Tatsu back. Even if she didn't,
Chen Na Wei knows where we live.
We have to go.
Look, Maseo, we...
You stay, Waller will
torture you to find us.
Contact your family, contact the press.
Once the world knows
Oliver Queen is still alive,
it will limit A.R.G.U.S.'s options,
make it more difficult for
Waller to assassinate you.
Well, that's reassuring.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to take Akio and Tatsu
on the ferry to Shanghai.
And from there, we will disappear.
You saved us.
Now save yourself.
[Reporters all talking at once]
Reaction to sentencing, Mr. Zytle?
The Roman governor
Porcius Festus maintained
that the accused
has the right to face their accuser.
Now, where is my accuser?
I speak, of course, of the Arrow.
Excuse me, Mr. Zytle
has no further comments.
ADA Laurel Lance. Take
him to the van. Thank you.
[Growling]
Stay back!
- [All screaming]
- Alderman, stay back!
- [Gasps]
- Where's Zytle?
Hey.
So you still haven't told me...
what did you think of my set last night?
Because fangirls on Vine
called it "epically epic."
More like epically profitable.
It's kind of hot when you
talk business in numbers.
Chase. God, if you ever
really want to kiss me again,
you're going to have to work on your game.
Later, Princess.
Ollie.
Hey, Speedy.
I'm so happy you're home.
What?
I have to show you something.
Where are we going?
Basement.
I... thought that you
said that it was flooded.
I lied.
Ollie...
[Scoffs] What's going on? You're kind of...
kind of making me nervous.
I know that this isn't going to mean much.
I've given you no reason
to believe me when I say it.
But I lied all of this time
to protect you.
You're...
You're him.
Yeah.
That night with the... the hoods, and...
that woman in black, that...
Was Ra's al Ghul's daughter.
That was you.
All those times I got so mad at you
for being... a flake,
or telling me something I knew
that had to be a lie.
You were saving someone's life.
[Sighs] Thank you.
Thank you, Ollie.
Thank you.
Thea: You know how many times I've wished
that I could thank the Arrow for
things he's done for the city?
Probably as many times as I've wished
we could have this conversation.
Did mom know?
The night that she died,
she told me that...
she'd known for a while.
I was worried that you'd be angry.
Only 'cause you broke my window.
Although I did kind of kick your ass.
You didn't.
But you did have a good teacher.
You were looking for Malcolm that night.
We know about each other.
Wait, Malcolm knows that you're the Arrow?
I am amazed that he didn't tell you.
Then why did you... tell me?
Why now?
[Door opens]
Because Ra's al Ghul is coming for us.
All of us. And the only chance
that we have to survive
is to work together.
To trust each other.
He's right.
No.
No, no, he's not.
I turned my back on everyone I know,
including my own brother,
because you told me there
was nobody else I could trust.
I was only trying to protect you.
Yeah, by driving a wedge
between me and Ollie?
You manipulated me.
- Thea...
- Let her go.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Yeah?
[Line ringing]
Moira, on answering machine:
You've reached Moira Queen.
- Please leave a message.
- [Beep]
Mom, it's me. I'm alive.
I'm, uh, I'm in Hong Kong.
I know it sounds crazy, but I'm alive,
I'm in Hong Kong, and I need your help.
I want you to call Ned Foster,
you tell him to issue a press release.
Tell everyone.
And you tell Thea.
I'm coming home. I love you...
[groaning]
What do we know?
Apparently the federal
marshal guarding Werner Zytle
just started shooting while
Zytle waltzed off in the panic.
This is my favorite part.
Roy: That's pretty convenient.
Guy decides to wig out,
and Zytle takes advantage.
It's not convenient, it's planned.
Those are the affects of his vertigo.
Zytle was in a full set of restraints.
How did he even manage
to dose a federal agent?
He didn't. One of the reporters did.
What's wrong? Was my form off?
She's right. About the reporter.
We need a name...
a name and address on our clumsy reporter.
I'm on it.
What do you think you're doing?
- I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
I just gave you your only lead!
Can I talk to you for a second? Alone?
I know what you're going to say,
but I risked my life for
this city while you were gone.
That should earn me some respect.
This isn't about respect,
and it's not about you risking your life.
I understand that you miss Sara.
And I understand that when
you go out there like this,
all of that pain goes away.
It's the only time it ever does.
And that relief isn't real.
It's a drug.
If you're implying...
You are an addict.
And just like with booze and pills,
that high that you're chasing every night
is endangering your life.
Go to hell, Oliver.
You don't get to play that card with me.
Ever.
And if there is anyone
who is using adrenaline
to hide the pain of real
feelings and real life,
it's you.
Oliver, Felicity tracked down
the reporter's work address.
Anthony Walker! Where's Werner Zytle?
He's not... he's not here.
You helped him escape today!
Zytle, he threatened my wife.
Said he could get to
her, that he'd kill her
if I didn't do this, then...
Do what?
Kill you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Anthony...
Give me the detonator.
He'll kill my wife.
We can protect her.
I promise.
Now hand me the detonator.
God forgive me.
I will weep for thee.
[Cell phone vibrating]
- _
- Thea: Ollie?
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
Can't sleep. Apparently insomnia
is a common side effect
of finding out your brother is a vigilante.
[Oliver chuckles]
You smell like smoke.
Korean barbecue?
C4. Yeah.
It's nice that we can tell
each other this stuff now.
It is, actually.
You always had the lamest excuses.
Lame excuses are sort of
an occupational hazard.
What was tonight's hazard?
Roy and I were looking for the man
that escaped from the
courthouse earlier today.
Found a bomb instead.
Yeah, I don't know how you do it.
Just risk your life out
there for people every night.
It's my job.
It is my job to keep the
people of this city safe.
And that includes you, too, Speedy.
Listen to me.
I'm always going to hate Malcolm Merlyn.
But right now, he is a necessary evil.
We can take care of ourselves...
Not against Ra's al Ghul.
You have to trust me on this.
I do.
But I don't trust him.
I can't.
And I won't.
[Oliver groaning]
- [Gasping]
- Amanda: Ten minutes.
I'm impressed.
I know special forces who
can't last longer than three.
Eventually, though,
everybody breaks.
[Coughing]
Tell me where the Yamashiros
are, and it will stop.
My family's going to be looking for me.
Everyone is going to be looking for me!
Because your mother issued a press release?
We erased your message before
she could hear a word of it.
Be glad.
If she had heard it, your
mother would be dead right now.
You would never risk the exposure.
Hmm, you're right.
Your mother's too public a figure.
But your sister, on the other hand.
What's her name? Thea?
Did you know she's developed something
of a substance abuse problem
since you've been gone?
I guess the strain of
losing two family members
must have been too much for her to bear.
One day, someone may just
find her in the back of a car,
dead with a needle in her arm.
Poor Speedy.
You stay away from my sister.
I will, if you answer one question.
Where are the Yamashiros?
The ferry to Shanghai.
[Knock on door] Knock knock.
Hey.
You know, half the department
is still talking about the
way you clocked that marshal.
[Chuckles] Those boxing lessons
look like they're paying off.
Yeah, I guess so. Uh, are
those the cargo manifests
- for the whole city?
- Yeah, yeah.
Although, you know, I got to
ask, what do you need these for?
Just a RICO case that I'm second chairing.
Right.
- Dad?
- Yeah, sorry.
I just... [Sighs]
Have you heard from Sara lately?
No. Why?
I ran into her a few weeks back.
And something just felt a little... off.
Then I ran into that friend of hers.
You know, the one with
the, uh, the boy hair?
Sin.
Yeah, Sin, that's it.
She said something strange.
She said that the woman
in black isn't Sara.
That doesn't make any sense.
No.
I mean, look, I just want to talk to her,
you know, Sara or not.
But look, don't worry, I
said I'd start taking it easy,
I meant it.
I'll get out of your hair.
Now I've been wondering,
how do you decide between the red hoodie
and the one with the mask?
I'm glad you know.
I feel pretty lame
for not recognizing my own brother
just because he's wearing a hood.
I can't believe you knew before I did.
He saved my life, Thea.
He saved a lot of people's lives.
He thinks we need Merlyn's help.
Hmm.
And what do you think?
I think I want to get as far away
from Malcolm Merlyn as I possibly can.
Well, there's your answer right there.
Hey.
Sorry.
May I borrow him for a second?
[Scoffs] Apparently,
he's been more yours
than mine lately, so...
What happened?
One of our trackers sent a signal
from the Starling City docks.
Except we don't have any
tracking devices in the field.
Unless we do.
It's Laurel.
You tagged Laurel with a tracer?
If she's going to be reckless,
I need to know what she's doing.
Well, she's definitely doing something.
I'm just not exactly
sure how reckless it is.
I ran the manifests on all these
shipping containers that you see here.
One of these leads back
to Zytle's old supplier.
Looks like Vertigo's back in business.
[Sighs] She's going to get herself killed.
Suit up.
Hey!
Werner: Wonderful seeing you again.
Ooh, I fancy the new outfit.
[Groaning]
[Gasping]
Feeling my Vertigo, dear.
Wonderful.
Dinah Laurel Lance.
- [Grunts]
- Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying to take my place?
Oliver: Get away from her!
You should be dead!
I salute your persistence!
[All grunting]
Laurel: Help me!
Help!
Help me, please.
Roy: Need an IV.
Watch her.
You're going to be ok.
It's going to be ok.
Why did I have to die?
Sara?
If you wanted to be me, you could have.
I didn't have to die.
I am so sorry! I am so sorry!
Sara! I am so... [Gasps]
Thea: Ollie?
I'm... I'm sorry, I just wanted to talk.
You need to go back upstairs.
Now!
Hey!
Don't talk to her like
that. You brought her in;
you don't have the right to kick her out.
I'm not. I'm protecting her.
By telling her what to do?
Work with Malcolm Merlyn, let
him get his hooks deeper...
Enough. She's my sister.
She makes her own choices, Oliver!
It's ok. I... we can talk later.
I just... just, is Laurel ok?
Is she a part of this, too?
She's going to be fine.
I promise. Just...
Please go back upstairs.
What the hell was that?
You think you're the only
person who can stand up for Thea?
I'm trying to figure out
why you're standing up to me!
- All right, maybe we just need to throttle back.
- No.
We need this. Oliver, you were gone.
Dead. At least we thought you were,
and we had to go on with our lives.
And doing that meant not
doing things your way.
Fine! I'm back now.
That doesn't mean that we can go back.
And you do not have the
right to come back here
and question everyone's choices.
Just let me know if there's
any change in her condition.
- Hey, how's it going?
- [Thea sighs]
What's that for?
My life has been really complicated lately,
so I... I just need something simple.
So...
This seat taken?
It's a free country.
Apparently.
The first time that we went after Zytle,
I told you that this was my crusade.
Doesn't seem to be the case anymore.
You're right. It isn't.
Diggle, I get that I was gone for...
No, you weren't gone... you were dead.
And all of us, including me,
we were ready to hang it up.
Why didn't you?
Because I realized we
weren't just fighting for you;
we were fighting for ourselves, too.
And that includes Roy.
And, yes, that includes Laurel.
- [Sighs] She's not a soldier.
- Neither were you.
That's not the same
thing, and you know that.
[Exhales]
What I know, Oliver, is
that you started something.
Something strong enough
to live on past you.
The question is,
can you live with what it's become?
[Footsteps on stairs]
Oliver.
Are you all right?
I told them you were on the ferry.
I'm sorry.
They tortured you.
I sold you out.
No, you didn't.
Because we were never going to Shanghai.
I lied.
A precaution just in
case you were captured.
Then how'd they find you?
They didn't. When I found
out you'd been taken,
I came back.
You're an idiot.
Maybe.
But I will not let you face
Waller alone for my actions.
So now we're both going
to get tortured, or worse.
Great plan.
I must speak with Agent Waller.
Hey! Why did you...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
When Zytle hit me with Vertigo, I...
I saw Sara.
She was alive.
And she was calling me a fraud.
I was crazy to think that I was fit
to wear Sara's jacket.
Much less follow in her footsteps.
You're right.
I hope I'm not out of line here,
but...
I think Sara wore her mask
just as much to hide her demons
as she did to help people.
And I don't see that with you.
You have a light inside of you
that Sara never had.
So...
Maybe you should stop trying to be Sara...
and just be yourself.
Thank you.
[Beeping]
What's that?
One of the chemical
drums Zytle stole tonight
just sent out a GPS signal.
Why?
'Cause he just opened it.
Ah. I dig your place.
- I'm sorry I interrupted the tour.
- [Laughs]
Pretty sure you saw
everything you needed to.
Mmm.
You want a drink?
Sure.
This was nice.
I almost took it personally
when you said I was simple.
Well, I never said that you were simple.
What?
Nothing. It...
It's just something my father once said.
We were sitting in this little
taberna in Corto Maltese,
drinking this amazing Carménère,
and he said that for centuries,
noblemen have been using
the rich aroma of red wine
to cover up a very different scent.
Cyanide.
Tell me who you are and what he
hell you think you're doing here!
Serving my master, Ra's al Ghul.
[Both grunting]
Please!
Don't struggle. I can do this
so you won't feel a thing.
Get away from her.
If you beg forgiveness for
trying to harm my daughter,
I'll grant you a quick death.
I'd never give you the
satisfaction, Al Sa-Her.
You're unarmed and you have nowhere to run.
But there's some place I can go
where you won't dare to follow.
[Groaning]
Felicity: Daggett
Pharmaceuticals. 5th and Kingsley.
Looks like Zytle found a
place to change those chemicals
into some new Vertigo...
and he's got hostages.
- Where's Roy?
- I can't reach him.
Laurel.
Oliver.
There isn't anything that you can say to me
that I don't already know.
Actually, there is.
I must once again thank you
for letting us use your laboratory
this evening. And my sincerest apologies
to your colleague here.
But mistakes will not be tolerated.
Werner Zytle...
This ends now.
As you wish!
May I suggest a grand finale...
chlorine triflouride.
Oliver, I'm registering an
enormous spike in thermal activity.
Oliver, the whole place is going to blow.
You have to get out of there!
Not yet.
Go! Run! Now!
Please! Help!
Help!
I'm surprised.
Usually women don't return
for a second go.
Hi, sis.
You're not her. You're...
You're not real.
Oh, I'm quite real.
[Both grunting]
You lied to me, Laurel!
Straight to my face, my own daughter!
Sara was my daughter, I
deserved to know! I had a right!
To grieve, to mourn!
Who do you think you are
to take that away from me?
Huh? Who do you think you are?!
I'm... I'm sorry!
I know you are.
She says she's sorry,
but she'll do it again.
You keep my own daughter's death a secret
because you think I'm
too weak for the truth?!
You think you can wear my mask?
You think you can be me?!
No.
And I'm done trying to be.
[Gasping]
Felicity: Oliver, are you there?
It's over.
No, it's not. You have to get home.
It's Thea.
Lance: See? All good.
Hey.
Is everything ok?
Oh, yeah, just the usual insurance policy
search and seizure.
Seems like I'm a high risk case.
I wonder what gave them that idea.
What's a matter? You ok?
Um...
There's, um...
there's something that I have to tell you.
And I didn't tell you...
I didn't tell you before, because I was
worried about your health.
But... I realize that...
that you deserve to know.
I already know it.
Sara's off God knows where,
and yet there's another blonde
in a mask running around
tuning up the bad guys,
and it's you, isn't it?
Sweetheart, come on.
It's all right. It's ok.
It's ok, honey.
I mean, look, I am pissed as hell.
But, you know, we'll figure it
out. We figure out everything.
No. No, no, daddy, that...
[crying]
That isn't what I was going to tell you.
What I was going to tell you
is about Sara.
No.
Dad...
No. Dad...
Daddy, I'm sorry.
Not my baby, not again.
[Both sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
I can't do this.
Oh, God, please.
[Door opens]
Oliver: Thea?
It's ok. You're ok.
I thought that I was stronger.
I thought that I could keep myself safe.
Who was he?
Malcolm: One of Ra's agents.
Roy...
Could you give us a minute?
Really hope you're not
expecting a thank you.
No parent needs gratitude
for saving their child.
I didn't ask to be a part of this.
I didn't ask for any of this.
[Sighs] Maybe you're right.
Maybe we can't do this without him.
But I am never going to
forget the things you've done.
Or the person that you are.
Understood.
But before we can begin,
there's something that
only the two of you can do.
Ra's al Ghul preys upon
the fears of his enemies.
Conquer your own fear,
and you eliminate that critical advantage.
For you, there is only one place
on earth uniquely suited to doing that.
So you're leaving again?
She's got a point, man. You just got back.
It's just for a few days.
Ordinarily, I wouldn't do this.
But it's for Thea.
And if you've shown me anything,
it's that the city is more
than safe in your hands.
All of your hands.
Thank you.
Ollie told you we're heading out for a bit?
You cool with it all?
[Exhales] After the whole chase thing,
I think it's going to be a little while
before I'm cool with anything.
[Chuckles]
What was that for?
Take your pick. Saving my life,
or standing up to Oliver about Malcolm.
I should get going.
[Exhales]
Oliver: Come on, Speedy,
we have four more miles
to make before night fall.
Ah, God.
I get that Malcolm wants
to whip us into shape
so we can face the
League, but don't you think
it's a little bit excessive?
We've been here for two hours.
Are you complaining already?
I... I started thinking it
after the first ten minutes.
Well, give it time.
Eventually this place will feel like home.
It does not look like home.
It was for me. For other people,
this is Purgatory.
You're not dead, if that's
what you're wondering.
Once again, you have the good fortune
of being uniquely qualified to help me.
Me? Why?
Chen Na Wei has left Hong
Kong. We've tracked her here.
Here? Where are we...
Welcome home, Mr. Queen.
sync & corrected by elderman / resynced to LOL by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com