My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
How long are you gonna be
staying here, man?
I'm a fugitive, Rene. I live here.
Why didn't you tell me
that Kovar was making a move
against the Bratva?
Well, Pakhan is going to be here
any moment. He'll explain everything.
You're going to blow his new casino up.
Hello, Oliver Queen.
My name is Konstantin Kovar.
Is there something you wanna tell me?
If that's code for
"are you still drinking,"
then my answer hasn't changed
since the last 50 times you asked me.
Oliver, I think we have
a real lead on who Prometheus is.
He's a member of the SCPD.
What's with the music?
It keeps the girls mellow.
She'll do. 5k.
Come on, man. Look at her. Seven.
Well, that's the Green Arrow.
Turning off the lights.
I heard he does that.
Run!
Come on, hoss. Ease up.
What's gotten into you today?
For the past three weeks,
I've either been living here or at HIVE.
Call it cabin fever.
Well, how about
you don't take it out on me?
I don't even know why you're teaching us
how to use these things.
What good is a wooden stick
if the other guy's got a gun?
You ever heard of Slade Wilson?
He could take you down
in about two seconds with a wooden stick.
Actually, they're more than
just wooden sticks.
They're from the Philippines,
and their technical name is...
Baston.
"All that most maddens and torments,
"all that cracks the sinews
and cakes the brain."
Rory, is that from the Torah?
Moby Dick.
Oh. Does that make me Ahab?
Well, if the obsessive
and really intense look fits...
Prometheus has stopped killing randoms.
You'd have to be as crazy
as he is to think he's stopped.
This guy's deliberate.
I mean, he has a very specific plan,
and we need to find him
before he executes the next phase of it.
But for now, we have a new problem,
or should I say another new problem?
Nathan Sierra and Pablo Estevez,
but I prefer douche bags one and two,
just showed up at SCPD.
Doing what?
I don't know. Just hanging around.
Damn.
What is it with this city
and serial killers lately?
Who says it's a new one?
Yeah. Look at the "V" on their faces.
That's not Prometheus' M.O.
Victimology doesn't fit either.
Sierra and Estevez both have rap sheets
for human trafficking.
SCPD thinks that these murders might
be the works of a different vigilante.
How do you already know that?
I have an inside man at SCPD.
You mean your boyfriend,
or whatever he is. Who needs labels?
So either we're dealing with Prometheus
or another multiple murderer.
Either way, he has to be stopped.
Uh... Does he though?
Blondie's got a point.
Two less scumbags on the street.
What's the downside?
The downside is that we already have
one psycho loose in this city.
We can't afford to have another.
Who gets to decide who's a psycho
and who's a vigilante?
Mr. Queen, dobry den.
I thought you might enjoy
a break in my men's questioning.
I trust you'll show the proper manners.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Please eat.
I must confess you've become
something of a fascination with me.
Oliver Queen.
Starling City's favorite son.
Presumed dead
after a maritime accident four years ago.
What do you want from me?
Answers.
You tried to blow up my casino.
Now my sources tell me
you've become Bratva.
I have many enemies,
but you're quite unique.
A week of questioning,
a week of torture,
and you've told my men nothing.
Except the occasional screaming
for a woman, to avenge her.
What was her name?
Taiana. Taiana.
Mmm.
Galina.
Okay.
Lovely lady.
I believe you knew her daughter.
Taiana.
Yes. Yes. She came to me.
Galina came to me a year ago.
She said both her children,
Taiana, Vlad, had disappeared.
I said, "Do not worry.
"I'll get you a job so you can get by
while you wait for them to return."
And she's been here ever since.
- Sorry for the wait.
- No worries.
Gives me time
for this Twitter war I'm having
with an investigative journalist
from Russia.
What can I help you with?
So formal. That's not fun.
Susan, I've got
a million things to do today.
Including dealing with whoever dropped
two bodies on the SCPD's doorstep?
How do you know about that?
I believe it's called
being good at my job.
Susan, the city is still reeling
from the throwing star killings last week.
I'm not looking to rile people up
if that's what you're implying.
I'm not implying anything.
I'm gonna ask you nicely
to please leave this alone
for the time being.
Okay. Fair enough.
Thank you.
- Okay...
- I know being mayor's a hard job, but
you look more in need
of a drink than anyone I've ever met.
You know, are you really surprised?
The police force is filled
with these corrupt officers,
the city has not gotten over
the serial murders last week,
and now there is
another psychotic in town.
Yeah, that does sound like
a whole lot of suck.
It just makes me wonder if what I'm doing
is having any positive effect.
Tonight, McGuire's, 9:00 p.m.
I'm gonna buy you
that drink you so desperately need.
I appreciate that,
but I don't, uh, need a date.
No, but you need a friend,
maybe even more than you need that drink.
See you tonight.
- Hey.
- Um..
Do you have a minute?
Branson's got a new poll
in the field as of last week,
and our approval ratings are up
but not as much as I would like.
Are you okay?
No, not even close.
Did you fall off the wagon?
Well, to do that I'd have to be on it.
You went to a meeting.
I took you there myself.
And I'm sorry.
Ready.
Let's roll.
Go! Go!
- Set.
- Ready...
Go! Go! Go!
Guys, we have incoming!
Guys! Hello!
Star City National Bank
robbery in progress.
We haven't had one of those in a while.
Suit up.
Felicity... Star City... No? Okay.
Tango spotted. Cover me.
- Clear.
Clear.
Overwatch, robbery's over. Suspect down.
We need immediate medical attention.
Vigilante.
Yeah, genius. That's what we are.
Vigilante did this.
These guys
are definitely my favorite crooks,
not that I'm condoning their actions,
just their choice in disguise.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I could totally see Paul and I's
next Halloween costumes.
That's almost a year from now.
Okay, back to things that actually matter.
The spooky crew's
been on a bit of a spree.
Yeah, more than a bit.
They've hit up seven banks in three states
over the past two weeks.
Who's running point?
Eric Dunn. It's not the first time
he's tried these scare tactics.
SCPD collared him in 2011
for multiple armed robberies.
He should be in Iron Heights for another
eight years trading cigarettes.
- So how'd he get out?
- Parole.
Our justice system at work.
Dunn must have formed a new crew.
So Dunn and this new crew hit the bank,
but Vigilante got there before you did.
Yeah, looks like he and his crew booked.
The guy they left in the bank,
however, did not make it.
The bank's CCTV coverage
got a glimpse at our new friend.
Okay, we are fighting a war on two fronts.
At least.
So we're stopping other vigilantes now?
I think what Evelyn's suggesting
is we're on the same side
as this Vigilante fella.
Really?
Because last week, all of you were pissed
when you found out that The Hood
used to play judge, jury, and executioner.
We can't have this both ways.
We're gonna find Dunn,
we're gonna find Vigilante
before any more banks get knocked over
or people get killed.
You don't believe me.
I believe Taiana.
She said you were a monster.
World is a complex place.
Who's to say who is the monster,
and who is the hero?
For example...
How does an American
become this Bratva devil?
KOVAR". Recognize this man?
Never seen him before.
Except in jail
where you snapped his neck
because the Bratva told you to do it,
because they told you
it would help to get to me.
A convenient lie
so they could steal his business.
And you killed this man,
and you gave the IP address
of a black market site
on the dark web to the Bratva.
It's a site the Bratva now controls,
like how they control you.
Good, evil, hero, monster.
My friend, truth is a matter
of perspective.
No more games.
You are gonna get me out of here.
You're late.
You didn't even know I was coming.
I dropped a resignation letter
on your desk.
You didn't think I'd expect you to show up
and try and talk me out of it?
And you can't, by the way.
And what makes you think
that I even want to, huh?
You lied to us, Quentin, repeatedly.
So what are you doing here then?
Look, you“.
You are like family to us, okay?
And I'm worried about you.
Well, I'm not sure I deserve your worry.
Yeah, neither am I, but I...
lam still here, aren't I?
Yeah, but that's not what I mean.
Listen, when I drink like this,
I black out,
I lose time,
and it's been happening a lot lately.
And last week, I woke up,
and I had blood on my hands and...
And this.
Uh, sorry, pal. We're just closing up.
Really? I was hoping
you could help me out.
It's kind of an emergency.
"Emergency"?
I'm going duck hunting tomorrow,
and I'm totally out of ammo.
Friend of mine said
that you might have the kind I need?
5.56-mil armor-piercing hollow points?
Big bullets for ducks.
Anyways, I'm closing up, so if you, uh...
Dude said it was an emergency, yo.
This is a nice shop.
Heard you're the only guy in town
selling 5.56-mil hollow points.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey!
Every week, you get a shipment
of 5.56-mil hollow points.
You sell to one customer!
Hey, we had this handled.
I want a name!
I don't know who he is.
I haven't even seen his face.
He's always got the mask on.
Scary as hell, man.
Worse than you.
Hey, baby. Where you goin'?
My house is the other way.
Huh?
I said you're going the wrong way.
Oh, baby, don't be like that.
What's the matter, baby?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
He's not a ghost.
We have a few questions for you.
What the hell was that?
I thought I was supposed
to be the wild animal.
Wild Dog.
You totally lost it on that guy.
Hey, listen, if I lose it, you'll know it.
Rene's right. You were kind of unhinged,
which isn't your style.
- What's up?
- Nothing, man, forget about it.
Try us. We're empathetic.
Well, one of us.
Today's my son's second birthday.
I missed the party.
It's not because I've been
chasing down vigilantes either.
It's because the US Marshals
have my home under surveillance.
- That sucks.
- Yeah.
Feel stupid even talking about this, man.
It's not like J.J. will ever have
another second birthday,
it's not like I'll ever stop
being a fugitive.
Tell us where to find Dunn.
Please. I don't know
what Eric's been up to.
I lost touch with him when he went inside.
Sorry. My friend and I don't believe you.
How far could you throw him?
Oh, it depends on how many bones
you want broken.
Eric Dunn's out of prison
and robbing banks again.
Give us a line on him,
and we'll go harass him instead of you.
I told you. I haven't seen him in a while.
Three bones. Better yet, make it four.
But I know how he operates.
He picks banks based on
proximity to police stations.
Furthest first and works his way inwards.
It shouldn't take you too long to figure
out which place his crew will hit next.
Please.
Hurry, hurry!
We got a minute or two
before the blues get here.
It's not them I'm worried about.
Hey!
Get down!
You're right to worry.
I'm not here for you.
Then stop trying to kill us!
Dunn.
I'm going after him.
Hey! Keep your guns down.
So then you can just shoot me?
We're on the same side.
You're out of control.
This city is out of control,
and you haven't been able to save it.
Take one more step,
and one of you isn't going home tonight.
If you're not with me,
then you're against me.
Then I'm against you.
Then you're a dead man.
I think we scared him off.
He'll be back.
Kind of reminds me of you,
don't you think?
- Where are we?
- We got two bags of bones in ACU custody.
- And Dunn?
- In the wind.
The recruits are still out
looking for him.
Send them home. It's been a long night.
If we don't find Dunn
before Vigilante does, he's a dead man.
Look, you said that I inspired
this new wave of vigilantes,
but I don't think that's true.
I think that Vigilante
is out there right now
because we haven't been getting
the job done.
It's been four years,
and things have only gotten worse.
Oliver, you saved this city
10 times over.
At least.
And I've been trying
to be a legitimate hero,
which means that I lean on the courts
and the justice system.
The fact that someone like Eric Dunn
is out there right now
should tell us something.
Like what?
Maybe none of it's working.
Twitch and I will open your throat.
Now you tell your men
to put their guns down.
Do it!
All right. Let's go.
Come on. Move!
Go. Go.
I need a vehicle.
Mr. Queen, think about what you are doing.
I know exactly what I am doing.
Keep moving!
And your partner will be very displeased
by this course of action.
Oh, really?
Tell me, does his mom work here, too?
Actually, we've reached an accord.
The Bratva will lay off hostilities
as exchange for a percentage
of my casino's profits.
Your first two lies were more believable.
I told you,
truth is a matter of perspective.
Ask yourself which is more likely,
that the Bratva will let an American
into their brotherhood?
Or that they're using you
for whatever little value you can provide?
Or option three.
You're too weak
to know the difference.
Okay, so tell me what happened again.
We've been over this 100 times already.
Okay, so you must be getting really good
at telling it then.
Okay, the last few weeks,
I've been blacking out.
Last week, I woke up with, uh...
I don't know, all bloody,
and my arm's cut with that.
So I had a friend on the force run
forensics on it,
and it turns out that
that thing is consistent
with the Throwing Star Killer
and his victims.
Okay, so... So, what? You...
You think you're him, you're that guy?
I mean...
I don't know what to think anymore, Thea.
But, no, I don't think even my drinking
could turn me into a psychopath.
So why did you even resign then?
Because I lied to you
about going to the meetings, the drinking.
And now, this psycho, whoever he is,
he's messing with me.
He's targeting me.
I'm damaged goods, Thea.
I shouldn't be anywhere near close to you
or the mayor of our city.
This is a nice mask.
Do you prefer Bonesy,
or can I call you Laura?
Go to hell.
Okay, Laura it is then.
So, Laura,
it actually turns out that
I'm a lot more interested
in Eric Dunn than I am in you,
which makes this your lucky day. So...
Come on.
How about you just tell me where Eric is,
and I'll let you walk out of here.
I said, "Go to hell."
What? Do you need directions or somethin'?
No.
I've been to hell,
and that makes me somebody
that you do not want to screw with.
Try the Papp Motel.
That was impressive.
It got results at least.
I'm gonna reach out to Judge Balderrama,
get a warrant to move on the Papp Motel.
Should take about an hour, maybe two.
Quick as you can. I don't think
this Vigilante waits on warrants.
No, I bet he doesn't.
Do not reach for that gun.
I'm already dead.
The other masked crazy has me marked.
You know what's funny?
The first time I got arrested,
I wasn't even guilty.
They got the wrong guy,
but the D.A., they didn't care.
They had to pin the crime on someone.
I was a good kid.
I spent two years in Iron Heights.
I wasn't a good kid after that.
Door! Now!
When Star City firefighters
responded late tonight,
they found three as yet to be identified
victims dead inside the adjacent...
Anyone still think that Vigilante
doesn't need to be stopped?
To be fair,
the story Dunn laid out is legit.
His conviction in '07 could be the basis
for Making a Murderer Season 2.
Eric Dunn
might not be a choir boy,
but he doesn't deserve a death sentence.
Point made.
The question being,
how do we stop Vigilante?
Better yet, how do we find him?
Well, we have Dunn
in protective custody downstairs.
I guess we can't just leave him
hog-tied on Main Street
and then wait for Ski Goggles to show up.
Let's assume that's not Plan A.
We work the problem.
All right. I have to go see someone.
At this time of night?
Who are you meeting?
'Cause we're all here.
I'm meeting Susan Williams
at a bar for mayor's office stuff.
"Mayor's office"? Sounds like a date.
If you get anything new, please call me.
He's totally going on a date.
Yep.
All right. So we're here. Where's here?
It's a place called New Oasis.
- Rehab?
- You need it, Quentin.
I don't think so, not with everything
that's going on right now.
- It's just not the time.
- This is exactly the right time,
and you know it.
Everything has just been an excuse
keeping you away
from feeling what you need to.
I suppose you're gonna tell me
exactly what that is.
I don't have to.
Laurel.
I know you think that you have dealt
with your grief on this
but all of this drinking
is saying otherwise.
It just hurts, you know? It just hurts
so much. It just hurts so much.
I know. I know. I know.
And the worst thing is knowing
how ashamed she'd be of me right now.
She wouldn't be ashamed of you, Quentin.
She would be concerned, okay?
Just like I am.
You know,
I used to get shot at for a living.
I don't know what it is
about this building
that's got me so scared.
We're afraid of things we don't know,
especially when we've been living
in pain this long.
It's hard to even accept
the idea of being happy.
Yeah.
When'd you become so wise, huh?
I've been through a lot,
in the last four years.
Yeah.
Your mother would be proud of you.
Why don't you go in there
and make Laurel proud of you?
What about being deputy mayor?
It will be waiting for you
right when you get back.
I promise.
Thanks.
For everything.
Thank me by getting better.
That's what you get
for leaving the corner pocket open, pal.
Good game.
- Hi.
- Ah, you are here.
You play pool?
Well, if by "play" you mean "win,"
then yeah.
- One drink as promised.
- Oh.
- Cheers.
Oh.
Okay, the friend part...
Try me.
I'd say that this is off the record,
but I'm pretty sure it's public knowledge.
- Um...
- Okay.
This job...
This job has proven to be a little bit
more difficult than I expected.
What's occasioning
the dark night of the soul?
It's tough to explain.
Let's say, that there
was someone else in my position,
but they were more extreme than I am.
And you don't want to go there.
I don't want to go there.
Okay.
But they've gone there,
which makes me question
if what I'm doing is actually effective.
I'm trying to come at things differently.
I'm trying to be more optimistic, for me.
Nah, but it just feels like...
It's one step forward, two steps back?
That's it.
I think that's what's called
"being in charge."
Look, the truth is,
you're all this city has.
So, however you go about your business,
just keep doing it the right way.
Even if it takes longer
to get the job done,
you'll know, and so will the city.
Will they?
Really.
So, stop being so hard on yourself.
Technically, that is your job.
Damn right.
You work very late hours, Mr. Queen.
You've no idea,
and, Susan, call me Oliver.
Hey. We can't find Vigilante,
but I think we figured out a way
to draw him out.
Talk to me.
How do you feel about us robbing a bank?
God, it's so hot in that mask!
- I'm used to it.
- Security cameras.
- I'm on it.
- Maybe I wasn't paying attention
during the briefing,
but isn't the point to get caught?
Yeah, not by the cops.
That's why I'm only cutting lines to SCPD.
You two take the safe upstairs.
I'll cover Felicity.
Okay, isn't that taking
the method acting a little far?
We have to make this look legit.
I can't wait to explain
that at my arraignment.
Terrific, Artemis, we're on the move.
Anything going on outside?
Negative. All quiet out here.
This was easy.
Maybe we're in the wrong line of work.
You had to say it was easy.
Call your boss.
We need to have a chat.
- Don't listen to him!
- Shut up!
Call him. Do it now.
They don't have to. I'm right here.
Tell your friends to beat it.
This is between us.
Do it, or I'll waste him and then you.
Go. I've got this.
There was a girl outside.
She's still breathing.
She'll wake up with a headache, though.
What do you want?
To operate without interference.
- So you can keep killing people?
- Criminals.
Like the people at the motel?
Collateral damage.
You don't seem to know that this is a war.
Maybe that's why you're losing.
We have to move!
We can't just leave him there
with that nut job!
The guy's got a gun right
to Curtis' head, Blondie.
But there's no way
we can be faster than a bullet.
What is he doing just standing there?
Don't worry. He's got this.
You got a lot of faith, man.
- Green Arrow...
- Shut up!
You're not getting the job done
because you don't take it
seriously enough,
maybe because you haven't lost anyone.
You don't have a full understanding
of what's out there.
Oh, I've lost people,
almost more than I can bear.
Then it hasn't been
more than you can bear.
Maybe you need a push!
You're right.
This is a war,
but I'm gonna fight it the right way
because I am all this city has.
Curtis!
Come on.
In the field, I prefer Mr. Terrific,
if you don't mind.
Where's Ski Goggles?
Gone.
Hey. Heard about the Vigilante.
I'm sorry he got away.
He will be back, and I'll get him.
You always do.
But, uh, I...
- I need to talk to you about Quentin.
- Okay.
He found this in his apartment last week.
Somebody is going
through a lot of trouble
to make it look like
he's behind the throwing star killings.
Why would Quentin believe that?
Because he's been blacking out.
Look, he's in a rehab.
He's just taking some time.
But I've been wondering why would
somebody be targeting him, and...
The only thing I can think of...
What if Prometheus
knows I'm the Green Arrow?
I've killed men for less than this.
So try, or are you gonna turn down
a challenge in front of your men?
Maybe that means
you're too weak to know the difference.
You will not interfere.
What madness is this, huh?
Kovar, we had a deal.
Your man did not believe me.
I was trying to convince him.
If he dies, it's coming out of your cut.
You believe me now, Mr. Queen?
Your precious Bratva
and I have made a deal.
Truth
is a matter of perspective.
Jeez! Do you ever not work out?
I have a few things
to get off my chest, remember?
I do, but I got a better solution.
Little man, look at you! Come here.
Oh.
How are you doing?
- Am I sweaty? What do you say?
- Mmm-hmm.
- You're sweaty.
- I'm what?
You're sweaty.
Yes, I am a little sweaty.
Did you plan this?
You couldn't make it to the party, so...
We could bring the party to you.
What about the US Marshals?
We did three SDRs.
Marshals are halfway to Hub City by now.
Hey, you want some cake?
- Yeah.
- Go get some cake.
- Let's get some cake.
Hey, you. I love you.
Go get some cake, man.
Thanks for doing this, brother.
What are friends for?
Hey, come here. Come here.
Fellas, can you give us a minute, please?
I was just headed out for the night.
I know.
I, uh, may or may not
have had one of the guys
on your detail text me
when you were headed out.
Wow.
Thank you for the other night.
That was, um...
That was some good advice
and a good drink.
Well, now you owe me the drink.
Should we go now?
- Really?
- Let's go.
Don't worry. Nobody followed me.
They don't suspect a thing.