Previously on "Arrow"
and "Flash"...
Brie Larvan,
a quite brilliant
roboticist who once
developed
miniature mechanical bees
for military use.
Barry, I hacked into
the bees' frequency.
I'm controlling them.
Brie's restrained.
Boom!
It's an implantable
biostimulant.
This little piece
of technology's
gonna help me
walk again?
After it's implanted
in your spine, yes.
I found Quentin Lance's
testimony to be
particularly compelling.
On the strength of it,
Mr. Darhk will be held
without bail
or possibility of release.
It is, uh, too hard
to be here with you
every night and not
be with you.
I don't want to
let you go.
But I'm
already gone.
Computer time's up,
Blondie.
Don't think so.
The judge granted me
a minimum
of 30 minutes
per week.
I have 90 more
seconds.
Well, the judge
ain't here. I am.
Let's see what you're
so hot for
without Internet connection.
Bees.
I like bees.
♪ Arrow 4x17 ♪
Beacon of Hope
Original Air Date on March 30, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Thea, your back foot's
sliding out.
No it's not!
Just because
you can't see me
doesn't mean
I'm not there.
You got to sense
my presence
even when I'm not
in your eyeline.
What advice would you
give to me?
Humor me.
You're
getting tired,
you're dropping
your shoulder,
and you're opening
yourself up.
So you took your
morning run
from 6 miles to what?
Maybe two?
Yeah. Well, taking care
of a toddler's
a marathon in itself.
Right, but when you
sacrifice your endurance,
you're losing steam
too early in our sessions.
Let's go again.
Ohh, pass.
I keep on running out
of excuses
for all my new bruises,
and they're from you,
not bad guys.
The streets have gone
quiet since we took
Darhk off the board.
His organization
hasn't been.
HIVE is still
out there.
Yeah, and when they rear their head,
we'll take care of them,
but we have to celebrate
our victories.
If we don't,
we forget what we're
fighting for.
What's wrong?
Alex has a new
job interview
with Ruvé Darhk.
What?
She's looking for a new
chief of staff
before the April 6
election.
Still don't see why
you just can't put yourself
back in the race, Oliver.
You know, voters,
they hate flip-flopping,
and that would be
a pretty big one.
I can't let him work
for the wife
of the Prince
of Darkness.
And what if he got
a better offer?
Are you gonna run
for mayor?
Palmer Tech.
They're hiring
a new head
of public relations.
Oh.
I just heard that
from someone.
Laurel, she's not
Voldemort,
and I'm fine.
That's a good idea.
You should tell Alex
to talk to Felicity.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Nothing. It's just--
it's shocking that you
know who Voldemort is.
Well, I'm not immune
to pop culture.
I read a few of
the "Harry Potter" books.
Really? I was gonna bet
Thea that you just saw the movies.
There were movies?
Mr. Queen,
where are my men?
I don't know, Reiter.
They're your men.
I wasn't gonna wait around
for them to kill me.
And what of
Miss Venediktov?
She's still here.
Don't move!
Where's my idol?
It's not your concern
anymore.
It's nearby.
I can feel it.
The powers they
bestowed
are on the wane,
but--
Enough!
As I was saying,
the magics are
losing their potency,
but I still have
enough to make
short work
of the two of you.
A quarter of a million
dollars per unit.
It's hard to believe
something so small
could cost
so much money.
When Digital Equipment
Corporation released
the first VAX,
it cost $700,000--
Achoo!
So you could think
of this as a bargain.
Except we're not
starting
a computer
revolution here.
We're trying to
repair spinal injuries.
The new estimate
of spinal injuries
per year are
at 12,000 people.
Unless everyone's
a billionaire,
walking again is
a luxury item.
Sounds like something
Mr. Dennis would say.
He already has.
He's called
a board meeting
to discuss how many
zeroes he can add
to the end
of that price point.
Achoo!
Anything I can do
to help you?
No. You can't do
anything with that cold.
Go home, get some rest,
get some chicken noodle soup.
You sound like
my mother.
And I'm sure
if she was here
she'd tell you to listen
to my favorite girl.
Hi, honey!
Fine, but only because
my cold medication
is starting to make
me see double.
- Aw.
- Help--help me. Help.
Did you hear that?
He thinks
we look like twins.
I don't think that's
what he said.
I think he did.
What can I
help you with, Mom?
Well, my beautiful
baby girl,
I am here to
rescue you.
After the...
B-r-e-a-c-k-u-p,
you could use some
regular socialization,
so how about
a leisurely lunch?
Oh, my God. I don't
know what's worse--
the fact that you just
spelled out breakup
or that you
misspelled it.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- No.
- Mom, I'm fine.
I have a lot
of work to do.
No. Just a quick one,
swe--oh.
Sorry. Is this
a bad time?
You people are like
Tribbles today.
What's up?
Everything ok with--
Oliver?
I was gonna say
your night job,
you know, that thing
that you do at night.
Yeah, no.
That--that's fine.
Ollie is--is fine, too.
It's actually
about Alex.
Um, he's no longer working
on the campaign,
so I was--
Oh, my God.
It's Mr. Dennis.
I have a board meeting.
You know what?
He's a jerk.
He can wait.
What'd you want to
ask me about Alex?
Unh! Ha ha! You know, usually,
someone buys me dinner
before we start
breaking out the cuffs.
Ha ha. Heh heh heh.
Heh heh.
I thought you just
lost your magic,
but your charm seems
to be waning, as well.
How the hell
did you get in here?
Heh. I used to be
Ra's Al Ghul.
This I know.
What I'm less clear of
is why my resources haven't been
deployed to get me out of here.
Well, that's what
I'm here to explain.
Although my time in here might be
limitless, Malcolm,
my patience isn't.
That's cute.
As I was saying, I've been in touch
with your resources,
and they don't seem to
have any particular
love left for you,
Damien.
Something to do
with hocus and pocus
and killing
fellow members
when you get miffed.
HIVE is moving forward
with Genesis
but not with you.
They like you here
out of trouble,
but they do wish you
the best of luck
with your trial.
Err!
Heh.
Don't be
embarrassed.
Performance issues
are common
for men of your age.
Wow. You really do have eyes in
the back of your head.
I thought you had
work to do.
I realized
it could wait.
You've been pushing us
pretty hard,
and I know why.
Oliver, it's ok
to miss Felicity.
I--I appreciate
what you're doing,
but I don't think
that you're the--
Person to help you
through it? Why?
Because of what we
used to have?
Yeah.
I thought maybe
it just gave me
a little insight.
Well, I mean,
in fairness,
I did wreck what
we had, too, so...
In your defense,
you were missing
and presumed dead
for 5 years,
but that's not
what I mean.
I know how passionately
you love
and how much it
hurts once that love goes away.
You know, between...
Merlyn, Slade Wilson,
and Ra's Al Ghul,
I thought that I'd be a little tougher
than this by now.
That's a different
type of pain,
and this takes
longer to heal,
but I'm here for you.
Thank you.
You're not late, Phil.
We're still waiting
on Ms. Smoak.
Are you all right?
Phil? Phil?
Phil!
Agh!
I'm calling 911!
I can't get a signal!
Aah!
You'll have to excuse
my tiny friends.
Their "beehavior" can be
appalling sometimes...
But it's
a necessary evil.
You see, I needed
your full attention.
What the hell
do you want?
Straight to the point.
I like that.
Your CEO has miraculously
recovered from paralysis
thanks to an implantable
biostimulant microchip.
Hand one over,
and I'll "bee"
on my way.
There's only
one prototype.
The one
inside Felicity Smoak.
So what's a girl got to do
to get on her calendar?
I can talk to Alex
if you want,
but I can't promise
a job he'll be excited about.
Probably best to
keep him away
from a supervillain's
wife.
Yep. You're right
about that.
Hello out there.
What the hell?
I'm looking
for Felicity Smoak
"beecause" it would be swell
if we could chat
about a certain
implantable biochip.
I'm sure your board
would really appreciate it.
Brie Larvan!
You know this wackadoodle?
I had a run-in
with her last year.
If this Brie Larvan
is coming for you,
we need to get you
out of here.
No, no, no. I don't think she
knew who I was.
She's after
something else.
She said something
about an implant.
A biostimulant
microchip.
There's only one
working prototype.
- Where is it?
- In the base of my spine.
Which brings me back to
we need to get you
the hell out of here.
Well, we have to get
everyone out of here!
I can't even get
a signal.
She's jammed
all communications.
Oh, my God.
Eyewitnesses report
the bees have been swarming
the Palmer Tech headquarters
for the past 10 minutes.
All communication
in and out of the building
has been cut off.
- Have you seen this?
I was just there.
I'd still be there
if Felicity hadn't--
oh, my God.
Felicity.
Gah!
You have a 104 fever.
Where do you think you're going?
To get help!
I'm pretty sure the police already
know about this.
I'm not talking
about the police.
We are hearing that
SCPD has sent in an ESU squad.
Felicity's in there.
Thea, too.
I tried calling but no answer.
She must have already
been inside
by the time
the swarm hit.
John's coming in.
This is HIVE, right?
There's no way that
this bee attack is a coincidence.
I don't think
it's HIVE,
and I don't think
those are bees.
No. Bees don't
give off hundreds
of different kinds
of radio frequencies.
Robot bees. Terrific.
Ok. Last year, Felicity
helped Barry Allen
take the bees' inventor--
Brie Larvan.
So it's payback.
Well, Larvan picked
a hell of a day for it.
Donna is in there, too.
- What?
- She stopped by Felicity's
office to, you know,
cheer her up a little.
Suit up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
The department just
tried sending in an ESU squad.
They couldn't get
through that swarm.
Now if their Kevlar
couldn't hold,
what makes you think
that yours will?
We have to try.
I am running out
of patience, Felicity Smoak.
You have 10 minutes
before I start voting
board members out.
FYI, my drones pack
a lot more "ow"
than your typical sting.
Ticktock, ticktock.
Ok. We need to
get out of here.
But, Thea, the bees
are out there.
Yeah, and sooner or later,
they're gonna be in here.
Ok. From now on,
I'm buying flats.
I mean, these
assaults are weekly.
It's ridiculous.
It's just so
not conducive
to high fashion.
Ok. Definitely
sooner than later.
We're trapped?
Uh, I don't know.
Not exactly.
Ok. Oh, no. I don't
definitely don't have
the right shoes
for that.
Oh, no, no, no.
Hello?
Anybody here?
"Yes, we are here, Curtis,
"and we just can't wait
to hear how you used
"the cell phone
that we gave you
"to help us rescue Dr. Palmer
to track us back
to our"...
"Secret lair"!
So we don't need
to take out the bees.
We just need to
take out Larvan.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't make much
sense if we can't get inside.
Holy frak.
You're the--
and wait--you're--
wait, wait, wait--
you're--you're--
just so you guys know,
if--if I pass out
it's because I'm sick,
not because, you know.
So can anybody
just walk in here?
So you're
the infamous Damien Darhk.
Oh, I get it.
You're big fans, aren't you?
You want me to pose
for a selfie?
Back in Star City,
you were a big deal.
In here, the only big deal
is him.
No, no, no, no,
gentlemen.
I think we're getting
off on the wrong foot.
There must be some sort
of way that we can have--
w-w-wow.
Heh. I'm sorry.
I just got to know
did you sew that
in yourself,
or do you have some kind
of lip-sewing guy?
How did you
deal with her in the first place?
The old-fashioned way--
hacking,
but I can't do that
without a working computer.
Ok. Well, at least all we have
to do is wait for Ollie
and the rest
of them to get here.
Just when I thought
I was out.
I thought I'd left
this all behind.
Hmm.
Do you hear that?
Bee.
Make that plural--
bees in the air vent.
Go! Run!
Is that a bee? Aah!
Aah!
Curtis.
Oh, this is
so weird.
I literally just
had a dream where
you were
the Green Arrow.
Wait. This is
happening?
- You're the Green Arrow?!
- Yeah.
I could have sworn it was Neal Adams
in data processing.
And this is
the Arrowcave.
Oh, my God.
Actually, we call it
the bunk--it's the bunker,
but yeah.
You're Laurel Lance,
the ADA.
I--I've seen you
on TV before.
Oh! And you're
Captain Lance!
And you're--
oh, I'm sorry.
I know I've met before,
but I can't really place
your name right now.
Curtis, that's
John Diggle.
I need you to focus
for a second, please.
Oh, my God.
This place is unbelievable.
I mean, you guys
must be drawing some crazy electricity.
How do you keep it
off the grid?
This is S.T.A.R. Labs'
5000 Exostation.
What are the specs
on this?
Curtis!
Get it together.
Ok. Now I'm starting to see
the whole Green Arrow thing,
and I'm actually
starting to feel better, too.
That's because we
gave you an IV
to rehydrate you.
It should keep you going
for a few hours.
Ok. Forget
the how for a second.
What are you
doing here?
I saw the bee HIVE on the news.
Felicity's in there.
Yeah, we're just about
to mount a rescue mission.
Do you guys even
know what that is?
That is an army
of robotic bees.
Yeah. That's my life now.
Brie Larvan.
Apparently, she hacked
the prison computer
network
and got herself
an early release. Clever.
Feel free to use
that, by the way.
I mean, you can't put me
in front of this beautiful machine
and expect me not to take
it for a test drive.
Looks like Felicity keeps
files on various criminals.
Who's the Dodger?
Looks like we have ourselves a taller,
more dude-like version
of Felicity.
And I can help.
Now look. These bees,
they're tiny computers, ok?
With Felicity
trapped inside,
you guys are gonna need
someone to hack them,
but I'll have to
"bee" careful.
Ha ha ha!
It's too soon
for bee puns, right?
- Let's assume that it is.
- Yeah.
Curtis, can you
immobilize enough bees
to give us a way in?
There's only one way
to find out.
Do it.
You want me on the team?!
I mean,
you want me on the team?
Let's go.
Whoo! Ha ha ha!
You see now
the value
of my prize,
Mr. Queen?
What have you done
to yourself?
There are primordial energies
that flow through all things.
I now command them.
You're insane.
Heh. Madness is
a matter
of perspective,
Mr. Queen.
Your morality blinds you
from understanding
what I
have achieved.
No, I understand.
You're killing people
to gain power.
And what would you
do about it?
Now tell me where
you have hidden my idol,
and I promise
to kill you both quickly.
We'll pass.
Ohh!
Ok. How many
are there?
Just try to think
happy thoughts.
Ok. Now it's time
to hack some bees.
Ok. So that's what
that button does.
Felicity.
Ohh!
Aah! Aah!
Felicity!
Curtis?
How do you know
that bee's name?
I did it!
I hacked the--achoo!
Bees!
How did you--
what are you doing there?
I know, right?
I am still pinching myself. Heh.
All the bees
are gone.
You're welcome.
The Green Arrow is on his way,
as well as Black Canary
and Spartan.
How cool is this?
Uh, they'll meet you
at the west utility entrance.
Can you get there?
Did I mention how cool this is?
Curtis, have you
deactivated the bees?
Negative.
Uh, I mean, positive.
Sorry. I'm nervous.
The bees are down.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's negative.
Negative!
The bees are back!
I--I got kicked out!
Duck! Agh!
Ugh.
Ok, ok, come on.
Go back inside.
Back inside.
What
the hell happened?
We couldn't see.
I lost the feed.
He got stung.
Yeah. He's having
some sort of reaction.
He didn't just get stung.
The bee's inside you.
Well, cut it out!
Do you guys have anesthesia
around here or something?
- Curtis, just do it!
- I can't find it.
Ok. Actually--and this
is hard to believe--
we have a bigger problem.
The bee is replicating
itself inside Oliver.
Ok.
What did that thing
do to the Green Arrow?
Stung him badly.
He'll be ok,
and he'll be back.
So will the others.
How do you know?
They just got
their butts kicked
by that--that--
that bee man.
This is why we leave
the nicknames to Cisco.
- Yeah.
- What?
Inside joke.
I thought we were
friends, Smoak,
that you were gonna
come through.
10 minutes ago,
you had 10 minutes to go.
You're out of time,
glasses.
"Beecause" we got
interrupted,
I'm gonna give you
an additional 5 minutes
before I start taking your board
members off the board.
Ohh.
Oh, and your fiance
looks awfully sweet.
Sorry. Ex-fiance.
Ugh!
Ok. You cannot
turn yourself in.
No. She'd kill
everyone anyway.
To think,
she's in your office.
You're gonna have to
sanitize.
Yes. She's in my office,
which is, "A," yes, gross,
but, "B," means she's not
with the board members.
You know, since she brought up Oliver,
honey, have you spoken to him--
Mom. Mom, Mom, Mom,
I'm thinking!
I'm sorry. You know
what, honey?
I'm curious, ok? I--
I have an idea.
It's not working!
You did it while we
were at Palmer Tech.
The drone has evolved
and adapted since then.
The damn things are
like the Borg.
The--the bad guys
in "Star Trek," which--
I wish Felicity
was here.
Well, she's not Curtis!
You are!
Now you have to be able
to do something, ok?
When these things hit
critical mass, there's--
it's gonna be like
John Hurt in "Alien"!
Sorry. When I get nervous,
I make pop culture references.
Ok. You can't
hack it out.
Can you lure it out
like some kind of--
I can't believe
I'm saying this--
some kind of digital
honey or something?
Not exactly, but if these are
really modeled after bees, then...
They'll operate  on a singular frequency
to orientate themselves.
If we can disrupt it,
then we can disperse the colony.
Only problem is that we need to generate
a high enough frequency
to damage the network,
but unless you guys have
a portable sonic projector
handy, then--
What?
This technology's
amazing.
It reads your own
vocal emissions
and then reprocesses it
via digital output into a multichannel.
Yeah, we get it.
It's badass,
but how is this
gonna help us save Oliver?
Just give him
the full Mariah Carey,
and it should disrupt
whatever connection
the bees are
operating on.
You sure
about this?
Err. Don't have time
to be sure.
Curtis, do it!
3, 2, 1.
That...Was...Awesome.
You son of a bitch!
My victory's inevitable,
Mr. Queen.
Just think.
All of this power came
from the life essence
of one man.
Imagine
what I will become
when dozens of lives
are sacrificed in my name.
You'll become
a monster.
No. A God.
Let me show you.
Unh!
No. I need more.
You get them?
Yeah. They were
in Curtis' office
right where you said
they'd be.
Uh, no pun intended.
Whoa! So this is
like that thing
from that, uh--
that Jodie Foster
movie!
Yeah. A panic room.
It's actually more
like a lair, decommissioned,
but if we can get
the board members in there,
then they can escape
through a secret exit.
Secret exit?
Um, don't you think
you should have thought of that,
like, I don't know,
15 minutes ago.
Oh, I'm sorry. I was busy trying
not to die,
and you were
talking, talking, talking.
Well, you don't open
up to me, Hon.
I have to force your feelings out
of you sometimes
like--like
a pistachio.
Ok, Smoaks.
We got to go. Come on.
Felicity.
Mom!
I meant Felicity!
Aah!
- Ohh.
- Ok. We're moving.
I know. Hold
on to something.
- What? Why?
- Why?
This elevator only stops
at the sublevel,
and we need it to
stop at the--
Aah!
Conference room
floor.
Um, I think we
missed our stop.
Nope. This is right.
Like I said, the elevator doesn't
stop at this level.
What? Um, honey,
I think this is a concrete wall.
Yeah, and these are
explosive devices.
Actually, they're autonomous
communication devices.
I'm just really hoping that Curtis
hasn't figured out
how to stop them
from exploding yet.
- Oh.
- Careful.
Ok.
Oh, my God!
Is it gonna be loud?
Oh! Aah!
Ok. Who wants
to go on a secret elevator ride
down to the, um,
panic room?
Yeah.
The panic room.
Trying to escape
the HIVE?
Keep them safe.
What? What?!
Beautiful creatures
my bees.
They obey you.
Neural implants.
You used to control them the
old-fashioned way.
How did you know that?
Lucky guess, I guess.
So why bees?
Why not an obsession with
flying squirrels?
Squirrels aren't dying off
at a rate of 30% per year,
and nobody cares,
but bees are essential
to life.
We're all connected.
The world is one
giant honeycomb.
That "Kumbaya" might
have a little more credibility
if you weren't
threatening people's lives.
What, you mean
like this?
I am running out
of patience,
and your friend is running
out of time.
Now give me the damn--
That was embarrassing.
I have a tumor
on my L4 vertebrae.
The tricky little guy's
wrapped around my spinal cord.
The only way to cut it
out involves a surgery
that will leave me
paralyzed
from the waist down.
All the bees in the world couldn't
get a cripple to walk,
and then I read
about your miracle chip.
Of course, I couldn't
afford it.
Maybe if you
asked nicely.
I want the microchip
specs,
or your friend relives
my favorite scene from "My Girl."
Ok, honey.
We all have a sad sob story,
but killing people
doesn't fix anything.
The blueprints are on a remote
hard drive in Curtis Holt's lab.
You are a smart girl.
Elastic nanotubes,
ultrasonic motors,
piezoceramic elements.
I mean, this bee's
got everything.
That was inside me?
Well, that and thousands
of its microscopic larvae.
Don't worry. Should pass
in a few days.
Can't wait.
Donna and the others
made it out.
Thea and Felicity?
They're still
inside.
Well, at least now
we know this stops the bees.
I wish it was that simple,
but now that we've
played that card,
they've undoubtedly
adapted to it,
but we just beat a group
of robot bees
using a superhero
doohickey,
and if that's
not high-five-worthy,
I don't know what is.
Curtis, now is not
the time for high-fives.
Sorry. I--you know,
I just got excited,
and, you know, you got to celebrate
the wins when they come.
What?
Thea and Felicity
are still trapped
inside Palmer Tech with who knows
how many more bees.
- We're not winning.
- Oliver.
So if you're gonna
be down here,
if you're gonna be
with us,
then you need to
understand the totality
of what it is you're
signing up for.
If we do not do
our jobs perfectly,
then people die
and not just
strangers
but friends, family,
and loved ones,
so think about that
every time you crack a joke
or make light
of what it is that we do!
Hey.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Any puppies you want to
kick while you're at it,
bags of kittens that
you want to throw down the river?
He needed
to hear that.
Nobody needs to
hear that, Oliver.
I know you're hurting,
but you can't take it out on Curtis.
I'm not taking it
out on Curtis.
I just need him
to see.
See what?
That this is not
a good life.
I walked away
from it,
and I was happy.
For the first time
in 8 years,
I was content.
So why did you
come back?
I came back because
of Felicity.
She convinced me
that we could do this job,
that we could save
this city and not
surrender
to the darkness,
but...
I don't--I don't
think that we can.
You're only saying
that right now
because you're
in 10 different kinds of pain,
but the harsh truth
is that Felicity--
she broke up with you
because of your choices,
because lies that
you told,
you--Oliver,
not the Green Arrow.
I know.
It just doesn't
seem fair
that I can save
a city
and not save
my relationship.
Oliver,
life's not fair,
whether you're
in Star City or Ivy Town,
but you're right.
You can save this city,
you do it every night.
You're a beacon
of hope to people.
I just wish that you
would try and use
some of that hope
for yourself.
Oh, hi, fellas.
You know, I usually
frown upon walk-ins,
but how can I
help you?
No guards are coming to
save you this time, Darhk.
We made sure of it.
Good because then
he only has to kill two of you.
Heh heh heh.
I know you're
probably asking yourself,
"self, what the hell
just happened?"
It turns out your friend,
my new friend,
Mr. Amar has
a soft spot
for his only
surviving relative,
a grandmother
in Monument Point.
It is amazing what
people will tell you
with a few phone calls
and a kind voice.
Anyway--are they dead?
Are they dead?
No! I had this
wonderful speech
about how I was gonna
kill your grandmother
had you not killed them.
Never mind.
On to other matters.
You may now call
your organization
and have that other
message delivered.
Heh heh heh.
I thought we were
locked out.
Well, we're gonna have
to see if I haven't lost my touch.
Then I have to see
if my mom
and the board members
made it to safety.
You really should not
have given Brie what she wanted.
I am sick of people being put in
vulnerable positions.
Yeah. Well, now there's
nothing stopping her
from bringing those
bee things back on us.
Well, at the very least, it buys us--
the team-- your team time.
Ollie's gonna be fine.
He always is.
Well, unfortunately,
in Oliver's case,
"he always is" isn't an accurate
predictive metric.
Sorry. I'm just sick
of worrying,
I'm sick
of the violence.
Yeah. So am I, ok?
Of course I am,
but we put up
with it.
We push past it
because what we do
is important, ok?
We have to be
the beacon of hope.
Nobody else is.
You're the beacon
of hope.
I quit the team because
I couldn't stand to work with Oliver,
but--but now that
I'm out,
I look at life from a different
perspective.
I mean, look around you.
Thea, we're in a "Die Hard"
movie with bees.
Maybe I'm meant for great things,
maybe I'm not,
but whatever it is,
it's not this.
I'm sorry.
I'm not coming back.
Curtis.
You know,
I'm beginning to see
why you and Felicity
didn't work out.
I probably deserve that.
Look. I'm all for hugs
and learning,
but like you said,
there's still danger.
Yeah.
And you are
a very scary man.
Any luck
with the bees?
Curtis is doing
his best.
Thanks, Laurel.
Now that I've been able
to actually
examine the bee,
I've deciphered
their upgrade protocol.
Next time they adapt,
I can upload a virus
that will disperse
into the entire HIVE.
Like what they did
in "Independence Day," right?
What, I can't watch
movies, too?
So what's the plan?
I rigged an arrow
with a computer virus payload.
Shoot it near one
of "bee" Arthur's minions,
the virus will transmit
to the rest of the colony,
and we're done.
That's nice work.
Uh...
Wait until it works
before you congratulate me.
I'm in!
I mean, I'm out.
I mean, I have
Internet.
Mom and the board members,
they're ok.
What about us?
I'm working on
overriding the bees,
the ones that are
outside guarding the building.
Don't bother.
These blueprints
will be useful.
Thanks for those.
You have what you want,
so go build it yourself.
I think we're confused.
To get the schematics,
I had to tip-toe
through Palmer Tech's
computer network,
and I saw some
very familiar computer code.
You never forget the hacker
who sent you to prison.
Hi.
We're clear.
At least there's no
signs of the bees.
Go!
Looks like your green friend didn't
forget about you.
Never will.
Hey. Are you hurt?
I'm ok.
Hey! Behind you!
There you go.
Team Arrow, which I am now
a member of--pinch me--
I need a few more minutes
to hack this latest firewall.
The bees adapted.
I thought you were
a better shot.
Hey!
All right. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
- Gotcha!
- Nice!
What is that?
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Oh, oh, oh!
Yah! Yah!
Eww!
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone you screamed.
Oh, right!
Thank you.
You never, never
have to thank me.
Agh!
If I can't walk,
you can't live.
Who should I kill first,
"A" or "Bee"?
Guess who's back in control.
It's me Curtis in case you guys
don't recognize my voice yet.
Uh. Unh! No, no!
Ha ha!
Lay down, "Bee-yotch"!
Heh heh.
Too on the nose?
Oh. Ah. The bee
came alive,
and, well, things
got a little out of hand,
but don't worry--
it's dead now.
You did good, Curtis,
and I'm--I'm sorry if I
made you feel differently.
Thanks, G.A. Heh.
Do you mind if I call you G.A.?
All right. Yeah.
I'll just stick to Oliver then.
Or Mr. Queen.
What about Larvan?
What's gonna happen to her?
She's
at Starling General,
overdosed on toxins
from the bee
and is in some sort
of a coma.
More importantly,
she's no longer holding
a dozen innocent
hostages.
That's both comforting
and horrifying at the same time.
Yeah. Welcome
to our world.
Hey. Is everything
all right?
Yeah. You know, I should probably
just head home.
You know, learning
that you're, you know, you
and the murderous bees
and this coma news,
it's just a lot
to digest,
plus that IV you gave me
is starting to wear off.
Well, you are always
welcome here, Curtis.
Just keep
the property damage
to a minimum next time.
Ok.
All right.
- What's the exit?
- Right there.
Oh, yeah. Ahem.
Hey. Nice apology.
Well, I'm just trying
to be a beacon of hope
and, like you said,
save a little bit
of the hope
for myself.
Taiana. Hey! Hey!
All right. All right.
Jeez. Come on, come on.
Oh, thank God.
Taiana, wake up.
- Hey.
- Oliver.
It's ok. You're ok.
- No.
- It's all right.
Reiter--he's gone!
He must be in the tunnels
searching for his idol.
We can't let him find it.
If he's in the tunnels
searching for his idol,
that means he's not
going to the prison.
This is our chance
to save your friends.
And what
of Reiter's men?
They're still up there.
That's why we're gonna
kill all of them first.
I don't suppose it's
too late to reheat that soup.
Where have you been?
You bolted out of here
like a crazy person,
like some kind of a superhero off
to save the day.
I was chasing some
silly fantasy that
I could help
the police.
It was scary and thrilling
and dangerous
and did I mention
scary?
The point is is that
I saw enough
to know that this
is where I belong--
at home with you.
So no more
disappearing acts?
I promise.
Let's get you some
of that soup.
Terrific.
Ahh. Maybe I should
burn some incense
in here or something.
Yeah. That's
probably
a very good idea.
Remind me to never
wear black and yellow ever again.
Wait. Where'd
your mom go?
Oh! Captain Lance
drove her home.
Yeah. That is something I'll never
be able to wrap my brain around.
Eh, it's kind of cute.
Don't you miss this?
I mean, I know you
said that you wanted
to get away
from it all,
but how could you?
What do you mean?
This. The--
the thrill of this, the rush.
I mean, we just took down a bad
"Bee-yotch" tonight.
It doesn't get any
better than this.
I was never in it
for that, not ever.
I wanted to
make a difference,
be a part of that
beacon of hope you speak of.
So come back.
Rejoin the team.
I think I figured out
another way.
It was actually that
insane bee lady
who gave me the idea,
ironically...
To remake this company
to use the technology
that helped me walk again
to make people's
lives better,
to make Palmer Tech
into the beacon of hope.
Our mutual friends
in HIVE have abandoned
our other mutual friend
Mr. Darhk,
but he reached out
to me,
told me about you.
He said you were
his ace in the hole.
Heh heh. Is that what
you'd like me to call you,
or do you prefer
Mr. Diggle?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.