My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
What are you doing in Russia?
I'm here to kill Konstantin Kovar.
Only people who have power
to get past his army are Bratva.
We lost one. It's in the air.
You need to divert that missile.
That's it.
Tobias Church, he and his crew
tore up Hub City and Blüdhaven.
Anybody else want to be in charge?
Church just became our top priority.
Felicity thinks that it's time
we put together a new team.
Evelyn Sharp. Basically,
a 16-year-old badass in the making.
Until her parents
met Damien Darhk I'm guessing.
You recruit me too.
You wanna help?
It's my city too.
I don't want to
see you out here again.
You again?
How's the leg?
You call yourself a vigilante?
You just let the Halcones' top seller
get away.
Now I thought I said that I didn't
want to see you out here again.
You don't listen very well.
You sound like my ex.
Rene Ramirez, you need to decide
if you want to be a man in a hockey mask
or if you want to be someone else.
Something else.
Conahan was struck
with an arrow and a sword.
Literally overkill.
Definitely not Church's M. O.
Totally different than
the Bertinelli murder too.
Ballistics show
that he was shot by his own men.
Well, that had to be Church.
In Hub City,
he killed every crime boss in town
so he could unite everyone
under one super-gang under his control.
How does he do this?
It's all in the core.
So, Curtis,
I'm guessing this wasn't
part of your Olympic training?
Impossible.
It's really hot. I mean, not. It's not.
Curtis, if you think this is hard
wait until I actually start training you.
What happens then?
The last guy got an arrow
in the leg before it even started.
That was Roy, right?
Also Roy, but I'm talking about Wild Dog.
And you did put two arrows
in Barry Allen's back.
I'm starting to sense a pattern.
Don't worry.
His bark's way worse than his bite.
And you're gonna get it worse than anyone.
Uh... Thanks?
The people that we're looking at have
at least some experience on the street.
You have the farthest way to go before
I'm convinced that you can do this.
I can do it, sir.
- Don't call me sir.
- Okay, Oliver.
Don't call me Oliver especially
in front of the recruits.
We don't know these people
and they can't know us.
Whoa, whoa! Hold up.
You're going to be wearing a mask
when you training our recruits?
Yeah. And so are you.
I only wear a mask once a year
and that's if my Halloween costume
calls for it.
This is not negotiable, Felicity.
I'm late for a budget meeting.
Yeah.
And I'm sure that kicking things off
by lying to everyone is an awesome idea.
Well, the original team started off
with Oliver lying about his identity.
And everyone who's not dead or
presumed dead, quit.
Yeah.
Now this trigger was taken from one of the
nukes that fell on Genesis Day.
Our intel tells us that a group of
Chechen rebels is close to obtaining it.
I don't have to tell you what
kind of a nightmare scenario will ensue
if that happens.
Now the mission
is standard retrieval and extraction.
Sergeant Diggle here, will be running
the op, wheels up at 0400.
All right, gentlemen, get some rest.
You're gonna need it. Dismissed!
You good, soldier?
I got through basic training, no sweat.
But this is my first day in the soup
and I don't want to be scared,
but I am a little.
Fear is part of war.
The part that keeps us alive.
See these stripes?
They give me strength, clarity.
Right or wrong, up and down,
they tell me what to do.
Which means that fear can kiss my six.
You understand, soldier?
- Yes, sir.
- Good. Dismissed.
It used to be that the Glades
were the worst part of the city,
but now it seems like
every other part is just as bad.
We've had three hospital closures
in the past eighteen months.
But with a Free Medical Clinic
event like this
we can start to walk back
some of that damage.
In a day, we can provide
medical care for up to a thousand people.
Plus, we already have about 30 doctors
and nurses just waiting to volunteer.
We're looking for a company
to cover logistical expenses and...
I don't need to hear any more.
AmerTek is in.
And not just for logistical expenses,
for the whole thing.
Well, that's amazing.
That's, that's incredibly generous,
thank you.
Please, you would be doing us the favor.
And by "us" she means our stock price.
Good PR is worth, literally,
its weight in gold.
Uh, well, we will make sure
this clinic is a success
and that everyone knows
they have AmerTek to thank for it.
Wow.
Thought I'd almost feel bad
about boosting their stock prices
if it wasn't so good
for your approval ratings.
But actually you should really handle
the press on this one.
Maybe you can?
Oh, God, Ollie, I really thought
that we talked about this.
I can't keep doing everything on my own!
I have faith that you can, but
either way now is not a very good time.
And why is that?
- I'm recruiting a new team.
- Oh.
You okay with that?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be? I quit.
I know, but there's a difference
between leaving and being replaced.
Oh.
It's really cute you think
I can be replaced.
That's not what I meant.
I know. But I actually think
it'll be really good for you
to not be out there solo anymore.
Plus, it would mean you would have
more time to actually be here.
That's the idea. But it's going to take
a minute to get these kids up to speed.
Wait, maybe I should hire my own team
for the office then.
That's also a good idea.
Start looking at résumés.
Hey, Quentin.
Have you actually heard about
this free medical event
Ollie and I are putting together?
- Rene Ramirez?
- Yeah.
Figures there'd be more of you.
Robin Hood needs his band of Merry Men,
right?
Well, I am just here for moral support.
She means she's here to make sure
that the Green Arrow's training technique
doesn't kill us.
He's not going to kill you.
I'm just here to make sure that the
horrible maiming stays a minimum.
I'm Curtis.
Evelyn Sharp.
So wait, there's training? I'm out.
Pretty early to quit, Mr. Ramirez.
I can't quit something I haven't started.
You think you can do this on your own?
I've been doing this on my own
for five months now.
And if you were getting it done
on your own, you wouldn't have come here.
I'm out of here.
- No mask?
- No chance.
On the line.
Wait. I thought there was gonna be,
I dunno, like an orientation?
Is that what the brochure promised?
- That's hilarious. He's good...
- On the line!
This is simple.
Get past me
and ring that bell.
So, we're playing games now?
Fine. I'll play.
On the line.
At least he's not shooting them.
This is stupid.
Still think it's a game?
I came here to work with the guy
who killed Damien Darhk
not ring a friggin' bell.
This isn't a game.
And if you need further evidence of that
then you walk down to the pier
and you look at the statue
of Laurel Lance.
Now, get on the line!
I'd love to, but I can't tonight.
Too much to do for this medical event.
Yeah, it's great, Janet agreed to it.
All right, see you Saturday?
Here you go, bud.
How's the victim?
Victim is Evan Wender. He's in the ICU.
Doctors think that
he was suffocated by something.
Is that lining up
with anything you've found?
You're assuming
I've actually found anything.
What's your interest in this, anyway?
AmerTek is helping us with a charity event
and all of a sudden one of their
Vice Presidents is attacked.
It cannot be a coincidence.
Not in this city.
- I have to go.
- Bye.
Thanks.
We're very sorry
about what happened to Mr. Wender.
But I would like you to know that I've
assigned the Anti-Crime Unit to his case
and I've asked them to make catching
whoever did this their top priority.
Well, I appreciate that.
But in the wake of this recent development
my board of directors, to say nothing
of AmerTek's army of attorneys
have advised us to
pull out of tomorrow's event.
They're concerned that
the attack on Mr. Wender
could be the start of a larger
pattern of violence.
And if something were to happen during the
Clinic, then AmerTek would be held liable.
What if Star City
agrees to indemnify AmerTek?
Ollie, that could cost millions.
And I will triple
the police presence at the event.
There will be plenty of security?
I will see to it personally.
Well.
I'm going to hold you to that, Mr. Mayor.
Thank you.
So is the plan,
to see to it personally with a new team?
No. They're nowhere near ready.
Then what's the back-up plan?
Me. It's one of the advantages
of having the mayor
moonlighting as a vigilante.
Or the vigilante moonlighting as mayor.
No hostiles, sir. We're a go.
Excellent. Intel was good.
Hostiles are on a shift change.
Bravo Team, you're upstairs,
northwest corridor, second floor.
Alpha Team with me, look sharp.
Alpha Team is here.
Bravo Team, where are you, what's your...
Come on! Move! Move! Move!
How the hell did they know we were here?
On the line.
Here to learn something, man.
Not just get beat up.
I told you, I'm teaching you.
Teaching us what exactly?
Because I actually find myself
agreeing with the scary, weird guy.
The goal of this exercise
is to figure out
the goal of this exercise.
Now, get on the line.
Actually, Green Arrow?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Now?
You know, I thought maybe we could hold
off on the criticism for a little bit.
Oh, yeah, no problem 'cause there's a lot.
Look.
I thought there wasn't any usable footage
from traffic cameras.
Yeah, but who needs traffic cams when you
got KH-ten spy satellites?
Could be a meta.
Or magic of some sort.
Exactly. So Thea may or may not have told
me about your brilliant plan
to protect the Free Clinic
all by yourself.
I won't be all by myself.
I'll have the SCPD and the ACU.
No way!
This is out of both of their leagues.
What?
It's out of their league too.
They're too green.
Some could say the same about you.
I've been waiting five years
to make that joke.
The convention center
has twenty entrances.
You can't be on them all.
Throw them around the perimeter for three
extra pairs of eyes. What could it hurt?
Okay, heads on swivels.
But do not engage under any circumstances.
- Copy that.
- Yes, sir. I mean, I mean, Green Arrow.
Wild Dog, do you copy that?
- We gotta talk about this code name.
- Not now. Stay focused.
You know, it'd help to know where you are.
No, it wouldn't because
you are not going to engage.
Come on, where's the fun in that?
Man,
it would take one major asshat
to make a move against all these people.
Something I learned recently
is this city is filled with them.
It starts at the top, you know?
Pretty Boy Queen here thinks
he's actually saving the city.
Thank you, Officer. Hey.
How are you? Hello.
- Hi.
What have we here?
Oh. Her broken bone never set.
Oh. You'll be fine.
I have some experience with that.
Evelyn, check the northwest corridor.
I don't get a code name?
We really thank you for sticking with us.
Oh. Well, I'm glad
that Oliver changed my mind.
It's nice to feel that this company
can still do some good.
Um, sorry I'm late.
If you'll excuse me.
The event is almost over.
Yeah, I know.
It's been that kind of traffic, you know?
Yeah, but you were supposed to watch
the Tenth Street entrance.
But I just said, this traffic,
it's terrible!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, you know?
Sorry, it won't happen again.
Yeah, but...
You haven't been drinking again, have you?
Janet Carroll.
You have been judged and found wanting.
He's here.
Son of a bitch!
GREEN ARROW; Overwatch?
I don't see him on any of the security
cameras. It's like he just disappeared.
I wouldn't believe it if I didn't see him
do all that other stuff
that I don't believe.
I'm almost afraid to ask... Actually,
I am afraid to ask.
You know, maybe I'm just afraid.
Is he coming?
He's on his way.
Did he sound unhappy?
Why did you do that anyway?
He specifically told us not to engage.
First, he's not the boss of me
and never will be.
Second, if he thinks I'm just gonna stand
back and watch some little girl get hurt
then he never should've
recruited me in the first place.
I think that's quickly becoming
the majority opinion.
Third, if I hadn't done what I did,
I wouldn't have gotten this.
Wait. Is that a piece of...
Yeah. Ragman.
Now, I may be new at this and all
but isn't that
what you guys call "evidence"?
On the line!
Listen, before you say anything,
I think you...
My instructions were specific.
By not listening,
you put every one of our lives at risk.
You need to calm down.
Now, I know
that none of you are ready for this.
But now I'm not sure
if you're ever going to be.
Because you are reckless. You're useless
if you're not behind a computer
and you are just a little girl
who should be doing something better
with her life.
Okay, that's enough pep talk for one day.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Did you learn nothing from what happened
with Curtis last year?
You know I don't have a bedside manner...
There's having no bedside manner
and then there is being
physically and emotionally abusive.
It took me five years in hell to turn into
someone capable of going out there.
You know who didn't have five years?
Laurel Lance.
And now she's dead.
Well, were those five years just full of
pain and suffering
or did you have someone who taught you?
I had a few people who taught me
and I'm trying to teach them.
What? To take a punch? An insult?
You keep expecting them to do
what you're telling them to do.
And then you're not giving them
any reason.
You just keep jabbing them with
a cattle-prod expecting them to perform.
And the guy that you called reckless
got us our only clue we have so far.
We need to do a full work-up on that.
Yeah, well, I can't, I mean, not here.
The Ghosts
destroyed our Gas chromatograph.
But, uh, I have other methods.
Good. I have to get to City Hall.
What about them?
The city just experienced the equivalent
of a terrorist attack.
Those three can wait.
You should get to the medic tent
when we get back,
but this should hold you for a few hours.
A few hours, why? We're not bugging out?
Our orders are to get that trigger,
that's exactly what we're going to do.
All the men are on the second floor,
we have no idea how
many guys are up there.
Do you remember
what I told you about fear?
- Gets you through.
- That's right.
And so does the chain of command.
We don't have to think about do or don't,
right or wrong.
There's a clarity in that, right?
A peace.
Do you understand?
Fall out.
Secure the south hallways.
I'll take the north.
Contacts will be here any minute.
So let's keep our heads
on swivels, ladies.
Thought you guys were either dead or gone.
Collins took a through-and-through.
He'll fine but...
What the hell is going on here?
Really sorry about this, Sergeant.
You're not here to secure the trigger.
You're stealing it.
Can't steal anything if nobody owns it.
Now, you be careful now, Sergeant.
You just might live through this.
Not that I would normally condone
drinking this much caffeine
but since you are so busy
trying to save the entire city and all...
Add it to the list of vices
I've been meaning to swear off.
Oh! Do I even want to know?
Just as much as I want to know
why you're really here.
You already bought me an Americano
this morning before I got to work.
Ah! And that's why you are the detective.
It's been a while since I dated anyone.
Is this a thing now?
No, this is not a thing. This is
a very long, funny story.
Do you want to tell me this story?
Yeah, it's why I'm here. Um...
This belonged to my friend's maid.
Cleaning lady.
Your friend's cleaning lady?
She's gone missing.
And he's very worried about her.
You want me to make a report to
Missing Persons?
No, no, no! I was thinking that...
Well, she left this rag behind.
So I was thinking there might be some
evidence left behind on it that, um,
could help my friend locate
her cleaning lady.
I thought your friend was a guy.
Are you jealous?
Only insofar as I haven't actually met
any of your friends yet.
Mmm.
And yes, that's a hint
officially being dropped.
Hint noted.
Okay.
So just a quick forensic work-up?
Like, maybe just a quick pass
through the gas chromatograph?
Fine. It's your tax dollars.
You are the best.
Thea, may I speak with...
- Hi.
- Oh, I was just leaving.
Is everything okay?
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
I was just talking to Thea
about maybe coming aboard,
- helping out with some stuff and...
- Yeah.
Yeah, anyway.
So anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Uh, thanks.
- What was that about?
- It's nothing.
Look, we have way bigger problems
on our plate right now.
Because of you we are on the hook
with AmerTek
and the CEO is in the hospital.
Actually, she was just released,
she's fine.
Okay, but she's gonna hit the city
with a multi-million dollar lawsuit.
Well, can you speak to her?
My hands are kind of full right now.
Okay. What else is new?
What is going on with Quentin?
I am 90% sure
he's drinking again.
And I'm 100% sure.
He told me when I saw him last week.
Ollie, I put him to work security
at the event...
The dude in rags came in through the door
he was supposed to be working.
Thea, I'm sorry.
I had no idea
that you were gonna reach out to him.
But why is he talking
like he's going to be working with us?
"I'll see you tomorrow"? What, is that?
He's hurting, Ollie.
But I don't think that putting him
in a position of responsibility
is the best idea for him,
or for us right now. Okay?
I'll talk 110 him.
I have to go. Thank you.
What's going on? Where are the others?
Somewhere not here.
They quit.
This really shouldn't come
as any sort of surprise to you.
It's not surprising.
We chose the wrong people.
- Including me, right?
- Curtis,
do you know what the purpose
of this exercise is?
To figure out the purpose
of this exercise?
No. It's to work together
because that's the only way that you win.
That is what I've been trying
to teach all of you.
Well, maybe there's a reason
why you couldn't.
- We don't trust you.
- That's on you.
No, man, that's on you.
Because you don't trust us.
Because you don't want us.
Okay, this is a setback.
But we can salvage this. Like...
They'll listen to you.
Can you just tell them how Oliver usually
approaches things and...
I tried that.
I told them all about how you
and Speedy and Spartan were a family.
And even though you were tough
and scary and even a little abusive,
they clearly trusted you
because they stood by you.
But then it hit me.
No, they didn't.
They left.
And now I know why.
You don't respect people.
You don't know how to have partners.
You don't build people up.
You tear them down.
I thought I could trust you,
we could trust you,
but I was wrong.
And that's why I'm out too.
Figured I'd find you here.
You were right.
Oh. As much as I usually love
hearing those three little words,
gloating right now
would be like kicking a puppy.
I failed these recruits as a leader.
Well, that's 'cause you're not a leader.
Well, in your defense,
you never set out to be.
You never planned
on doing this with partners.
Though, I don't think
you really ever had a way
- around that one.
- How so?
When I got to know you, the real you...
I was in awe.
I had never met somebody so passionate,
so focused and determined
to make a real difference.
But the recruits
didn't get to see the real you
because all you showed them
was this angry guy in a mask.
Like scary angry-
I just thought that if they didn't know
who I was it would make things easier.
How would that make things
easier for them?
For me. Easier for me.
- When I was in the Bratva...
- Mmm.
You never talk about your time in Russia.
Nobody in the Bratva
uses their real names.
Nobody knows anything about anyone's life
before they were Bratva.
- Sounds lonely.
- It's effective.
They teach you that the only person
you can trust is yourself.
That without personal attachment,
there can be no loss.
Laurel,
Thea, Digg, even Roy.
I let them into my crusade,
I let them in...
And they left.
I was protecting myself.
I just think you're missing something.
Only one thing?
The reason the original team
worked so well,
was because of the trust and respect
that everyone had for Oliver Queen,
not the Green Arrow.
Oliver is the one who makes a good leader.
He's the one that runs a good team.
He's the one that I chose to stand by
and that I continue to choose to stand by.
I got to take this.
Hey, hey. If we can move them
to the left, we may have a chance.
We need to divert their attention
and then one of us sneaks past
and we ring the bell.
Congratulations, Oliver.
Well, it looks
like we have our work cut for us
getting AmerTek back in our good graces.
Couldn't even get past the reception desk.
So we need
to get this handled with... But...
Just call me back whenever you get this.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It couldn't be helped.
Help it next time.
I don't like waiting.
Are we all set for tonight?
We are if you have the money.
$100 million.
For everything I need
to take over this city.
Mr. Church, I'm selling you
enough ordinance to take over a country.
Argh. Sons of bitches are late.
Go topside. See if you can get a visual.
Don't you just hate it when your plan
to steal illegal nuclear technology
hits a snag?
So that ambush, that was you.
You had your own men,
soldiers, brothers walk into a trap.
And I'll carry
that with me till the day I die.
But till that day comes,
I'm going to be a very, very wealthy man.
- You swore an oath, man!
- Then Genesis Day happened!
ISIS. Taliban. Al-Qaeda.
I could take 'em all on!
But what hope does the world have
against men with magic?
All those meta-humans in Central City?
How long before one of them,
manages to tear the world apart?
Sarge, what's going on?
It's all right. No! No!
You son of a bitch! You son of a bitch!
You know, I've been puzzling out
why none of my contacts have showed up,
fretting that maybe this whole thing
had gotten a little bit sideways,
wondering what to do about it.
And you showed up to solve my problem.
Thanks.
So, are you sure that it was them?
Yeah, that son of a bitch
leaves a pretty good impression.
Well, if AmerTek is in bed
with Church, then...
Then maybe that guy in rags isn't so bad.
He's probably trying to take down AmerTek.
So, why is the CEO of a
Fortune 500 company like AmerTek
willing to deal weapons to a crime lord?
Because they are trying
to avoid bankruptcy.
Got the forensics work-up back
on that piece of cloth from Ragman.
Please tell me that's
not what we're actually gonna call him.
What'd you find?
That it is over 2000 years old.
- And radioactive.
- Which means trackable.
If this weapons buy is going down,
this guy's going to try to stop it.
Leading us right
to Janet Carroll and Mr. Church.
Wait. What did you mean when you said
that AmerTek is going bankrupt?
The isotope that made the cloth
radioactive is very specific.
It came from one of the nukes
that Darhk launched on Genesis Day.
Specifically, a nuke manufactured
by a company
called "Atomic Defensive Systems."
They're likely a subsidiary of AmerTek.
Aw! People say he's just a pretty face.
Hmm!
Bottom line is the
subsidiary's connection with Genesis Day
has made AmerTek's stock prices go...
Which explains why they were so eager
to have a big public relations bonanza.
And why they'd be willing to unload
their excess ordinance on Tobias Church.
We need to find our friend in the rags
and hope he leads us to that weapons sale.
Wait! They did just say
that there was enough weaponry
to take down an entire country.
So I would think this would be a good time
for you to test out your new team.
There's no team anymore, Thea.
If I'm going in, I'm going alone.
This is the spot.
There's a crazy amount of hostiles inside.
I say crazy because
that is what you would have to be
to take them on all alone.
All right. You have your merchandise.
And now you want your money.
What kind of dent
can $100 million
make in your balance sheet?
- That's my worry.
- No, I think that's your golden parachute
and I admire that.
Hello, Janet.
Easy. This man's about to
save us $100 million.
They all died in fire. Your fire.
Your weapon. All for your money.
Where you at?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a KN-zero-eight.
Your pride and joy.
Over 15,000 missiles
launched on Genesis Day.
Only one found its mark. Yours.
No. No. We built those missiles
to keep people safe.
It was Damien, it was Damien Darhk.
Couldn't have done anything
if you hadn't given him the tools.
Your missile killed everyone in my home.
I am the very last living soul
of Havenrock.
And I carry with me a message
from all those souls you killed.
Ragman!
Thank you.
Thank me
by not standing in my way.
Let her go.
It's over.
Thank you for coming.
Your offer sounded intriguing.
Why'd you make it?
Why did you give up your vengeance
to save my life?
I don't know.
I think it's what my father
would have wanted me to do.
He saved my life.
On Genesis Day
he wrapped me in these rags.
He said they were ancient.
From the time of Devarim.
That they would protect me from the fire.
And they did.
So you see why I have to avenge him?
Your father didn't give up his life
so you could become a killer.
You don't know that.
My father gave up his life to save mine.
He made me promise to be better than him.
To save this city in a way
that he never could.
It's been nearly ten years since that day.
So far, I've failed.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I don't want to fail anymore.
I can't do it alone.
I need a team.
Let's honor the legacies of our fathers.
Together.
Why, Anatoly? Why kill them?
You rang bell. They did not.
I only rang the bell because of them.
I couldn't have done it alone.
But using team was your idea.
You used them to win, huh? Intelligent.
Bratva wants that, Bratva need that.
I never would have done it if I had known
it was gonna cost them their lives.
First part of initiation.
Only person you can trust, yourself.
You seemed
to have re-opened a wound, friend.
What the hell?
Still think you can write
with your cuffs on?
I mean, it wouldn't be much.
Just a signature.
You want to read your confession
before you sign it?
Screw you!
Now, Sergeant,
I am offering you an opportunity here.
I'm not owning up to this. You did this.
Yeah, but I used your gun
to shoot Private Collins.
Apparently, he walked in
on your attempted illegal appropriation
of a WMD for your own personal gain.
I got six men
out there who'll testify to that.
No one will ever believe your story.
I will.
Good luck with your court martial.
Oh, please, come in, sorry.
Sit down and I will be right with you.
Okay, thank you for coming.
Um, yeah, well, I almost didn't.
'Cause, you know, l...
I screwed up, didn't I? People got hurt.
Now it seems like you figured it out that
I'm drinking again and
I understand,
I don't wanna be any trouble.
I'm just sorry it didn't work out.
Okay, Quentin, that's...
It's not gonna work for me.
What?
You leaving
and hitting the bottle again, okay?
No! I think we can do better than that.
- I've been to meetings.
- Not a meeting.
A job.
How does Deputy Mayor sound?
You want to, hire a drunk
to be your deputy mayor, huh?
What, Oliver's approval ratings
are not low enough?
If we were hiring a drunk,
that would be a very good point.
But that is not what we are doing.
We are hiring the former captain
of the SCPD who...
Who just lost his daughter
and is honoring her memory
by dedicating himself
to the city that she loved.
All right, what do you think
about that one?
Why, I think
maybe the wrong Queen ran for mayor.
Look, Ollie, he told me you said,
that you needed a reason
to stay sober, so I...
I thought maybe this could be it.
Yeah, maybe it could.
You let Church almost kill you
so that you could recruit Ragman?
I was betting that his heroism
would trump his vengeance.
That's a big risk
to take on a stranger, don't you think?
Yeah. Well, I'm not done yet.
"- Hey.
- Yeah?
- Are you all right?
Yeah. Fine.
Thank you all for coming.
I only came 'cause blondie said
there'd be an apology.
Well, "blondie" made a good point.
You're not just joining up
with the Green Arrow.
You'd be joining up with me.
The Green Arrow is the Mayor?
I had the same cognitive dissonance.
I hope you don't think I'm gonna apologize
for the trash I talked about you.
No more than I'm going
to apologize for the tough training.
But I understand
that you all need to trust me.
This is as far as I know how to go.
You're sort of asking without asking
if we want to come back, right?
That's exactly what he's doing.
Okay, good. Then I'm in.
Me, too.
Wild Dog?
I'll fight any war long as I trust
who's leading me into battle.
But we have got to rethink this code name.
No chance.
Ah.
Can't stay away from me, can you?
You almost killed
the Green Arrow the other night.
If you had, you'd be dead right now.
Who the hell are...
The Green Arrow is mine.
You kill him, you die.
Who are you?
Prometheus.