Oh, my God!
Run, run!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, come on, man!
I'm just trying
to make
an honest living!
There's nothing honest
about what you do!
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
Tell me now and you live.
Please!
They'll kill me!
Whoever you fear...
Fear me more!
Okay, okay!
We call him The Count,
that's all I know.
I swear to God!
Hey!
Get me down
from here!
Find what you're looking for?
Took down three Vertigo
pushers tonight, Diggle.
Last one finally knew a name.
The Count.
The Count?
That's worse than The Hood.
You're not going
back out there.
I'm not done
for the night.
Whoever this Count is,
he has a lot of blood on his hands,
and it is long past time
he started paying.
Well, slow down, I think
you're missing the point here.
What?
Thea.
Her hearing's
in a few hours.
You think she cares more
about some drug lord
getting his
just desserts,
or you being by her side
when she needs you the most?
Hey, we should
get going.
Judges don't
appreciate the value
in being
fashionably late.
Got any other tips?
Let the lawyer
do all the talking.
They'll give you
a pad and paper
but do not play
tic tac toe.
Judges don't
appreciate that, either.
Come on, Speedy.
I know, I know.
Keep on trying
to get up and go,
but...
just don't.
I wish dad were here.
I'm here.
We should leave now, Thea.
Ms. Queen.
Thea, over here.
Can we get a comment?
Just one comment!
Thea, are you
going into rehab?
Miss Queen, are you being
dispelled from Balliol Prep?
Are you worried
about the outcome?
Docket ending 1-10-5-6,
People vs. Thea Dearden Queen.
Possession
of a controlled substance,
driving under the influence
of a controlled substance.
Counselors, I understand
you've reached a plea agreement.
We have, Your Honor.
Given that my client
is a juvenile,
the people have generously
agreed to probation.
Juvenile?
Says right here she's 18.
She is 18 now,
Your Honor,
but at the time of arrest,
she was still two days shy
of her 18th birthday.
Ms. Queen
has no priors.
Well, just because
Ms. Queen's family
sweeps her priors
under the rug,
doesn't mean they don't exist.
You get your client off,
and you help your boss
avoid dealing with the drug
that's sweeping across
our city like the plague.
Everyone wins, except us,
the people of Starling City.
Your Honor,
with all due respect--
Ms. Queen,
like it or not,
you are now the poster child
for this menace.
Maybe if people see
that the Queen family
can't get away
with using Vertigo,
they'll think twice
before using it themselves.
The plea arrangement
is denied.
This case will
proceed to trial.
They can't do this.
That man cannot send
my daughter to prison.
What are our options?
An interlocutory appeal.
But trial judges have discretion
to reject plea agreements.
I think you might want to
prepare yourself for the possibility
that this isn't going
to go our way.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen.
I'll get to work
on the appeal.
Well, so much for the best
criminal defense attorney in the city.
Thea, we will handle this,
I promise.
Like you promised Walter
you'd always stay faithful to him?
I feel better already.
That's enough!
Don't worry.
Sounds like you won't
have to be putting up
with me much longer.
What, does she not realize
how serious this is?
She took drugs.
She drove. She could have
killed someone, or herself.
I know.
All that judge is looking for
is someone to make
an example of.
What does it have to be her?
Maybe it doesn't.
Listen, I have to go
do something.
Are you going
to be okay?
I'm not the one facing prison.
You working
for them now?
Why are you
doing this to me?
I thought
we were friends.
Or...something.
I mean, why'd you bother
keeping me safe
if you were just going
to hand me over to them?
Just get me out of here.
I can't.
Hey! Don't leave me here!
I came back for you!
Do you hear me?
♪ Arrow 1x12 ♪
Vertigo
Original Air Date on January 30, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hi. Looking
for Detective Hall.
I was told
he works in Vice.
Oliver?
McKenna Hall.
Hi.
Here I was,
expecting a middle aged guy
in a bad suit...
And I got McKenna Hall.
I live to surprise.
Well, I remember.
What was that club
that you got us kicked out of?
The Club Deville?
Okay, in my defense,
there was no sign
that specifically said
you had to keep
your clothes on.
So, a cop?
I guess you're not hitting
the party circuit anymore.
I still go to raves.
I just go
undercover now.
And I have to dress
slightly more appropriately
to hide my badge and gun.
Right.
So what do you need
with a vice cop, Oliver?
Vertigo.
Right. I saw your sister on TV.
I'm sorry.
The judge is trying
to make an example of her.
So I was thinking,
if you could find the person
selling the drugs,
it make take some
of the heat off Thea.
Easier said than done.
Did some digging
and came up with a name.
Um, The Count?
Oliver, we've known
about The Count for months.
Oh.
I wish this
was thicker,
but we really don't
have much on him.
Love to say we're
going to catch him
before your sister's
trial, but it's highly unlikely.
Oh, I am late
for my shift.
Well, if you hear
of anything about this guy,
just...let me know?
I always loved how much you cared
about your sister.
But leave the policing
to the police, okay?
Okay.
What did Queen want?
He's an old friend,
sister's jammed up.
Anything else,
Sergeant?
No.
You need a tailor.
You know about
the hood guy.
He just
cornered me, man.
The hood guy?
I didn't
say anything.
Oh, I know.
You can't divulge secrets
you don't know.
But...
examples must be made.
Vertigo,
in its purest form.
When injected directly
into the bloodstream,
it affects the thalamus
region of your brain.
Which is where all
of the information
from your pain receptors
is collected.
No doubt you're in
excruciating pain.
But actually, you're not.
You just think you are.
I've seen it last for days,
until finally
the heart gives out.
One bullet left.
Now, you can use
that bullet to shoot me
and take your revenge,
or...you could
shoot yourself.
It's your choice.
The Hood.
Coming for me.
Interesting.
I'm learning you're not much
of a morning snuggler.
And I'm learning that
you don't like to wake up
at any hour
that ends in a.m.
That's true. Yeah.
So if you're busy
being a lawyer all day
and I'm managing
a night club all night,
when exactly do we get
to see each other?
Hmm.
I got it. Stay.
Hey.
Hey, how--
how is Thea holding up?
She's doing okay.
Thank you.
Um...Actually, I--
I came to talk
to Laurel.
Yeah.
Hi.
Thank you for coming
to court yesterday.
Yeah, of course.
But I don't think
the judge is willing
to move off his position.
Taking a hard line
against criminals is
a platform for his reelection.
I need you to talk
to your father.
He's inside the system,
and...maybe he cashes in
a chip with Judge Brackett,
gets him off throwing the book at Thea.
Oliver, I don't--
Laurel, I am working
on something on my end,
but...
If it doesn't work out,
this is my best chance
to help my sister.
Please.
I'll see
what I can do.
But no promises.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Absolutely not.
Dad, I know
how you feel about Oliver.
Then why would you even
ask me to do this.
Because Thea,
she's only 18 years old.
Which makes her an adult.
She can take her medicine.
It's about time someone
in the Queen family did.
What about
the Lance family?
A young girl
acting out,
engaging
in reckless behavior,
does that sound
familiar?
Laurel,
don't go there.
Thea, she's just like
I remember Sarah.
That is not how
I remember your sister.
That's because
you remember her
the way that you
wish she had been,
not the way that
she actually was.
She's not the Saint that
you make her out to be.
I know she was arrested
for shoplifting
and I know
you made it go away.
Well, maybe
if I let her go to jail,
Queen wouldn't have had her
on that damn boat.
Dad, you make it sound
like he kidnapped her.
For so long,
you and I have blamed Oliver
for Sarah's death,
but Sarah's
to blame, too.
When I look at Thea,
I see Sarah's
potential in her.
And her flaws, too.
Yes, Thea made
a mistake.
But she's been
through a lot.
She lost a father
and a brother.
She doesn't need prison.
She needs help.
So please...
I'll make some calls.
I've seen a fair amount
of Cyrillic back in Afghanistan
left over
by the Soviets.
Is this Russian owned?
This is the not
so hidden headquarters
for the Starling City
chapter of the Bratva.
Diggle...
Whatever I say,
whatever goes down,
just go with it.
Zdravstvuyte.
Good to see you.
Long time.
Particularly
for Bratva captain.
I was trying to figure out
where to put my interests.
I decided on pharmaceuticals.
I don't mean aspirin.
A wise choice.
Mepheodrone would be a good
investment for you.
It's the newest thing.
I was thinking Vertigo.
Newer thing.
Tough market, Vertigo.
Only one seller.
I know.
I was hoping you could
do me a favor
and arrange a meeting.
He's difficult man.
And he does not
like new friends.
This is everything
the police have on him.
Tell him it's a gift.
I will see
what I can do.
Provided you do
favor for me.
Vse chto ugodno.
It is unusual
for an American
to hold such
a position of esteem
in our organization.
Mr. Queen.
Anatoli Knyazev.
He speaks
very highly of you.
He should.
I saved his life.
What did he do?
Something
I told him not to.
Now the favor.
Kill this man for me,
and I will believe
your interest
in our organization
is genuine.
And then I will arrange a meeting
with The Count.
Oliver...
Hey, shut up!
What are friends for?
I'm out of the gates
now. What's going on?
Are we getting
out of here?
Where are you taking me?
While I admit that bout
was particularly one-sided,
would anybody else
like to give it a try?
The point of these little
gladiatorial distractions
is to strengthen
unit cohesion.
To that end, I think
our newest recruit
ought to be afforded
the opportunity
to try his hand.
I can't believe
you just killed that guy.
You really have
a low opinion of me.
Whoa! That's a neat trick.
You going to teach me
that one day?
No.
What are you doing?
You need to arrange
a new identity for this guy.
Get him out of the city.
Right, so your Ruskie pal
draws out The Count,
vigilante takes him down.
No, Diggle,
because then the Bratva
would know that I used them,
and that relationship is too valuable.
I do the meet
with The Count as myself,
let him leave, then we follow him
to his hideout.
Just that easy, huh?
Well, I will still need
my trust bodyguard.
Fantastic. Looking forward
to my new and exciting career
as a drug dealer.
He's a captain.
And he has money.
Are you interested?
Hmm.
Let's say...yes.
My father was able
to get Judge Brackett
to back off
his hardline stance.
Your father hates me.
No.
My father hates him.
Look, nobody asked you
to get involved.
I did.
The judge has agreed
to a sentence
of 500 hours
of community service
and two years of probation.
Provisional on the appointment
of someone to act in loco parentis.
In loco what?
It means that
the court will appoint
an individual to assume
responsibility for you.
Me.
I say thanks,
but no thanks.
Thea!
You don't actually
have a choice.
Oh, actually, I do.
See, I'm 18 now and I can make
my own decisions.
So I decide not to be
your ex-girlfriend's office monkey.
Well, if you change
your mind, then.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thea...
You're in real trouble,
and rightly so.
Doing drugs
and driving?
It is beyond stupid. That is
a good deal that Laurel got you.
Why aren't you
jumping at it?
I already have a mother.
So...
you're going
to go to jail
and it will ruin
the rest of your life.
No.
I want to ruin mom's life.
She's a liar and a cheat.
I mean, deal with, Ollie.
You can pretend
all you want to
that she's a saint,
but I hate her.
And she betrayed dad.
So you're just--you're going
to go to jail to spite her?
Thea...
Mom didn't cheat on dad.
He cheated on her.
Is that the best
you can come up with?
Dad wasn't the man
he said he was.
On "The Queen's Gambit"
right before he died,
he admitted to me
that he failed us.
You.
Me. And mom.
That he wasn't the man
he said he was
and that he just wished...
he wished he had more time
to right his wrongs.
I don't believe you.
Yes, you do.
Leave me alone.
How dare you.
She was old enough
to know the truth.
Oliver, the Russians called.
The meet is set.
It's tonight.
You know why
they call him The Count?
When he was
developing this drug,
he experimented
on the homeless.
Prostitutes, runaways.
The police
would find their bodies,
puncture marks
on their neck,
like a vampire.
You should not be in such a hurry
to meet this man.
Thank you for this.
But I'm not
overly concerned
about the SCPD.
Now, I understand
you gentlemen
wish to participate in
the feel good business.
Yes.
And why is that?
Well, I am opening
a nightclub,
and I'd like my customers
to have a little...
something extra.
Well, as it happens,
I'm looking
to expand my brand.
A good wine's value is measured
by its vintage.
The number of years
it took to ferment.
Vertigo is measured
in lives.
56 people died
to perfect this high.
Believe me when I say
that they did not
die for nothing.
The cops!
We've been set up!
Let's get out!
Go! Go!
SCPD! Put your weapons down!
Down!
Oliver!
Hey!
No witnesses.
Get out of the car!
Keep it.
Yeah, we got to go.
Steps. Let's go.
Oliver!
Drink.
Wait!
Mornin'.
How you feeling?
I feel like
I'm getting
the worst hangover
of my life.
That coming from a guy who spent
most of his twenties in a hangover,
that's really saying something.
You think
you can uncuff me?
Not going to kill you.
Promise.
Ahh.
You're standing.
That's pretty impressive.
The Count only got you
with half a dose,
but you still sweated out
a small swimming pool coming down.
The Count.
Any chance our friends
in SCPD took him down?
None at all, but we did
manage to get this.
Think we should analyze it.
Listen, Oliver, maybe you need
to give it a few hours.
A near drug overdose isn't something
you just walk away from.
Neither is Thea.
What's wrong?
Is everything
okay with Thea?
This isn't about your sister,
this is about you.
Last night we got a call
from a C.I.,
busted up a drug sale between
a big time dealer and the Russian mob.
"We"? I thought
you worked Vice.
Joint task force. Vertigo's
got everybody holding hands.
Like I said...
Last night,
drug deal gone south.
An eyewitness
put you at the scene.
Whoever he is,
he's mistaken.
Yeah?
I saw you, Oliver.
Is this true?
I was checking
into The Count.
He's the guy who
sold drugs to Thea.
And I figured if I could find out
what he looked like,
then I could give your sketch artist
something to go on.
So I paid a low-life
with a Russian accent
an obscene amount
of money to arrange a meeting.
And? Did you get eyes on him?
No.
All right, are you pressing charges
against my son?
You get involved
in this again,
you'll see the inside
of a cell,
and unlike last time,
you will not see the way out.
Detective.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for what
you did for Thea.
My daughter asked me
for a favor and I did it.
And that's the end of it.
Hope you don't think
I sold you out.
No. Just doing your job.
What on earth
were you thinking?
I was trying to help.
By running around
with the Russian mob
and a murderous
drug dealer?
Are you out
of your mind?!
Mom, look,
the real reason
that you're upset
is because I told Thea
the truth about dad.
She never needed
to know that.
Yes, I did.
I'm old enough
to know the truth, Mom.
It wasn't about
your age.
It was about preserving
your memory of your father.
He loved you.
No matter his faults,
he loved you.
I said that I wished
you had died
instead of him,
but...you still
didn't say anything.
Why?
One day,
I hope you're lucky enough
to have a daughter,
and you'll know why.
I'm so sorry for what I said.
I know, I know.
Now what?
Like you said,
we analyze the Vertigo.
It's in liquid form,
which means it contains water.
So maybe we can
trace back to where
in the city The Count is...
cooking up this garbage.
Hey, we need
to get you to a hospital.
No.
Oliver, God knows
what was in that drug.
It could be causing
permanent damage.
Felicity.
Hey, they said
you'd be up here.
You look like something
the cat dragged in.
Not that there are cats
in this building.
Well, once a cat did get in,
but a guard tazed it.
It smelled like fur and static
in here for like a week.
Ahem.
Would you mind stepping
away from the window for a moment?
I have a little bit
of a hangover.
Sounds like you need
a bloody Mary and a pretzel,
not the I.T.
Department.
Actually, my buddy Kevin
is starting
an energy drink company.
He says it's fantastic
for curing hangovers,
but I am very particular
about what it is
I put in my body.
I've noticed.
I said, not noticed.
Right?
I'm trying to find
a secret recipe.
Could you please
do a spectroanalysis
of the sample
and find out exactly
where in the city it's made?
If it's an energy drink,
why is it
in a syringe?
I ran out of sports bottles.
Okay.
Your B.S. stories
are getting worse.
I'm well aware.
Looks like Felicity
came through.
The solvent used
in the Vertigo sample
was run off water originated
within a ten block radius
of where East Glades
meets the bay.
Nothing there except
for an old juvenile detention center
abandoned about three years ago.
Cutbacks.
You can't go out there,
though, Oliver.
You're still suffering
the after-affects of the Vertigo.
Did you hear The Count?
He's taking
this drug citywide.
If we don't stop him now,
this becomes an epidemic.
I can stop you from leaving.
Try.
Oliver, you hit this
and you can leave.
I'm glad you came
to your senses.
You should always
remember one thing, Dig.
What's that?
I don't need the bow.
My C.I. swears
this is the place.
Bring your men
up on the flank.
Okay, this way.
Follow me.
He's here!
He who?
The Hood!
Looks like we're not
the only guests.
You should have stuck
to your depraved elite.
I am merely providing people
with what they want.
I am providing
a public service!
So am I.
Enjoy the fruits
of your labor.
Freeze! Put down the needle!
Or I will shoot you!
Put down the syringe.
He deserves this!
Not according to the law.
The people that think
you're a hero,
people like my daughter,
if they could see you now...
You're no hero.
You're what I always
said you were--
a killer.
Get him!
Get me an ambulance. Now!
Juvenile delinquent
reporting for duty.
Since you lost
your driver's license,
I'll pick you up at 5:00.
6:00.
We have a lot of work
for her to do.
Well, then, let's say
7:00 just to be safe.
Is it too late
to choose jail?
Yes.
I need you to go
through these files
and pull out all the documents
dated March 2007.
Do you think
you could do that?
I think I can.
I know I messed up.
I really appreciate
this, Laurel.
We are going to make
an upstanding citizen
out of you yet, speedy.
Thank you.
And this will be good for her,
having a role model,
somebody better than me.
Oh, you're not so bad.
And besides, it'll be nice
to have her around.
I got to take this.
Excuse me.
Hello?
We got The Count.
Bust up his lab,
got him on everything
from drug trafficking
to homicide.
He'll be gone
for a long while.
That's great, thanks.
It was great
seeing you, Oliver.
You, too.
See ya.
He's still critical.
I've never seen
anyone OD
on this much Vertigo
and live.
There's just
no way of knowing
what kind of damage
has been done to his brain
and nervous system.
Or if its irreparable.
Shengeun...
Survive.
Hi.
Thanks for meeting me.
I was...nervous
to come to your house.
Okay...
The thing is,
I've been debating
whether or not
to share this
with you for weeks.
Can I trust you?
I'm not an idiot.
You've dropped some fairly
ridiculous lies on me,
and...yet I still feel
like I can trust you.
Why is that?
I have one
of those faces.
Sorry.
Yes.
You can trust me.
Then I have something
to show you.
Have you ever
seen this before?
No.
Where'd you get it?
From your stepfather.
From Walter.
Um...
Well, where did
he get it?
He said he found it
in your house.
That it belongs to your mother.
Walter thought
she was hiding something.
Something more, and...
He wanted me to look into it,
but then he vanished.
I think this list might have cost
Walter his life.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==