Previously on "Crisis
on Infinite Earths"...
There's a wave
of antimatter sweeping
across this universe,
destroying everything
in its path.
He fought to his last breath
knowing every moment
was another life saved.
Dig, we are working
on bringing him back
the same way that he
brought me back, remember?
You're talking about a trip
to Purgatory?
- Yes.
- Fine. Count me in.
I need you
to come back to us.
You're my brother.
Can't lose you, man.
Oliver Queen.
- Who are you?
- Jim Corrigan,
but I'm also a Spectre.
It's your turn now.
Only you can light
the spark, Oliver.
It is your destiny.
What's happening?
Iris!
Where are we?
This is
the vanishing point.
It's a point outside
of time and space.
- Something's wrong.
- No. Hey, hey.
What did you do?
Well, I held
The Book of Destiny,
and I thought destiny
could use a little rewrite.
What do we do now?
Are we ready?
Just about.
You better suit up.
I love you.
Okay. This will be
temporal jump trial one.
All systems nominal.
I look ridiculous.
Is this really the height of fashion
at the dawn of time?
The suit provides
a shield against...
the coronal radiation...
my body will be...
yes, yes, yes.
I'm familiar with the jingle,
but you couldn't have
designed something
a tad less... bulky?
Remind me again,
why did I marry you?
You have a thing for men
of towering ambition.
Are you seeing this
quantum flux cascade?
I am just a time traveler
here, my love.
You are the Monitor.
Engaging quantum portal.
Field is stabilizing.
The portal is engaging.
Next stop...
the dawn of time.
I am in the temporal zone.
Oh, I wish you could
see this, Xneen.
The birthplace of all creation.
It is beautiful.
Mar, I'm getting readings
here I don't understand.
Your presence has
corrupted the zone somehow.
It's... it's releasing radiation
I've never seen before.
I think...
I think this might be anti-matter.
You have to get out of there.
Get out of there
right now!
Xneen... Xneen,
can you hear me?
Something went wrong.
I do not think this is
the dawn of time.
No, it is.
It just isn't the dawn of time
of our universe.
What?
You breached the wall
between our universe
and its opposite.
An anti-universe?
Your body
was suffused with coronal radiation.
The suit couldn't
contain it.
Mar? Mar, can you
hear me?
I'm sorry, my love.
My towering ambition...
has doomed us all.
Dear Amanda,
so... you're dead
along with, well, everyone,
everyone who's ever lived
in any reality ever,
and me, I'm supposed
to be a Paragon,
one of seven people who are
supposed to be
the multiverse's
last, best chance.
I don't see it.
The so-called
Paragon of Destiny,
she doesn't even believe
in tomorrow anymore.
The Paragon of Courage
spends every day
working herself to the bone,
training for a fight
that will never come.
The Paragon of Honor
just meditates
for hours on end.
The Paragon of Hope
has lost hers...
and me, I spend my days
trying to repurpose
the broken technology
of this place
to find us a way out.
Careful, careful.
Narcissist,
sociopath, evil genius...
there are a lot of ways
to describe Lex Luthor.
Agh! Idiot!
Why couldn't I be trapped
at the edge of eternity
with someone possessing more
than 200 IQ points?
But I find
"douchebag" to be the most descriptive.
As for Barry Allen,
aka the Flash,
aka the Paragon of Love,
he's just gone.
Missing.
What, you guys
building modern art now?
Hey, team.
We're repurposing
leftover time masters tech.
Mr. Luthor and I think
we've retrofitted it
into a teleportation
device.
To teleport us
to where exactly?
Kate makes a good point.
There is no... there
out there anymore.
So we send
somebody to test it.
- I'll go.
- No.
We've lost too many
good people already.
Thanks for
volunteering, Lex.
Well, that's very cold.
Is it because I killed
your parallel reality cousin?
Start it up.
If this works...
We get
out of here,
we defeat
the Anti-Monitor,
and we find a way
to get all the people we lost back.
Perhaps it was
too much to hope for.
Is there some way
you can get it to work?
It was a longshot
to begin with.
Watch out!
- Barry!
- Ugh!
Where am I?
The Vanishing Point.
You've been gone
for months.
What are you... what
are you talking about?
I just left
two seconds ago.
To go where?
To the speed force.
I didn't...
I couldn't... it was like...
it was like running
into a mountain at mach 10.
I couldn't...
there's no way
out of here.
What did you see?
Everything.
I see everything now.
Then you're ready.
Why would you make me
relive all that?
Every fight, every punch
you've thrown,
every kick
you've landed,
every arrow you've fired,
they have all led you here
to this moment,
to the ultimate fight.
Who am I fighting?
Not who.
What.
The Anti-Monitor.
The Monitor's adversary.
Not just adversary.
A being who stands against all there
ever was or will be,
the apocalypse itself
given life and form
and terrible purpose.
How do I beat him?
With help.
It's time to get your friends.
Barry, wait.
You look spent. You need to rest.
No. I'm fine.
I have to try again.
Hey, Barry,
that's a bad idea, okay?
The effort alone
could kill you.
It's better than just
staying here.
We're not gonna let
you kill yourself.
Get out of my way!
- Barry!
- We're not letting you
go anywhere.
- So try and stop me!
- In the condition you're in, Barry,
- it's not gonna be that hard.
- Cut it out!
Whatever's going to happen is not
going to include us turning on each other.
M-maybe you're right.
Maybe the speed force
is our last, best hope.
It is.
The speed force is
the key to saving you.
It's the key to
saving everyone.
Oliver?
Yes and no.
It's complicated.
Nice outfit.
Very... Sith.
Oliver?
I am Oliver Queen,
but I'm also
something more.
More what?
Some might call me a ghost,
a Spectre...
that's in tune with the entire
multiverse.
So there's still
a multiverse out there?
No. It's gone,
replaced with
its antithesis.
An anti-matter
universe.
Which we need to prevent
from happening.
Right now,
the Anti-Monitor
is at the dawn
of time,
fighting to make permanent
his destruction of worlds.
Then we go there,
and we end him.
He's
extremely powerful.
The eight of us might
not be enough.
We need
a backup plan.
You have our attention.
Several millennia ago
on a planet named Maltus,
Mar Novu attempted to travel
to the birth of the universe
but instead... opened a breach
to the anti-matter universe.
So the Monitor
gave us the Anti-Monitor.
Correct.
So while some of us
fight at the dawn
of time,
others must go
to Maltus.
And prevent Novu from
freeing his doppelganger?
I'm in.
Travel to an alien world?
So in.
Same.
Come on. You know you
don't want to risk
letting me out of your
sight for even a millisecond.
We can get to both
through the speed force,
but I can't get
into the speed force right now.
It's probably because
there's no multiverse left,
but you said you're in tune
with the multiverse.
Does that include
the speed force?
What you're asking me
is very dangerous, Barry.
But possible.
You could give me
the energy boost I need.
Please.
We have to do this.
Everyone's lives depend on it.
I've unlocked
your potential, Barry.
By touching my head?
Use this power
with caution.
Do you trust me?
Are you Oliver Queen?
Yes.
Then I trust you
with every cell of my body.
Good. Now run, Barry.
Run.
Okay.
Thanks for the kind
assist.
Why doesn't this
alien forest look more alien?
Let's focus. Mar Novu
could be anywhere,
and it's not like we can
just do an internet search for him.
Well, actually,
maybe we can.
Look at that.
Any city that large
has to be a bureaucracy.
And?
Well, bureaucracies
require some form
of central data bank
to function.
We find that,
we find Novu.
That's actually not
a bad idea. Lex...
Where's Lex?
Sorry I'm late,
but actually
my train was late.
Well, the second one.
The first one I did miss,
but that was
my cab driver's fault.
I've got this great traffic app,
and he thought that...
Queen consolidated?
Not exactly.
You're in
the speed force, Barry.
What happened to you?
You're not...
spectrey anymore.
Oh. Well, I'm lost.
I'm out there somewhere
in the speed force, too.
Right. The Anti-Monitor attacked.
We were separated,
and I am utilizing
various pieces
of my essence
to keep me, Sara,
J'onn, and Kate together.
That's why I'm here.
This is...
this is where we
first met.
There are few things
more powerful in the universe
than memory
and connection.
I am using our memories
of our friends
and closest allies
to keep all of us from falling out
of the speed force.
Wait. What happens
if they fall out?
We'll be consumed
by anti-matter.
I can buy you time, Barry,
but... you need to get
to each of us.
I mean, the speed force
is infinite.
I-I could never know
where to begin to look.
Remember, Barry,
memories and connections.
You need to consider
our greatest victories,
our most crushing defeats,
the moments when the bonds
between us were forged.
When the bonds were forged.
Now do this, Barry.
Because you have to.
What the...?
Um, hello?
What the hell is this?
I'm asking myself
the same question... literally.
No. This... this
can't be happening.
This... you... what are
you doing here?
Well, I'll tell you that
when you tell me
where... here... is.
Is this cosplay?
Oh, do you want a selfie, bro?
- I'm sorry.
- No, no. We're not... no.
I'm also the Flash.
You're also the what?
- The Flash?
- The Flash.
- It's complicated.
- I like your outfit. It seems... comfy.
- I was thinking yours is pretty cool.
- Smooth.
- Seems safe and...
it's breathable.
I'm Barry Allen.
- No!
- What?
What does that mean?
How can this...
This should be
impossible now.
Should be impossible now?
You don't know
about the...
Oh, my God.
Don't do this to me.
I don't know
about the what?
- Are you okay?
- Oh, my God.
I told Victor this was possible.
What does this mean?
What do you think
you're doing?
What you should
have done the moment
Fleet Feet dropped us
off here...
checked out the lay
of the land,
looked for
hidden dangers.
We are on an alien world.
Any number of chest busters
or predators could be lying in wait.
Don't you capes ever
watch a movie?
You know what?
Whatever it is you're planning,
I'm gonna figure
it out, and...
I'm gonna stop you.
I doubt that.
In a contest of mind over muscle,
mind wins every time,
but here.
Let me make it
easy for you.
Ask me what I'm
up to.
Go ahead.
All right.
What are you up to, Lex?
Universal domination,
of course.
Oh, I probably
should have mentioned
that I gave myself
a few upgrades
when I checked
The Book of Destiny out of the library.
What are you
doing?
God, I am so tired
of answering that question.
Moving on.
Yeah.
The Black Canary.
She tried to shut me up,
but it's not gonna work.
I didn't
kill those people.
Yes, I know.
Felicity told me.
An impersonator, right?
Hate when that happens.
Five years on
a deserted island.
That kind of thing
really changes you, doesn't it?
Must have been difficult
if not impossible
to hold on to your sanity
all those years,
and here you are,
pretending you have
everything in control.
Felicity told you
the truth,
and you should trust
her judgment.
How can I do that?
Her perception of you
is clearly clouded
by her emotional
attachment.
She's not seeing you
for what you really are.
You have no idea
what this city is up against.
Actually, I think I do,
and I'm gonna
stop him.
Who are you?
I want to limit
your involvement in this.
Why? Because I'm an alien?
I also happen to be
your biggest weapon.
You're an unknown quantity,
and this isn't personal.
Except that's exactly
how this feels.
When I... when I started
living this life,
I was going up
against human threats alone,
and I could handle that.
Then there were metahumans,
and I could
handle that.
I just discovered that
there are multiple Earths,
and I was brainwashed
aboard an alien spacecraft.
I'm sure that
was unnerving.
I don't get unnerved.
When I go up against something new,
I push back.
Right or wrong,
it's who I am,
and it's what I do,
so I am asking you
for just a little
bit of space
so that I can draw
a line somewhere,
so that I can claw back
just a small sense of normalcy.
I'm afraid we're well past normal.
J'onn, what are you doing here?
That... is a very long story.
Supergirl?!
Supergirl, please
wake up.
- Hey.
- Ryan?
Yeah. I think Lex
pulled a Luthor on us.
On the bright side,
I've never been knocked unconscious
on an alien planet before.
It's pretty much the same as
being knocked unconscious on Earth.
No broken bones.
You'll be fine.
Thanks. This definitely
makes me question again why I'm here.
I haven't got
special powers
or, you know, powers.
I'm pretty much
the dictionary definition of unspecial,
and I definitely don't feel like
I'm a Paragon of anything,
let alone Humanity.
Hey... wait.
Are you sure you guys
got the right guy?
You left your family
because someone
you never even met told you
you were needed.
I'd say that makes you
pretty special.
I don't know
about hope,
but you're definitely
the Paragon of Pep Talks.
Years of practice.
We need to catch up to Lex.
How do you know
where he's headed?
Well, before he
knocked me out,
he said was looking for
universal domination, so...
Hardly sounds like
a newsflash.
The universal part is new,
but if I know him,
he's looking to mess with
Novu's experiment,
change history to his advantage.
He really is a selfish asshat,
isn't he?
You really have
no idea.
What are you doing?
I'm guessing you haven't
flown on an alien planet either.
- I've never flown.
- No, but it's okay, Dr. Choi.
You don't have
to be nervous.
It's just up, up,
and away.
It's over, Deegan!
No. I decide
when the story ends!
Come on, Oliver.
Where are you?
Agh!
I wasn't here for this.
Told you you'd
catch me.
Thanks for the save.
With a magic arrow,
no less.
It's a gift
from the Monitor.
- Barry?
- Hey.
Did you go out shopping
for a new costume
while you were supposed
to be out saving the world?
What? Uh, no. No.
I-it's a crazy, long story,
and you wouldn't
believe me if I told you.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Please. Excuse us.
Are you okay?
What I'm about to tell you
isn't gonna make any sense,
but... you're not really
h-here right now.
- You're actually...
- In the speed force.
I remember. I...
I remember everything.
Okay. Well,
in that case...
that arrow...
from the Monitor,
I always felt like
there was something
you weren't telling me.
I didn't want to burden
you with the choice I made.
The choice to do what?
You and Kara, Barry,
you were fated to die
trying to save the world.
Right before you died,
you said you'd given up everything
for me and Kara.
You made some kind
of devil's bargain
with the Monitor to save us,
didn't you?
No. It wasn't
a devil's bargain, Barry,
and I'd make it again
in a second.
It cost you
your family, Oliver.
Cost you your life.
Dying's the easy part.
The dead are at peace,
but the real heroes are the ones
who have to keep going.
Go find the others.
Laurel.
Laurel, it's time.
It's time to put her to rest.
What am I supposed to tell my parents?
My father, he...
he has a bad heart.
He won't live through this.
It should have been me.
She was
the true hero.
A hero sets
an example, Laurel...
so follow hers.
Wear the mask.
Be the Canary.
That's how you keep
your sister alive.
Oh, boy.
Engaging quantum portal.
I wouldn't do that.
Xneen?
No.
No, obviously.
Hi. Lex Luthor.
I'm here to make you an offer
I won't let you refuse.
How did you get in here?
Our security
protocols are...
A joke,
but the fact that I was able
to circumvent them with astonishing ease
is exactly why you need
to listen to me.
- Xneen?
- Is taking a little nappy time.
Not to worry.
So you are a scientist.
Tell me you're not intrigued
by what I have to say,
or do you get regular visits
from humans with future knowledge?
Speak.
The experiment
you're conducting
will not only
destroy you
but your planet
and your wife.
Another ancient zealot.
I am so sick...
Don't know
who they are.
I'm not even
from this universe.
What I am from
is the future,
so I know exactly how your little
time-jumping experiment will go wrong,
and I am willing to share
my future knowledge with you.
And in return?
Well, I don't cotton
to aliens,
but you will soon have
certain abilities
that I will need in order
to deal with some,
shall we say,
super problems
popping up
in my world.
I do not have
any... abilities.
Stick with me, kid.
So what do you say?
Team up?
The brave and the bald?
Who are you?
Hey. Um, this is awkward.
Long story short,
you guys aren't really you guys,
and none of this is
really actually happening.
What are you talk... hey! Hey!
Don't you touch her!
I'm so sorry.
It's a miracle.
- Barry?
- Hey.
- What's happening?
- It's a long, very weird story.
- I'll catch you up on the way.
- On the way to where?
You're not taking
her anywhere.
I'm sorry.
Like I said,
you guys aren't really here.
The speed force?
I can only assume.
We were moving through the speed force
when we were attacked.
Uh, by someone called...
The Anti-Monitor.
Doesn't even sound like
an actual name.
We're all trying to stop him.
We're working together.
The two of you...
work together.
I know you don't trust each other.
Right now, I know you
don't even like each other,
but all that changes.
In fact, we all come
to depend on each other.
We all come to
trust each other.
Why are you telling us this now?
This seems to be a pattern with you.
You don't trust people.
They don't trust you.
Then all
of that changes,
and the bond
between you is stronger than iron.
I'm sorry.
What's your point?
It's maybe something
I can learn from.
So basically, you tore
a little hole
in the space-time
continuum,
opened a doorway into something
called the anti-matter universe.
Matter and anti-matter
cannot coexist.
Hence a lot of bad stuff
happening that we would
just as soon not
have happen,
so I think what we need to do is adjust
the Ronstrom coefficient.
Lex, we need to talk.
Mar Novu, do not trust
this man with anything!
Give him a knife
for his food,
and no matter how much
he thanks you for the dinner,
he'll stab you right
in the back with it.
Or the front.
I'm not choosy.
Last time, you caught me
by surprise.
That's not gonna
happen again.
Get Novu outta here.
Come with me,
sir, please.
Xneen!
Okay. Listen to me.
Whatever you do,
you can't open that portal.
The hairless one
warned me.
No. This isn't
a warning kind of situation.
This is a don't do it
at any... cost kind of situation.
It is my life's work.
Trillions of other
people's lives,
an infinite number,
will be lost if you go
through with it.
It's not worth it.
You just show up here
as if by magic
and demand belief.
The fact I'm here at all
should be enough to convince you.
You are a remarkable
individual.
Funny. A new friend
of mine just told me I'm special.
I didn't believe
her until now.
I wonder, is it
a double-cross
if I never trusted you
in the first place?
Why do you Kryptonians always
have to take things so personally?
You tried to kill
my cousin,
you tried to kill me,
you betrayed Lena,
left her with nothing
but a ruined name and a broken heart.
All I did was tell
her the truth,
something you never had
the courage to do.
Don't take it personally.
Hey! If you would stop trying
to kill each other.
I got through to Novu.
You just ruined
a perfectly good bad guy plan,
you know that,
new guy?
Where are we?
The anti-matter
universe.
At the dawn of time.
We arrived, and he was
already here...
the Anti-Monitor.
That's impossible.
I got through to him. I know I did.
Some fates are inescapable.
You spoke to one man
across countless universes,
but within the tapestry
of the multiverse,
there will always be
one Mar Novu
who cannot turn
from his towering ambition,
and in that inevitability,
there is destiny.
Welcome to mine!
All of you,
listen to me.
This is why you were selected.
You're Paragons.
Yeah. I'm still a little unclear
on what all that means.
It means you're
powerful enough
to hold the line,
to buy us the time we need.
To do what?
Rebirth the universe.
What, like, a do-over?
The dawn of time is
the only place it can happen.
I'll light the spark,
you fan the flame.
And how do we do that?
You'll know when it's time.
Why do you cosmic types
always have to be so obtuse?
If I knew, I'd tell you.
I don't.
All I have is trust.
Do you trust me?
With every cell
in my body.
Let's do this.
Die, you creepy shadow things!
That's for Oliver!
Idiots! If anyone's
gonna take over the universe,
it's gonna be me!
It is too late.
After 10,000 years,
I shall be victorious.
No, you won't be.
Such confidence.
You believe Corrigan prepared
you for this fight.
I believe my entire life
prepared me for this fight.
All life ends.
Only death is eternal.
Only I
am eternal.
We'll see about that.
Is this typical for you guys,
saving the world?
Yes!
No!
My team and I
usually mess things up
for the better!
Focus! We're in the fight
of our lives here.
You have failed...
this universe!
We... we did it.
So this is what
being a hero feels like.
Interesting.
Where's Oliver?
There!
Oliver.
What is that?
"I'll light the spark"...
"While you fan
the flame."
He said you
would know what to do.
I think dying kind of
messed with his head.
Well, think.
You're meant to be the genius.
A genius who's had
the fortitude
to read The Book of Destiny
and retain his sanity.
I think the jury's
still out on that one.
The Book of Destiny.
I made myself
the Paragon of Truth.
What if truth can
tell us what we need to do?
Being what?
Use what's left
of the book
to fan the flame.
How do we all
use the book?
We focus.
A singular, laser-like focus.
On what?
Humanity,
truth,
love,
destiny,
honor,
courage...
and hope.
No!
Oh, my God!
- Oliver!
- Barry, get us there.
Oliver.
I...
I need both of you to watch
over my family.
Hey, Ollie. They're
gonna be fine, all right?
You're gonna be fine.
You did it.
You all did...
you all did it.
Did what?
What did we do?
Just look.
Ollie, we saw,
but what is it?
It's the new universe.
It's kind of small for a universe.
Wait for it, Barry.
It's almost time,
almost time.
There. You did it.
No, Ollie,
you did it, okay,
and that's why you got to
come back with us,
so we need you to
hang on, okay?
Sara, this is just what the Monitor
said would happen.
- No.
- What?
There was an end...
and there's a beginning.
You remember what I told you?
Dying is the easy part.
I'm at peace.
The real heroes...
They're the ones who
have to keep going.
So keep... going...
don't ever stop.
This world,
this new world...
it needs both of you.
Barry...
An end.
And a beginning.
Thank you, Oliver.
Greg, move your head!