My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city,
but my old approach
wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become
something else.
the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
You won't be able
to stop him.
We need to trap him.
Dad?
We are the same,
you and I.
You are wrong.
I am nothing
like you.
John, voice-over: I had to put him
down, Lyla.
He had reached
for my gun.
Alex,
where are we?
- Thea.
- No. I can't.
Where are you going?
Rubicon--
designed to prevent
any country,
even our own,
from firing
a nuclear missile.
Darhk ripped it out.
Darhk would control the world's
nuclear stockpile.
Andy told me that
Genesis was coming.
God wanted to give the world a do-over,
so he destroyed it.
He destroyed
it with a flood.
So nuclear annihilation
is Darhk's flood.
What's he planning
on building as his ark?
Rubicon security
compromised.
Russia, Markovia,
Corto Maltese, us,
every NATO Ally--
Rubicon has control
over all their
nuclear systems.
You mean HIVE does.
I know it's a little
late for this,
but whoever created
an algorithm
that could override
any country's nuclear weapons
really screwed up.
That would be
Amanda Waller.
How much time
do we have?
We?
Oliver, I'm
the director of Argus,
and this goes
way over my head.
This is
executive level,
and this is
Department of Defense.
Right, right, right, right,
but how much time?
There's a start-up
sequence
before Darhk can
actually launch a nuke.
We have just
under 21 hours.
You're gonna have to
find a way to interrupt that sequence.
Rubicon is a failsafe against
nuclear Armageddon.
Argus designed it
to be 100% unhackable.
No. She can do it.
She's the best.
Well, actually,
that would be my father
as far as Rubicon
is concerned.
It uses Fourier protocols.
Noah practically wrote
the book on them.
The world is facing
nuclear Armageddon.
My pride and my
general dislike for my father
can take a backseat
for the next 20-plus hours.
Felicity, this isn't
about pride.
Your father's
a criminal.
He can't be trusted.
I'm not saying
we should trust him.
I'm saying we need to.
Ok. He got out in Darhk's jailbreak.
How do we find him?
I'm already running
a search.
Can you try to get
in touch with Thea, too?
Please. We need her
back here.
John, can I talk
to you for a second?
- How you doing?
- Been better.
Well, I'm not gonna pretend to understand
what you're going through.
Well, Oliver, you've
been through this with your mother,
which is why I can't
quite understand
why you're putting
the fate of the world
in the hands
of another evil parent.
I'm not trusting
Kuttler.
I trust Felicity,
and we should just
let her do her job, ok?
We have one
of our own.
Yeah, stopping Darhk.
His magic is powered
by death,
so if even one
of those nukes hits--
he will be unstoppable.
Ok. What's your play?
Well, if he is planning
on harnessing
all of this death,
he's gonna be in something
called a Nexus chamber.
Basically, it's
a collector magic.
And here I thought earthquake machines
were as strange as it got.
Esrin Fortuna told me
that one of these chambers
exists in Star City.
I'm betting it falls
on a Ley line.
What did Vixen call
them--Wi-Fi for magic?
- Yeah.
- It's a big city, Oliver.
We got 21 hours.
One step at a time.
We have
to help them!
We're gonna help
these people!
What are you
looking for?
Reiter's men found
a way on the island.
There has to be
a way off.
There's a plane
east end of the island,
and it's far.
We'll make it.
What's that?
This may be a way
to call for help.
Let's go!
And...
Woof.
I know.
The predictability
was a terrible flaw in the design.
Predictability
is your flaw, too.
Every time my life
starts to suck, you show up.
Heh.
Leave us.
Is that hand a present from your
new best friend?
I'm not doing this
for a prosthetic, Thea.
I'm doing it
to keep you safe.
Keep me safe.
- Yes. Keep you safe.
- Hmm. Yeah.
Like I said,
predictable.
Only thing I don't get
is how is brainwashing
some guy I really like
in your plan to keep me safe?
His conditioning
wasn't my idea.
Ruvé Darhk wanted
to ensure his compliance
in the final phase.
Final phase of what?
Something called
Genesis.
Darhk plans to burn the world
in a nuclear fire
while we are protected
down here.
Oh, God.
Then he and his followers
can rebuild.
Truth be told,
it's not dissimilar
to the plan I had for the Glades
once upon a time,
but on a much,
much larger scale.
Let me guess--
you don't think
that destroying the entire world
is completely insane?
The world is
what's insane.
It is beyond saving.
It needs a do-over,
a reset.
Look. Once I realized
Darhk's plan was inevitable,
the math was simple.
Save yourself.
And my daughter...
Even if she doesn't
want to be saved.
Look. I am way,
way past the point of telling you
that you are crazy.
I just want to see Alex.
I just want to know
he's ok,
and look, I--I get it.
I'm stuck here,
but I can be stuck
here and compliant,
or I can be a pain
in your ass,
so take me to him now.
Heh.
Hey.
- Hey, hon.
- Hi.
What's up?
Um...
When I was at your
place this morning, I, um...
I found this.
Ooh. What are you doing going
through my stuff?
Snooping.
But--but--but this isn't any of your
business, Donna.
No, no, babe.
It is my business actually,
you getting suspended.
It is kind of.
- Donna.
- Hey!
What is this?
It's--it's, um--
it's an affidavit.
Pike said if I put
my name to it,
then--then I get
my badge back.
It says you didn't know that Laurel was
the Black Canary.
I may not be
in mansa,
but I know how
to read, sweetie.
I think it's
Mensa actually.
You told me that you
knew what Laurel was doing.
- Yeah.
So this is a lie.
Yeah, but it's
a complicated lie.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Because according
to Pike,
IAB are willing to
look the other way
about my working with Darhk
because I was...
protecting Laurel.
Why would you have to
protect her if she was a superhero?
Yeah, exactly.
Now you see.
I see that they're
asking you to lie.
Sweetheart, come on.
All I ever wanted
was to--was to be a cop,
and what's a small lie if it means I can do
some good for this city?
No. No.
That's just it.
There aren't
any small lies, hon.
Take it from someone
who had a child
with a man
who was a liar.
I'm not Noah Kuttler.
I know, honey,
and that's why I love you.
Ok?
I love you...
And that's why
I have faith that...
You're gonna do
the right thing.
Gentlemen, I have a little errand
I need you to run,
a loose end that
needs tying up,
not unlike...
Err.
Oh. Do I detect some
obstinacy, Mr. Brick?
I'm used to giving the orders, Darhk,
not taking them.
Not even as a little thank-you
for busting you out of Iron Heights?
Whatever happened
to gratitude?
I'm here, ain't I?
And when the whole world
is sitting under a field of mushroom clouds,
you will be glad
that you are.
Now then, back
to the errand.
Have either of you boys
heard of the Calculator?
There's no one here.
I found a deep-trunk
fiber optic hookup
with polymorphic
encryption.
Noah is there,
trust me.
I think she's right.
Look.
Whoever rigged that up didn't want
to be surprised.
I'm tracing
the Bluetooth signal.
Head southwest.
Well, he's not here.
He has to be.
He was.
Looks like he bolted
and in a hurry.
Bolted from whom?
This was 20 minutes ago.
Looks like Kuttler wasn't the only one
that left Iron Heights.
Those are Ghosts with him.
What does HIVE want
with my father?
Ok. Find that
scrawny son of a bitch,
and when you do,
kill him.
Welcome
to Tevat Noah,
your home in the new era.
Please proceed
to the registration building
to receive your
residence assignments.
Aah!
Sorry about that.
It wasn't easy
finding my way down here.
You Ghosts are swell
at keeping secrets
but less swell
resisting torture,
so why don't you
spare me the trouble
and tell me where I can find
Damien Darhk?
♪ Arrow 4x21 ♪
Monument Point
Original Air Date on May 11, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You're right.
Kuttler's the only one
that can stop Rubicon.
That's why Darhk
wanted him dead.
You all right?
Yeah. The word conflicted
comes to mind.
Well, at least we know
he got away.
But not much
of a head start.
I hacked Kuttler's server
to see if there was
anything in there that could point us
to where he would run to,
and he cleared the cache,
so I can't recover
any files,
but there is a root directory
called Ravenspur.
What's Ravenspur?
Don't know.
Does sound familiar.
I just don't know why.
We're running
out of time.
The whole world is,
so yeah.
Meantime, my Ley line
algorithm kicked back
a possible twenty
on a magical clubhouse for Darhk.
We drove some
of them off,
but Reiter's sending
reinforcements.
Reiter's dead.
We heard him
on the radio.
He's alive.
There's a map of the island
in the pack.
Get them to the plane.
What about you?
I'm gonna find Reiter,
and I'm gonna end this.
Then I'm
staying, too.
Do you remember
what you told me?
It takes a monster
to kill a monster.
Now get these
people home.
Felicity just called.
She needs to see me
about something.
Is everything
all right?
I don't know.
It's Felicity,
so, you know,
you never know.
Were you signing
that thing?
Yeah, I was
about to.
Hey. Uh, before you
give me that dirty look,
you might want to,
uh, read this thing.
I already read it.
Just read it,
please.
Oh.
It's looks a--
Yeah, it's a little
different, huh?
"Although I was
against at first,
"I came to see
what Laurel was doing
"was vital...
"And important
and good
as the Black Canary."
I gave it
a little rewrite.
Baby.
I am so proud
of you.
Laurel would be, too.
This is me signing
my badge away.
No. You don't
know that.
All you can know
for sure
is that you're doing
the right thing.
Oh, Mr. Dennis.
Ms. Smoak.
You haven't returned
my calls.
Yes, I am sorry.
I've been busy.
So have I.
Running your company.
Do I need to remind you
of your responsibilities
to Palmer Tech?
No, you don't, but you're just gonna
have to believe me
when I tell you that
what is on my plate right now
is much more important.
Hey!
Hi. Um, uh, should
I come back?
No, no. Please stay.
Miss Smoak, the board--
Can wait.
Whatever's so important,
I hope it's worth it.
Hi. I like your tie.
It's very--awkward.
Hi.
Thank you
for meeting me.
Of course,
my baby girl.
Oh, my God.
Ha ha ha!
Are you kidding?
I'm always here for you
as long as there's
no bees around.
No bees.
What--are you ok?
Does the word Ravenspur mean
anything to you?
If this is something
to do with your father, honey--
So it does. I remember the two
of you talking about it.
Not just talk.
It's a--it's a cabin
in Cypress Cove
we used to like to go to.
We'd, you know--we'd
nurse a bottle of wine,
make love
to Lionel Richie.
I was his penny lover.
You know, your father
could go
all night long.
Ok. That's enough.
I don't--
You know what?
Actually, I think you were conceived
in Ravenspur.
Ohh, please make
it stop, please.
No. Seriously, honey.
I want to be serious for a minute.
If this is anything remotely to do
with your father--
Don't worry.
I have it handled.
I wouldn't be
a Jewish mother
if I didn't worry.
Heh.
Baby, what's
that for?
With any luck, you'll never have
to find out.
There's
nothing here.
What, you think he was
gonna put up a sign?
I was thinking more
along the lines
of Ghosts with
automatic weapons.
Maybe we should
have brought our work clothes.
Can I talk to you
about something?
- Yeah.
- I spoke to Lyla.
She's worried
about you because
you said that you shot Andy
in self-defense.
Oliver, I don't want
to talk about this.
You just never said
anything about
self-defense
to me, John.
Couldn't tell Lyla
the truth and have her
look at me
the same way anymore.
Come on.
You don't know that.
Oliver, you're
the last person on earth
to lecture someone
about lying
to the people
they love.
I'm not lecturing.
I'm worried.
You're better
than me at this,
and you're hurting
worse than I have ever seen you.
Don't compound that
by lying
to your wife.
The fact that I lied
to Felicity does not
give me less
credibility.
If anything, it
should tell you
that I know what
I'm talking about.
- Yeah.
- Noah's at a cabin
in Cypress Cove.
We got him.
We're on our way.
You're a hard man
to find, Kuttler.
Come out now.
We'll make it painless.
Make us work for it,
we'll make it last.
I hate it
when they run.
Rahh!
Unh! Agh!
You make me chase
you anymore,
I'm gonna put
a bullet in you.
Isn't that
the plan?
I'm willing to give
you a sporting chance.
I heard about this game while I was
in prison, Mr. Brick.
You let me walk
if I take you down.
Darhk said you was
a smart bloke.
So what do you say?
It's the end of the world
as I understand it.
Don't just
stand there. Get in!
I got him.
Spartan, fall back!
Let's make
this simple.
This isn't
a reconciliation,
this isn't a reunion.
This is you helping me
save the world.
And what makes you
think I can?
Damien Darhk
thinks you can.
That's why he sent
last year's greatest hits
to take you down.
You're a smart man.
I'm assuming you know what Rubicon is.
And I'm assuming it's
under Mr. Darhk's control.
We have 12 hours
to stop it.
That's it?
You seem surprised.
I was expecting
a quid pro quo.
Felicity, I may be
a terrible father...
May?
But I'm not
a monster.
Terrible or not,
I am your father.
As long as you
live in it,
I have an interest
in seeing that
this world
doesn't end.
That said, I do
need something.
Color me shocked.
I can't hack Rubicon
with this setup,
not in the time
we have.
I'm going to need
the quantum subluminal processor
you developed
at Palmer Tech.
How did you even know
that we--
God help me if you are
using the end of days
to steal from my
company again.
I'm an excellent
multitasker,
but you can trust me
this time.
Ms. Smoak.
Oh! Mr. Dennis. Wow!
You must be very desperate for me to
talk to the board
since you brought
security to dragoon me.
These men are not here to take you
to the conference room.
They're here to escort
you out of the building.
Heh.
Excuse me?
The board has
grave concerns
about your plans to
basically give away
the biostimulant implant.
- Mmm.
- They wanted to discuss
the matter with you.
And I will talk
to them.
It's too late
for that.
They voted to
terminate you
effective immediately.
Wow.
Ok. Well, I just need
to grab something,
and I will show
myself out, thank you.
Uh, I'm sorry,
but everything in this lab
is proprietary.
We cannot allow you to leave
with company property.
Excuse me? You have
to be kidding.
I'm very sorry.
I had hoped that this
would end differently.
All right, folks.
You're just moving right on in here.
Have a great day.
Alex?
Hey, you. You ran off
like a crazy person.
Are you feeling
better?
Do you know what's
going on here?
Yeah. Ruvé told me.
Sir, we have
a situation.
Isn't it fantastic?
It is not fantastic.
It's the end
of the world.
No. It's just
the beginning of a new one.
I got into politics
to make a difference, right,
to--to make the world
a better place,
and Ruvé has shown me
that the only way to do that
is to start over.
Just listen to me.
You are under
the influence
of some type
of drug right now,
and we need to
get out of here.
You're just gonna
have to trust me, ok?
Hey. He can trust
you later.
Lonnie Machin is here.
He's killed 5
of Damien's men
that we know about.
There's plenty of ways I can
respond to that,
but I'm gonna go
with good.
He's hitting the co2
scrubbers hours
before nuclear weapons
will render
the atmosphere above us
unbreathable.
If the ark's
life support fails,
we all suffocate.
Who's Lonnie Machin?
Heh. He's kind of
an ex-boyfriend of Thea's.
Damien told me about your special
connection to him.
I need you to help me
put him back in the box,
or we're all dead.
You all right?
Did you get it?
I got fired before I could
take the processor.
I can't even show
my face in there.
Maybe we should call
in a bomb threat,
just empty
the place,
or maybe plant
an actual bomb.
Just a small one,
one that doesn't hurt anybody,
but we have to--
maybe we should
just go in.
It's--ehh--too risky
to wear the gear
in the daylight.
What about the elevator
at the old lair?
Uh-uh. Mr. Dennis
shut it down
after the Larvan
attack.
So John's right.
We'll go in
and help you and your
father boost it from--
It's in Curtis' lab.
You want me to help
my father steal from me?
Well, it's not exactly
yours anymore, is it?
Nope. Guess not.
Door's unlocked.
Give me a count of 3
and then come on in.
Copy that.
I love all this
subterfuge.
Might our guardian angel
be the Green Arrow?
This was a line item
on the budget list,
and it's still
not fixed,
and they have the gall
to fire me.
This is fun,
working together.
Let's make this clear.
This is not a father-daughter
bonding exercise.
Felicity, we have
personnel walking the floor.
You might want to just
go on my signal.
Copy that.
Look. I know I've
done what appears
to be some
terrible things.
You tried to
steal from me.
Are we not stealing
from you now?
No. "A," it's not
my company anymore,
and "B," we're
trying to save the world.
Hey. Didn't I say
go on my signal?
Ok.
Now.
Ahem.
I'm good at solving
binary problems,
but matters
of the heart--
Are not your forte,
and stealing a processor
to save the end
of the world
is not the right time
for this conversation.
On some level,
I've always told myself
I just didn't know
how to be a father
or a husband.
And for a smart guy,
you don't seem to understand
the concept
of not the right time.
I don't know why I tried to steal
your company's tech.
Habit, I suppose,
or something deeper.
Gah! That son of a bitch!
I've been fired
for, like, 45 minutes,
and he's already
locked me out.
You have an electromagnetic
wave generator
and battery tender?
To force the restart.
Yes.
Yes!
Open sesame.
That's it.
Guys, I've got incoming,
northeast stairwell.
On it.
It's under a sublock.
It won't eject.
That never happens unless...
That. We can't leave
without the processor.
- We can if we clone it.
- Your sniffer device.
We can copy the processor's
operating code wirelessly.
More movement.
Felicity, you must have
tripped something
because I have security
coming to the lab right now.
We're running
out of time.
The device
isn't finished.
- Come on.
- It's almost there.
Come on.
Felicity, you have to
get out of there.
Security's inbound.
The R&D lab is secure.
I heard you needed
a lift.
You're the one who
arrested me.
He's not doing
that now.
You get it?
No.
How bad is it?
Kuttler was able to clone
90% of the processor.
He may be able to extrapolate
the remaining 10%
to build us
a workable processor.
I'm gathering parts
for him to work with,
but we're still gonna need to upload
the override codes
to every nuke silo
individually.
Can you do that?
Only from
a server farm.
Mr. Queen!
My men are searching
the woods for my property,
but you chose not
to die with them.
I killed a few
of the stragglers.
My power has grown
beyond your imagining.
Let me show you.
Ohh!
Valiant effort,
Mr. Queen,
but still only mortal.
The primary
scrubber's in here.
I'm betting
Machin is, too.
Well, don't I get
something to fight him with?
I don't think I can
trust you with a weapon
for some reason.
You're just gonna
have to make do
with Krav Maga,
I'm afraid.
Oh, the irony.
All Darhk's parasites
living underground,
breathing the waste product
of sludge.
What happens if I
turn this dial?
Well, if you're not
gonna tell me,
I'm just gonna have to see
for myself.
Step away
from that.
Run along, little girl.
I'm a tad busy
at the moment
trying to kill
everyone here.
I'm not a little girl,
Lonnie.
Remember me?
My name is Thea Queen.
I'm the one that
gave you that face.
Mommy. Ha
I didn't recognize you
without the red leather.
Whatever are you
doing here?
Look. I get it.
You're mad at Darhk
because he screwed
you over,
and now you're
trying to get payback.
I'm not gonna stop
you, ok?
If anything,
I'm gonna help you,
but there are innocent
people here,
people that have
been brainwashed,
and they don't
deserve to die.
Lonnie, don't do this.
I will help you
take down Darhk, ok?
We can do this together.
You just need to get
out of here.
What the hell did you
do that for?
I had him.
No, you didn't.
Explosive charges.
He was gonna blow
the scrubber
no matter
what you said.
Can you disarm it?
We'll soon find out.
Clear!
I'm gonna need
the subnode taken offline.
Ok. I can do that.
I'll cover him.
I'll take care of him.
Get to work.
Nice to meet you.
My daughter certainly
has some very impressive friends.
How long is this
gonna take?
Ideally, less than it takes Mr. Darhk
to nuke the world.
I'm not the man
my daughter thinks, you know?
Don't tell me.
Tell her.
I've tried.
I tried explaining
that there are two sides to me,
the father
and the hacker.
She sees only
the criminal.
I mention this because you strike
me as someone
with experience
leading a dual life.
Any insights
you'd care to share?
Yeah. It doesn't work.
You leading a dual life
is why you lost her.
You sound like you're
talking from some personal experience.
What's that?
Felicity's taken
the subnode offline,
and we've developed
a new problem.
- What?
- Tapeworm in the Rubicon code,
antihack failsafe
courtesy
of your friends
in HIVE.
- Can you override it?
- I just did
but not before
the tapeworm transmitted
this terminal's
location.
Figure we have
about 90 seconds.
- Until what?
- Till HIVE rains all manner
of hell
down on us.
What happened?
HIVE has
our position.
We have maybe a minute
before they arrive.
They're working
on shutting me down,
but I know
a few tricks.
This will go twice as fast
with the two of us.
We'll hold them off
as long as we can.
Establish a perimeter.
Shoot to kill.
I don't need to tell you
what's riding on this.
POTUS and SECDEF have
taken us to DEFCON-2.
Just two?
They're optimistic.
They don't want to
cause a panic.
The president asked me
if the fate of the world
is resting the hands
of an IT girl,
a criminal, and two guys
in Halloween costumes.
They're not
Halloween costumes.
Get the idol!
We got to go!
What about Reiter?
He can't do anything
without the idol.
Come on!
If this is the end
of the world,
I don't mind
going out like this.
Don't you ever stop?
Not when it comes
to my daughter, no.
Alex? Everything's fine.
We took out all
the explosives.
Al--Alex?
Alex, oh, God.
Oh, God. Are you--
Fine? Ok?
Hunk dory?
Believe me,
there is nothing
hunky dory
about screwing up someone's
plan for vengeance
a second time,
which means I've got to wait for
Mr. Darhk to arrive
and go
with plan "B."
It's left me with some time to
kill, so to speak.
Ok. Alex, come one.
Relax. He's fine.
Just taking
a little nap.
What is it
with you?
Why are you always
at the mercy
of some guy?
You can make your
own decisions, Thea.
You're not a pawn.
You're a Queen.
Get it?
Yeah. Yeah, I get it.
Here they come.
That's a lot
of firepower.
We don't need
to beat them.
We just need to buy
Felicity and her father enough time.
Thea?
Alex, get out
of here!
Get away from him!
I'm liberating
you, mommy!
You don't need another man
clouding your mind.
Alex, run!
No!
Alex!
I'm sorry.
I think I got
an algorithm down to 300 lines
for the uplink.
Have you tried to
break the JSI encryption ?
That way, you can
directly bypass the PAL.
Yeah, you're right.
3 minutes till Rubicon
launches the nukes.
Overwatch,
Amar is headed inside.
We're running
out of time.
- Are you hit?
- No!
No, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
What's happening?
We got every nuke
except one.
_
We lost one.
It's in the air.
Headed straight
for Monument Point.
The bullet went through,
but I need you to hold still.
I think we have
more important concerns,
such as preventing
another launch.
I thought you two
stopped Rubicon.
Rubicon knows the missiles
didn't launch.
It keeps trying to
send launch codes.
Which we have to
override manually one by one.
It's kind of like
whack-a-mole.
Except we don't get
a stuffed animal if we win.
Is it true?
There's one
in the air?
Headed straight
for Monument Point.
- Can you override?
- That is what I'm trying to do
while Noah keeps
the missiles in their silos.
We need to start
evacuations.
There's not enough time
to get everyone out.
This is Argus director
Lyla Michaels.
I'm reporting
an Endtime event.
Target is Monument Point.
Felicity.
I'm trying to hack
their navigation systems.
What's that?
Another hit in the Ley line
algorithm I set up.
I cross-referenced it
with news reports and--
the mayor's office
just evacuated city hall
due to a gas leak.
Like you said, why
would Darhk's wife run
for mayor of a city
he wants to destroy?
To gain access
to city hall
for this exact moment.
The Nexus chamber must
be beneath that building.
If he's hiding where
he should be hiding
to absorb the power
of a nuke attack.
Let's go.
You need to divert
that missile.
You are lucky I'm too busy to come up
with a witty response
to that right now.
Stop. Stop!
Unh!
Taiana, are you ok?
Are you hurt?
Something's...
Got it!
Mostly.
- What?
- Sent the remaining
launch algorithms
into an infinite loop.
Should buy the world 24 hours,
give or take.
What about the nuke
headed to Monument Point?
It's stubborn.
There's a reason why these things
were designed to be
impossible to move off course,
which is why I have to move
Monument Point instead.
GPS realignment.
What do you mean?
As a prank, I once
relocated a GPS satellite.
Everyone on
the eastern seaboard
thought they were 20 miles west of
their actual location.
Do that to the missile, you
avoid a direct hit.
That's it.
Direct hit
on Havenrock.
Maximum yield.
How many casualties?
Tens of thousands.
Monument Point would
have been a couple million, Felicity.
Damn it. We searched
everywhere.
Hello, Oliver. Nice timing.
I think you're gonna need
much bigger arrows.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.