My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But I couldn't honor that commitment
and honor the promise I made
to the mother of my son.
So I asked the best man I know
to help.
His name is John Diggle,
and he is the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Our old friend, Alex Faust.
Okay, clearly, he was at SCPD
when the explosion went off.
- So he either died or escaped.
- He escaped.
Special Agent Samanda Watson.
Can we help you with something?
I'm here as a courtesy to inform you
of the investigation
I'll be conducting in your city.
- Investigation into what?
- You.
The present us is only worried about
you quitting your
nobody-told-you-about job.
When are you gonna let that go?
- When you go into business with me.
- I'm sorry. Go into what with you?
- Think about all the good we could do.
- Yes.
On Lian Yu, Felicity and I got caught
in one of the explosions.
- I thought you guys were fine.
- I have nerve damage.
That's why you haven't been
pulling your gun.
It's just a tremor,
I can manage it.
You nearly got killed last night
because you couldn't rely on me.
But what are you gonna do about it?
Tell Oliver.
Eyes on Faust.
Shoot her!
I got him.
He's in the structure next door.
Everyone, get into position.
- Copy that.
- On it, hoss.
You got it.
Hurry! Hurry!
Down for the count.
No more bombs for you, bitch.
Go, Green Arrow.
Should I call you the Green Arrow?
It feels kinda weird.
It's weird.
But, at some point,
we all have to get used to it.
Seemed to go well out there tonight.
Yeah, we make a good team.
And yet you still have worried face.
Because sooner or later,
someone is gonna find out
that the Green Arrow
isn't shooting any arrows.
Yeah, well, Curtis and I
are working on that.
We're gonna figure something out.
Good. Thank you.
Okay.
I'm gonna go home.
I'm going to sleep,
and maybe I'll even get four hours.
Maybe in another week,
I'll get used to that
judgmental stare you keep giving me.
This isn't judgment.
It's amusement.
"Sooner or later
someone's gonna find out
"the Green Arrow
isn't shooting any arrows."
Dinah, I'm not an archer.
No, it's not about the arrows, John,
it's about the injury.
Thought you were
gonna talk to Oliver.
I was.
Until he asked me to put this on.
Which he never would have done
if he knew the truth.
Dinah, what do you want from me?
The man's under the FBI microscope,
he's worried about his son.
Imagine how worried he would be if he
knew you were out there compromised.
Did you see me tonight?
Did I look compromised?
Dinah, I have this handled.
The tremor's gone.
Well, I guess I worried
for nothing, then.
Good morning.
Morning.
You like your eggs scrambled, right?
Yes, I do.
Good. It's what I made you.
This is for real, for real, isn't it?
Me being around more?
And not the other guy.
It is for real, for real.
That's cool with you?
Yeah.
Good.
What you got there?
Math.
Big test later this week.
Yeah, I know
what it's like switching schools.
Don't worry about it,
you'll get there.
Not by the end of this week.
I will be lucky to get a C.
Nothing wrong with getting a C
every once in a while.
I used to get Ds,
I would've been psyched for a C.
You don't get it.
Buddy, I'm kidding.
I think if you relax
a little more, it'll come easier.
I got to study. Can I be excused?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey. You all right?
Yeah. No. William is stressing
over a test.
I tried to be supportive,
but I feel like I just...
Making it worse.
I feel your pain.
That was Dinah's department.
I don't know what I would've done
parenting alone.
Uh... I mean,
you'll figure it out, though.
Thank you.
Agent Watson, I do not believe
you're on my schedule.
I think you'll come to find
I really don't give a damn.
Okay.
Your office issued a statement
on last night's apprehension
of Alex Faust.
We did. He was apprehended
by the Green Arrow.
And I'm sure you have
an airtight alibi for last night.
Rockets game with my kid.
We were on the jumbotron.
And only an idiot
of the highest order
would be fooled by someone else
running around in that hood.
Whoever your understudy is,
he might want to brush up
on his archery.
Or did you think we didn't notice
that no arrows were used
in taking down Faust?
- Are you done? Okay.
- I'm not.
Whether I can prove
you're the Green Arrow,
there's no question
you support him as mayor.
You're known to protect and
communicate with him and his team.
Is that a crime?
No.
But you're sending a message
to the police of this city
that they can't do their job
without vigilante help.
I'm glad I don't work for you.
She's not wrong.
About the "Glad she don't
work for me" part?
Or the "Nobody is buying
John in the hood" part?
The "undercutting the cops" part.
I know they're not enough
for this city,
but they never will be
if we keep saying it.
Well, it's a catch-22, Quentin.
I mean,
can you try to find a solution?
Yeah. I'll try.
Thank you.
It would be nice to have something
before John and the team
have to get back in the field.
Hey, I'll be back in five.
Uh...
Guys?
Yeah, we heard you. You'll be...
What the...
Officer Lopez.
Hope you don't own
any Kord Industries stock.
My pension fund does.
Though it seems a little crass
to worry about that now.
What do we got?
The vics all died of broken vertebrae
or blunt force trauma.
- Forensics?
- Not even a fingerprint.
And speaking of, the UnSub used
one of the vics' palm prints
to gain access
into Kord's internal server.
- To get what?
- The company doesn't know yet.
I'm gonna need a chat with the CEO.
In the meantime,
I'm gonna take a look around here.
You get all that?
Yeah. And a bag of chips.
Sorry, I didn't get a chance
to eat breakfast this morning,
I'm feeling a little peckish.
Ten will get you 20, the Kord CEO
won't tell you anything.
Can you access the server?
Already here. Now what?
Okay, you're looking
for a master port.
Female with a yellow border.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Insert our toy
and let us do our thang.
You keep saying "thing" wrong.
All right, we're in.
Curtis has got it from here.
- You going somewhere?
- I got start-up work to do.
Yeah, we're still trying
to decide on our name.
Hey, so I think I have a solution
to our cops' catch-22.
That was fast.
I was chatting
with Councilwoman Pollard.
She is in the early stages
of drafting
some anti-vigilante legislation.
- No.
- Hear me out.
If you were to join it, sponsor it...
Still no.
You could tailor the bill
to however you want it.
You could take the teeth out of it,
so it can't bite the team too hard.
Okay, first,
Pollard is not a pushover,
so we know this isn't true.
Second, I am not going
to put John in a hood
and then actively support legislation
that furthers brands him as a criminal.
Find another way. Please.
- Hi.
- Hey.
City Hall is six blocks that way.
I thought maybe you could
use a late afternoon snack.
Who are you, my mother?
I mean, that's not even accurate.
My mother rarely remembered
to pick me up from school,
let alone make me a snack.
- May I come in?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I, uh, love what you've done
with the place.
Yeah, well, you know,
it's near impossible to find
affordable office space in the city,
someone should
talk to the mayor about that.
Oh, speaking of, how do you feel
about the name,
"Bit By Bit"?
Sounds like a sitcom from the '80s.
Great. That's like,
really not what we're going for.
Well, who knew, when you stopped
balancing being vigilante
with everything else, that you
would have time to drop off snacks.
Speaking of, how is William,
now that you're done pulling double
vigilante daddy duty?
It's a two-steps forward,
one-step backwards sort of thing.
I was just thinking I would really love
to be able to lean on Thea.
But, um...
I mean, she just has a knack
for this sort of thing.
Yeah, she would be
the most badass aunt ever.
Would she ever.
Well, I know I'm not Thea,
but I'm so down to help
in any way you need.
Well, truth be told,
aside from snacks,
- I do sort of need your help.
- Ah.
William has a math test
later this week
that he is really
stressing out over and, um...
Every time I open my mouth,
I'm making it worse.
So the man who took down Damien Darhk
is bested by arithmetic.
Wasn't my strongest subject
in school.
No? What was? Truancy?
Charm.
Yeah, no doubt.
Let me guess, you told him
something along the lines of,
"Just relax, I would've been psyched
to get a C, all I got was Fs."
Ds, I mean, most...
How did you know that?
'Cause I know you,
and I know that if you
even cared about school,
you would've been good at it.
- Thank you.
- Nothing would grind my gears more
when I was his age when my mom was
just telling me to stop worrying
when I was freaking out
about a project.
- Why?
- I didn't need to learn how to relax,
I needed to figure out
how to do the work.
So what do I do when...
Well, ask him...
Ask him what he needs and then
put him in the driver's seat
and he'll show you how to help him.
You make things so simple.
Always have.
- Curtis?
- No wonder Kord doesn't like
to share their secrets.
They invent
a lot of really nasty stuff.
Including this new military-grade
nerve gas, ZX.
What's that have to do
with our mystery killer woman?
She downloaded the transport schedule
for said nerve gas.
Do you find that alarming
or is it just me?
No, I definitely find that alarming.
- When is it moving?
- One hour.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Alert the Green Arrow.
I mean, Diggle,
I mean, John, I mean...
It's just good OPSEC
to use code names in the field.
I agree.
Go.
If you're not gonna say anything,
at least turn on the damn radio.
With your presets,
I prefer the silence.
Just turn it on.
Children of Aquarius
Your world is my world...
It's not safe on the road.
That's what he's for.
My team's more equipped.
...Children of Aquarius
Your dream is my dream...
You have horrible taste in music.
- Why are we slowing down?
- I don't know.
Stay here.
Overwatch.
Any bogies on thermal?
Just you guys.
And I'm guessing you're not bogies.
What's going on, guys?
Why aren't you moving?
Trying to find out right now.
Perfect. Ignition blocker.
Surprise, bitch.
Careful. Bullets
and bioweapons don't mix.
Your friend's right.
Lead is in the cab, hoss.
Go after her or the gas?
Or both?
They're getting away, hoss.
Make a decision.
Screw this.
Couldn't get to it.
Couldn't stop her.
Wasn't your fault.
What the hell happened out there?
Ask him. Dude just froze.
- Casualties?
- No. Everyone got out.
A dozen people were sent
to the hospital for smoke inhalation,
and two are in critical condition.
What the hell, hoss?
There were two targets and two of us,
what was so freaking complicated?
I don't know.
This never happened to me
in the field before.
Not in the army
and not with this team.
Fog of war.
Things don't always
go perfect out there,
so we close ranks and we move on.
Thanks.
It won't happen again.
Okay.
Good, 'cause it looks like you guys
get another shot at these guys.
Facial recog came back with a match.
Onyx Adams.
Leader of a CIA black ops squad
working undercover in Syria.
They disappeared in 2015 with
100 million dollars
in Syrian government gold.
And what have they been doing since?
My guess is preparing
for the ZX gas heist.
And finding the tech
they need to do it.
Why weren't they blinded
by the flashbangs like we were?
Also, if these guys got away
with 100 million in gold,
why would they risk it
by trying to steal nerve gas?
See if you can pick up any chatter
on the dark web,
encrypted message boards, whatever,
I'll check with Lyla.
See if any intel has changed.
Also, I'm sorry about tonight.
That wasn't me.
Hey, when I said move on...
I meant you, too.
Fortunately, the two victims
in critical condition
are expected to recover.
Multiple witnesses
spotted Green Arrow
and his team
of vigilantes at the scene.
Becky, can you get the
fire chief's latest report, please?
And can...
Would you mind putting in an order
for some coffee?
One of the big boxes
of coffee, please.
Thank you.
So I guess being the Green Arrow
involves something
of a learning curve.
We don't know the circumstances
surrounding last night.
Yeah, but we know
how it's gonna play out.
What do you mean?
Wow. Speak of the devil.
Got to admire her sense of timing.
- Who?
- Pollard.
She's seizing the moment.
She's using last night's disaster
as a pretext to introduce her
anti-vigilante legislation
to the council.
- Does she have the votes?
- I don't know.
Can you make sure she doesn't?
Hey.
Can we talk for a second?
I just wanted to say thank you
for having my back with the team.
Now truth be told, I...
I was a bit surprised
considering you...
Don't be surprised.
And don't think I said
what I said for you.
I said it because this team
needs a leader.
Without a chain of command,
we're easy pickings out there.
Okay.
I guess this is why you decided
not to tell anyone
about my injury, right?
It is.
But, honestly, as worried as I am
about your hand,
after last night, I'm a little more
worried about your head.
I know.
Hey, Dinah.
Look...
Every time I've had to give orders
in the army,
on this team,
there is always someone there
backing my plays.
I'm not used to making
the hard calls alone.
No one is more disappointed in me
than me.
Well, next time, get it right.
Our lives depend on it.
She shoots, she scores.
What do we have?
Okay, these are our new friends
back in 2015.
But last night,
you said there were five.
You think when their leader
went rogue,
not everyone went with her.
Well, Wild Dog for the win.
Three of the original members
defected back to the CIA,
for a little while, at least.
What do you mean,
"for a little while"?
'Cause this guy and this guy
were both killed
in separate poison gas attacks
last year.
One in Mosul, one in Tripoli.
The video footage is... Is...
It's really gruesome.
Well, poison gas
can't be a coincidence.
No. I mean, ISIS is linked
to both of them,
but I'm sure this is how
Onyx likes to solves her problems.
So she staged two terrorist attacks
just to settle a grudge?
No, notjust a grudge.
These are the only two
that can pin her to the stolen gold.
- Bingo.
- Right.
So she's wiping out defectors.
Got one left, Rob Reynolds,
whereabouts unknown.
Yeah, but you got to figure Star City
or somewhere close by.
Well, I'm guessing we should worry
what this gas could
do to a populated area.
Oh, yeah.
Look.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hi.
How's it going?
Fine.
Still worried about the test?
Yeah.
Anything that I can do to help?
Do you know quadratic equations?
Wow! Um...
Those sound... Vaguely familiar.
Then again, I wasn't the most
enthusiastic math student, so...
I really shouldn't be talking to
anyone who can't help me right now.
Okay.
Got a minute, hoss?
Sure.
This about Pollard's bill?
No, uh, sorry.
I've been out of the office.
No, this is about John.
What about him?
It's not working out.
You talking about last night?
I'm talking about something...
I'm talking about something
a hell of a lot worse
than what happened last night.
That poison gas could kill thousands.
John can handle it.
That's why I'm here, hoss.
He can't.
He's in over his head.
We're lucky nobody died last night.
But luck runs out.
We need you to come back.
I'm still working
on a 20 with Reynolds.
It's gonna take a while,
these black op guys
are really hard to find.
Hey.
Wow... Just surprised
to see you here.
And also surprised
that you remember the access code.
It's been like a week.
Yeah, it was a joke.
- Okay.
- I'm guessing you're here for...
Well, yeah. And the guy that you're
searching for, this Reynolds.
- Yeah.
- Couldn't Curtis handle it?
Yeah, I'm sure he can.
Why? What do you need?
Well, I asked William what he needs,
and he needs a tutor.
Well, lucky for you and for him,
you're looking at Nevada's
three-time State Mathletics Champion.
Only three times?
Yeah, they wouldn't
let freshmen enter.
It was an ordeal.
I got over it but still kinda hurts.
This can't interfere
with an operation.
No, we're in a holding pattern.
I'm sure Curtis can come
and cover me.
I might have to leave abruptly,
but other than that, yeah, no,
it's not a problem.
Well, I'll probably see you
back there. I'm gonna...
Okay, yeah. Okay, yeah.
Yeah, I'll call Curtis.
He'll be here soon.
Okay. Okay, bye, bye.
This is weird.
Being back down here?
How many times have you
come down here to find me brooding?
I'm not brooding, Oliver,
I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Okay, maybe I'm brooding
a little bit.
Well, if you haven't
figured it out already,
that expression is as much a part
of the uniform as the green hood.
Every time you were
down here brooding,
it was because you made
some kind of mistake.
I think you made
another one, man.
No.
Not even close.
Who came to you? Rene?
I needed to come
and ask Felicity a favor.
And then, of course, I saw that very
familiar expression.
Makes me wonder
if maybe I asked too much of you.
What do you mean?
I gave up being
the Green Arrow for William.
But...
You have JJ, you have Lyla,
it doesn't exactly seem fair...
That's not the issue at all, Oliver.
I made my peace with
this whole life a long time ago.
So what's the problem?
I don't know how you did it.
You never hesitated to make the call.
You were always sure, I'm not.
I was never sure.
Not one time.
I'm very flattered that it looked
that way on the outside,
but on the inside, it was...
It was instinct, it was instinct
and it was fear.
Yeah, but you worked past it.
Well, you'll work past it too.
Now, I'm not gonna sit here
and say that you won't
make mistakes, that you won't
lose people along the way,
you know most...
Most will be strangers but some...
Well, some won't be.
Because, John,
you're one of the main reasons
that the Green Arrow even exists.
What are you talking about?
The Restons.
- The bank robbers?
- The bank robbers, yeah.
You were the first person
who convinced me to look
past just the names
on my father's list.
You helped me discover that the hood,
that persona,
he wasn't a hero,
you helped me find one.
All of this, the Green Arrow,
the idea of it,
it exists because you had
faith in me.
Now you got to have
the same kind of faith in yourself.
'Cause if you do,
you can be a better leader,
you can be a better hero
than I ever was.
- Sit Rep.
- Good to go.
Any doubts?
You ask that each time.
Because we are going after
our brothers-in-arms.
Comrades.
I need your resolve.
You got it.
And tonight, Reynolds gets his.
Roger that.
What about the Green Arrow?
What about him?
You've seen him in the field.
Being highly trained operators,
would you consider him a threat?
- Hell, no.
- There's your answer.
Move out.
Okay, and after you divide by X?
Solve for X?
Yes, but first...
Is it factor the binomials?
Yeah, right. Cool.
But why can't I just solve for X?
Well, you will, I mean, eventually,
probably in high school, but,
first you have to master
the binomials.
Well, I'm gonna bomb this.
You know, it sucks
because you're new and
probably a little behind. But...
The fact that you're frustrated means
you can see how useful
math could be,
which means, unfortunately,
you're really good at it.
Oliver said school doesn't matter
in the real world.
Hmm. Well, Oliver didn't grow up
School changed my life.
I used to love school.
Yeah.
You will again. Promise.
How is it going in here?
- Good.
- Yeah, I'd say we're
- making progress.
- Good.
Could you tutor me some more
before the test?
Yeah, I mean, if it's cool
with your dad, it's cool with me.
If it's cool with you,
it's totally cool with me.
Special delivery.
Okay,
that's not grilled cheese.
No, it's not grilled cheese,
those are Monte Cristos.
What's a Monte Cristo?
What? You've never had...
This is the best night-time snack
you can ever have.
- And you used waffles.
- Well...
That is how we do it
in the not-real world.
Ha.
Curtis got a location
on Reynolds.
We got to... Well, I got to go.
This is... Without you. It's weird.
Best of luck out there.
Oh, I'll be in the bunker if it is.
- William, you're awesome.
- Thank you.
See you soon.
She is pretty cool.
Yeah, she is.
Traffic cams picked up
Reynolds heading north on Hillcrest,
the only things out there
are souvenirs and Haselby Grand.
Hotels are a great place for
an ex-spook to stash a gold bag.
Try to slip out
with the tourist crowd.
Huh. Makes you wonder if
his old crew tipped him off
or if he's just the luckiest target
in the world.
Either way, there are
hundreds of people in that hotel,
- so if they disperse the gas...
- They won't.
Let's move out.
Did he forget to say "Suit up"?
Or was "Let's move"
like, his version of "Suit up"?
Because, personally, I like "Let's
suit up" 'cause then you know...
- Go suit up, Curtis.
- Yeah, I'll go suit up.
Hey, hey.
Can you handle this?
I asked Oliver to come back.
Well, the fact that he didn't
should tell you something, right?
Maybe. Look, all I know for sure,
if John doesn't
straighten himself out,
it's gonna be another rough night.
- I got eyes on the tango.
- Roger that.
Package is deployed.
What do we know, Overwatch?
Lots.
Thermal reads a potential
166 casualties inside
and Onyx's team cut the CCTV.
So we're going in blind.
Literally, if we get hit with
those flashbangs of hers again.
Your dorky ass glasses better work.
Hello?
What's going on? The door's locked.
I have visuals, thanks to
Mr. Terrific's T-Spheres. Go now.
We need locations on Reynolds
and the gas.
I have him. Upper lobby.
But I got no way
of detecting the gas.
Canary, Terrific,
see if you can locate the gas.
Dog, you're with me on evac
after we clear Reynolds.
I really hope
he's not making decisions
based on animal code names.
Incoming!
All right, hoss,
let's check these out.
Guys, you got two hostiles
in the lobby.
Guess your old tricks don't work.
I don't need tricks.
Just collateral.
No.
Onyx just released
the gas. What should we do?
Gas is spreading, do you copy?
Arrow? Arrow, do you copy?
Handle the gas.
We've got Reynolds, move.
Gas is coming from the trashcan.
Everybody, get behind me now.
Get behind me now.
I'm going after Reynolds.
Night-night.
Overwatch, we need a way
to neutralize the nerve gas.
You could burn it,
but I don't suggest it
since you're still
inside the building.
We won't be for long. I hope.
The breaches are too small
to evacuate all these people.
Which is why we're gonna
make them bigger.
Going somewhere?
I wasn't gonna tell anyone
about the gold.
You know, it turns out
money can buy happiness.
Just can't buy peace of mind.
You all right?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the Green Arrow.
I got one of Onyx's flashbangs,
should be enough to ignite the gas.
Okay, everyone,
when I count to three,
that wall is going bye-bye,
so I need you all to haul ass.
There is nerve gas
followed by a huge explosion.
I don't think they
need the motivation.
Good point.
One...
Two...
Three.
Gas dispersed.
All civilians accounted for.
Good work.
The other four are down.
Onyx is in the limo.
What about this guy?
He helped steal millions in foreign
gold and turned a blind eye
when his comrades were being
killed off of fake terrorist attacks.
It was good work back there.
Following your lead, hoss.
Can we do this after every win?
New tradition for a new era,
I like that.
To go with our new
Team Arrow victory dance.
Didn't know we had an old one.
We don't, never will.
Things won't be changing around here
that much.
Look...
There is something you should know.
You went to Oliver.
- You told him.
- She didn't have to.
I know you, Rene.
I know all of you.
It's a leader's job to.
Oh, yes.
So, Curtis and I have been
working on a little something
in our spare time,
very limited spare time, may I add.
We call it...
The Green Monster.
Or something cooler than that,
pretty much whatever
you want to call it.
The important part is that it shoots
arrows instead of crossbow bolts.
260 pound draw weight,
the arrows exit the gate at 400FPS,
that's feet per second.
Integrated recoil
energy dissipation system.
Adjustable mount, scope,
quick detach quivers,
pistol grip, finger guard,
non-slip rubber insert.
Do you two want a moment alone?
You want to take it for a spin?
Damn, hoss.
Did you guys put stabilizers
on that crossbow?
Nope. That aim there
is pure John Diggle.
Not a bad idea, though,
for the next upgrade.
Nice going.
Steady.
See? Told you. Tremor's gone.
Well, I'm convinced.
You were wrong
about one thing, though.
What's that?
You can make the hard calls
on your own just fine.
Thank you.
Hey.
So your friends did good last night.
I had a feeling
John would get it together.
How did you manage?
Too many councilmen owe Pollard
too many favors.
It's gonna pass, Oliver.
We'll veto it.
You got enough PR problems as it is,
don't you think?
Besides, they've got enough votes
for an override.
There has to be something
that we can do.
Matter of fact...
Let the record show there are no nays
on the anti-vigilante measure.
Those in favor.
Point of order.
Does it address
the matter at hand, Mr. Mayor?
It does, Madam Parliamentarian.
Thank you.
And good morning.
As you know, I have been accused
of a great many things recently.
Including but not limited
to supporting vigilantes
at the expense
of our men and women in uniform.
This was never my intention.
In the wake of the attacks
on the SCPD,
putting this police force
back on its feet
is my number one priority as mayor.
We need the women and men of the SCPD
on our streets protecting us,
but they can't do that
if they are busy hunting vigilantes.
That is why I oppose this bill,
and that is why I am invoking
chapter 9 of the City Charter.
And you are aware that will convert
Councilwoman Pollard's bill
to a citywide referendum.
I certainly am.
Because last night,
a group of vigilantes
saved hundreds of lives.
So if we are going to decide
on diverting police resources
towards stopping them,
we are not gonna do that until
the people of Star City have spoken.
What the hell was that?
Stay of execution.
The mayor's procedural maneuver
took both the Council
and the public by surprise.
How the public will decide
on the issue of vigilantism
is anyone's guess.
According to multiple reports,
the City Council was set to pass
strict measures against
the Green Arrow and his team.
This anti-vigilante legislation
was introduced...
Who are you protecting?
Oliver.
- With a gift.
- You busy?
No, um...
No, I... Come in.
I was just working
on a name for the startup
which would be a lot easier
if Curtis and I actually knew
what we were trying to start up.
You know,
"That's tomorrow's problem."
Is it my birthday?
William got an A on his test.
Oh, he did? Oh, that's awesome.
I mean, I knew he would,
he is super smart,
his understanding of math
is at prodigy level, much...
Like me at his age.
Can you believe he's your son?
I didn't mean it...
That's not what I meant. I mean...
Math isn't everything.
I mean, you have, you have so many
redeeming qualities, you know,
you have amazing abs and...
I'm just gonna open this.
- Please.
- If it's okay.
Hmm.
It's a key to my apartment.
Okay.
Um...
Won't that be confusing for William?
I mean, it sure as hell
is confusing for me.
I know that when I took William in,
we agreed that we would
keep our distance because
he was gonna have a lot to process.
- He's still got a lot to process.
- Yes, he does.
Every day there's a new challenge.
I sense a "but" coming,
there is a "but" coming, right?
But I saw you with him.
And I became 100% sure that...
If you want...
His life
will be better
with you in it.
Just like mine.
Are you sure
that's what you want?
I'm sure.