Previously on "Arrow"...
So my brother's
a Ghost?
10 years ago, I found
out you were dealing.
Yeah. You convinced
me to enlist.
John, voice-over: You saw what kind
of man my brother was,
what kind of man he is.
He's your family.
You said he was a good man.
Maybe part of him
still is.
I don't know.
Get down.
The damage
to her spinal cord, it's permanent.
She's never gonna
walk again.
If we don't get
home soon,
the sitter's gonna
charge us an extra hour.
We should have
taken the car.
Sitter's what, another 15 bucks
for half an hour?
It's a bargain
at twice the price.
Lyla.
- Dear God.
- Alan?
Sorry to crash
your evening.
Then don't. Just call
like normal people.
I don't have
a normal job,
and I've been compromised.
I'm not Argus
anymore.
Which makes you
the only person I can trust.
I need you to
tell Waller--
Get down!
-You're hit!
-Ugh.
Alan!
Unh!
Johnnie!
Are you ok?
You were right.
We should have taken
the car.
♪ Arrow 4x11 ♪
A.W.O.L.
Original Air Date on January 27, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Just be careful.
Slow down, slow down.
Careful, careful, careful.
Do you want me
to be careful?
Oh, this is more
Oliver 2.0, isn't it?
You think being cute
is gonna distract me?
Mission
accomplished.
You don't
have to wait on me
hand and foot,
though I wouldn't say
no to a blanket.
The doctor says
stick
with the two tablets
to keep with your
current
pain management
regimen.
You know, I really
appreciate what you're doing,
but you have
a city to save,
a mayoral campaign,
a freaky superbad
who can move things
with his mind.
None of which are
nearly as important
as your recovery.
Thank you.
I think the people
in the city
that Darhk wants to
destroy might disagree.
Well, those people
should know that
I stand no chance
of stopping Damien Darhk
without your help.
Well, you might
have to.
I have a spinal cord injury.
I might never make
a full recovery ever.
That is worst case
scenario,
and either way,
you are still
a vital member
of the team.
Your superpower
is right there.
Maybe my new code name
could be Hot Wheels.
Keep pitching on that.
All jokes aside,
like you said,
what I do bring
to the team is my mind,
and there's a lot
on it.
So talk to me.
I just don't think
I'm ready to come back yet,
and the last thing
you need
in a life-or-limb
situation is me.
Wow. We are going to
agree to disagree
on that one
for the moment.
What's going on?
John and Lyla
were attacked.
Oh, my God!
Are they ok?
John was shot.
It was a flesh wound.
I should go see them.
We should go see them.
Nice try.
Dinner is in the fridge.
Reheat in the oven
at 425 degrees.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And they just
left you there?
Yeah, but not before
leaving me with this.
We are sure that
this wasn't HIVE?
These men looked
military.
Right, but you said that Chang
said he was compromised,
and he specifically told you
to go and speak with Waller.
Knowing her, she had
Alan working
on something
off the books.
I need to call
the sitter.
Ok.
We need to find
Chang before
this kidnapping
becomes something worse.
Yeah, well, the van didn't
have any plates on them,
and Chang's phone is
Argus-issued,
which means it will be
untraceable.
We could really use
Felicity's help right now.
Yeah. She's not
up for it yet.
I can have SCPD
see if John's bullet
is connected to any
open cases.
Yeah.
I can go check
the crime scene
for any leftover
evidence.
You should go
to Starling General
and have that
looked at.
I'll be fine.
Why? Because eating
a cheeseburger
is a better option?
This isn't for me.
It's for Andy.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
Hey. What happened
to your arm?
Nothing. It's
an occupational hazard.
I never pegged you
for the masked vigilante type.
Yeah? Well, I guess
we're both full of surprises, Andy.
You know what?
You keep coming down here,
asking me
all these questions,
but I never get
to ask them back.
What do you want
to know?
Uh, how do you end up
working out of a basement
or wherever we are
and fighting crime
with a guy
who wears
a green hoodie?
Well, he's
a good man,
and we're not
fighting crime, Andy.
We're taking a city
that's holding itself together,
and we are helping.
Don't you remember
when that was your mission?
Appreciate you two
volunteering for this mission.
Chance to ride
with my little brother?
Wouldn't miss it.
Yeah. The Taliban's
not ready
for the Diggle brothers.
HQ's got eyes on
a primo opium shipment
that's been funding the local
arms trade.
We cut them off,
the terrorists
will be left
with nothing but
rocks and sticks
to fight us.
Copy that, sir.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
Incoming.
Stay frosty, boys.
Copy that.
RPG!
Perimeter!
Go! Go, go, go!
Move, move,
move, move, move!
We're screwed if
they come around the other side.
I'll see if I can
buy us some time.
Move, move.
I have to draw
them to it.
I got you.
I'll cover.
Come on,
come on, come on!
It's in!
Andy!
Hey!
Talk to me, man.
You ok?
Did we get them?
You got them, brother.
Let's go.
Aw. Why didn't I
get invited to this pity party?
Hello?
At least you found
the right party favors.
3 pills is a bit much,
but who am I to judge?
Ok. Whoever you are,
you picked
the wrong woman
on the wrong night to mess with.
Please.
We both know
you're in no position
to do anything.
If you did, you'd be
back out in the world
instead of holed up here.
Oh, my God.
What is going on?
Oh, my God. Ha ha!
Oh, my God.
I am losing it.
I am completely
and utterly losing it.
Agh! Now I'm talking
to myself.
Not exactly.
Laurel Lance,
district attorney's office.
What do we
have here?
Deceased male,
around 35, Asian,
multiple lacerations,
contusions,
and blunt force trauma.
You canvass
the area yet?
There could be
a witness who saw something.
I don't need an ADA to
tell me how to do my job.
Well, I'm sure
there's a murderer
out there who appreciates your
lack of initiative.
Ahem.
Go ahead.
Private security
found him
at the start of
a graveyard shift.
That's Chang.
Whoever did this
took their time.
Multiple lacerations
to the knees,
a broken arm,
at least 3 pulled fingernails.
They were torturing
him for something.
Information wasn't
the only thing they wanted.
I told you. What Agent Chang
was working on
is none of your concern,
and it's even less of yours.
Thought would change once you
found out Chang was mutilated,
tortured, and killed.
I'm afraid you've overextended
your welcome, Mr. Diggle.
Which is Argus-speak for
get the hell out of here.
You always were
a quick study.
I mean this
with all sincerity.
Your presence has
truly been missed.
Even if I don't show it,
I am deeply regretful
for Mr. Chang's death.
Hopefully we'll
meet again
under happier
circumstances.
Of course.
Hey. What was that
look all about?
"Ketorolac. Possible
side effects include
"swelling of the hands
and feet,
increased appetite,
risk of infection."
Oh, good, good, good.
Hallucinations.
I really thought
I was smarter than this.
You are not me,
and you're definitely not real.
I used to be you,
or you used to be me--
strong, confident,
brunette--
but you wasted
all that away to go play superhero,
and look where
that got you.
Ok. So wait.
This Waller person said
that she couldn't
tell you anything
and then gave you
that flash drive?
Argus has 24/7
internal surveillance.
She didn't want anyone
to know she was giving me
what she was giving me.
The question is
what did she give you?
I've seen
that symbol before.
It's a logo actually.
Shadowspire is a U.S. army
special forces unit.
Argus took them down
3 years ago
when they were exposed
as war profiteers
in an Op run
by Alan Chang.
What about those
other two guys?
They've been reported
missing for two days.
If those were
the missing agents
that were a part
of Shadowspire, then--
then the rest of Shadowspire
is gonna be
on a payback mission.
We need to find
the other two agents
before they end up
like Alan.
Hey. I think
I found something.
That logo that was on the flash drive
that Waller gave you.
Shadowspire.
I thought I recognized
that from someplace.
I ran into alot of those guys back
in the 'Stan.
I need to talk
to my brother again.
Who would think
the reward for confiscating
an opium shipment would be
additional duty guarding it?
What you expect,
a kiss from the president?
How are my two
conquering heroes?
Wet and tired.
We are good, sir.
You gentlemen
did good today.
Thank you, sir.
Ever think
about your future
beyond working
in this hell hole?
I don't know.
Personal security,
bodyguarding maybe.
You boys are meant
for better things.
The 3 of us could
make bank
if a few bricks of that sweet
Afghani powder
happened to go AWOL
before the morning.
You know, I'm gonna
have to decline, sir.
My mama taught me
never to trust dirty war profiteers.
You should probably
watch your tone.
You might end up
in worse shape than
those Talis
yesterday.
As you were.
- Well, look at you.
- What you talking about?
Back in Starling, you would have jumped
at any opportunity
to earn a little
extra scratch.
This place has been
good for you.
I'm proud of you, Andy.
So exactly how many
evil organizations
are you associated
with?
I'm beginning
to lose count.
What are you
talking about?
Shadowspire!
Your old army
buddies are in Starling City.
Have them to
thank for this.
They tortured and killed
an Argus agent
and abducted
two others.
Look. I have nothing
to do with them anymore.
After I got discharged,
they cut ties.
They only want
enlisted men.
How the hell could
I not see this?
You were with me
the entire time!
Because you saw
what you wanted to see.
Look. You wanted to believe
that the army
had straightened me out.
Look. I'm your brother,
but I'm not
built like you.
I didn't take to the military
like you did.
You saw the world
as something to be fixed.
I only saw it as broken,
so I made sure
I had enough
to survive in it.
So you pretended
to be
a completely
different person
around your
own brother?
It spared me the look that's
on your face right now.
But maybe some good
could come out of this.
Andy...
What are you
talking about?
The two missing agents--
you still think
they're alive?
- I can hope.
- And I can help.
Look. I know how
Shadowspire operates.
If they're consistent,
they'll use
the nearest freeport
as a base of operations.
The best place to hide
illicit things
is right next
to legitimate ones.
It's called
a freeport
it holds commodities
while they're in transit
between international
destinations.
Pretty low-end.
Looks like
somebody upgraded
their security system.
Motion sensors,
laser tripwires,
digital locks.
I think I know somebody
who can help.
Not gonna get that?
Smart move.
Oliver?
I'm out in
the field actually.
We've come up
against some tech,
the kind that you
typically eat for breakfast.
Now I know that you
said you're not
ready to get back
in the saddle,
but we could really
use your help.
You're not really falling
for that again, are you?
Where are you?
Pacific Freeport.
It's a--
security's down.
That was amazing.
All you need to
do is get back in the game.
I thought vomiting inside my mouth
was just an expression.
I'm inside their
security system.
I got eyes on 7
very menacing-looking fellows
guarding a bunch
of holding containers.
I'm reading
infrared on one of the containers.
I'm working on opening
that lock.
Go for the hostages.
We'll take care of Shadowspire.
Container's open.
Should be 10 feet in front of you,
second container
on your right.
Got it.
We found
the two Argus agents.
They're both dead.
Get out of here then.
What about you
and Spartan?
We got this. Go!
Felicity, what's going on?
I don't know. I, um--
I must have tripped
some sort of failsafe.
The system's overloaded
with too many requests.
Oopsie.
You hear so much
about these vigilantes,
but I've never seen one
in person.
Wish I could say
the same about
a cold-blooded
murderer.
Have we met before?
Unh!
All right. Let's go.
I've got Spartan.
We're good!
No thanks to you.
Hey.
You ok?
That depends.
Is John ok?
John's fine,
but you seem to
think that
what happened
tonight is your fault.
Well, I'm pretty sure
I was the one
who couldn't stop
the security doors from closing.
And I'm the one
who pushed you to get involved
when you signaled
pretty hard that you weren't ready.
I wasn't signaling...
That hard.
I'm sorry that
I pushed.
I just thought that
if you got
behind a keyboard
again that things
would just start
to feel normal.
I love how playing superhero
is what we consider normal.
Heh.
But there is no going
back to normal.
You know what
I mean.
I know what you mean.
What I mean is that
I can no longer be a part of the team.
Because of your
injury?
You can't let that
stop you.
Except it has.
Look at me, Oliver.
I've spent the last week and a half
stuck in this loft.
I can't...move.
I can't drive.
I can't walk
down the street
and get a cup
of coffee,
and if tonight is
any indication,
I can't do the one thing
that I'm supposed to still be able to do.
You just need to
give it time.
Hey. Talk to me.
Go ahead. Tell him.
Tell him you're
hallucinating.
That should go over
like gangbusters.
I'm not going
to pretend that I understand...
Come on, Felicity.
Tell him. Tell him...
What you're
going through,
but you are the strongest person
that I know...
That you're no good for the team anymore,
that in addition to having
legs that don't work,
you've got a full on case of the crazies...
And we have your back the same way that
you have our back.
We don't stand a chance
to take down those guards last night--
- seeing visions...
- Just shut up!
I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean
to upset you.
No, no, no.
It's not you, it's not you.
Can I just be alone
for a little while?
You know,
I guessed I hoped
by giving you Intel
on Shadowspire
you would, um, let
me out of my cell,
but this isn't what
I had in mine.
Hey, Lyla.
It's been a while.
Andy.
Mr. Diggle.
I'm the director of Argus.
Those 3 dead men
were my agents.
I want to debrief you
on your relationship to Shadowspire.
Which is interesting
because you couldn't even
say Shadowspire
last time we met.
I was taking
an understandable precaution
in light of a potential
security breach.
The two agents
you found tonight
were assigned to
safeguard a shipment
of confiscated
railguns.
Heh.
But that was
a completely black assignment,
so I'd be very interested
to know how Shadowspire knew about it.
Amanda, you don't
see the bigger problem here?
Those things fire off
electromagnetic projectiles.
Just one of them could
take down a building.
- Your point?
- My point...
Is that if Shadowspire's
looking for that type of ordinance--
I'm far more
concerned
with a catastrophic
security breach
in my organization,
Mr. Diggle.
It doesn't matter.
Shadowspire's not
after railguns.
And what if you're
wrong, Andy?
We thought you
weren't hooked up
with Shadowspire
anymore.
I'm not, but I know
the way they work.
Shadowspire's all about
misdirection.
An elite military unit?
A cover for a criminal
organization.
A heist of a shipment
of railguns?
No.
Distraction.
They're
after something else.
You want to
talk about it?
What is there
to talk about?
Felicity's upset,
I don't know how
to help her.
It seems entirely
straightforward.
As the only other person
here who's had
the privilege of dating you,
a piece of advice.
Ok.
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
Everything that's
happening is my fault.
I knew you were
gonna say that.
Last month when we
went up against Vandal Savage,
Barry traveled
through time
and changed things.
Uh, what?
Barry can travel
through time,
and he warned me
that when you change the past
the past fights back,
so for the past month,
I have been tortured
by the idea
that what happened
to Felicity might have happened
because I wouldn't
listen to him.
The only person who
is responsible
for what happened
to Felicity
is Damien Darhk.
John.
We're on it.
John thinks
Shadowspire's going
after a shipment
of railguns.
- Can you call Thea?
- Got it.
Hey, Oliver.
Felicity--she makes
her own choices, you know.
I'm sure that's one of the reasons why
you love her so much.
Yeah.
Wow.
"The Shining."
Not sure if I
should be flattered or insulted.
Oh, my God. Die.
Just go away already.
Since I'm you,
that could be a little difficult,
don't you think?
Fine. I'm here, you're here,
so why are we here?
Do you have anything
the least bit interesting to say to me
besides the little jabs
you keep making?
Those jabs are just to
get your attention.
So what do you
want to tell me?
I'm not here to tell
you anything.
I'm here to show you.
The last time we
looked like this,
Cooper had just
fake died.
What does this have
to do with my ex-boyfriend?
The day we thought
he died,
you broke out the hair dye,
ditched the contacts,
and decided
you weren't gonna rely
on anyone else for help
ever again.
It was just going to be
you against the world,
and that was going to
be your armor.
Guess I should have
chosen Kevlar.
Stop it. Stop feeling
sorry for yourself
and stop pretending!
Pretending?!
Pretending that this
is the real you--
the blond hair,
the glasses,
the sensible
fashion.
People wear masks
for a reason--
to hide who
they are--
just like you have
been doing for the past 5 years.
First, you decided
to sign up for being
the world's most
overqualified I.T. girl,
and then you decide
to try being a hero,
and look what
it got you,
a ringside seat
to the rest of your life.
You thought you were
such a badass.
Waller says
the shipment of railguns
is in the back
of that truck,
moving out in less
than an hour.
What does Shadowspire
want with a whole shipment
of railguns?
Absolutely nothing good.
It's nice to
have you back, Agent Michaels.
Feels like old times.
What feels like old times is you
keeping secrets
that get
good people killed.
Did it ever occur
to you that Alan
and the other two
agents might still be alive
if you hadn't tried
to keep your
anti-Shadowspire operations
off the books?
Of course it has,
but the ugly side
of our business
is that sometimes security has to be
paid for in blood.
Thank you.
I was wondering why I'd left.
I don't know what
you're worried about, man.
Your team's not
seeing action tonight.
And I'm not with them
because I'm here babysitting you.
Where are they?
Something's wrong.
There's no movement
on the railgun ship--
Amanda, it's been ages.
Lieutenant Joyner, wish I could say
it was a pleasure.
Oh, man.
Stop moving.
You are making
me dizzy.
Oh, my God.
I told you, John.
The railguns were
a distraction.
Argus is
the endgame.
If this is retribution
for the work
Agent Chang and I did
crippling Shadowspire,
clearly it didn't take.
Vengeance and retribution
are useless pursuits.
For one thing,
they don't pay.
I'm here
for Rubicon,
and you--you're
gonna give me
the codes to
access it.
You know I can't
do that.
I do. That's why
I kept all these people alive.
I'm gonna give you
20 minutes,
and then...
I'm gonna ask
you again.
Damn it!
They must have
jammers in here.
No cell or Wi-Fi service.
Uh, would you like
to share
with the rest
of the class?
These monitors work
just like TVs,
receiving broadcast
signals on the 700 megahertz band.
Um...
I have a friend who's
into this kind of stuff.
Occasionally,
I listen to her.
If I can just switch
the chipset
into transmitting mode,
I should be able
to contact my team.
Oh, man. Lyla does not have time to
wait on your team.
We've got to
do something.
Yeah? Well, you're not
doing anything, Andy.
Look, man. Your wife
is in there!
Now's not the time
to not trust me.
Come on, come on,
come on.
Son of a bitch.
- Hey.
- You were just putting on
a little show
for me, huh?
Get your hands
off me, man.
What's wrong with you?
I see you buddying
up with Joyner,
talking to him,
thick as thieves.
Would you relax?
We were talking
about Blackjack.
I was telling him about the card counting
technique you taught me.
- Really, Andy?
- Yeah, really.
Ok, man.
Because I can't have
you backsliding, all right?
Man, I agreed to go
through this whole army thing,
and I kept my end
of the bargain.
Now I need you
to keep yours,
and I need you
to start treating me like a brother
and not like
a criminal.
Ok.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
John, Shadowspire never made
a move on the shipment,
so whatever their
next move is, it--
it's not railguns.
Just call me when you get
something new from your brother.
All right.
Ahh.
I am so glad our new lair has
elevator access.
Hi.
Curtis has anointed
himself my personal chauffeur.
Fancy. It's a good
thing he didn't ask
too many questions
about coming to your campaign office
in the middle
of the night.
What are you
doing here?
Well, I was at home,
feeling more
self-pity
than I have in my entire life
when it hit me.
This is who I am.
I wanted to come
along on your
awesome superhero
adventure
because I wanted to
help people,
and the old me
was so angry at the world,
but that anger
never accomplished anything.
It just created
more anger
and some seriously
bad personal style choices.
I wanted to do
some good in the world.
Hmm.
Ow.
That was
a good speech.
I thought you'd be
a little more impressed.
It was a good speech,
but--
- but--how did it go again?
- Felicity.
"If I know you"--
and I do--
you're probably thinking
what happened was your fault."
I'm here to tell
you that it's not
and that it's
not mine either.
It's the fault
of only one man,
and he has
an extremely
on-the-nose
and alliterative name.
Heh.
And we're going to
stop him,
not out of guilt
or vengeance, or regret.
We are going to
stop him because it's what we do.
That's who we are.
- That was a good speech.
- Yeah.
I'm very happy
to hear it.
Uh, we're gonna need
to get some ramps.
Argus has been
compromised,
and Lyla's being
held hostage.
I found this
in your office.
Hope you don't mind.
Lieutenant, we picked up an
unauthorized comm
out of the detention
area.
Take someone
and look into it.
Go on.
You might not get
the chance to enjoy it again.
It's been
20 minutes.
Am I gonna have to
downsize your
organization
yet again?
Apparently.
Well, that's rather
cold-blooded.
You really don't know her that well
at all, do you?
Ms. Michaels is one
of my most trusted agents.
She knows better
than anyone
that I'm perfectly
capable of watching you
execute every person
in this room,
and I'll still never give you
the Rubicon access codes.
Hmm.
Is that right,
Ms. Michaels?
It's right.
It's why I left.
Amanda Waller doesn't make
decisions based
on the value
of human life.
Pity.
No!
Well, Ms. Michaels,
most trusted agent,
looks like you now
have 20 minutes.
John.
Oh, my God. No. No!
John, John, John.
John, please!
He's gonna kill her.
You can't afford not
to trust me.
Overwatch, we're on site.
Excuse me?
Well, I thought that
it was time
you got a code name.
- What do you think?
- It's perfect.
Was gonna go with Oracle,
but it's taken.
Shadowspire's
got the entire area
around C&C in lockdown.
You guys are the only
game in town.
Can you get us
inside?
Like that you mean?
Well, it's about time
you guys came looking.
Who the hell are
you supposed to be?
Sergeant Andrew Diggle,
52nd regiment, 5th battalion.
What are you doing
locked up here?
It's a long story,
shorter version being
my brother's a jerk.
Lucky for me, though,
your CO and I go way back.
If you're serious
about Lyla Michaels
giving up
the Rubicon codes,
you will get on the radio
and tell Lieutenant Joyner
the guy that taught him
how to count cards is here
and, uh, wants to
help him out.
Andy Diggle? You look
pretty good for a dead man.
Here I thought
I put on weight.
What are you doing
at Argus,
much less alive?
Amanda Waller
brought me in
because of my former association
with you guys,
but, uh, small
world, though.
Your friend
Ms. Michaels--
she's my
sister-in-law.
- Andy.
- Point being,
her husband is
crawling around
these ventilation
shafts right now.
If you put a gun
on him,
she'll tell you whatever you
need to know.
You son of a--
Hey.
Turning on your
own brother.
That's ice-cold.
Well, you know
better than most.
John and I never
saw eye to eye.
Gentlemen, check
the facility's ventilation shafts.
Overwatch?
C&C, 3 floors down,
northeast corner.
Well, give us
a few minutes.
The other Diggle brother.
Isn't this quaint?
I get out of these cuffs,
and you'll see how quaint
you think I can be.
It's a shame you can't be
more like the little Diggle.
His pragmatism has proven
to be quite the asset.
Now if your brother's right,
you should be able
to convince your wife
to give me
what I want.
Johnnie, if Rubicon
ever got out in the open--
Ms. Michaels,
in 5 seconds,
it's your husband's brains
that will be out in the open.
4...
3...
2...
Do it.
Do it, Lyla.
It's all right.
Excellent.
Unh!
If you've run out
of guys to punch,
Spartan needs an assist,
two assists actually.
Tell us what to do.
Shadowspire's getting
the access codes
for a secure vault
in the sublevel.
I'm trying to stop
the codes from working,
but I'm going to need
Canary and Speedy
as my insurance policies.
Where do you want me?
This is taking
too long.
Something's wrong.
Someone's locking me
out of the system.
Go away.
I'm not you anymore.
I haven't been
for a long time.
I can't get in.
I have all
the right codes,
but someone on the outside
is preventing me
from entering
the sublevel vault.
That's extremely
unfortunate.
- You ok?
- Yeah.
You ok?
Yeah, we're fine.
Good job.
It was like you said.
It was the only way
to get us both in here.
Just remember whose
idea this was.
Eh, what were you
expecting,
a kiss
from the president?
To Amanda Waller?
To Amanda Waller.
You remember
that time that she tried
to take down the city
with a drone strike?
Good times.
Hey. Thanks for
the assist tonight.
I'm just glad to be useful.
Good job jury-rigging
the security system, though.
Just trying to make
you proud, Felicity.
You did.
What are you
gonna do about Andy?
Still haven't made
a decision on that.
You mean, even though
he just saved you life?
Yeah, well, you guys
had a whole lot to do with that,
but you're right.
This is the first
time in 8 years
I've seen shades
of my old brother.
You wanted to see
me, sir?
Already got my cut.
Eh, it's a token of appreciation
from the boss.
Traded the opium
for something else.
Like what?
Ask him yourself.
Thank you for your
assistance, Mr. Diggle.
Lieutenant Joyner sings
your praises.
Happy to help.
What did you get
for the opium?
Legend speaks of a place
of immeasurable power.
Many have disappeared
searching for it,
so much so that the locals
simply refer to it
by one word--
Purgatory.
I thought we were
totally unpacked.
Just humor me.
Ahem. What am I
getting?
Ah, yes.
The white box.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Ahh. You ready?
Wow!
When you said that
you made some
bad personal style
choices,
you weren't kidding.
This is the old me,
a rebellious
brunette hacker
who didn't listen to anyone
else's rules but her own.
You're not that
person anymore?
Nope.
What you did
last night was amazing.
- I was really badass.
- Yeah.
Though the old me
probably would have stolen
the plans for Rubicon
and released them
as some sort
of political statement.
The old me would have
snapped Joyner's neck.
Yeah.
We've both grown.
Thank you for always
being on my side.
No place I'd
rather be.
Hand me that garbage can
and this lighter.
Ahem. How much
medication are you on?
Absolutely none.
Ok.
Just want to make sure
that my past stays the past, you know?
Wha-pa!
One more thing
from me.
The doctor said your
condition is permanent,
and I don't think
that it's healthy
or productive
for either of us
to live in denial,
but...
I have seen people
speed and shrink and fly.
We watched a friend
of ours come back from the dead.
That is the world
we live in now...
And I will not stop
searching it
until we find a way
to make you walk again.
Hey.
Are you sure about this?
Because I'm not.
Better than being
in that cage, right?
You might want to wait outside.
I have it from here.
Make yourself
comfortable.
Lyla's cooking something.
Hey.
If this is about
reconnecting
with Carly and Andy,
as well, I, um...
I get it, Andy.
Step by step, right?
Andy.
Hey.
I'm making pork roast.
Johnnie said it's
your favorite.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
I got another
surprise for you, man.
Just a second.
Hey, Lyla. I, uh--
not a word.
John and I both
agreed to this.
She's excited
to meet you.
This is
your niece...
- Hey.
- Sara...
And that's your
uncle Andy.
Andy.
Yeah.
She's got mom's eyes.
Welcome home, man.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.