Previously on Arrow:
If I only knew
how you were spending your nights.
Why should I trust you?
Oliver.
- It's past time we talked.
- About what? You being a serial killer?
Start with Laurel. You're
still in love with her.
So are you.
Lord knows I am guilty of a lot of things
between us...
but not you and her.
She chose you.
My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
I'm the CEO of Queen Consolidated.
I have been complicit in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose.
To destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
But you need to know that the architect
of this nightmare is Malcolm Merlyn.
You can't beat me, Oliver.
Because you don't know, in your heart,
what you're fighting for.
- Is Laurel safe?
- Yeah, you saved her.
Tommy? It should have been me.
Felicity, if you're so scared, why
did you insist on sitting up front?
It was the only
seat with a seatbelt.
Which will come in handy
when we hit the water at 180 miles an hour.
Which will not happen.
I think that means we're here.
Lian Yu.
You said the parachutes
were just in case.
Yeah, just in case
we made it here.
- Come on.
- No.
All right, Felicity, on three.
- I don't think I can do this. I can't...
- One.
Thanks for waiting until we touched down.
My pleasure.
Let's move.
- Shh.
- What is it?
Thought I heard something.
Dig?
Don't move.
It's a land mine.
I'm gonna try to disarm it.
You can't.
Diggle, back away.
Felicity, don't move.
- God, you're really sweaty.
- You're a hard man to find.
You shouldn't have come here.
Would have e-mailed,
but this isn't exactly a Wi-Fi hotspot.
This was where you lived
when you were here?
I mean, the first time you were here.
For some of it.
Could you at least pretend
like you're glad to see us?
Dig and I spent weeks tracking you down,
we've traveled halfway across the world.
And this morning we flew
in a plane so old I'm
pretty sure I was safer
once I jumped out of it.
You could at least offer us a water.
Or coconut.
Fresh out of coconuts.
I am happy to see you.
But I know why you're here.
I'm not coming back to Starling City.
I can't. My mission, my father's list,
it was a fool's crusade...
and I failed.
Malcolm Merlyn destroyed the Glades.
Tommy died.
And the Hood couldn't stop it.
So don't ask me to put it on again.
Ever.
This isn't about you being the vigilante.
This is about you being Oliver Queen.
Your mother's in prison, Oliver.
Her trial's coming up.
Thea's out on her own.
Your family needs you.
So does the family business.
All the bad press after the Undertaking
left Queen Consolidated ripe...
for a hostile takeover by a
Stellmoor International.
They've gutted every company
they've taken over.
Once they gobble up Queen Consolidated,
30,000 employees are gonna be out of a job.
Including one very blond IT expert.
Listen, I get why you had to leave, Oliver.
Probably better than anybody else.
I've been there.
And after what happened,
nobody can blame you for leaving.
But it's time to come home.
You're not the first man to learn the
hard way women are a distraction.
You've come very far in a few months.
- Don't beat yourself up.
- Well, uh, apparently that's his job.
And I love my job. Not that I wouldn't
trade it for a way off this island.
While you two were playing with each other,
I was hunting.
There's nothing more attractive
than a woman who can hunt.
When I was marooned here,
my first meal was a pheasant.
Your father cooked it for me.
He was an awful cook.
- Yeah.
- But a great father.
I'm looking at the proof.
Let's eat.
What's that?
That's Fyers' proximity detector.
We salvaged it from the wreckage
of the soldiers' camp.
Picks up anything moving
outside our safe zone.
It's been five months since we stopped
Fyers. He and all of his men were dead.
- So maybe it's an animal.
- Here's an imaging interface.
Those are not animals.
We're not alone on this island.
Who's Blood?
An alderman from the Glades trying
to save the city.
Fill your shoes.
Here's everything
on Stellmoor International.
Vice President of Acquisitions
is a woman named Isabel Rochev.
She looks angry in every photo.
So where to? Office?
Home. I wanna check in on Thea.
- Uh, she's not at your house, Oliver.
- Where is she?
- I only have a second.
- That's all right.
- My boss has been all over my ass anyway.
- Ha, ha. She sounds like a real...
Ow.
You have got to be kidding me.
Come on, I don't wanna fight.
Clearly you do.
Since you keep on taking on every street thug
or drug dealer you can get your fists on.
It's not like that.
The Glades are worse than ever.
I know, but you already saved a busload of
people and managed not to get buried alive.
I mean, how much more of a hero
would you need to be?
It's like you have a death wish.
And guess what. It's going to come true.
Yeah, well, someone has to do something.
And stand up for what's right, like he did.
The vigilante?
Who hasn't been seen since the earthquake,
which means he did get buried alive...
- and isn't coming back.
- I'm back.
Ollie.
You remember my friend Roy.
- Still here?
- Always.
So how was Europe?
You never texted, no postcards.
Almost like you were on
the island all over again.
Yeah, sorry. I was kind of distracted.
Snow skiing, water skiing.
A lot of skiing.
I hear rumors that my club
is under new management.
Uh, it's my club now,
and you're not getting it back.
- You're not old enough to drink.
- But I am old enough to run a bar.
Have you made it to Iron Heights?
To visit the woman who dropped a city
on 500 innocent people?
- No, thank you.
- Thea.
That's not what Mom did.
Right.
She had no choice.
But guess what. She did.
A choice not to be a mass murderer.
And I have a choice too.
So I choose not to be her daughter.
But I am so happy you are home.
Look, I need to deal with
our liquor distributor
who shorted me on
yesterday's delivery.
And one of my bartenders called in sick.
So... What?
Nothing. It's nice to see you like this.
Like what?
Together.
Central City says construction
on the S.T.A.R. Labs
Particle Accelerator...
should be completed by Christmas.
And in local news, billionaire Oliver Queen
has returned once again to Starling City.
With his mother's upcoming trial
and his father's company in free fall...
analysts are asking what the Queen
family scion has planned next.
Wasn't our country founded
on a brand of vigilantism, Mr. Donner?
The revolutionaries at the Boston Tea Party
were certainly choosing justice over law.
I'd hardly compare our founding fathers
to the Hood, Mr. Mayor.
Or these twisted copycats who have risen
in his wake.
Miss Lance.
What do you think about vigilantes?
I'd be foolish to
disagree with my new boss.
I knew I was smart to hire you.
I'd heard you'd joined
the District Attorney's Office.
It was time for a change.
Still, I'm sorry that
you and your colleagues
at CNRI won't be opening
your doors again.
- There were no doors left to be reopened.
- Ladies and gentlemen, the mayor.
They're playing my song.
Good evening.
It has been a very difficult year
for Starling City.
Our losses have been incalculable.
Our grief unimaginable.
But with the generous donations
you people are making tonight...
we will come back from this tragedy...
You have failed this city, Mr. Mayor.
The Glades descended into hell
on your watch.
You swore to protect all the citizens
of Starling, not just the wealthy.
I'm very sorry about this, folks. Uh, we'll
have this sorted out in just a minute.
Mr. District Attorney.
We are the Hoods.
And what was taken from us,
we will take back.
All units be advised...
Laurel.
Dad, I'm fine.
You've got one very brave daughter there,
sir.
Yeah, one daughter.
I can't stand to lose another.
I still can't believe this happened.
The Hoods' attacks have strictly been
limited to the financial sector...
trying to redistribute wealth
in the Glades at gunpoint.
Yeah, well clearly that's not getting
the result they're looking for, is it?
Did you get a good look at any of them?
Hard to focus on anything other
than the gun barrel pointed at my face.
- Well, tattoos, distinguishing marks.
- What do you think you're doing?
Interviewing the witness is the job
of the detective, Officer Lance.
This is my daughter.
She was nearly killed tonight.
Well, as a parent,
you're welcome to stay.
But as a beat cop, you're
more than free to go.
You know, one of the downsides
of being demoted, I don't
get to witness his sunny
disposition on a daily basis.
- Dad, give me a sec.
- Yeah.
I didn't know you were back in town.
I just got back a little while ago.
And I was gonna call...
but then I saw you on TV...
so I thought that I would come
and make sure you were safe.
Just four hooded gunmen.
Nothing a few self-defense classes
couldn't handle.
- Take a walk?
- Yeah.
Sorry I left.
Believe me, I get it.
After the funeral, I think we both
needed time to figure things out.
On our own.
I didn't get very far on my own.
And you?
Figure anything out?
That I made a mistake.
When I slept with you.
I know it wasn't exactly cheating...
because Tommy had broken up
with me.
But he only did that because he thought
that you and I should be together.
All I know is that I feel
like I betrayed him.
And now he's gone.
And there's nothing I can do
to make it right.
I know how that feels.
When I brought your sister
on the Queen's Gambit.
I betrayed you.
Your father.
There's no forgiveness
for what I led Sara into.
I would give anything to...
To go back.
Yeah.
But we can't go back.
Diggle. I don't like being played.
I'm not sure what you mean.
It's why you came to the
island and brought me
back to Starling City,
these Hood copycats.
And what if it was?
They're just doing what
you did last year,
terrorizing 1 percenters
into cleaning up their act.
Except they don't have
your restraint, Oliver.
- Or your honor.
- I'm done being the vigilante.
- Maybe this town still needs a vigilante.
- Now it has four of them.
How's that working?
Please take me home.
I've got a big day at the office tomorrow
trying to save my family's company.
Absolutely.
Mr. Queen.
And in local news, billionaire Oliver Queen
has returned once again to Starling City...
Unbelievable.
We off the mayor on live TV,
and what's the local news keep showing?
Oliver Queen.
Why?
Because he's taking
over the family business.
- We've been going about this wrong.
- What do you mean?
If we want real payback...
we gotta take the fight to the name
that did this to us.
- Queen?
- Yeah.
He's just some useless brat.
The Applied Sciences Division
of Queen Consolidated...
built the earthquake generator.
If we want real justice...
then that family has to pay
for the suffering it's caused us.
In full.
Hello? Earth to Queen?
Did you drop a Vertigo
when I wasn't looking?
Just distracted.
About what your brother said?
About your mom?
Eavesdrop much?
What I lack in height,
I make up for in wicked good hearing.
Heh. Well,
don't keep me in suspense, Harper.
What's your take on the matter?
Though, keep in mind...
I do control your paycheck
and your sex life.
Well, both my parents weren't worth a damn.
Either of them.
You never talk about them.
You got nothing nice to say, right?
Still, I'd be glad to see them.
And talk to them, if I could, but...
Look, you already lost your dad.
Your mom, she's still here
and I'm sure she'd love to see you.
Sure she's dying to.
Just like a lot of mothers in the Glades...
who won't ever get to see
their kids again...
because my mother helped kill them.
I'm not going to that prison.
It's the only way I know how to hurt her.
You might want to consider
how much it's hurting you.
Queen Consolidated,
how may I help you?
They're in the conference room.
Just FYI, no one is eating the bagels.
- Isabel Rochev.
- Oliver Queen. Sorry I'm late.
For this meeting or a career in business?
I didn't realize hostile takeovers
were filled with so much hostility.
Not at all, I'm actually
in quite a good mood.
Really?
- So destroying companies agrees with you?
- Winning agrees with me.
You haven't won yet.
Since you majored in Dropping
out of College, let me
put this in terms that are
easy for you to understand.
You control 45 percent
of Queen Consolidated stock.
I control 45 percent,
leaving 10 percent outstanding.
But in two days, the board will
release the final 10 percent.
And I'll buy it before you do.
With what money?
I doubt your trust
fund is that large.
And no angel investor will
go near the company...
that built the machine
that destroyed half the city.
Companies rise and fall, Mr. Queen.
Your company has fallen.
Oliver Queen!
You've failed this city.
Get down!
Fall back!
Oliver, go! Go, go, go!
Get Queen!
Queen's getting away. Go, move!
- Miss Rochev. I'm sorry about this.
- Because they were after you?
Because what happens in this building
is my responsibility.
Only for the next 48 hours.
Still can't get used to you
in that uniform, Detective Lance.
It's "officer" now. I'm
just glad it still fit.
They hurt you?
Thanks. I'm okay.
You, uh, heard anything
from our mutual friend lately?
Nope.
In fact, I keep waiting for him to show up.
- You could've stopped those guys.
- Yeah, not without giving Isabel Rochev...
and the Hoods a pretty good
idea what I'm capable of.
I think what Felicity's wondering is
whether you avoided taking those Hoods on.
And Oliver, she's not
the only one wondering.
I told you. I did not come
back to Starling City...
- to be the vigilante.
- But they came after you, Oliver.
- You could've taken them out.
- No, I couldn't, Diggle.
Look, there's a part of being the Hood
that neither one of you are considering.
The body count.
And excuse me for saying this,
but so what?
Since when do you care?
Since Tommy.
After he found out my secret,
you know what Tommy called me?
A murderer.
He was right.
My best friend died thinking
that I was a murderer...
and anyone that I kill
dishonors his memory.
So don't.
It's not like you've killed
every guy you've faced.
I could've.
Because when I put on the hood,
it's kill or be killed.
That is what kept me alive.
So I should've stayed on the island.
Is that where you're going now?
The two of you won't help me
save my family's company.
I'm gonna talk to somebody who will.
Someone's definitely out there.
They're moving closer.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Flanking position.
If they get the drop on you,
you'll want some backup.
She's teaching you Chinese. How sweet.
I'm sure she'd be happy
to teach you too.
Shado!
- Hey.
- I'm sorry I didn't make it here sooner.
- No. No, no.
Please, Oliver.
There are gonna be enough apologies
with me apologizing to you...
- for the rest of my life.
- You don't have to.
You saved hundreds of lives.
And killed hundreds more.
- Including Tommy.
- That was Malcolm.
Your sister doesn't see it that way.
And my attorney is thrilled.
If my own daughter can't forgive me...
she's not too optimistic
about 12 strangers in a jury box.
All right, enough of that. How has
it been going at Queen Consolidated?
- Yes, we do get the news in here, Oliver.
- Right.
You know, if I'd known the key...
to you taking your rightful place
at the company was its demise...
I would've declared bankruptcy
a year ago.
I don't know if I'll get
to run it for long.
Stellmoor.
Their VP is coming after us hard.
- Isabel Rochev.
- Yes.
Do not trust that woman, Oliver.
She is dangerous.
Mom, everywhere I look,
there are no good options.
I don't know what to do.
You don't have to do it yourself.
This is a family business.
Heh. I love Thea. I don't think
that she wants anything to do with it.
I wasn't talking about Thea.
Table 7 needs bottle service and I need
a round of martinis on the three-top.
You go see your mom yet?
- Ugh, I thought about what you said.
- And?
And I'll go see her when you stop going out
at night looking to clean up the streets.
What does one thing have
to do with the other?
I guess they're both things
that are never gonna happen.
We're looking for Oliver Queen.
He's back in town. He owns this dump.
Where can we find him?
Okay, then, plan B.
I'm gonna start shooting people
until Mr. Queen...
grows a pair.
Roy!
Back off, hero.
I'm just as happy to kill this Queen
as her brother. Let's go!
Roy, help! Help!
- One of the guys was missing a hand.
- What's going on here?
Most of it, anyway. He still had sutures.
- It was the Hoods again.
They came here looking for you.
They took Thea instead.
Where?
I'm sorry. I really tried
to stop them, but...
Queen. Oliver.
We'll get your sister back.
I'm just gonna check something
downstairs.
- Anything else?
- That's all I got.
I've made a few improvements
down here...
just in case, you know,
you decided to come back.
- We need to find these guys.
- I've been trying ever since you got back.
Figured you'd come around eventually.
I kept that. Heh, I liked
watching you do that.
Thea's boyfriend said one of them
was missing part of his hand.
Maybe a veteran?
Check hospital records,
any males that have had
surgical amputations
on their extremities.
Cross-checking by race and age.
Got one.
Jeff Deveau, African American, late 30s.
What else can you get on him?
- Ex-Marine.
- Would explain how he could handle himself.
- Did he lose his hand overseas?
- No. In the earthquake.
Says here he and his wife were trying
to make it across the 52nd Street Bridge...
when it collapsed. She didn't make it.
Phone records, please.
I wanna know who he's in contact with.
He's made a lot of calls
to a church in the Glades.
Something called "Standing Strong."
A support group
for those who lost loved ones in the quake.
Great place to meet three other guys as
angry as you looking for a little payback.
Get me an address, please.
You're gonna need this.
I had it custom-made.
How'd I do?
It's perfect.
You were right. Once I signed on, I stopped
thinking about all the bodies you dropped.
Because I knew that being the Hood
meant occasionally being a killer.
Maybe there's another way.
They have my sister.
What other way is there?
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna save her.
Listen, kid. You are not
the only one who cares for her.
But there are a lot of them.
Wait for my signal.
Where are the graves?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Tell me.
Damn it.
Oliver, no!
Oliver!
So, what do you wanna do with her?
We could knock her out,
drop her off somewhere.
Why don't you just buy her
a new pair of Pradas while you're at it?
She's seen our faces.
Look, offing Oliver Queen's one thing,
but his sister?
She's not much older than my sister was
when she was killed in the earthquake.
Your sister wasn't killed.
She was murdered.
By her mother.
What we're doing here is justice,
which makes us the heroes.
She didn't kill anybody.
My mother didn't kill anyone.
Malcolm Merlyn destroyed the Glades.
With Mommy's help.
Merlyn killed my father.
She thought he killed my brother too.
She was afraid of him.
She must have been so afraid.
Just like my wife...
when our house collapsed on top of her.
Get away from her!
- Help!
- Let's go.
- Please!
- Move!
- Go, move!
- Please!
Stop!
Let her go.
You want to save her?
There was no justice for people like the
Queens till you showed us how to get it.
You showed us.
Go!
You shoot me, we both die.
You'll drop me anyway.
I know you. You're a killer.
Keep it under 40 next time.
Have a good evening.
Do you know who they are?
I think the Hoods gives
me a pretty good idea.
Bring them in.
Where you been? Typically
when I bring in guys that
you've gone after, they
were a little more dead.
I'm trying another way.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
I didn't know you were here.
I was just...
I come here a lot.
- I can go.
- No, it's...
You don't have to. It's, uh...
Laurel, I understand.
After everything that's happened...
I understand why we can't be together.
But I still need you in my life.
We've been through too much
for it to be any other way.
I feel like I betrayed him too.
Before the Hood, we didn't have things like
earthquake machines or copycat vigilantes.
Laurel.
Malcolm killed Tommy.
He was killed in the crossfire
between two archers.
And now that Malcolm's dead,
there's only one archer left.
And I'm gonna help my boss catch him.
That outfit with your coloring.
Isn't that cruel and unusual punishment
or something?
I've done my best to avoid mirrors in here.
- So...
- How've you been?
Don't worry about me.
I want to hear about you.
How are you doing?
Are you still seeing, uh...?
Roy was his name, wasn't it?
Sweetheart, I'm fine, really.
It's not that.
I...
- I almost died last night.
- What?
- Thea, what happened?
- It doesn't matter.
When I thought it was over...
I kept thinking that if...
If I died...
you would spend the rest of your life
thinking that I hated you.
I don't want to hate you.
I really tried to.
But I can't.
I can't, Mom.
However long I am in this place,
you have freed me.
If I hug you, are they gonna shoot us?
I'm willing to risk it if you are.
You can't win this.
I now own 50 percent of the stock.
By tomorrow I'll have the outstanding 5
percent and I will control your company.
Any attempt to fight me will lead to
litigation and leave you penniless.
And trust me, poverty isn't as glamorous
as Charles Dickens made it look.
What if I found someone to invest
new equity capital?
A white knight?
With all due respect, your last name
is now associated with mass murder.
- Even you don't have that good a friend.
- You're right.
I have family.
Mr. Steele, it was my understanding
that you had resigned as CEO.
I did.
I'm now chief financial officer
of Starling National Bank.
And my institution has committed
rescue financing for Mr. Queen.
We bought the remaining
shares of Queen Consolidated
when they were
released this morning.
Now I know I majored
in dropping out,
but I'm sure that makes us
partners going forward...
so I guess we will be seeing
a lot of each other.
You aren't at all what
people say about you.
Most people fail to see the real me.
Thank you, Walter.
Thank you for reaching out to me.
Whatever's happened between
your mother and me...
I'm gratified that you know
you can still count on me.
Your father would have been
very proud of you, Oliver.
- Ms. Smoak.
- Mr. Steele.
You did it.
Not bad for someone who got a D
in 10th-grade algebra.
If it's online, I can find it.
Uh...
Well, it was just like a good friend
once told me.
I had to find another way.
We're not alone.
Question is, where did they come from?
Hey, what's up?
- Just came back from visiting my mom.
- Really?
- Good for you.
- So, what do you say?
You ready to start spending your nights
safe with me?
Absolutely.
- Stop it!
- Come on, baby.
I'm gonna pick us up some
Big Belly Burger right now.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
We just want to be friendly.
What, we scare you or something?
Yeah, I think you do.
Me, though, not so much.
Run.
Is that all you got, man? Huh? Is that it?
Where the hell did you come from?
Well, looks like Starling is back down
to only one man in a hood.
Then the three of us are back
in the archery business.
No.
I spent the past year trying
to avenge my father.
If we're gonna do this,
it has to be about honoring Tommy.
I need to become the man
he hoped I could be.
You two have helped me take the first step.
So, what's step two?
I'm game for anything
as long as it doesn't involve skydiving.
And I'm pretty down on landmines now too.
The city still needs saving.
But not by the Hood.
Not by some vigilante
who's just crossing names off a list.
It needs...
something more.
It needs a hero, Oliver.
Too bad the Hoods kind
of ruined your nickname.
No, it's good. I never...
I don't want to be
called the Hood anymore.
Okay.
So, what do you want to be called?