Previously on Arrow...
Galaxy One has us
outmanned and outgunned.
You want to even the odds,
you get out there
and you fight
the hell back.
Hyah! Hyah!
Dinah sent you.
Give this to Felicity.
You military types
are like Swiss watches.
Youse are always
on time. Show me.
Show me what you got.
Where's Emiko?
Well, if I told you that,
Mr. Queen,
she'd have me head.
And, frankly, that's a part
of me I'd like to keep.
That Virgil is
damn slippery.
At least now we know what
he's trying to acquire.
A.R.G.U.S. vault drive,
triple-level encryption
for eyes-only documents.
If someone at
the agency's leaking
classified intel to
The Ninth Circle...
right. But if we have
some indication
as to what they're
planning finally,
it might help me
find Emiko.
And you said
you didn't need any backup.
Yeah. Well, we
lost Virgil,
but we got what
he was after.
This drive feels like our
best lead at finding Emiko,
at least
until Archer's back up.
Alena is pulling
all-nighters
to get Archer
back up and running,
and once it is, we will
be able to find Emiko.
And finally tell her that
Dante killed her mother.
And, hopefully,
she'll come to her senses
about The Ninth Circle.
Well, that
would be enough for me
to turn myself against
the evil organization
that raised me as a child.
- Crap!
- What's that? What's wrong?
The drive has
a security failsafe
that fried all the files,
probably to prevent
someone like me
from trying to do
what I am trying to do.
But these aren't
A.R.G.U.S.-encrypted protocols.
Someone else must've written the
security program for this drive.
Wait. If it's not
A.R.G.U.S., who is it?
Well, I have hacked enough
government servers in my day
to know that this is the
department of defense.
Not that I do that anymore,
because I work with the SCPD.
But this branch is
the D.I.A.
What would
The Ninth Circle want
with the defense
intelligence agency?
We need to find out.
You're married to
the A.R.G.U.S. director.
Maybe she can help.
Yeah, well, any inquiries to
A.R.G.U.S. will send up red flags,
paint an even bigger target on
Lyla's back than there already is.
I think I might have an
old contact at the D.I.A.
A General.
The General will be
right with you, gentlemen.
Hey. What's...
what's going on?
You're acting like we're
being sent
to the principal's office.
This guy can be
a real hard-ass.
Just let me do the talking.
OK. How do you know him?
Ah. I must say,
I was surprised to hear from you, John.
Well, sir, I wouldn't
have made the call
unless it was very,
very important.
No, I imagine you
wouldn't have.
You must be
Oliver Queen...
the legendary
Green Arrow.
I'm General Stewart.
A pleasure to meet you,
General Stewart.
Thank you for taking
the time.
I'm not gonna lie, son.
I wasn't always a fan.
But since you
got out of prison,
you seem like a changed man,
and I respect that.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, we made the call
because we were hoping
you could tell us what
was on this.
Ah. Where'd
you get it?
We intercepted a handoff
between an A.R.G.U.S. agent
and a man that works for a
group called The Ninth Circle.
The terrorist
financiers.
I heard they
were just a rumor.
No, sir,
they are very real.
And we have reason to suspect
they are planning something.
We were hoping you had
intel that you could give us
and the SCPD.
I'm afraid I can't.
But even if I did,
John, you know
I can't just hand over
classified intel,
not without
proper clearance,
which you no longer have
since you left A.R.G.U.S.
Of course. But, sir, we
were still hoping that maybe
you could, uh...
you were on a path
destined for the Pentagon,
maybe even a post with
the joint chiefs.
Now where are you?
Working with the cops,
playing vigilante?
That's no career.
That's a dead end.
No offense.
I wasn't even sure you
were keeping tabs on me.
Sir, I had my reasons
for leaving A.R.G.U.S.
You left to protect
your wife.
I know you better
than you think.
And I'm sorry to say
you lost your way.
I didn't leave
A.R.G.U.S. for my career.
I left to protect
my family.
And that's not something
you would understand,
is it, sir?
John,
we should probably go.
Again, thank you
for your time, General.
I always have time
for my family.
Excuse me?
Oh, John didn't
tell you.
I'm his stepfather.
Frak! Ugh!
Well, I guess I don't have
to ask how this is going.
Well, as glad as I am that
you both got to meet Laurel,
her cry really did
a number on this helmet.
How did it go
at the bunker?
Good. The bombs we stole from
Galaxy One are now secure.
Roy and Dinah are
setting up a perimeter
in case they ever come
looking for them.
And William is making sure
they can't be detonated
unless,
well, we say so.
Although maybe
he'd be more useful
helping you out with this?
The helmet is inlaid
with this highly
advanced circuitry mesh
and retinal display,
and I will not be able
to figure out why until I
get it up and running.
What do you think
you'll find?
Hopefully, whatever
Galaxy One has planned next,
if they haven't stopped from
making the city go boom-boom.
Well,
can't we just ask our man on the inside?
No. We can't come in
contact with Rene
until we get
the go-ahead from Zoe.
They're at Glades
city hall now,
and we don't want to
blow their cover.
OK, so how do we get this
piece of junk up and running?
The power module
is comprised
with an alloy
proprietary to Galaxy One.
I've been trying
to work around it,
but I can't without
the real thing.
Wait. I thought
this helmet was
a one-of-a-kind
prototype.
As far as we know. But
the power module is not,
which means we
need to find one.
All right, public enemy
number one, sit tight.
I know where to go.
Be back in an hour.
Anyone dealing in
secret weapons tech
won't be friendly.
You need backup.
Better safe than sorry.
Keep up.
Felicity Smoak now
entering Smoak Tech.
I have missed
your sweet Voice.
You know she's not
a real person, right?
Of course
she's not.
No. I am just so glad
that we were able
to start building the
program out again.
It feels wrong confining
Archer to just one tablet,
even temporarily.
She deserves to
spread her wings
right after we find
Oliver's evil half-sister.
Speaking of
spreading wings, um,
I think I've found a way to
help Smoak Tech really soar.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. There's someone interested
in buying the company.
It's just you, me,
and Archer.
I mean, who would be
interested in that?
Dr. Will Magnus.
What? Huh.
The Dr. Will Magnus?
Mm-hmm.
The world's foremost
authority
- on robotics engineering.
- Mm-hmm.
When I was ceo of
Palmer Tech,
he wouldn't even
return my calls.
My friend at Magnus Labs
says that Archer
could really help Doc Magnus with
these new a.I.S he's building.
I could set a meeting.
Magnus Labs is
the gold standard
in A.I.S.
Oh, my god. With their backing,
we could expand Archer to be
more than just
a genetic tracking system
or surveillance
for the SCPD.
I mean, it could be a bigger and
better overwatch system. I mean...
it's a chance
to change the world.
Uh-huh.
Warning.
Intruder alert.
Warning. Intruder alert.
Tick-tock, lads.
In and out.
Look for the device
drawing the most power.
Ohh. Ohh.
Hidden on a tablet.
Ha! Crafty.
Put the tablet down,
call your men off,
and I'll let
you live.
Felicity!
Sorry, love. No can do.
Pistol beats keyboard,
darling.
Who the hell
are these guys?
You're safe now.
They weren't after me.
Oh, my god. She's gone.
They couldn't have
gotten her, could they?
The Ninth Circle has Archer.
Then this crazy Irish guy
came busting through,
and Alena and I
tried to fight them off,
but then the D.I.A. came crashing through
the ceiling and took them all out.
- What about Archer?
- Virgil made away with it.
We'll get it back.
I'm glad you're OK.
How did they find out
about Archer?
I'll give you
one guess... Emiko.
I'm sorry my men weren't
there sooner, Ms. Smoak.
It seems The Ninth Circle was
a step ahead of us as well.
You must be General Stewart,
a.k.a. The stepfather that John hasn't
told his closest friends about.
So this is
where you people work.
Impressive.
How did your men end up
at Smoak Tech, General?
Several months ago,
the D.I.A. Got wind
of a Ninth Circle mole
inside A.R.G.U.S.
Since then, we've
made it a point
of tracking their
activity, including
the theft of that drive,
which led us
to your friend Virgil.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I thought you said you didn't know anything.
I said I couldn't tell
you anything.
A lie of omission is still a lie,
General.
I'm sorry, John,
but it was classified.
What was on the drive?
A list of assets we have
in the field...
special operatives with
high-level security clearance.
That's why
Emiko took Archer,
so that she could
hunt them down
and then gain access
to what they know,
which she could
pretty much do
with anybody now that
she has their DNA.
It's only a matter of time before
they find everyone on that list.
We need to make sure
those assets are secure.
We have protocols in place.
I'll call my assets to
a safe house.
This is General Stewart.
We need to start evacuations.
Uh...
Oliver, before
you get started,
I'm fine, man.
The second time that you've
broken the chain of command
with a 4-star General.
That's not like you, John.
You expect me to say
"yes, sir" to that man?
I... you know, i... I'd like
to know why you won't.
And...
I would like to know
why you never...
never mentioned that
you had a stepfather.
I didn't see much
of a need to.
That man has not
been in my life
since I left home
and joined the military.
OK. I just met him.
All I have is my
first impression,
and my first
impression is that
he doesn't seem like
that bad of a guy.
Oliver, when I first met
the General,
he was a lieutenant,
my father's co on
a covert military op
to quell an insurgency
in vlatava.
The op went bad.
The unit was pinned down
with heavy gunfire from
insurgents.
My dad stayed behind
to hold them off.
Saved the whole unit.
Stewart made it out.
My father didn't.
So do you blame him
for your father's death?
It was his op.
He should've stayed behind.
Six months later,
he's coming by
the house for dinner.
Six months, Oliver.
I didn't know.
It was bad enough that, uh,
he just appeared
in our lives, but...
Once he and my mom
got married,
he had me and Andy running
Spartan survival drills he
learned as a recon marine.
I mean, how long could we
be out in the cold
trying to find our way out of
the woods without a compass.
He called it "tough love."
Said he didn't care how we
felt about him
as long
as it made us strong.
I don't know.
If he was so strong,
how could he just abandon
the first rule of the corps
and leave my father behind?
- Thanks. Owe you one.
- You got it.
You get a lead?
Finally, someone not
afraid to talk.
There's a guy here
trading galaxy merch.
The only problem is
he's in Deathstroke territory.
Well, that won't be
a problem. Trust me.
Trust you?
Funny.
OK. Are you ever gonna
let me off the hook?
Doubtful.
Great. Well, you should
let me handle this.
You're backup,
remember?
So back me up.
Hey. There's a vendor back
there we need to talk to.
And I'm just gonna let
you in because why?
'Cause I'll kick your
ass if you don't.
OK. That won't be necessary.
I got the mark.
- From who?
- Your boss.
Check it.
How you know jj?
You just need
to know that I do.
We good?
Hey.
Who the hell is jj?
He's my brother...
John Jr.
John Diggle has
one son in knightwatch
and another who's the leader
of the Deathstroke gang.
That must make family
dinners interesting.
Well, he grew up
hating my parents,
and the expectations
they put on us.
That's why I'm glad that
you finally figured out
the truth about
your family.
Look, I've wanted to
tell you the truth
for a long time.
What else don't
I know about you?
How long you got?
I don't think that gun's gonna
get any cleaner than that.
I just want to be
prepared.
I can't slip up with
The Ninth Circle.
- And Emiko?
- What about her?
Well, I know you two
were close,
and you haven't said a thing about
her since she went all evil.
I'm not so sure
she's all evil.
When we were at
the airfield,
there was a moment
when Emiko and I
were alone, and...
She had
the upper hand.
I thought I was dead.
I mean, I should
have been dead,
but she let me go.
And that tells you what?
I don't know, but it
can't be as simple
as her being
all bad.
I mean, we've all
gone through paths
where we've come
to regret.
Hell, if Laurel can
redeem herself,
then maybe Emiko
can do the same.
We got
a problem, people.
What's going on?
I just got off the phone
with intelligence.
All of our assets have been accounted for,
except one...
an undercover agent by
the name of Julian Sison.
He should be
at a safe house,
but there's been no response
since the call came in.
- Where is the safe house?
- 30 miles norTheast of here.
We'll get into it.
I'll check with the other assets,
see if there's been any...
I'll come with you.
Somebody needs to keep
an eye on you.
You think I'm trying
to mislead you?
"Fool me once," right?
That's not
very fair, John.
It's OK. You can come.
Follow my lead.
This place is
a pigsty.
Either he's messy as hell...
or someone made it that way.
Overwatch, any sign
of our guests?
I'm getting
3 heat sigs further in.
What the hell's going on?
- Are you Julian Sison?
- Yeah.
Then why didn't you
answer your transponder?
'Cause I'm in
the middle of an op,
and you three just blew it.
Overwatch, there is
no sign of Emiko
or The Ninth Circle.
If this guy isn't
the target, then who is?
Those are my assets.
Overwatch,
we have men down.
The Ninth Circle knew
we were coming.
General, we've been
looking for you.
I'm trying to track John's Spartan helmet,
but it's offline.
Clearly this was an elaborate
play to draw General Stewart.
We need to find he
and John, and quickly.
I'll put a bolo
out for both of them.
I'll put the word
out around The Glades
in case Emiko shows up
in the old 'hood.
Or we just find
Emiko and end all this.
We will.
We have found people without Archer before.
We will find John
and his stepdad,
and then we will
find your sister.
Kidnapping a 4-star General
is a risky move
for The Ninth Circle,
especially if
the Pentagon's on to them.
So why? Why do it?
I don't know.
We need to find out more about who he is,
what makes him
so important.
I'd imagine his files are
really, really classified.
"Really, really classified" sounds really,
really fun.
I'm on it.
General?
John, are you
all right?
Yeah. You?
I've taken worse hits
than this.
Where do you
think we are?
I don't know.
Maybe a Ninth Circle
safe house. I don't know.
They must've found out I
was looking into them.
Agh! We got to get
the hell out of here.
You're not going to will those
things into breaking, John.
Do you not remember
anything I taught you?
How could I forget?
I know I was hard
on you, son,
but I wanted you
to be prepared.
It paid off.
Look at you now.
Really? We're captured,
probably gonna die in here.
We're not dead yet.
What about your helmet?
Yeah. Yeah, that could work.
If we could get to it,
I could send a signal to the others,
tell us our location.
Time for us to have
a little chat, General.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
- Oh, good work.
- Thanks.
All right. Anything
in the file
that will help us
find them?
No. But, uh, plenty on why The
Ninth Circle would want him.
OK.
Thrice-decorated commander
of the 1st recon battalion
during the khandaq
conflict, after which
he was appointed commandant
of the Marine Corps,
then chairman of the
joint chiefs of staff.
I mean,
the guy is a real bona fide American hero.
Not to John. John blames
General Stewart
for his father's death
during a mission
they were both on
in vlatava.
Oh, yeah. That would be
enough to alienate
someone like John,
and why he wouldn't have told us about him,
but it's not true.
Which part?
According to the Pentagon's
official account,
the vlatava mission was
so successful that
the General was actually,
for a stint of time,
appointed Head of DARPA.
But if... If the mission
was a success,
why would he lie
to John about it?
To protect him?
It's been a long time since we've
seen each other, agent Diggle.
Go to hell.
Hold that thought.
I want the codes to
project Cygnus X-1.
My name is
General Roy Stewart.
Serial number
498003145,
United States
Marine Corps.
Yes, yes. The military's
trained you well,
but you'll break eventually.
Leave him alone!
Now let's try it again,
General.
The codes,
project Cygnus X-1.
My name is
General Roy Stewart.
Serial number
498003145...
enough! I guess we're
gonna have to do this
the hard way.
Leave him alone.
This has nothing
to do with him.
Give me the codes or...
Don't tell him anything.
Stop. Stop it!
I'll tell you. Stop.
5693016.
Now, was that so hard?
You all right,
John?
Why did you give him
the code?
A thank you would
be good enough.
What the hell is
Cygnus X-1 anyway?
Something we don't want The
Ninth Circle to know about.
Now, let's get
out of here.
There's a box cutter
on the table.
I got something better.
What the hell are
you doing?
You really don't remember
anything I taught you, do you?
With enough pressure
applied at a steady pace,
a shoelace can saw
through plastic.
Damn. There's no power.
How about we give it
a boost?
John's helmet just
came back online.
Morse code... sos.
Location?
Warehouse in
the meatpacking district.
Call the team.
Clear.
You know, you could be
court-martialed
for giving up that info
to Dante.
It was a necessary
risk.
You don't leave
a man behind.
Sooner or later, they're gonna
send someone looking for us.
Let's get you the hell
out of here.
That's got to sting.
Yeah, I've been
through worse.
What'd The Ninth Circle
want from you, General?
Access to an experimental
weapon I oversaw
during my tenure at DARPA...
Cygnus X-1.
The project was shelved
because it was too dangerous
and unstable.
The goal was to genetically
engineer bacteria
to consume the by-product
of nuclear fission.
So it's
a biological weapon
that can literally
eat through anything.
- That's terrifying.
- Yeah.
A weapon like that falls in the
hands of the Ninth Circle, we're...
it won't.
We're gonna stop them.
The problem is
I don't know where it is.
- Archer.
- Great.
They are going to use
the intel they get
from the assets
to locate the DNA of the
people involved in Cygnus X-1.
That DNA
can lead them
to exactly where
that weapon is.
If I can piggyback
off Archer's signal,
I'll be able to...
Lead us right
to them.
It's like we're tracking
the DNA of a DNA tracker.
This is so meta.
We need to be ready the moment
they reactivate Archer.
It's the only way
to locate her signature.
Yeah, like one of
those FBI movies
where you have to keep
the kidnapper on the line
to trace the call.
Yeah, except the kidnapper
is the tech I invented,
which almost makes me
wish I hadn't.
What happened to Archer
putting Smoak Tech on the map?
Well, that was before I
realized
all the bad that
she could do.
I wanted to invent something
that would help save the city,
and instead I made something
that can destroy it.
Oh, my god.
I'm a mad scientist.
Oh, my god, no. It's
so much worse than that.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
I'm my dad.
I am your friend who has
some real-life experience
working with evil geniuses,
and you need to trust me
on this one.
You are not one of them, OK?
OK.
You gonna tell me
what's really bothering you?
I love Team Arrow,
but it is not enough.
I need to do
something separate.
something separate
that can still do good,
and that's what Archer
was supposed to be.
You know,
my way of making my mark on the world,
and not as overwatch.
As me.
Well...
It can still be that.
We just need to get
Archer back,
and when we do, you just
need to figure out
how to make sure that
your beautiful creation
is used exactly the way
you intended.
You got this, Smoak.
Normally I'm the one
off by myself
staring into nothing.
That's usually true.
Usually I'm the one
with the father-son issues.
Oliver, people's lives
are in danger
because my stepfather
couldn't be honest with me.
It j... It just surprises me
that you don't see his position.
You know, he's at the top
of the chain of command.
The John Diggle that I know,
he would have done
the exact same thing.
Oliver, you sound like
you're on his side, man.
I'm on your side, but I'm
looking at a guy over there
who cares for you, who
was trying to protect you.
Frankly,
he deserves a little bit more of your trust.
What is this?
Those are
the unredacted files
from the vlatava mission.
Your father didn't die
saving his unit.
According to that, he died
because he was negligent.
And he took two marines
with him.
The only reason that anyone
got out of there was
General Stewart.
That's not possible.
It's all in there.
I'm sorry to be the one
to tell you this, John.
One Galaxy One
power module.
I guess there are
perks to having
a gang leader
black sheep brother.
Hmm. Sounds like my
kind of people.
When do I get to meet him?
I don't know. I haven't
seen jj in a year,
maybe more.
Funny thing is he used
to be my best friend.
What happened?
Ah, he and my dad
started butting heads.
Guess I got caught up
in the middle.
And this
Deathstroke thing,
that was just a way
to rebel.
I just thought one day,
he'd outgrow it.
But I tried to
reach him.
In the end, I think
I just reminded him
of everything my mom and
dad expected him to be.
I'm sorry.
Ain't your fault.
No. I just...
got so mad at you
for lying to me that I...
I never thought about
how much it must've
sucked for you,
and not having anybody
to share things with.
You know, this life.
It was unfair to
both of us.
Hey.
Jj has a message
for you.
Hey!
This way. Come on!
Get back!
It's time to go.
Hey, guys, we found
the weapon.
Well, technically,
The Ninth Circle did using Archer.
Felicity and I rode
their coattails
right into the secure facility,
where it's being stored.
Yup, that's definitely
a secret weapons depot.
OK, well, now that
we know where we're going,
we just have to figure out
how to get past Archer.
The moment you
set foot onsite,
The Ninth Circle will
know that you're there.
So we lose the element
of surprise.
I'll call my team.
No. Wait.
We got this.
Copy that.
Let's move.
Perfect.
Perimeter breach
detected.
Scanning intruders' DNA.
Identifying.
It's your brother
and his friends.
Stop them.
Overwatch, do you have
a bead on Emiko?
I'm hacked into the
exterior cameras,
but she must
already be inside.
Without Archer,
it's like I'm flying in blind.
Isn't that what these boosters are for?
Yes.
Once you've planted the signal boosters,
I will be able to take
back control of Archer
and find Emiko.
Go find your sister.
We'll plant
the boosters.
Oliver,
you have company.
Archer has
our positions locked.
Where are we with
the boosters?
Boosters are in place
and activated.
Good to go, overwatch.
We have uplink.
It's not working.
I can't get through
their firewall.
Wait. They locked you out
of your own program? How?
I don't know, but whatever they did,
I can't get back control of Archer.
Get down!
We need an exfil
route now! Now!
Most black-level facilities
follow the same blueprint.
There should be a door
near your position
that leads
to an access tunnel.
Are you sure?!
Trust me.
Let's move!
Move!
We're clear, General. Thanks.
Emiko is headed to the parking
garage with the weapon.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm infecting it with a
self-destruct protocol.
Those boosters were
the only reason we
were able to access
Archer.
If The Ninth Circle gets
their hands on it,
we may never be able
to access Archer again.
Well, what about all your
hard work, your legacy?
I guess I'll just have
to build a new one.
Archer's gone down.
It doesn't matter.
We got what we came for.
Take the weapon and go.
Me and my brother have
unfinished business.
Emiko!
You need to listen to me.
You need to hear this.
Dante's been
lying to you.
He killed your mother.
Liar.
Hyah!
Listen to me.
He set all this in motion.
He used The Ninth Circle's
resources to cover it up.
He misled you.
He doesn't care about you.
I do.
Emiko.
I told you to go.
And I told you I
won't leave you.
We're currently in a tie
between good news and bad news,
the good news being
that I destroyed Archer,
which I can't believe I'm
counting as good news.
The bad news is
The Ninth Circle
got away with a very
dangerous biological weapon.
How did things
go with Emiko?
I told her that Dante
killed her mother,
and it didn't make
any difference.
I guess bad news
wins this round.
We need to plan
our next move.
What is our next move?
Start by figuring out
what The Ninth Circle intends
to do with Cygnus X-1.
I should take this
to the D.I.A. Brass.
Thank you.
I'll walk you out.
Hey.
I know how much you wanted
Oliver's plan to work.
Maybe I should be grateful
that I can finally
get to see Emiko
for who she really is.
Maybe.
It doesn't make it
hurt any less.
Hey, I, um...
Wanted to say thank you.
I know this...
I know I haven't made
it easy for you.
This is the most time
we've spent together
since you turned 18.
As hard as it may be
to believe,
I'm grateful for it.
Yeah, I'd prefer
a round of golf
to kidnapping and...
And torture.
I know you might not
feel the same way,
but you will always
be a son to me.
Oliver told me the truth
about vlatava,
about my father.
Why did you let me
believe a lie?
You let me hate you.
Every child
deserves to believe
that his father
is a hero.
And believing it,
you became one.
If he could see you today,
I know he would be
so proud of you.
If I'm a hero...
It was all because
of you...
Sir.
- John.
- Yes, sir.
Call your mother.
I figured out
the silver lining
to the whole torpedoing
our only viable product is
that we are gonna save
so much money on servers
because Archer was
a power suck.
Not even a chuckle.
I guess I'm not
really in the mood
for the whole
dark humor thing,
what with our only viable
product being destroyed and all.
I'm sorry I destroyed
our golden goose.
Golden egg. Goose?
You know, we could rebuild.
Make it better,
less stealable.
Heh.
When you were uploading
the self-destruct code,
I copied Archer's root code.
But with that and your notes,
we could start over.
No. I appreciate that.
But as long as Archer's
out there,
it could fall into
the wrong hands. And...
I don't know what my
legacy's going to be,
but it can't be that.
Well, that sounds
like someone
who hasn't heard
Doc Magnus' offer.
Relax. I know.
Legacy trumps payday.
Well, I'm really glad you're
the cto and not the cfo,
because the cfo wouldn't
be so chill
about me deleting our
only, only asset.
I have a question.
Do we have a cfo?
No. Quick question,
do we need one?
Hmm, I think we should
probably focus
on coming up
with our next project,
one that makes us
a lot of money.
Yes. One that
can help people
but also not lead
to mass destruction.
If we have to.
Yes, we do. We must.
Hey, for what it's worth,
being overwatch
won't be your only legacy.
It'll be whatever you do
next here at Smoak Tech.
Because it's not Archer that was
destined to change the world.
It's you... Felicity Smoak.
Thank you.
All right, madame helmet,
let's see what
you're hiding.
Here goes nothing.
It seems like it worked.
That's not possible.
What is it?
This helmet is a satellite
to a much larger network.
Galaxy One was able
to expand Archer.
Hold on. I know big brother
getting bigger
isn't exactly great, but isn't Archer
just a surveillance program?
No, not if you
weaponize it.
Wearing one of these
would be like
wearing an a.I.
- Powered sixth sense.
Pair that with tech-enhanced
strength and agility.
One of those troopers
was able to take out
half the canaries.
A whole army of them,
they'll be unstoppable.
Acquiring that weapon
was a great victory,
but Oliver Queen is
still a threat.
You need to deal with your
brother before he jeopardizes
the last phase of
the plan.
I couldn't
agree more.
But first things
first.
You lied to me,
you betrayed me,
and you killed
my mother.
Emiko, you
don't understand.
Stop lying...
And tell me why.
She was the last reminder
of your former life.
Your mother was making
you weak
just like your father did.
And I needed you strong
to lead The Ninth Circle.
She was the only
family I had.
No, we are
your family.
Don't you see?
I did it for you.
This is for my mother.
Rot in hell.
Greg, move your head.