Previously on Arrow...
I had no idea you
were one of them.
The district attorney's
office
will not be pressing
charges on your friends.
Tomorrow, you will issue one
of these to each of them.
They'll each be deputized
like Mr. Queen.
Felicity used to force
this stuff on me.
There's another solve.
This could be the key
to finding our mom.
I want our children
to know
that they are the most
important thing to us.
You said, "children."
I'm pregnant.
Ha ha!
Becoming part of
the SCPD is
a great responsibility.
The whole city will be
watching you,
holding you to
the highest standard.
And now that you're
working with us,
you need to learn
how we do things.
We have rules, protocol.
And abiding by them
is critical.
The use of excessive force
will not be tolerated.
Your objective is to
defuse the situation,
not escalate it.
Firearms
should only be used
as a last resort.
Do not discharge your weapon
unless you are fired upon,
or your life is in danger.
All evidence against
a suspect must be gathered
within the parameters
of the law.
Any evidence obtained not
in that manner
will be deemed inadmissible.
In tactical situations, avoid
suspect-based decisions.
This only leads to chaos
and confusion.
And, above all,
follow the orders
of the commanding officer
on-site.
Wearing the uniform
of an SCPD officer
is an honor.
It isn't just a uniform.
It's a symbol of
the law, of justice,
of transparency.
Thank you,
sergeant Bingsley.
Any questions?
Rene.
He does know we have
our own uniforms, right?
Heh heh.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Oh, hey!
How's my favorite new
team of recruits doing?
Missing the good old
days when catching a bad guy
didn't involve homework.
Ah. Well, this is
uncharted territory,
so the SCPD just wants
to make sure
we're on the same page.
It's a lot, but it'll
be worth it.
I mean, we can finally
work together
and on the right side
of the law.
Wait. Does that mean that
the Black Canary's back?
Well, I did get a clean bill
of health from the doctor.
You all are deputized,
so no reason I can't be
captain and Black Canary.
Within the confines of the law,
of course.
Of course.
I want to be clear.
Just because you've
been deputized
doesn't mean you have
the latitude to operate
the way you once did.
You work for the SCPD now.
And this arrangement is
on a provisional basis.
Your actions will determine
how long it lasts.
Mm-hmm.
I think she's
starting to like us.
Well, that was a different
type of workday for us.
Can you believe that Pollard
made us go through all that?
Well, I know we're not
used to doing things
by the book, clearly,
but this partnership is
what's best for the city.
But she's seen what
you can do.
I mean, she knows what
we're capable of.
Just trust me. There's no use
arguing with the mayor.
- Can...
- you hungry?
Want a tartine,
some sauteed broccolini,
something like that?
As much as I appreciate the
"master chef" initiative
that you
got going on here,
are you gonna tell me
what's going on with you?
Because you are
100% agreeable and zen
about this whole
police 101 thing.
I want this partnership
to be done right
and to be legitimate
from the beginning
for our baby
because I did not get
that chance with William.
This partnership's
not gonna work
if she forgets
who she's hired.
The partnership
has to work, Felicity,
because working with
the SCPD
and not
hiding in the shadows,
I truly believe
that's what's best
for the city.
Then we can stay here,
and our children
can grow up safely.
Well, if you believe
that this is
what's best for the city
and what is ultimately
best for our family,
then I agree.
We're a team, too.
Always.
Except maybe we don't,
you know,
until the city's safe
and our family is
really secure,
that we don't, you know,
tell anybody
about what's happening
in here.
Because I think it's
too early,
and I don't want anybody
crying and asking
about, like,
if it's a boy...
- for the... for the city.
- Yeah, for the city.
And for our family.
It's for a better future.
Yay.
So about that tartine.
I'm starving.
I'm also nauseous.
Are they all staring
at you or me?
Both. You reek of money,
and, well,
I'm undefeated.
Don't wander off.
Don't talk to anyone.
Let me handle this.
You don't even know
what we're looking for.
Sure I do. It's
a tape mini thingy.
A microcassette player
or an answering machine,
old tech from the eighties.
It's the only thing
that'll let us listen to the
message Felicity left for us.
Right. I'm gonna talk
to my contact.
Look, I know
these people.
They're lowlifes,
criminals, like me.
Just stay here
and don't do anything.
W...
Bingo.
Something catch
your eye?
Uh, yeah. How much for
this piece of junk?
Our best
microcassette player.
It's incredibly rare.
I'll give it to you
cheap.
$1,000.
Cheap?
Look, you and I both know
that no one else is
interested in this.
Except you, it seems.
700.
- 400.
- 600.
500. Final offer.
We have a deal.
Good doing business
with you.
Let go. Let
go. Ugh!
You're making
a big mistake, man.
You're stupid if you think
you can come at Los Halcones.
Stop talking!
Him next.
Hey, what the hell...
15 seconds. Impressive.
Let's try a leg next.
Last night, 4 Los Halcones
gang members
were found dead
in a warehouse.
Whoa.
That's some face/off level
weirdness right there.
Do we know
what caused it?
The bodies had
bullet wounds,
but there were no shells
found at the scene.
Autopsy revealed traces of
an unidentified substance,
which caused a chemical
reaction with the blood
that resulted in tox...
their skin melting off.
The proper term is
toxic epidermal necrolysis.
- But, basically, yes.
- Yeah.
OK, how can a bullet
just disappear?
There have been rumors
of a new weapon
making its rounds
on the street.
Toxicology is working
up labs now.
We should have a better idea of what's
going on in the next few hours.
Or I could just put it
into my trusty mass spectrometer
and then compare it to all
the government databases
that I've hacked...
um, accidentally tapped into.
It would just be
so much faster.
I'm sure it would,
but, um, I think we're
just gonna wait to get
results when we get them.
In the meantime,
let's talk suspects.
The blackout gang.
Never heard of them.
Right.
They came onto the scene
about a month or so after
you went to prison.
They are
some bad dudes.
And with
the vigilantes gone,
they've been causing a lot
of trouble in The Glades.
You know,
that place you guys tend to forget.
Los Halcones are
their main rival.
So we're looking at
a gang war.
It seems that way.
All right. I want everybody
working their contacts, OK?
And I want eyes on
the hideouts for both gangs.
You think maybe
we should pay a visit
to the Los Halcones?
I don't think so.
You heard Pollard.
She's looking for any
opportunity
to disband this partnership.
Got to run our leads
the SCPD way.
- Oh, sorry.
- That's OK.
I thought I told you
to stay put.
If I had, I wouldn't
have found this.
I know you think I'm just some rich idiot,
but I...
Had it.
The cassette player.
It was right here.
Let me guess. Little girl
bumped into you.
Seemed cute, innocent.
Felix... he played you.
You couldn't have just
listened to me, could you?
Wait.
Blackstar.
Screw you, Felix.
You might think twice
before you swing that
right hook at me.
One word from me, and
you'll be in SCPD custody.
Ha ha!
No problem, sir,
right, Blackstar?
We're just passing
through.
District attorney Laurel Lance.
Yes, I'll accept
the charges.
Put the prisoner through.
I don't know what you thought
was gonna happen here,
but you're wasting
my time.
There's no way
that I'm...
Fine. I'll be
right there.
Visitors aren't
typically allowed entry
in the cell block.
Slabside doesn't say no
to this D.A.
So, tell me, what
exactly am I doing here?
Ricardo Diaz is dead.
Why hasn't this been
reported yet?
Well, you,
of all people, know
slabside's under
some major scrutiny,
so they're trying
to cover it up,
saying he was shivved
by another inmate,
but that's a lie.
And you know the truth.
Better.
I know who killed him.
Oh. Oh, I get it.
You have demands.
Oliver made me a promise
before he left here.
He said he'd get me
my freedom.
- Where is it?
- We're working on it.
Work faster.
The terms of your
sentence are rock solid.
There's a lot of
red tape,
especially when
A.R.G.U.S. is involved.
Well, then I guess
we're done here.
Ricardo Diaz died
the death that he deserved.
I don't care who did it.
Yeah, but you're
still here.
I told you I can't
get you out of here
any faster.
Then I want to see my son,
and not through
a wall of glass.
I want him here with me.
Do that,
and then we'll talk.
One of my officers just
received word from a contact
the blackout gang will be
convening for a weapons buy
tonight in orchid bay.
Sounds like our best chance to
get our hands on the new weapon.
Take down the supplier
while we're at it.
Get the unit ready
to move out.
- Whoa. Scpd's coming with us?
- Yeah.
Look, that's really gonna
cramp our style.
No. We just need to learn
to suit up together.
About that.
Pollard really wants to make sure
that we're treated the same
as any other officer.
But we're not like
any other officers.
No, that's true.
But for now, we still have
something to prove.
And so we will be
wearing, um, this...
Out in the field.
Pollard's taking
away our threads?
Look, it could be worse.
She wanted to put you in standard blues.
That's also not all.
We can't use
our normal weapons.
I know. We have to use
SCPD standard issue.
We'll make it work.
We got to make it
work.
Alpha team's
in position.
No sign of
the seller yet.
Bravo's in position.
Overwatch, do we have eyes, please?
Hold on. Pulling up
thermal now.
From satellite?
What did I tell you
about off-the-books hacking?
You said no public
resources.
This is private.
Loophole.
Yeah, looks like
you got incoming.
Looks like a vehicle.
That's our supplier.
Where's Mr. Midas?
He was unable to make it,
but he sends his regards.
Midas, as in the big cheese
ceo at midas medical?
I trust you were
happy with your sample.
Very.
We'll take as many of those
bullets as you have to sell.
Start moving in.
Do not engage until the buy is complete.
All 4 of us can't go in
together. We'll be spotted.
We don't split up.
That's protocol.
On my signal.
Have you seen
all the blind spots?
We need to maintain
the element of surprise.
This isn't up
for debate.
Now. Scpd! Freeze!
Go! Move!
Let's get out of here.
I'll get the supplier.
You guys take that case.
Hey!
They're using
the poison bullets!
Damn it. Fall back!
All units fall back!
Overwatch, the SUV's
heading south.
Can you track it?
No, I can't, because this dinosaur
of a system just crashed.
Did you not listen to
anything I said in training?
Following protocol is
not optional.
Your protocols
are flawed.
That's not the problem.
The problem is your refusal
to participate in our system.
We don't need a lecture on
how to handle ourselves
on the field.
Clearly, there was
a miscommunication.
Is that what you'd call it?
I'd call it a disaster.
OK. We just need
to simmer down.
Because of you,
we have no evidence.
Without the evidence,
we'll be lucky to put them
away for a year.
How we do things matters!
Then you're doing things
the wrong way.
And you're putting
this on us?
Sending two teams
into the field
was a mistake.
You should've
listened to me
and let us do things
our way.
This is our way now,
Oliver.
And I'm sorry. But we're all gonna
just have to get used to that.
Excuse me.
Oh. Sorry. Heh.
So I'm sensing
some tension here,
but I'm just gonna cut right to it
because csis were able to recover
the bullet that went
into the officer's armor.
Thank god he was
wearing that, right?
I mean, nobody wears
helmets anymore.
Anyhoo, I ran
a tox screen on it
to see why it was making people
go all wicked witch of the west.
I'm melting.
Oh, what a world!
Ahem. Hey.
What'd you find?
Chlormethine is a cytotoxic
agent derived from mustard gas.
But that chemical weapon
was banned decades ago.
Except when it's used
for medicinal purposes,
like chemotherapy.
Let me guess. All roads
lead back to midas medical.
It is one of 4 labs
in Star City that still uses
chlormethine as
an active ingredient.
And the buck stops with
this guy, James midas.
I met this guy at
an SCPD fundraiser.
He's got deep pockets.
It does benefit the SCPD.
OK. We got
to bring him in.
Not until we have proof
that he's behind this.
Dinah, he got
name dropped at the buy.
His company produces
the chemical.
How much more proof
do you need?
The concrete kind.
After what this department went
through last year with Diaz,
we have all eyes on us.
We just need
actionable intel.
Then we can get a warrant,
search his company.
You get a warrant,
he's gonna know we're coming,
and I know that you
know that.
I know that if we don't
do things the right way,
then everything
we've worked for
since you got out of prison
will be for nothing.
Is that a risk you're
willing to take?
Well, that could've
gone better.
All the training,
the rules. And now this?
We are not gonna be able
to make Star City safe
if we're constantly being
micromanaged by the SCPD.
Well, that was our first time
out in the field all together.
Maybe it'll get easier.
What if it doesn't
get easier? What, then?
Well, we go after
midas our way.
No, you heard Dinah.
We do things their way, or this whole
agreement is just gonna blow up.
We just have to
prove to the SCPD
that our way is
better,
and then they will
be adapting to our side
instead of
the other way around.
All they want to do is
bring this guy in.
We deliver midas,
everybody wins.
Have I told you lately
how smart you are?
Well, I never get
tired of hearing it.
I want mint chip.
Do we really expect
one of these boxes
to magically connect midas
to those poison bullets?
There's always
a paper trail.
How many more boxes
are there?
Monroe's about to bring up
another half-dozen
from the file room.
So #readfaster.
You know,
Felicity was right.
We should've digitized
these files years ago.
Maybe Oliver was
right, too.
Maybe we go after
midas the vigilante way.
There is no more
vigilante way, OK?
There is only the SCPD way.
It's my job to enforce it.
Look, I get it.
You're the captain,
but you're also
the Black Canary.
I thought that came
first.
- It doesn't.
- Since when?
Since I stuck my neck out to
make this partnership work.
Vigilantes cannot operate
without SCPD sanction.
The sooner all of us
understand that,
the better it's gonna be
for all of us.
Everyone's got something
at stake here, d.
But if this fails, I'm
the one who loses my job.
It's my ass on the line.
I don't understand
why this is
so hard for all of you
to understand.
Captain Drake.
Yeah. OK, great.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
That was Monroe.
He found us probable cause.
I'm going to
get my warrant.
I just got
the first quarter reports.
We're already up 60%
from last year.
Yeah, I wanted you
to hear it from me.
See you tomorrow.
James midas, you have
failed this city.
You have some balls
showing up here.
You know who I am?
Chlormethine.
You've been
weaponizing it.
Now I want
to hear you say it.
I press one button,
the whole city comes
to my rescue.
Yeah. Not with that circa 2017
first build security system.
I don't understand why people
don't just click "update"
when it says "update."
Try again, James.
I'm not telling you anything.
You can't touch me.
Really? Come here.
Stop! You'll regret this.
Not as much as you.
Now tell me what you
know about chlormethine.
Go to hell!
Wrong answer.
Wait. Wait!
I'll tell you everything.
I did it, OK? I've been using
chlormethine to make the bullets,
and then I've been selling
them to rival gangs.
Good.
Overwatch,
you get all that?
Signed, sealed, delivered.
Good.
James midas, by the authority of the SCPD,
you are under
arrest. Come here.
Again, James, you have
my personal promise.
There will be consequences
for this egregious mistake.
I appreciate that,
Emily.
I used to have such
faith in the police.
I'd hate to think
Star City's finest
have become
nothing more
than a bunch of
bullying thugs.
So you're just
cutting him loose?
We have no grounds
to hold him.
He confessed.
While you were
dangling him
over a vat of
hydrofluoric acid.
OK, he was never in
any danger.
Yeah, well, that's
not his story.
You know, instead of
using this case
to work within the
confines of the law,
you all went rogue.
And you,
you let him.
It's time for you
to make a choice.
Are you the captain
or are you a vigilante?
I'm the captain.
Then start acting
like it.
I asked you to be
patient.
It wasn't working.
Well, it would've.
I had a warrant.
If you had listened
to me,
we could be searching
midas' house right now
instead of being told to
stay 5 miles away from him.
But now we have nothing.
Go on.
Oh! Connor.
Hi, dad.
Come here, my little hawk.
I missed you so much,
little man.
Thank you.
Go take a seat on
the bed.
Dad owes Ms. Lance a chat.
I don't know what to say.
I'm a woman of my word.
And I'm a man of mine.
The Night Diaz died,
I was serving another
stint in solitary.
The guard forgot
to close the meal slot
after delivering dinner.
So when I heard yelling,
I got up to get
a better look.
The killer walked
right by my cell,
wearing green leather,
but it wasn't Oliver Queen.
Whoever's been running
around dressed up
as the Green Arrow,
that's your murderer.
They killed Diaz.
"I'm the captain"?
Really?
I've know you
a long time, d,
and I've never seen
you roll over
the way you just did
with Pollard.
She's the mayor, Rene.
And she can put an end
to this whole operation
anytime she wants.
That's not the point.
You've been yelling
at me,
been yelling at
Oliver,
and pretty much
acting weird
ever since
the weapons buy.
So what's up, d?
What's going on?
At the weapons buy,
I tried to use my cry,
but something went wrong.
It didn't work right. It...
It hurt like someone
was scraping knives
along the inside
of my throat.
I'm sorry.
Being captain is the only
thing I have left.
I can't be the symbol
of being on both sides,
both SCPD and vigilante,
because I am...
I'm not the Black Canary.
Not anymore.
That's a bunch of crap,
and you know it.
Your cry doesn't
make you the canary.
Did you know that
the pin you gave Zoe,
she wears to school
every day?
You think she wears
that pin
because of your cry? No.
She looks up to you
because you're the person
who will go above and
beyond to do what is right
no matter the personal
consequences.
That's who you are
no matter what.
Even if that's true,
it doesn't matter anymore.
Of course it does.
You say you can't be the
symbol of being on both sides.
That's exactly what
you are.
You really
fixed this place up.
Yeah, I thought
we'd need it
once the whole team
got sanctioned.
Oh, it's good to be back.
So good to be back.
How long till we're
up and running?
Just a couple minutes.
I can't believe that
confession got dismissed.
Hey.
I had a feeling I'd
find you two here.
So I take it you are
going after midas.
He knows we're on to him,
so we need to move fast
before he dumps
the evidence.
Right. And what about
working with the cops?
Oh,
you've seen what a train wreck
that's been?
We all know that we
operate better on our own.
Now, I would like for you to
be onboard with this,
but if you're not,
I would just...
I would ask you
to stay out of our way.
Oliver, I will always
have your back,
but you're giving up
on this partnership
before you're really
giving it a chance,
as if you're up against
a clock I don't know about.
So what don't I know about?
We're having
a baby.
Really?
- Yeah.
It's a little early.
We're not telling anybody yet.
That's amazing!
This is wonderful!
It would also explain
a hell of a lot.
We don't want a child born
into a city like this.
Our mission is
not complete.
So we're going
to go about this
the only way that
we know how,
without politicians and
without a precinct.
We're going to do this
the Team Arrow way.
OK, and that
would work
for a while.
And then, uh,
then I have to say,
we will be right back to
where we started, Oliver,
without a team, you
in prison, us on the run,
and a city no closer to being
saved than where we started.
Our partnership with
the force
is not working.
Then we have to find a way
to make it work.
Compromise, do whatever
you have to do
because if you want a new
future for this baby of yours,
it won't come by doing the
same thing we used to do.
We have to... we have to be
something else...
Something better.
You should've let me
take him
and the cops.
I can handle a couple of
poorly-trained goons
who don't know their
right from their left.
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
Nothing.
Spit it out.
I just half-expected
you to shout,
"Felix, you have failed
this city."
Well, that's
a dumb thing to say.
That's what our dad
used to say.
Oh.
You reminded me of him
back there.
So how do you suggest we
get this cassette player
if you're not gonna let me beat
the living hell out of him?
I have an idea.
Got it. Only cost me
my next two fights.
Better be worth it.
Oh, this is perfect.
Care to share the plan?
What is the one thing the
SCPD wants more than anything
in this city?
- To kill vigilantes.
- Exactly.
So let's hope
this works.
I got a canary sighting on the
south side of the Star City bazaar,
headed east.
Let's go!
Vigilante
sighted on south side of bazaar.
- Heh heh.
- You're a genius.
I am, like, literally.
I warned you
to stay away.
We are not good listeners.
Your friends are off
chasing a canary.
Well, that's what they
think anyway.
You'll regret this.
- Dick.
- Nice punch.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Wow. The place
looks great.
Wow.
Why did you guys
call us here?
To apologize.
We shouldn't
have gone off-book
to go after midas.
I appreciate that.
And while we're clearing
the air here,
I'm... I'm sorry, too.
OK? I was hard on you.
I was too hard.
You guys want to hug
or something?
Why don't we
save the hugging
until after we
catch midas?
The second reason that
we called you here.
We found a lead. Or
Felicity found a lead.
In trying to find
where midas is storing
his skin-melting poison,
I was able to alter
my security system algorithm
to track DNA
anywhere in Star City.
You have midas' DNA?
Well, it turns out he's not as
squeaky clean as we thought.
I got his DNA
from the SCPD archive.
He was arrested
15 years ago.
Thank goodness the police
are record hoarders.
And since he has a record
and we work for the SCPD,
voila!
I interfaced with the SCPD's
surveillance system
and was able to legally
monitor everywhere
midas has been
in the last two weeks.
Country club, office,
home, and...
And a warehouse
registered
to what is clearly
a shell corporation?
Obviously, he's keeping
the chemicals there.
And look whose
DNA is there right now.
Midas is probably trying
to destroy the evidence
as we speak.
He can try, but he's
not gonna get away with it.
We're gonna get him.
We want to do things
the right way this time.
That means doing
a few things differently.
What did you have
in mind?
First things first...
Suit up.
I want all of this gone,
not a single drop
left behind.
Overwatch to Team Arrow.
I have confirmation on midas
and a crapload
of gun-toting goons.
What about the chemicals?
Being loaded
into the back of a truck.
Dinah, what's
your status?
Almost in position.
Take it to the reservoir.
Anyone tries to stop you...
I don't care who it is...
kill them.
Guys, you may want to speed things up.
They're about to move out.
If those chemicals reach
the reservoir,
everyone in Star City
will be at risk.
We can't let
that truck leave.
No, we won't.
Hyah! Hyah...
You have the right
to remain silent.
Now!
Get me out of here,
and I'll double
your salaries.
Bad news, guys.
Midas is about two minutes
away from being a free man.
We've got to stop him.
You go. I'll secure
the evidence.
We're taking heavy fire!
We're cornered!
Man, I really missed
our toys.
The chemicals are
secure. Where's midas?
James midas,
you are under arrest.
Not tonight.
You think this is gonna work
out better than last time?
Because now I'll have your
badge and your costume.
Uh!
I don't think so.
Thanks to all those chemicals
we just confiscated,
you're going away
for a long time.
Like I said...
You're under arrest.
James midas is
in SCPD lockup.
We got what we need
to put him away
for a very long time.
Thank you for doing it
the legal way.
Thank you for letting
us do it our way.
And for joining us.
We missed you,
canary.
I missed her, too.
Thank you for reminding
me of that.
Wait.
Why do I get the feeling
the canary flight was a
one-night-only kind of thing?
I'll be back in the field,
just, uh, without my cry.
When my nerve was ruptured,
it created lasting damage.
I'm... I'm sorry,
Dinah.
Well, Dinah, cry or no cry,
you are the Black Canary.
You proved that tonight.
Thank you.
You know what else
we did tonight?
We forced Pollard's hand.
I leveraged her
relationship with midas
to convince her
to sign off on creating
a special
vigilante task force.
We're still sanctioned
by the SCPD,
but we're operating
as our own unit
out of the bunker
in our suits.
And the anti-vigilante law?
It's on her desk for repeal.
She's gonna sign it.
So we're like the black ops
for the SCPD now?
That's cool.
I'm just glad
we're all back.
It feels right.
I'll second
that.
It's nice to be
part of a team again.
And be here
at the bunker...
the sweet bunker.
Do you guys feel like hitting up the,
uh, "sweet" bar?
You guys go ahead.
I ate something that's not gonna
mix well with alcohol.
Yeah. I'm gonna hang
back, too, guys.
OK.
I got you
something.
Gee, you shouldn't have.
Well, it was the only
thing that Lyla said
helped her with
her nausea.
They're ginger
candy chews.
Oh, god. I'll try anything.
Morning sickness
or not, Felicity,
you have not
missed a beat.
You were absolutely
amazing out there today.
Your tech was
phenomenal.
Well, Curtis would've had
5 ideas to make it better,
- but...
- Well, maybe...
But if Curtis was
still at A.R.G.U.S.,
I would've asked him
to buy your tech.
And I'm sure A.R.G.U.S.
wouldn't be
the only corporation
hunting for it.
And I think that's more
than a security system
you're working on.
I think you're on
to something big.
Thank you for coming in.
I'm Laurel Lance,
district attorney.
I know who you are.
And I know who you
are, too.
Emiko Adachi.
Your mother was
killed a year ago.
Your father is
Robert Queen.
And for
the last 7 months,
you've been running
around the city
dressed like your
brother.
And you've also managed
to endear yourself
to Oliver
and his team.
I also know that
you were at slabside
the night that Ricardo
Diaz burned to death.
What's your point?
That you're lying about
who you really are.
You're not a hero.
And I wonder how Oliver
and his team will feel
when they find out that
their new vigilante friend
murdered Diaz
in cold blood.
I'm guessing family
dinners are gonna be
a little bit more
awkward.
And, uh,
what makes you think
they will believe
a word you say,
Black Siren?
Do you think I'm showing,
just even a little?
I think you look
exactly the same.
How you feeling?
Oh, I feel like I
could sleep for 2 weeks.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, so in between
updating the SCPD's tech
and taking down evil CEOs,
I was brainstorming
baby names today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Any frontrunners?
For a boy, I've
always liked Lucas.
Yeah. Lucas.
That's good.
I may have thought
of a name for a girl.
Yeah?
Mia.
Short for moira.
Sweet and fiery.
I love it.
And regardless of
whether we have
a boy or a girl...
I just want to make
sure that...
She or he end up...
Growing up in a better
and safer Star City
than I did.
Yeah.
I want that for both
of our children.
They'll always have
each other to lean on.
And we'll always have us.
What are you
waiting for?
Let's play
the damn thing.
I don't know.
What are you waiting for?
Fine.
Maybe I should do it.
It's not as easy
as it look...
just give it to me.
This is some, like,
feelings thing, isn't it?
Well, I haven't heard
Felicity's Voice
in almost two decades,
so, yeah, it is.
Look, whatever
she says on there,
it's clear she wanted
both of us to hear it...
Together.
All right. Let's just
get this over with.
William and Mia,
you know,
this is the first time
I've ever said
your names together?
20 years, and I avoided ever saying
your names in the same sentence.
It feels like the work of a paranoid,
overprotective mother.
I guess we really do
turn into our parents.
I'm rambling. Sorry.
Not just for the rambling.
For everything, but mostly for
keeping the two of you apart.
I'm not asking
for your forgiveness,
but just know that your father
and I did it to protect you.
We did it because we love you.
Now that you've found
each other,
I just have
one request.
Give these coordinates
to the team:
47.6119 North, 122.3301 West.
And then get the hell
out of Star City.
And whatever you do,
don't come looking for me.
So we're
ignoring her.
Definitely.
I know where these lead.
That's where.
We're going over the wall...
To The Glades.
Greg, move your head!