Previously on Arrow...
Anatoly said that you had a plan
to take control of the city.
It's like you're firing Overwatch.
I need to stop Diaz.
And in order to do that
I need to bring
the mission back to basics.
The impeachment was
just the latest step.
And what's the next one?
Star City, it's open for business.
Get your ass out of bed, chillón.
You can look at that picture
all you want.
Your father ain't never
coming back, Diaz.
I'm getting breakfast.
When I come back, this place better
be clean for inspection.
No wrinkles on the bed.
Seriously, or...
You get another souvenir
to help remind you.
If you do it again,
I'll tell Sister Heller.
You think they'll believe
someone like you, chillón?
What...
You want to take a shot at me?
Go ahead. I'm right here.
Give it back! That's my only one.
No family's gonna wanna take you in.
Why would they?
You're nothing. You're a loser.
I think you need that reminder now.
You know that they
invited us here, right?
Breaking and entering is a bit
disrespectful, don't you think?
I'm tired of waiting.
You're the one who wanted
to tag along.
To see how you operate,
to see your big job.
So far all we've done is drive in
a car for three hours
and wait outside
for two more.
Patience. It's one of the most
important virtues a person can have.
Meaning?
If you think short-term,
you're gonna drift moment to moment.
If you want something big,
something truly remarkable,
you got to think long-term.
We've been waiting out here
long-term.
Let me put it in perspective.
I've been working on something
for five years.
What's waiting two hours?
A slap in the face?
Small price to pay for
introduction to the Quadrant.
I thought they were an urban legend.
They're very real.
They control all criminal enterprises
across the entire country.
The four corners.
Yeah, "Quadrant," I get it.
Very clever.
They didn't get that type of power
without patience.
Well, if they're so powerful,
then why didn't you
come with any backup?
I'm not. I got you.
You're early.
My father couldn't make it.
You don't mind, do you?
Let's get started.
We have a lot to discuss.
Indeed, we do.
Hey, you made it.
Yeah. Um...
- I did.
- That's great. I'm glad you did.
What's wrong?
It's just been a while since
we've done any Helix Dynamics stuff.
Yeah, well, we've been busy.
We've been fighting.
Not you and me. Our teams, yeah, but
that's not an issue for me anymore.
Glad it's not for you, but you know,
Rene is still in the hospital.
He's only now just getting out.
I'm sorry. About our teams...
I'm sorry.
I'd really like Helix to work.
Looks like you're trying to
stabilize a neural interface.
Yeah, I mean it's just still
really twitchy.
You know,
actually I had a thought about this.
I think the serotonin interface is
a result of the pathogenic reaction.
Star City is open for business.
We have the police, the ports,
the whole city...
We got it wired.
Now, you wanna run merchandise,
you wanna move product,
launder money, anything...
Star City is the place.
Assuming we're interested, not saying
that we are, but assuming,
how much are you looking to charge?
It's free.
Nothing's ever free.
I just want a seat at the table.
Of the Quadrant?
Mmm-hmm.
That seems reasonable to me.
You make the Quadrant
sound like it's a potluck.
As if there's always room
at our table for anyone
with something to add.
But it's not.
We're a family.
We're not really that welcoming
to outsiders.
At least, not before we know
that you can operate at our level.
I just offered you a whole city.
Hell, if you can't see
the opportunity in that,
why don't I talk to your father?
He sent me.
We're just looking
for a little something extra.
Call it establishing your bona fides.
What did you have in mind?
This is Robert Baylor,
one of our guys.
The FBI pinched him.
- That's not ideal.
- Right?
We need to know where the Federal
Marshals are holding Baylor
so we can get him out.
You want him to audition?
Well, that's not a very productive
way of putting it.
- And yet...
- It will be nothing for me.
It's not a problem. Whatever it takes
to get the deal done, right?
Champion mindset.
You got a john in this place?
It's right over there.
I'm at the location now.
Thanks for the address.
I'd say I owe you one,
but you owe me 20.
He wants contact with the FBI.
So more waiting then.
We have to get a picture of the guy.
Proof of life.
They tell you to fetch, you fetch.
So, what's next? Roll over?
Oh! That's right.
You've already done that.
You think I'm giving in
to these people too much?
I don't think it, I know it.
It's just business.
You're okay with all this?
How that guy talked to you?
Cartier is nothing.
He's a stepping stone.
Long-term thinking, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
How's that working out for you?
Smoke break.
Fetch, roll over, sit. Good boy.
You know that the Quadrant is the
most powerful criminal organization
on the continent?
When I joined with Cayden James,
I gained a city.
When I join the Quadrant,
I'm gonna have an empire.
Okay. Try it.
- Success.
- Yes!
Pathogenic reaction is completely
stabilized.
Yes! Damn, we make a good team!
- Speaking of team...
- No, don't do that.
Why would you do that?
We're having such a good time.
Earlier you said the team thing
wasn't an issue for you anymore.
- Did I say that?
- Yeah, you did. The question is why?
Oliver sort of fired me. I mean,
he's saying that he didn't, but,
it sure feels like he did, you know.
Well, sort of fired... He fired me.
Wait. I'm sorry. What happened?
Long story short, Oliver had a run-in
with Vertigo... The pharmaceutical,
not a person,
and he came out of it with this
epiphany that to stop Diaz he has to
"go back to basics."
- Meaning?
- Meaning he's a lone wolf.
- No more Team Arrow.
- So, did he also fire John?
No. John left about a week before.
Wow! Okay, well...
I am going to have to try not
to take satisfaction out of that.
Try really hard.
Okay, so it was down to
you and Oliver.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Now it's just Oliver.
Yep.
- How are you doing with all this?
- I'm fine.
You're not fine.
What?
So, none of your people
could find him.
I did.
I'll tell him to start
carving the monument.
They brought your boy
out for a smoke.
Looked more like a guest
than a prisoner.
Honey, ease up.
That's a 30-year-old single malt.
Call me "honey" again,
and I might only break your legs.
Mmm.
I like this one.
So, I held up my part of the bargain.
Time for you to deliver yours.
You know, your pretty little friend
makes an inconvenient point.
Seems that Mr. Baylor
has gotten a little chatty.
So what?
So, my father's going to have to
debrief him.
You know, to find out what
he told the Justice Department.
- You want me to...
- Fetch him?
What's a little favor between
future business partners?
So, what's next?
You want me to roll over,
you want me to play dead?
You're absolutely right.
Forget I asked.
Thanks for tracking down
Baylor for us.
We'll take it from here.
You should've asked me
from the beginning.
Are you wasting my time?
I don't react well
when people waste my time.
Hey, I had no idea that Baylor would
be cooperating with the Frisbees.
I'm gonna deliver Baylor to you.
Afterwards, I meet your father.
You solve this little problem for us
and my dad will be asking
to sit down with you.
Call me when you've got Baylor.
I'll send over a car.
Hey,
what happened to your hand?
I got angry at someone.
The Quadrant's making you jump
through a lot of hoops.
I hope it's worth it.
Why don't I knock on the door?
Hello, boys.
- Who are you?
- It doesn't matter.
Are you gonna kill me?
If you keep asking me questions.
On your feet.
Send the car.
Move. Move!
Cartiers take care of their own.
Once you're in, you're family.
That's my expectation.
All those days,
I knew they'd send for me.
I would never snitch.
Sure you wouldn't.
I wouldn't take the chairs, though.
You're lucky you don't work for me.
Baylor, buddy.
Feds treat you all right?
Whoa. I didn't say nothing.
I swear to God.
Tell him in person.
They're gone.
That packs a punch.
What would you have done
if they shot you in the head?
I'd be dead probably.
Getting shot wasn't part of my plan.
Understatement of the year.
You just can't trust anyone
these days.
Dad?
Is it done?
Baylor's off the board.
And Diaz?
Never saw it coming.
Idiot really thought he had a shot.
As if we'd share space
with a thug like him.
Tomorrow we'll send
a crew to Star City
and lean on Diaz's networks.
And we'll make his city ours.
So, this whole plan of yours
has gotten a little complicated.
Anything worth wanting
shouldn't be simple.
Not my philosophy.
Plans are like men. It's best
to avoid the complicated ones.
Ah, shucks.
You think I'm not complicated.
You do realize that
the guys that you wanted to impress
tonight are the same guys that
just tried to kill you.
And I was prepared.
It still doesn't explain what
we're doing back here at their place
when we should be on our way
back to Star City.
Maybe that's the difference
between us.
When you get knocked down,
you give up.
I get up.
I just don't get stupid, too.
Must be nice being pretty.
Pout your lips, you bat your eyes,
everybody gives you what you want.
Everything I wanted, I had to take.
Bar's closed.
Everybody move!
Move!
Son of a bitch.
In your enthusiasm to take out
your man,
you forgot I was standing next to him
when you started shooting.
But you're sorry about that,
aren't you?
It wasn't anything personal.
Bullets make things personal.
May I ask you something?
Did you ever have to fight
for a meal?
Not once. Not one time.
Mr. Silver Spoon, I had to fight
for every scrap of food
I ate as a kid.
You don't know what it's like
to be hungry.
To want something so bad,
you'd kill for it.
I've killed. Plenty.
Not for survival.
Not when the outcome of your life
hangs in the balance.
It's funny you should
put it that way.
You really got to tell your guys,
creep a little quieter.
There's two to my right,
three more behind me.
That's pretty confident for a thug
who's outnumbered.
You wouldn't think I was outnumbered
if you knew what she can do.
Wow. We really need
to restock the fridge.
Do you think soda can go bad?
I should probably not even answer that.
- Felicity? Hey.
- Mmm.
It's working. Remember?
We high-fived.
Yeah, doesn't mean
it can't be improved.
Sure, so maybe improve it tomorrow?
When you've had some sleep and
some food and some non-expired soda.
Yeah, I just want to make
a couple adjustments here.
Because that's easier than
talking about your husband?
Hey, he's going back to basics,
so, so am I.
You're one who described it
as "getting fired."
I said "kinda" and that was just
shorthand.
As much as I love being
a part of Team Arrow,
as downsized
as it may have become...
It was taking us away from our real
work. Helix, this is where it's at.
And you're not worried about him?
No, he can take care of himself.
And I have been doing this
for over five years.
Yeah, in the bunker
with computers and body cams and GPS
so you knew where he was
and what he was doing
and if he was okay.
Curtis. Yeah, I thought throwing
myself into work would work,
but it's not working.
I mean, I don't know where he is,
he doesn't tell me
where he is anymore,
I need to know if he's okay.
I'm dying here.
Sorry. News alert.
Shootout in the Glades. Oliver?
The Green Arrow was last
seen in the center of an altercation
moments before the explosion
overtook the area.
SCPD has yet to issue a statement.
We will keep you updated.
You're toying with him.
Come on. What's a little fun
between future business partners?
Well, we wouldn't want him to think
that we're wasting his time
by sending him on some fool's errand.
Yeah, that would make anyone furious.
Your daddy buy you this place?
A not-so-shiny toy to distract you
while he's running the real business.
I never got anything from my family.
You know I'm an orphan?
It's true. I grew up
in a real-deal orphanage.
With nuns and...
And everything.
The full package.
There was this older boy.
His name was Jesse.
Jesse thought he was better than me.
And I believed him.
And I was afraid of him.
I'd cry every night.
For years, he treated me like a worm.
Like I was worthless.
Like I was beneath him.
I had to make his bed,
I'd clean our room.
He treated me like
I was his damn servant.
Look at me.
I'm nobody's servant now.
If you cut me, my father will
never give you what you want.
That's prospective, the future.
I'm more interested in the past.
Why did you try and kill him, Eric?
Because I could.
That's not good enough.
Stop!
It was my father's idea.
We were gonna take Star City,
co-op your networks.
Take credit for my sweat equity?
That is so inconsiderate.
It sounds like your
precious little Quadrant
is a bunch of selfish jerks.
They didn't know.
We never told them about you.
What?
My father and I, we never brought
your proposal to the Quadrant.
You're a nobody, so...
Satisfied yet?
No.
You're alive now.
You wanna stay that way?
Tell me when the Quadrant is meeting.
- Tonight.
- Well, isn't that convenient?
You're going to give me
all the details?
They're not just gonna let you in.
I'm not planning on knocking.
Somehow we moved past complicated
and straight into crazy.
What I did to Cayden James,
you think that's crazy?
This is manning up.
"Manning up." I hate that phrase.
Okay, let's talk this through.
If the Quadrant is as powerful
as you say,
who knows what kind of firepower
they have in there?
You're selling yourself short, kiddo.
You're better than 10 men.
And if there's more than 10?
Trust me.
While I appreciate
your self-confidence,
you could be overestimating
your powers of persuasion
by just a little bit.
You might not be their favorite
person in the world,
considering what we've just done
to the prince of hair gel.
I said, trust me.
And I would find it
a whole lot easier to do so
if you could just tell me why
it is so important
for you to be a part
of this exclusive club.
There are other ways
you can build your empire.
It's not about empire-building.
It's about respect.
Right, which you want.
And you're willing to disrespect
yourself in order to get it from them.
- That's not how it is.
- Really?
Because that's how it looks
like it is.
Back at that bar,
you were talking about Jerry
like he's still haunting you.
Jesse. It's "Jesse." And he does.
Little bastard was right,
I'm a loser.
Well, not anymore.
Hey, now you're a king.
Forget about him.
I can't.
I was afraid of Jesse for so long
that all I had was my fear.
So I named that fear.
- "The Dragon."
- That's cute.
I've lived with the Dragon
for so long
that it's all I had.
But now being a part of the Quadrant,
I'm gonna have something else.
That type of power,
well, I'll never be nothing again.
You remind me of the guy
that brought me here.
To this Earth.
He had so much hate inside of him,
it took control over him.
I control the Dragon.
It doesn't control me.
We're here.
You coming or not?
Glad you decided to come.
Someone's got to make sure
you don't get yourself killed.
That's why I'm glad.
If the Quadrants are everything
you say they are,
they're gonna see this coming.
Maybe. But family can be blinding.
You think they saw that coming?
We got incoming.
That sounds like a little bit more
than the 11 guys he said there were.
Had to soften the beach.
C-4 sends a message.
Why don't you send another one?
Now the beach is soft.
I went through a lot of trouble
to get to this meeting.
It didn't have to be though.
You killed my son.
C-4 killed your son.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Who we are?
Yeah.
It's why I wanted to meet.
If you know who we are,
you know I'm not going to kill you
for what you did to my boy.
Well, that's a relief.
I'm going to send you someplace
far away from here.
To a hospital I own.
They know every way there is to keep
a man alive
as other men carve pieces out of him.
Sure.
Sure, you could go that way.
You could try.
But if you do,
it'll cost you billions.
Annually.
Take him.
But make sure he doesn't die.
Wait.
He killed my boy.
Frankly, I'm surprised your idiot son
made it this far.
Talk as if your life
depended upon it. Because it does.
Like I said,
it wasn't supposed to be this way.
Mr. Cartier's son
was supposed to arrange this meeting
without bloodshed.
But Cartier Sr., he wanted
to go another way.
Because you're not fit to be
in the same room as us.
You're a street thug.
Not even qualified to work on
one of our crews.
I came to this meeting
because I have
a business proposition.
You know what's happening
in Star City, right?
I see it's falling apart.
I've seen chaos.
No, no, no. Controlled chaos.
What you see as dysfunction,
I see a machine
running on full efficiency.
I control the PD, City Hall,
the ports, the rails...
I control everything. And it could
all be yours. All of it.
In exchange for one thing.
One thing.
A seat
at this table.
I don't see an empty chair.
Even if there was one,
I would never sit beside the man
who killed my own blood.
He pushed me to it.
And he pushed and he pushed,
and he pushed.
A man's got his limitations.
And you are mine.
Look at you.
A street thug
who couldn't even keep himself
out of prison. You're nothing.
A loser.
Oh.
Looky here.
That's an empty seat.
We are successful because we're
deliberate, disciplined and precise.
We're not animals killing
each other for scraps.
We are civilized. This is not.
But your proposal intrigues us,
Mr. Diaz.
We'd like to hear more.
Let's get started.
What's wrong?
You got what you wanted.
You're not a loser anymore.
You are a legitimate crime lord.
And yet, you still seem on edge.
You think a ring and a seat
at the table changes things for me?
I think we ran a gauntlet
because you thought it would.
It's not over yet.
There's still one last thing
I have to care of.
Can I help you?
Oliver?
There are no survivors
in the explosion that consumed
a city block in the Glades
earlier this evening.
Given the power of the blast,
experts say that
forensics may be required
to determine the fate
of the Green Arrow.
Come on.
Hey, you.
- Oh, my God.
- You okay?
Oh, my God.
I saw the explosion on the news
and you were right
in the middle of it.
Yeah. No, I fired a grappling arrow.
It flew backwards,
right out of there. I'm fine.
- Well, I'm not.
- Okay.
Worrying about you out here is...
Well, it's completely different from
worrying about you in the bunker.
Right, because when
you're in the bunker
you feel like
you can make a difference.
I can. I can make a difference.
I can deploy backup. I can do...
I don't know, I can do something.
Out here...
I'm helpless out here.
You aren't helpless anywhere. Ever.
And I'm not helpless either.
All right?
I made a promise
to that guy in there.
I would always come back.
William made an excellent point
when he said
you coming back is not always
going to be your decision.
William does make excellent points.
But I made the promise anyway.
I'm making the same promise to you.
Right here, and right now.
Felicity,
I will always come back.
Let's go.
I've been waiting an hour.
Get up the stairs.
I know you hate waiting.
Who's this?
That last thing
I have to take care of.
I've got kids.
They need me, please. Please.
Don't hurt me. Whatever you want,
I can give it to you.
You're lucky if you got two dimes
to rub together
on a good day.
How do you know me?
What?
How do I know you?
I've known you my whole life.
What?
Laurel, meet Jesse Frederico.
Jesse,
meet Laurel.
I don't think people are supposed
to know that Laurel's working
with a crime lord.
"Crime lord." Crime lord.
I love the sound of that.
You really don't remember me?
Chillón.
Diaz?
That is really disappointing.
I thought I made a bigger impression.
On your knees.
Hey, what are you doing?
Getting my payback.
I think that this is
a little bit more than payback.
See that?
I took this from the fire.
I stuck my hand
right in.
I had blisters.
I had raw, cracked skin.
For weeks!
Hey, Jesse.
Hey.
You still like fire?
Ricardo.
I promised myself
when the time was right
that I'd get my payback...
When I wasn't a loser.