Previously on "Arrow"...
These people,
they're volunteers?
True believers.
Thank you
for your service,
your mind,
and your belief in me.
What happened?
The prisoners were out
of their cells.
Miss Lance, I want you to give
your father a message.
Err!
Help! Help
in here, please!
And, Ollie, I know that
I am not the love of your life...
But you will always be
the love of mine.
Out of the way!
- What happened?
- I don't know. She was fine.
Time of death 11:59.
A life that hasn't
had a chance to fully grow
and live out its purpose
in this world
is a life that has been taken
from this earth too soon.
Oliver Queen, whom I'm told
is practically family,
will be delivering the eulogy.
Mr. Queen.
Mr. Queen, are you ready?
Um, I could probably
say a few words.
Tommy Merlyn was--was one
of the greatest people
that I've ever known.
He was--he was
so much more than just...
A billionaire playboy.
I loved him.
I loved him in--
in every way
you could possibly love someone.
And so did Oliver...
And I'm sure if Oliver
could be here today
he would say so...
But clearly,
it's too painful.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry. I...
Ok.
Excuse me.
Are you a relati--
Oliver, softly:
Doctor, he's her father.
I'm, um,
terribly sorry for your loss.
These are
her belongings.
I'll--I'll take care
of those.
Laurel.
Baby.
We should get you
out of here.
I love you, too.
Give that baby girl
a kiss for me.
Didn't expect to see
you standing there.
Where else
would I go?
How's Lyla?
She and baby Sara are
at a Argus safe house.
I have an army buddy
looking after Carly and Andy Jr.
You worried
about your brother?
I don't think he would
do anything
to hurt my family,
but...I don't know.
Clearly, I never
knew him.
All right, John.
As the...
World's leading expert
in blaming yourself,
please don't do it.
You warned me,
Oliver.
Straight up,
you warned me.
If I'd listened to you
instead of trusting my brother,
Laurel would be
alive right now.
You can't know that.
On behalf of Mayor Adams
and everyone at city hall,
I'm very sorry
to announce the death
of assistant district attorney
Laurel Lance.
Miss Lance was conducting
a deposition
of Damien Darhk prior
to tonight's incident
in Iron Heights
correctional facility.
I'm informed
by the Department of Corrections
that Mr. Darhk remains
at large
and is the leading suspect
in Miss Lance's death.
I'm gonna get
some air.
John.
Smith & Wesson
460XVR revolvers,
50-Cal Desert Eagles,
Boberg 9-mil semiautos.
15 large,
and they're all yours.
How about it?
♪ Arrow 4x19 ♪
Canary Cry
Original Air Date on April 27, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hi. I didn't know--
you called
for the team.
What's going on, Oliver?
Well...
Darhk is out there,
and he has his magic back.
As much as I'm sure
all of us want to
climb up inside
of our own grief--
We have to get
that son of a bitch.
Definitely,
but we haven't
even put her
in the ground yet.
Uh, Captain?
Page 3.
This was last night
a-a-after Iron Heights.
This article says that
she used a Sonic weapon
against the dealer
and--and the buyer.
Guys, CCTV footage
from last night's attack.
S-Sara came back.
All the crazy things
that we've seen.
Maybe my baby--
my baby girl, maybe she's not gone.
I--I mean, we--
we saw her...
Yeah,
but, you know,
I mean, ev-everyone
thought Oliver was dead
when the Gambit
went down.
Everyone thought
ray Palmer was dead,
your brother.
Captain, I know.
I know,
but this is different.
John's right.
This bag
from the hospital
was supposed to contain
all of Laurel's belongings.
Supposed to?
Sonic device is missing.
That explains it.
There were people
in and out
of Laurel's room--
doctors, nurses,
orderlies.
Wait. You think
someone took it?
Yeah.
Laurel.
Uh, Captain, let's not
go there just yet.
Now you don't think
that with everything
that we have seen,
that we have all seen,
that there is a ch-chance that
Laurel is back?
Cisco keyed the Sonic device
to Laurel's vocal cords.
No one else is supposed
to be able to use that.
Right, right.
What do you think?
Quentin.
Yeah.
Dr. Schwartz--ahem.
I'd like to thank you
for your discretion
throughout all
of this.
Doctor-patient
privilege,
and in any case,
she, uh, helped this city.
I mean, the least
I can do is help her
and you.
At least 12 staffers
saw me bring her
into the hospital
last night.
And they saw
the Black Canary,
but we operated
on Laurel Lance,
who I believe was
injured
during an Iron Heights
prison riot.
There was a Black Canary
sighting last night.
This person was wearing
a Sonic device,
the same Sonic device
that was taken
from Laurel's belongings
in her room.
Are you saying--
I have reason to believe
that someone
walked into her room
and took it.
Now can you put me
on a path?
There's
a frequent flyer.
Frequent flyer?
What does that mean?
A patient who pays
repeated visits to the E.R.
Now I've treated
her a few times,
and there's
something--
there's something
off about her?
Mm-hmm.
Would you give me
her name?
Doctor-patient
privilege applies
to all my patients,
Mr. Queen.
Yeah.
Oliver?
I'm sorry. I...
I didn't know
where else to go and, uh...
Do you want to
come inside?
I don't think that
it's the best idea.
I'm sorry they didn't
let your mom attend the funeral.
It was a nice service.
Tommy would have
liked it.
He would have liked it more
if you would have
said a few words.
I stayed up
all night.
I was working
on a eulogy,
and...
I just filled
page after page with...
Stories of us,
but then I realized
that I just didn't
have the right to say any
of those things.
What are you
talking about?
Oliver, Tommy loved you.
Laurel,
I failed him.
I came back from that island
with another chance.
It was a chance
to help people.
It was...
It was a chance
to make this city better...
And I couldn't,
and now
Tommy's dead.
Ahem.
Oliver...
You can't blame
yourself.
You'd blame me, too,
if you knew the truth.
What truth?
That was Oliver.
Laurel's still,
you know, there.
So he thinks he has
a lead on some woman
who recently visits
the emergency room a lot.
I'm gonna try
and cross-reference
facial recog
with last night's attack
with the hospital
security footage.
Hey.
At the hospital,
you said that
you'd never forgive
yourself for what happened.
Andy's working
with Darhk,
has been
the entire time.
He helped him
find the idol,
helped him
out of jail.
Oliver warned me,
but I pretty much
told him
to go to hell.
Laurel is dead
because of me.
I don't know what happened.
I wasn't there.
I don't know what to say.
There's nothing
to say.
Thank you for everything
at the hospital.
I don't think any of us were ready
to talk to the media.
One of the few
advantages of dating
a political operative,
I guess.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to joke.
Please. I could--
I could use some jokes,
anything to keep
my mind off of...
Everything.
Speaking of actually,
you--
you never told me why
you became
a political operative
anyway.
Alex Davis.
You work for them!
What are you
talking about?
Ollie.
What's going on?
Alex just got
attacked by some girl
wearing Laurel's
Sonic device.
Do you know
where she went?
You're dressed like
a friend of mine.
Why?
Why did you
abandon us?
We needed your help,
and all you cared about
were your friends!
You didn't care
about any of us.
What are you
talking about?
You left us.
You left us
at Reddington!
You left us there to die.
You failed this city.
It wasn't Laurel,
but it was sure like seeing a ghost.
And hearing one.
That Sonic device
has been modified.
My ear plugs did
not do a thing.
The Sonic device is what shouldn't
have done a damn thing.
You said Cisco keyed it
specifically to Laurel?
It should have
only worked with Laurel.
The crazy
part is that this girl is using it
at much higher decibels than
Laurel ever did.
Ok. So who
is this girl?
When she attacked Alex,
she accused him
of working
for someone.
Ruvé Darhk?
HIVE. She said
the Green Arrow left them
at Reddington to die.
What's Reddington?
Reddington
industrial is where
Darhk held you all
hostage over the holidays.
You think this girl is
one of HIVE's prisoners.
They weren't prisoners, remember?
They were volunteers.
Right, but still, let's check
missing persons
for a family with at least one
teenage daughter
who went missing
over Christmas.
The Sharp family.
Mom and dad's bodies
were found two days after Christmas.
Cause of death hypoxia.
Could be HIVE's
gas chamber.
What about
the daughter?
Class president,
academic decathlete, gymnast,
basically a 16-year-old
badass in the making.
She never even missed
a day of school.
Until her parents
met Damien Darhk, I'm guessing.
She said we left
them there to die, and we did.
What do you mean?
All those people
at Reddington.
There of their own
choosing, Oliver.
And we know that HIVE
drugs people
to make them susceptible
to suggestion.
She told me that
we failed this city.
She's not wrong.
Thanks for coming.
I fear I lack the words
to convey the true depths
of my sympathy.
To lose a child once
is unimaginable,
but for it to be
both children...
Look. I know you and I
haven't always been
on the same side
of things,
but, uh, Laurel, you know,
she thought of you as a friend.
Just as I thought
of her.
She brought me
comfort during
a difficult
time period,
the word will be
a darker place without her.
Yeah. Well, not for long.
Ok. I got all her things.
What else do I need?
I'm afraid I don't
understand.
What else do I
have to bring for her
when she comes out of this,
you know, Lazarus Pit thing?
I would do anything
for your daughter,
but I destroyed
the Pit months ago.
Um, ok. Well, there's
got to be,
uh, something else.
I am so very sorry.
So you don't want
to help me.
Fine. I'll find some other way
to bring her back.
I've been scouring traffic
cameras for Evelyn,
but I keep
striking out.
What are you
doing here?
Thinking.
Which is
Oliver-speak
for beating
yourself up.
Thought you were
reformed from that.
Feels like as good
a time as any to bring it back.
Because of Laurel or because of what
the girl said?
Bit of both.
I tried to do the right thing,
and I came up short.
I came up short
for that girl...
And for Laurel.
Maybe I shouldn't
feel responsible, but I do.
Yeah.
It's going around.
You mean John?
- I mean me.
- Hmm?
John was looking
for someone to absolve him,
reassure him that what happened
wasn't his fault,
and I couldn't
do it.
I think for a second
I let him blame himself
because for a minute
it saved me from blaming me.
I should have
been there.
I wasn't there with the team
in the bunker.
I know I would have just been
behind a keyboard.
I know it seems
like hubris,
but I've made
a difference before,
and I can't help
think that if I was there,
you know, maybe
she'd still be here.
Do you know why
I always blame myself
in situations
like this?
Because at least
it's an answer.
Sometimes, we just
need a reason
when a situation is
completely unreasonable.
Hello?
Lyla called
asking for John,
except he's supposed
to be checking in on her.
I'm getting
a bad feeling about this.
I have trackers
on all of you.
I'll check, and I'll get
back to you.
Well, tell
those curious
that the city has
undertaken
to do a massive upgrade
of the sewage system.
I mean, what happens
below ground
is simply not
their concern.
Why are we stopping?
Get down!
Get out!
What do you think
you're doing?
I am the mayor
of this city.
I don't care who you are!
You're gonna be a lot less
if you don't get out
of that limo right now!
Move.
Can I help you
with something?
I mean, I always enjoy spending time
with my constituents.
Shut up!
You know who I am.
You know exactly
who I am,
and you know where
my brother is!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Stop lying!
Fine. We'll do this
your way.
Maybe you can give your
husband a message for me
and let him know I'm not
playing games with him anymore.
Get away from her, John.
Agh! Stay out
of my way!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Trying to find Andy!
By attacking
the mayor of the city?
By going after
Damien Darhk's wife!
It doesn't matter if
she's Darhk's wife.
She is the mayor. She has the media.
She has the police.
I don't give a damn!
Ugh!
I'm so angry,
I can hardly breathe.
I know.
Every minute he's
out there is a--
is a--is another minute
he can hurt someone I love.
John...
I know...
But this isn't
who you are.
I don't know--
I don't know who
I am anymore, Oliver.
All I know is,
all I can hold on to is that...
I have to find
my brother.
And--and--and
do what?
Laurel's gone,
and finding Andy
and whatever you're
gonna do to him,
it's not gonna
bring her back,
but if she were
here,
she'd tell you the same thing that
I'm gonna tell you.
You cannot forget
who you are,
and we...
We can never
become them.
Where have
you guys been?
Doesn't matter.
Have we had any luck
tracking down Evelyn Sharp?
No. I keep hitting
dead ends.
Not the best choice
of words.
News alert.
Tonight, my security
detail and I were attacked
by one of these
lawless vigilantes
who claim to protect
this city.
This attack came
less than 24 hours
after another vigilante
named the Black Canary
assaulted my chief of staff
Alex Davis.
Now these same
masked criminals
were confirmed to be
at Iron Heights
when one of this city's
beloved civil servants
Laurel Lance was
fatally injured.
Well, tonight,
I say no more!
Tonight, I asked
district attorney Wallace
to issue arrest warrants
for these so-called vigilantes,
beginning with Mr. Davis'
attacker the Black Canary.
We will dedicate the arrest
and prosecution of this
so-called Black Canary
to A.D.A. Laurel Lance,
one of this city's
brightest lights.
Shut it off.
Thank you.
She knows Laurel was
the Black Canary.
And now she has
the whole police force
gunning for a scared,
frightened teenage girl.
I'll call Alex.
Ok. We need to find
Evelyn before the SCPD does.
Yes.
Yeah?
Mr. Lance's agony
is understandable,
but its pain is
sharpened by denial.
I fear that--
that refusal to accept reality
will lead Mr. Lance
to take desperate action.
Thank you for
letting me know.
I will keep
an eye on him.
Oliver.
Are you all right?
Our friend was killed
at the hands of a man
that I am currently
powerless to stop,
and his wife is dragging her legacy
through the mud.
Nyssa, after everything
that she's done,
after everything that
she's stood for,
it just doesn't
seem right.
I'm glad you finally
decided to come over.
Well, it's been a week.
I feel like Tommy
would be pissed at me
if I didn't eventually
come out of my self-pity.
Heh. Yeah.
He loved you
so much.
This was right
after you won
student body president
our senior year.
Do you remember
how I won?
Of course. You were
the most deserving candidate by far.
Well, gift baskets encouraging people
to vote for me,
that didn't hurt either.
That was Tommy's idea.
No, but seriously,
it's easy
to buy people off
with money
that you didn't
even earn.
You did all
the hard work.
Hmm. We always did
make a great team.
Yeah.
You know, I was thinking
about what you said
in the hallway
after Tommy's funeral
and wanting to help
make the city a better place.
We still can.
Laurel Lance always
trying to save the world.
Yeah, but it doesn't
have to be just me.
You can, too.
We can do it together.
I'm really excited
about the future, Ollie.
Wha--ohh.
There's no one
in there.
It's where the League
of Assassins hang
their black hoods.
No. That's right,
but there is no Lazarus Pit
and no League in there.
No, but there might
be something,
just some clue,
all right?
Next step
on the trail.
There's no trail,
Quentin!
Laurel is gone, and there is no
bringing her back.
No, no, no.
To hell with that,
and if you don't
want to help me,
to hell with you,
too!
I am helping you.
No, you're not
because you know why?
Because you do not
know what it is like to lose a child.
No idea!
But I have lost a father,
I have lost a mother,
and I have lost Laurel!
We have lost her!
We have.
If there was a way,
if there was any way
to bring her back,
I would find it,
and I would do it...
But there isn't
for either of us.
You don't understand.
When we lost Sara,
when I became a drunk,
when no one else
believed in me, she did.
She's always been there.
She's my rock!
I...
She was my rock.
I can't do this.
Oh, God. Oh, no.
Oh, God.
She can't be gone.
- John.
- You got something?
Yeah, an apology.
I never should have
let you think that
you could have prevented what
happened to Laurel,
not even
for a second.
I was just dealing with my own guilt
for not being there.
You have nothing to be
sorry about, Felicity.
If I had listened to Oliver and not
trusted my brother,
Laurel would be alive.
You don't know that.
Oliver keeps saying
the same thing,
except I keep going
through this
over and over again
in my head,
and it--
it's true.
The only thing
I don't quite get
is how I could have
been so blind.
Well, Andy's your
brother, you know?
We make exceptions
for family.
Yeah...
And I'm the one
constantly telling Oliver
not to have a blind spot
for family.
And here you are taking
the blame for something
that's not your fault.
You're just one
illegitimate child away
from a really awesome Oliver Queen
impersonation,
but just like
we tell Oliver,
what happened
was not your fault,
and Laurel would have
wanted you to know that.
- What's that?
- Evelyn Sharp.
Facial recognition
picked her up outside
of Star City Plaza hotel.
What's she
doing there?
That's where
Ruvé Darhk is.
She's getting
revenge for her family.
Well, if she's gonna
kill Ruvé Darhk, my vote is yes.
It's not just
killing Ruvé Darhk.
In that mask,
in that costume,
she'd be killing
Laurel's legacy.
Keep your eyes peeled.
She's out there somewhere.
I'm on site.
There's no sign of Evelyn.
Yeah. So is the anti-vigilante
task force,
and they have come
ready to play.
We need to find
that girl before they do.
Hey!
I'm heading in.
Ma'am, you shouldn't
be in here.
Funny.
I was gonna tell you
the same thing.
The Black Canary
is in the building.
I need to get you
to a secure location.
Oh, you'll do
no such thing.
Let her come.
Let her try.
I found her.
Second floor,
200 feet from
the Liberty ballroom,
Ruvé Darhk, and a lot
of a lot of innocent people.
On it.
Unh!
Don't!
Don't go in there.
Get away.
I can't do that.
You can't do this.
Now I know you want
revenge on HIVE
for what they did
to your parents,
but this isn't
the way.
It's the only way
I have left.
Evelyn, don't!
Agh!
You failed this city!
I understand that
you're trying
to make
things right.
That is not how you
get justice done.
What did you know
about the real Black Canary?
What did you know about what
she stood for?
She was there that night.
I saw her.
Then you saw what kind
of person she was.
She was a hero.
Now maybe you are
wearing that mask for a reason,
but right now,
I need you to ask yourself
what would the Black Canary
want you to do?
Come on.
Arrest him!
I've seen this
movie before.
No sign of Evelyn.
Kid must have found out
I was tracking her.
Really missed her out
there tonight.
In a way, she was
out there.
In spirit, I mean,
not in a Lazarus Pit kind of way,
and ultimately, she
made the right choice.
I think Laurel would have liked that
she inspired someone.
How can you
say that?
Evelyn Sharp just
destroyed
Laurel's memory
out there tonight.
Now the Black Canary's
only gonna be remembered
for whatever
Evelyn's done.
Evelyn's not
the Black Canary.
Well, to every reporter
and person with a camera
in the room tonight,
she was.
Ruvé Darhk's gonna make sure
everybody sees that footage.
As far as the rest
of the world is concerned,
the Black Canary is
now a gun-toting, would-be murderer.
I'm not gonna let
that happen.
Oh, Quentin.
I never thought
we'd be here again.
Me, neither.
I figured we were
punished enough first time around.
We were.
Oh, at least
for a while,
and then Sara
came back to us.
I don't think that's
gonna happen this time.
How can you
say that?
Our girls always
come back to us, Quentin.
Yeah, maybe before
but not this time.
I'm sorry, Dinah.
She's gone.
She's never
coming back.
She's...
Mr. Queen has
requested to say a few words.
This, uh...
This doesn't seem right.
Uh, I knew
Laurel Lance for...
Almost her entire life.
She was my friend,
and I loved her.
Before she died,
I was--I was lucky enough
to hear her tell me
that she loved me, too.
Laurel Lance became a lawyer
to help people
who may have appeared helpless.
She wanted to give
a voice to the silent,
but just being a lawyer
wasn't enough.
She wanted to do more
for those people
and for this city
because she loved
this city so much.
By now, everyone knows
that Laurel was killed
in the Iron Heights
prison riot,
and while it's true that she was
an assistant district attorney,
that's not what she was
doing there that night.
Before she died,
Laurel told me the truth.
Laurel Lance was
the Black Canary.
In the past few days,
I have had to sit
and listen to people
try and paint
the Black Canary as a criminal.
She was not a criminal.
She was a hero.
She was a hero
in every way
that a person can be,
and if Laurel were here,
I know that she would
expect all of us
to live up to the example
that she set.
She'd want us
to save our city.
Oliver, voice-over: Dear Laurel,
I wrote this letter
because I don't
have the courage
to see the disappointment
on your face.
I know you're gonna go on
to do amazing things,
to help people, and to raise
this city up
because that's who you are,
that's who you've
always been,
and that's why I
have to go away.
I would only hold you back.
You're the hero, Laurel.
Maybe I'll come back eventually,
but for now, I have to
spend some time alone.
I hope someday you'll
understand my decision.
Never doubt my love for you.
You've always seen
the best in me
because you've always
been the best of me.
All my love, Oliver.
I'm sorry I missed
the funeral.
- Zoom?
- Yeah.
There was a time I would have thought
this was my fault,
that I brought
this darkness upon us,
but now I know it's
not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility
to do what?
To end it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Is there anything
I can do?
I want to be
left alone.
Are you ok?
Are you?
No.
You know what you
have to do, right?
You have to kill
the son of a bitch.
I know.
I don't know how.
Because of his magic.
His ma--
it's too strong.
I've seen it before,
back on Lian Yu,
and it is not
just magic.
It's darkness,
and whenever I have
come up against it,
I have gone nowhere.
It--
he feels
unstoppable.
I refuse to
believe that.
And I refuse to let
you believe that.
If Darhk wins,
Laurel died for nothing.
I fell in love with you
for many reasons,
and one of those reasons
is is that you always find a way,
and you have to find
a way now
for Laurel,
for the city...
For all of us.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.