My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years, I was stranded
on an island
with only one goal...
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish...
To bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become...
Something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
[Thunder]
The company Mrs. Queen
invested in doesn't exist.
Tempest purchased a
warehouse in Starling City.
I could never really tell if the
playboy thing was all an act,
but I guess after a while,
it doesn't really matter.
He's a vigilante.
He's a damn criminal.
Here's the security footage from the exchange building.
What do you want me to look for?
I want you to look for anything
that's out of the ordinary.
What is that? Play that again.
Oliver Queen,
you're under arrest
on suspicion
of obstruction of justice,
aggravated assault,
trespassing...
- Are you out of your mind?!
- and murder.
Dinner.
Ah, come...
hey, I got an idea,
why don't you let me
shoot that thing
and you can go
pick up the bloody,
dead, disgusting animal.
What?
Try. Breathe.
Everything, breathe.
Breathe, aim... Fire.
Here.
Aim that tree.
Breathe.
[Branches rustling]
[Speaking native language]
What does that mean?
You will die badly.
Get.
[Muffled yelling]
Ahh! [Groaning]
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
Wait, wait!
You can't leave me here!
Don't do this to me, please!
Oh-oh! No!
Please! I didn't
do anything!
Oliver: The police think
they know who I am.
They think I'm the vigilante.
The man in the hood terrorizing
the city's criminals.
They also think
they have me trapped.
That I have no way out.
They're only half right.
Downloaded from
GlowGaze.Com
Oliver: This is a mistake.
I'll be asking you
a few questions,
standard stuff for the report.
Have you been arrested before?
That's ok, I know the
answer to that one,
plenty of times.
Like I said, this is a mistake.
Far as I can tell,
the only mistake I made
was not shooting you down at
the docks when I had a chance.
I am not who you think I am.
Oh, you're exactly
who I think you are.
You're a dangerous menace who
doesn't care about who he hurts,
except now you're doing
it with bows and arrows
instead of trust funds
and yachts.
Detective... You hate me.
I get it.
But that doesn't make me
a vigilante.
No. The security camera
footage of you
at the Unidac auction
with a green hood
does that pretty well.
And as I said again,
I ran into the stairwell
once I heard the shooting.
I saw a duffel that I thought
maybe belonged to the shooter.
I grabbed it, looked inside and saw...
A hood.
And what about harassing
Adam hunt?
That just happened
to take place
right across the street from
your little homecoming bash.
Those were coincidences.
No.
When they pile up like that,
it becomes evidence.
His parents are here.
Tell them to wait.
I want to see my son.
I'm in the middle of
an interrogation here!
Detective Lance,
I know you hate my family,
but I had no idea
that you'd go so far
to arrest my son
without any grounds whatsoever!
I have solid grounds,
and I have evidence.
Which you can present to Mr. Queen's
attorney when he gets here.
Until then, this interrogation
is over, Detective.
Sure. You have
15 minutes.
[Door closes]
Detective Lance appears to be
on some personal vendetta.
He is.
He blames me for the
death of his daughter.
He also thinks that
I dress up in a green hood
and shoot people...
With arrows.
The important thing is not to say
anything until your attorney gets here.
Fine. I want Laurel.
[Both scoff] Brilliant.
Oliver...
I don't think
your ex-girlfriend
can be counted on
to be objective here.
She knows me better
than anyone.
She knows that I could
never be this guy.
Walter, you say Lance
has a vendetta?
Yes.
I think Laurel
can get him off of it.
He raised her
to do the right thing.
That includes representing
an innocent man.
So... Mom.
Please.
[Indistinct chatter]
Laurel.
Mrs. Queen! What are you...
it's Oliver.
Something's happened.
It's been all over the news.
[Sighs]
These charges are ludicrous.
I know.
Can I ask you,
who's representing him?
Well, that's why I'm here.
He wants you to represent him.
Me?
Yes. I told him
it was a mad idea,
but to be Frank,
I am desperate.
He says if you don't
represent him,
then he doesn't want
any attorney.
Mrs. Queen, my father
is the arresting officer.
Yes.
And I don't think
it's a good idea
for me to represent someone
who I've been involved with.
Listen, I am sorry
for what your family
is going through...
no apologies.
Your idealism, I think,
is why my son,
for all his mistakes,
is so smitten with you.
Regardless, it was a
bad idea on his part,
and I am sorry if I made
you feel uncomfortable.
Docket 81941,
people vs. Oliver Queen.
Murder, aggravated assault,
assault with intent,
menacing and trespassing.
Where's your attorney,
Mr. Queen?
I'm representing myself, judge.
I'm not sure that's the
wisest course, Mr. Queen.
I think it is.
I'm innocent.
Then we'll consider
that your plea.
Thank you.
Now, as to bail...
your honor,
Mr. Queen's family
owns a pair of private jets,
and, well, on the subject
of their wealth,
I would point out that there
is virtually no bail amount
that can guarantee
his presence at trial.
So then I guess
it's a good thing
that the people's case
is so circumstantial.
Dinah Laurel Lance, your honor.
I'd like to file my appearance
on behalf of the defendant.
Mr. Queen's wealth
should not deprive him
of the right to be
released on bail
while under the
presumption of innocence.
He is a flight risk.
Then minimize the risk.
The defendant is willing to
submit to home confinement
and electronic monitoring
through the wearing
of a UKG45 administrated
ankle device.
No, he wouldn't.
Sold.
Your honor...
Bail is set at $15 million.
$5 million bond.
Defendant to see probation
for the fitting
of a GPS device.
I knew you couldn't resist
saving my ass.
You're going to make me
regret this, aren't you?
No. It's going
to be like old times.
Fortunately for you
with the legal case,
there's no way that
you're this vigilante.
I agree.
Because he's actually
trying to make a difference.
We both know that's not
really your style.
Mom. It's not that bad.
Ok. This device has a direct
line into the precinct.
Stay on the property,
you're golden.
Any questions?
Yes.
I'm having a sizable
get together
here tomorrow evening, and there
is a better than likely chance
it spills into
the outdoor pool.
Pool, that's fine.
Step on the grass,
they're sending a SWAT team
to forcibly subdue you.
- Thank you, officer.
- Of course.
A "sizable get together"?
I'm confined to this house
for the foreseeable future. I might
as well make the most of it.
And this party
is going to be themed.
I'm thinking prison,
uh, burning man meets
"Shawshank Redemption".
The invite says, "come before
Oliver Queen gets off."
Maybe a party's not
in the best of taste,
you know, considering
the circumstances.
Tommy, the circumstances
are why we're having
the party in the first place.
I want people to know that I'm
not worried about any of this.
Well, that makes one of us.
Before you start yelling...
Why would I yell?
You're only defending the man
that killed your sister.
Oliver did not kill Sarah!
If it wasn't for him, she
wouldn't have been on that boat.
Have you consider
the possibility
that that's the reason
you're trying
to make him out
to be this... this menace?
No, it is the video tape,
is the suspicious timing,
that is the reason!
This is Oliver Queen
we're talking about.
He wrecks fancy cars
and he dates models.
He doesn't kill people.
No, he just uses them,
like he used Sarah
and like he used you,
and he's only asked you
to be his lawyer to get at me.
No, he asked me to be his lawyer
to get through to you.
You hate the hood
and you hate Oliver,
and you want more than anything
for them to be the same person.
But Oliver isn't the reason
why Sarah died.
Or the reason mom left.
I don't have to listen to this.
By the way...
You're not the only
one who misses them.
[Exhales]
[Sighs]
[Knock on door]
Yup?
Thank you for coming.
Shut the door.
I guess it was just
a matter of time
before the police
caught up with you.
Except they didn't.
Oliver, they got you on video.
I knew the security camera
was there,
just like I knew the police
would review the footage
and arrest me.
All part of the plan.
So you wanted to get arrested?
Well, I returned
to Starling City
and a few days later,
the vigilante appears.
Sooner or later, somebody was
going to make the connection.
So what part of serving
yourself up to the cops
will help you avoid going to
prison for the rest of your life?
There's more to it.
Well, there better be,
for your sake,
because your family is
freaking out downstairs.
Oliver, your mother and your
sister just got you back,
and now you're going to put them
through a trial, maybe even worse?
Don't you care?
Of course I care.
The mission comes first.
Who is he?
Leo Mueller.
German arms dealer.
Suspected in the theft
of a hundred m249
squad automatic weapons.
Ok...
Last night he arrived in
Starling City to sell the guns.
Oliver, don't you imagine
there's enough trouble
you're in this week
than to go after this guy?
I imagine what would happen
if a street gang
got their hands
on military-grade hardware.
I imagine our city's streets
turned into a war zone.
But you're under
house arrest, Oliver,
which means you can't
just go after this guy.
Look, for now, I would just
like you to shadow Mueller.
I would like you
to track his movements.
I want to know
where the buy is happening.
Ok.
And how am I supposed
to track him?
Well, you know us
billionaire vigilantes...
we do love our toys.
Ow!
Oooh.
[Beep]
Oh, well, that's sweet.
You wanted to see me, sir?
No. I didn't.
In fact, this meeting
isn't taking place.
How long have you been
head of security
at Queen consolidated, Josiah?
Going on seven years now, sir.
Sounds about right.
But what I'm about to tell you
will test the bounds
of your discretion.
You're aware
of the "Queen's gambit",
Robert Queen's
ill-fated yacht?
Well, I found it.
Sir, the boat went down in the
South China sea five years ago.
Which is why my discovery
of its remains
in a warehouse downtown was
unexpected, to say the least.
I want you to transfer
those remains
to a secure location.
Can I count on you?
[Chuckles]
What's going on, sir?
That's very much what
I'm trying to determine.
[Door closes]
Thank you both for coming.
No, thank you.
It's nice to get
out of the house.
I'll cut right to it. Detective
Lance arrested your client
without consulting
my office first.
So congratulations.
I am willing
to consider
a plea in this case.
Absolutely not.
Mr. Queen spent
five years in seclusion
on a deserted island,
cut off from civilization.
It is quite possible
he's suffering from some form
of post traumatic stress.
Given that, we would support
a plea of insanity.
Conditional on a period
of indeterminate incarceration
at a psychiatric facility.
No, thank you.
I'm not crazy.
Finally something we agree on.
He's not a nut,
he's a killing machine.
Actually, I'm neither.
There is nothing
you can say to me
that I would believe.
I'll take a polygraph.
Uh, polygraphs
are inadmissible.
In front of the jury.
I'll take a polygraph
in front of him.
He's the one
I need to convince.
I'm going to need a minute.
You're looking
at life in prison.
What Spencer
just offered you is a gift.
I'm not crazy.
I am innocent.
I kind of want
to take the polygraph.
And if I take it
and I fail, then...
I will consider making a deal.
Fine.
I'll set up the poly.
And I will tell Spencer
that we're not pleading out,
but Oliver, you have a family.
Friends. People
who actually care about you.
So don't, for one second,
think you're the only person
with something to lose here.
[Exhales] I'll be right back.
[Door closes]
[Groans]
Please, sit.
You're making me feel rude.
[Breathing heavily]
I do apologize for my men's
treatment of you.
[Opens can]
They're...
they're trained
to view any stranger
as hostile.
I'm Edward Fyers, by the way.
And you are?
I'm Oliver Queen.
I was shipwrecked here.
I don't... Know
for how long.
My family has money.
They have lots of money
you would be...
You'd be really well
compensated for my rescue.
Well, I look forward to that.
But for the moment,
let's just talk.
About what?
Well, for instance...
This gentleman.
Do you know him?
No.
No?
No. Who's he?
You're a poor liar.
I've been polite.
I'll offer you one more chance
before my manners leave me.
Hey, hey.
I don't know this guy.
I thought I was on this
island all by myself.
Do you know what
this island is named?
We're on Lian Yu...
mandarin for "purgatory",
and I can make it
feel like hell.
I don't know
why you're protecting him.
You're young, foolish.
Perhaps you don't know
why, either.
Think on that when
you're begging for death.
He's yours now.
Hey, sweetie.
One of the workers left a
keg too far from the bar.
Can you ask them
to move it please?
I got the ankle... thingie.
I don't want to set off
a SWAT invasion.
Hey!
All this stuff?
It's going to be
fine, I promise.
Yeah, well, when you and dad
left on the yacht,
you promised me I'd see you
in a few days.
Which didn't happen.
This is different than that.
I didn't do any of this
stuff, you know that.
Right?
You're out all the time.
You have those scars,
and since you've been back,
you've been acting really weird.
None of this makes me
some Robin Hood wannabe.
And you get me this.
I mean, it's an arrowhead.
Oh, man.
[Exhales] Thea, I bought that
in the gift shop
of the Beijing airport.
[Stammering]
Now I'm sort of happy
I didn't buy you
the shot glass
with the panda on it,
'cause then you'd be
worried I was panda man.
[Chuckles]
You know, I knew
you couldn't be
this person.
I-I just...
I can't lose you again.
Deal.
Moira. Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Yes. Could you please
make this quick?
I'm in the midst of somewhat
of a family emergency.
Yes, of course.
It's all over the local news.
[Chuckles]
Possibly even national.
Well, I know what you're thinking.
Do you?
My son is not the man
targeting the list.
The charges are preposterous.
Not according to the
district attorney,
assistant district attorney,
investigating Detective
in the police department
that filed charges against him.
That Detective has a
vendetta against my family.
Why? Is there
something untoward
about your family?
If so, something really needs
to be done about that.
Is your name Oliver Queen?
You don't know
who I am, Detective?
The questions are to
calibrate the polygraph.
Is your name Oliver Queen? Yes.
Were you born in Starling City
May 16th, 1985?
Yes.
Is your hair blue?
No.
Have you ever been to
iron heights prison?
No.
Are you the man
in this picture?
Where can I find the man
No.
You steal 40 million
dollars off Adam Hunt?
No, I didn't.
Were you marooned
on an island called Lian
Yu for 5 years? Yes.
How is that even relevant?
I don't need to show relevance,
but since you asked,
whatever happened
to your client on that island turned
him into a cold blooded killer.
No!
The physician that
examined you reported that
20% of your body is
covered in scar tissue.
[Screaming]
The machine won't work
unless you ask a question.
Did that happen to you there?
Yes.
When you came back,
you told everyone that you
were alone on that island.
Are you claiming
that your scars were...
Self-inflicted?
No.
I wasn't alone.
I didn't want to talk about what
happened to me on the island.
Why not?
Because the people
that were there tortured me.
Have you killed anyone?
Yes.
When I asked your daughter Sara
to come on my father's
yacht with me.
I killed your daughter.
I'd have to study the data,
but just eyeballing it,
he's telling the truth.
Hmm.
Can I assume that
you'll be recommending.
Ms. Spencer to drop
all charges against my client?
No.
I know a guilty man
when I see one.
He is guilty, whether
you can see it or not.
[Deep voice]
You're going to love this.
[Dance music playing]
[Music stops] Hi, everybody!
All: Hey!
I'm very touched that you came
to celebrate with me
before I am
sent up the river.
Closest neighbors
are six miles away,
so don't worry about the noise.
Actually, on second thought...
Let's wake those losers up!
[All cheering] Whoo!
[Dance music playing]
If you think this is what
prison's like,
you are in
for a rude awakening.
Mueller's car has been parked in the
warehouse district of the glades
for 45 minutes.
Yeah, that's a good
place for an arms deal.
Ok, since this is
going down tonight,
what do we do, drop a dime
on Mueller with the cops?
No, the man in the hood.
He's going to stop them.
Oliver, you can't
leave the house.
It doesn't have to be me
in the hood.
[Chuckles]
That's why you threw
this ridiculous party?
So you have a hundred witnesses
placing you here at the house
while I'm supposed to be across
town dressed as a vigilante?
I thought that it was
going to be good enough
just for you to be seen
in the hood.
I didn't count
on Mueller showing up
and I didn't count
on the possibility
that the glades
could be flooded
with machine guns.
Look.
I promise, it was
never my intention
to put you in harm's way.
Oliver, I didn't think joining your
crusade was ever going to be risk-free.
I just don't like being played.
Now you might have gotten used to
lying to everyone else in your life,
but I'm the one guy
you don't lie to.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
So am I going to jail?
No, man.
I got to stop an arms deal.
[Telephone rings]
Hello?
Mr. Steel, I'm sorry
to bother you, sir.
This is Mike Vogel
down in security.
But I have some
sad news for you.
The company's head
of security, Josiah Hudson,
was in a car accident tonight.
He's dead, sir.
♪ You said that you're
a freak in the sheets ♪
♪ that my eyes
had to see to believe ♪
Hello.
Do we have a legal meeting
or something?
Because I have friends over.
Do you think maybe you
can tear yourself away
from this inappropriately
themed rave
for a couple minutes?
Wow.
I can't remember the last time
that I've been in this room.
I can. Halloween, 2005.
We were getting ready
for Tommy's party.
Ah. Yes.
I wore those horrible fishnets.
I thought you looked good.
Listen...
I just wanted
to come by and apologize
for my father's behavior today.
During the polygraph.
You don't have
to apologize for him.
He has a right to feel
any way that he wants.
It wasn't just Sara, Ollie.
What do you mean?
After Sara died,
my father threw himself
into his work.
I think that's part
of the reason I'm an attorney.
He ran to the law
and I followed.
But my mother couldn't.
So she left him.
[Sighs]
Left us.
Look, I'm not trying
to tell you this
to make you feel bad, or worse.
I just... I really want you
to understand him.
Why don't you hate me?
You should.
I did.
For so long, I did, Ollie.
But after today,
I realized that...
I was so focused
on what happened to my family
that I didn't even
stop and wonder
what could have
happened to you.
[Inhales and exhales]
I didn't know about
the torture, or your scars.
What happened to you
on that island
was far more than you deserved.
And I was wrong
that I didn't ask you before,
but I'm asking you now.
I need to know.
I need to see.
Are you sure?
Yes.
How did you survive this?
There were times
when I wanted to die.
In the end...
There was something
I wanted more.
[Gasping]
No. Laurel,
you don't have to go.
Oh, God.
I have to.
Amazing.
You have resolve
I didn't credit you for.
Or perhaps he truly
doesn't know anything.
We should put him
out of his misery.
[Grunts]
[man speaking german]
It's an M249 machine gun.
Gas-powered, air-cooled,
fires up to 800 rounds
per minute.
[Whistles]
[Electricity crackles]
We need to move, now!
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
Move! Let's go!
[All grunting]
[Tires squealing]
Well.
I'm not accustomed
to being summoned
to the office
in the middle of the night.
Well, what was it
that was so important
that I had to race down here?
I found the "Queen's
gambit", Moira.
I know you secretly
had the boat salvaged.
I wanted to move it
to a more secure location
before confronting you about it.
In fact, I sent Josiah Hudson
to the warehouse for
precisely that purpose.
But he died mysteriously
in a car accident.
I hope you now have
a better understanding
of why it is I've been
so distant of late.
It's very disconcerting
to discover
that the person with whom
you share your home,
your bed and your heart
has been lying to you
so convincingly,
and I would be a fool
not to consider
all the things that you
have told me were lies.
Walter, you're my husband, I...
yes, I am.
Walter, please.
You've got to stop looking
into this, it's not safe.
You'll be... you'll be
upsetting people,
people with influence.
You are very far
out of your depth.
[Phone vibrates]
Diggle: Man in the hood, one,
gangbangers, zero.
[Knock on door] Hang on.
Yeah?
Mr. Queen, if you're
entertaining guests upstairs,
should I have
some drinks sent up?
No. It's just me up here and
I'm on my way back down.
Good job.
Now get back here.
[Grunting]
Yeah. Yep.
How did you know
I was in trouble?
Because when the guy
was fighting you,
he broke the ankle monitor.
Are you all right?!
I'm fine.
Oliver...
Mom. I promise.
This is on you.
By accusing my son publicly,
you've made him a target.
Do you have any idea
who attacked Oliver?
We haven't identified him.
Though it must be someone
with a grudge against
the hood, obviously.
What are you doing?
I got a call from my lieutenant.
An arms dealer was attacked
across town tonight.
By the vigilante. Multiple
witnesses put him there.
In light of that, all charges
against your son are being dropped.
I'm truly sorry for what's
happened to your family, Quentin.
But would you kindly get
the hell out of my house?
Mr. Lance...
Thank you.
[Zipper] Moira.
Did we have an appointment?
No, but I decided
to screw propriety after you
tried to have my son killed.
I'm sure you understand,
I was justified
in suspecting your son
of being the vigilante
targeting our associates.
I had to take steps.
And now that you know your
steps were taken in error,
that Oliver is not your enemy.
[Chuckles]
I offer my sincerest apologies.
I know you found out I
had the yacht salvaged,
just as I know you had
Josiah Hudson killed.
Well, accidents tend to befall
people who are too curious.
I've been the good soldier.
I've done everything you asked.
But if any member of my family
so much as gets a paper cut,
I will burn your
entire world to ashes.
[Groaning]
I tell you, island dangerous,
but you not tell them
where to find me.
You stronger than I thought.
Take it.
I lead them off, you stay.
Breathe.
You breathe,
you survive here longer.
No! I'm coming with you!
[Door opens]
Rough party.
My father told me
what happened.
Are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
These are your
polygraph results.
My father asked you if you'd
ever been to iron heights.
It's the prison where the
vigilante saved me last week.
It's also where you and I went
on our eighth grade field trip.
When you said that you
had never been there,
I thought maybe
you were just nervous,
or that you'd forgotten.
But then I looked
at your results,
and there is a slight flutter in
your answer to that question.
And if you lied on one,
you could have lied on others.
What happened to me
being too selfish
to be a masked crusader?
Oliver!
I saw your scars.
Do you want to know why I don't talk
about what happened to me there?
Because if people knew;
If you knew...
You'd see me differently.
And not as some...
Vigilante guy.
As damaged.
I don't sleep.
I barely eat.
I can barely sign my name,
let alone aim a bow and arrow.
After last night...
Clearly we're still
attracted to one another.
Oliver.
Nothing can ever
happen between us.
I know.
So you lied to her.
Or maybe you just gave her
a version of the truth.
I told her what
she needed to hear, Diggle.
She was too close.
Sad thing is, I think you
actually believe that.
I think things didn't go down
exactly how you planned.
You didn't count on so many
people having questions,
doubting you.
You didn't think about
what happens when you lie.
Thank you.
Especially when you lie to
the ones you love the most.
What is this?
Business trip.
I decided it's long overdue
for me to inspect
our holdings in Melbourne.
And how long will you be?
I don't know.
Diggle: When you were
stuck on that island
plotting your grand plan
to save the city,
I don't think you stopped
to consider the effect
it would have on the
people in your life.
Or how it might hurt you.
Let's go.
[Grunts]
[Stammering]
You're ok.
No, no, no.
Or how it might hurt them.
You're wrong.
I think about it all the time.
And just to be clear,
not being able to tell
my family the truth...
It doesn't hurt anyone
worse than it hurts me.
Where are you going?
Mueller still has to sell those
guns and I have to stop him.
Oliver...
He had his chance.
Man: 28 crates,
four guns in each crate,
$250,000 cash.
Take it or leave it.
That's the deal.
Leo Mueller,
you have failed this city.
[Arrow whistling]
For more new Episodes visit
GlowGaze.Com
Money.