This season on Arrow...
Either I'm willing to do
whatever is necessary,
or I shouldn't be out there at all.
One day, your actions might have
some unintended consequences.
Prometheus, you want revenge.
I'm going to show them
how everything you touch dies.
He calls himself Adrian Chase.
He means to destroy you utterly.
Your crusade was based on a lie.
Make it home, make it better,
right my wrongs. Survive.
NO!
You used your father's memory
to justify a killing spree.
I'm not going to kill you.
I am never going to give you
the satisfaction of being the man
- that you think I am.
- You're wrong.
Please help me.
Where is my son?
No! No! I said you let me go,
and I keep your loved ones safe.
I'll see you on the boat.
I know where he's taking them.
The name of the island
they found me on is Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin for purgatory.
What brought you back to the island?
Like I said...
I need your help.
What the hell's going on here?
We have a problem,
and I need you to get off the island.
I'm not going anywhere, neither is he.
I'm taking him.
And I'm taking Digger Harkness.
There's an A.R.G.U.S. supply boat
that is docked on the eastern shore,
you take it and you go.
I'm not abandoning my post.
Suit yourself.
Would you like to explain what's going on?
I'd like to talk about you for a minute.
- You seem...
- What, in possession of all my marbles?
The Mirakuru wore off
a long time ago, kid.
I mean, I remember
everything that happened,
I'm not trying to escape that,
but it feels like some bad dream.
Now, regardless of my sanity,
why do you want to help me
after everything I've done?
There is a man here on the island
named Adrian Chase.
He's holding my friends
and my family hostage,
including Thea
and my son.
Since when you do you have a son?
Slade, are you gonna help me or not?
I think I'm stating the obvious
when I say I killed your mother.
And for that alone
you should've killed me.
Maybe what's happening now
is the reason I didn't.
This is all the intel that I've been
able to gather on your son, Joe,
including his present whereabouts.
Are you offering to help me find my son?
I want us to find both of our sons.
You and me, kid, like old times.
You know,
if we're going to fight side by side,
you're going to have to
at least speak with me.
I know, it's awful.
Pity.
By now, I thought you'd realized
that by disbanding
the League of Assassins, I freed us both.
Are you looking for applause?
Clapping is a little more difficult
for me these days.
Have you offloaded the supplies?
Most. Guns and ammo
are still on the plane.
By the way, what do you need an RPG for?
Well, like I said,
Chase has Talia, an army of her students,
Evelyn Sharp, and a meta-human.
I have no interest
in this being a fair fight.
Is that why you released
the animals from their cages?
Oh, come on, love.
That is no way to start a new friendship.
Look at me again like that,
and I'll feed you your eyes.
You're not her type anyway.
All right, that's enough.
Let's offload the rest of the gear...
Ooh.
So much for our gear.
There goes our ride home, kid.
Are you sure you heard the gunshot?
Very sure. You sound surprised.
Yeah, well, I know he would crack
but I expected him to last
a little longer,
it was almost disappointing.
Find him.
And, Gennady,
no one kills him but me.
- In 48 hours.
- Da. In two days.
The RPG that took out the plane
came from over there,
and the call from my son
originated just west of here.
Hostages could be at either place.
Or neither. This is a large island.
- I'll check the RPG site.
- I'll accompany you.
Oh, it's almost like
you don't trust me, Nyssa.
No, it's exactly like I don't trust you.
Check it out. Stay on comms.
Why does he get a weapon and I don't?
I trust him more than you.
Didn't he kill your mother?
You listen to me very carefully,
you help me take down Chase, you walk.
You screw with me even a little bit,
and I will put you
right back into that hole.
Just a gun is all I'm saying.
Kid.
I see movement.
Stay sharp.
Oliver!
Keep your voice down.
What the hell is he doing here?
- Where is William?
- I don't know, we were separated.
Oliver, what is going on?
Why are they unguarded?
Seems pretty obvious to me, mate.
- It's a trap.
- Don't even think it, Oliver.
Or your son loses his mother.
Oh, and...
And don't worry about that gun, mate.
Mr. Chase gave me this nice new one.
Along with a better offer.
Adrian said it would be pointless
to reach out to you.
Although, given this turn of events,
perhaps you've changed your mind?
What's it gonna be, Slade?
Care to side with the winners?
What's it gonna be, mate?
Put a gun to his head.
Sorry, kid,
but there's no giving up to these guys.
I assumed you'd wanna be
on the winning side.
Assumption is the mother of all failures.
Sister!
Six men are dead. It's impossible!
Nothing is impossible with him.
Where you going?
Vertolet. I'm gonna end this.
- You okay?
- Go to hell.
I'll take that as a yes.
You've been left behind.
You should choose your friends
more wisely.
Where is everyone else?
Not sure, Chase split us up into groups
when we got here.
We are gonna talk about that, right?
Yes, we're gonna talk about that.
Right now, we need to focus
on finding the others.
- Where are they?
- I wish I knew.
So I could tell you
to go screw yourselves.
Why did Chase split up all the hostages?
Why does Chase do anything?
So far, he hasn't laid out a single hoop
you could keep yourself
from jumping through.
Maybe leaving me here
was part of the plan.
- How did Chase get you here?
- A plane.
Do you think
you can find your way back to it?
- Yeah, probably, but...
- Malcolm, can you fly a plane?
If it's anything like
the three Gulfstreams I used to have, yes.
Get them to the mainland
and then come right back for us.
We are not leaving you here.
I need to focus, and that means
getting you out of harm's way.
And despite my better instincts,
when this is all over
I will come back for you.
When this is all over, you'll be dead.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Yeah.
- Okay, what the hell are you doing?
- What do you mean?
I mean Slade Wilson and Malcolm Merlyn!
- Thea, there...
- No, we are orphans because of those two.
You know what I'm up against here.
Yes, so why are you
sending Curtis and I away?
Because I need the two of you
to keep Felicity and Samantha safe.
- We need to get them off of the island.
- Okay, Curtis can handle that.
I understand
if you don't wanna go with Malcolm.
Damn right, I don't.
And I do not want to rely on Slade Wilson.
There's nothing about this situation
that's ideal, Thea.
I need your help, Speedy,
and this is how you help me.
- Okay.
My sister and Harkness fled
into the forest, but I can track them.
They might lead us
back to the rest of the hostages.
They're our friends,
and we don't need your help.
I see you haven't lost your feistiness,
Ms. Smoak.
Get them to the plane,
make sure that everyone stays safe.
Comms, just in case something goes wrong.
You mean "when," right?
Detailed satellite imagery of the island.
Again, just in case.
- What was that for?
- "Just in case."
We're gonna make it through this.
You can't know that for sure.
I didn't wanna regret not kissing you.
When it comes to the two of us,
I regret enough as it is.
Let's talk more about this
when we're off the island.
You all keep each other safe.
Nice place.
This island got a Big Belly Burger, too?
Before the Chinese turned Lian Yu
into a prison, it was a holy retreat.
But now you're using it for payback
for a guy you barely know,
on a guy you barely know.
Chase freed me.
I don't owe Oliver Queen a thing.
- John!
- Hey.
Hoss. You okay?
- Rene.
- Okay, everyone, calm down.
The four of you are gonna have
plenty of time to catch up.
See you later.
I'm assuming
that you tried your sonic scream.
Sonic dampener. I can't even whistle.
Don't worry.
Oliver will get us out of this.
Yeah? What makes you think
he even knows where we are?
- The trail's gone cold.
- Are you sure?
No doubt my sister knew we would follow.
Let me go on ahead,
see if I can recover the trail.
Okay.
So instead of marrying the blonde,
you marry Ra's al Ghul's daughter?
Nyssa talks too much.
She hasn't explained your beef with Chase.
My past is coming back to haunt me.
Seems to be
a recurring theme with you, kid.
Don't know why.
Well, it's not really that complicated.
You suffer from survivor's guilt.
You can't get over
the death of your father.
Adrian Chase
has nothing to do with my father.
Kid, when it comes to you,
everything has to do with your father.
You and I are not dissimilar.
We're both haunted by our pasts.
And the only way you to bury that ghost
is by forgiving yourself.
Forgiving myself? For what?
You blame yourself
for your father's suicide,
and everything else
that has gone wrong since.
You need to forgive yourself
for your sins.
You say that like it's easy.
It is the hardest thing in this world.
If the two of you are done relaxing,
I've picked up the trail.
There's something I need to tell you.
Can we save
the horribly awkward conversation
for when we're off this island?
No, that's what I need to say.
When we get to the airplane,
I'm not gonna get on it.
- What?
- I'm not leaving William behind.
- No, Oliver will bring him back.
- I know,
but I can't abandon my son.
You know, for what it's worth,
I wasn't in favor of sending William away.
Not that I was consulted, or...
ls that why you two broke up?
I'm sorry, I saw you're not wearing
your engagement ring.
Yeah, no, it's just...
It was complicated, you know.
I saw that kiss you gave him.
Doesn't seem that complicated to me.
You know, I traveled
halfway across the world to rescue you,
I thought it would at least entitle me
to a conversation.
Yeah? Well, it doesn't.
Did it ever occur to you
that I'm here because I'm your father?
No, you are not.
We are nothing to each other.
Don't you ever understand that?
Thea? You okay?
No, she's not.
She just activated a land mine.
Don't move.
The trigger's rusted over.
Okay. That's good, right?
That's a good sign?
No, that's really bad news.
It means we can't disarm it.
Well, somebody needs to do something.
Thea, on the count of three,
take your foot off the mine.
No, that'll blow us all up!
- I'm gonna take her place.
- That's crazy!
Yeah, you're not the first one
to call him that.
Look, I'll just find a boulder
around here or some...
No, we don't have that kind of time!
- Thea.
- No, okay? No one is doing this, okay?
Okay, okay, it's all right.
All right.
I forgot how stubborn you could be.
Oh, my God!
- Thank you for reminding me.
- What the hell are you doing?
I'm gonna take care of them,
disarm the mine,
and I'll catch up with you.
- Yeah, and how are you gonna do that...
- He's not going to.
No, okay? If you think that you needed
to prove something to me, you don't, okay?
- You've proved it.
- I'm not trying to prove anything.
From the moment you were born,
all I ever wanted was to protect you.
You don't have to,
I didn't ask for you to!
A child doesn't have to ask.
Don't do this, okay?
You may not think of me
as your father, Thea,
but you'll always be my daughter.
All right, go, quick!
Get her out of here. All of you, go!
- No, seriously, this is insane!
- Go!
- Go after the rest.
- I wouldn't do that, if I were you.
Oh...
Well, you don't seem too bright,
just standing out here
in the open like this.
What kind of ass backwards strategy
is that?
Let me show you.
The trail continues this way.
This place brings back memories?
Feels like a lifetime ago.
For Shado, it was.
No time for nostalgia.
I know where they're going.
Do either of you
know anything about this place
that could give us a tactical advantage?
I've only seen it one time,
and that was from a distance.
Well, maybe we should split up.
Should we?
Yeah, go on, Nyssa, we'll be fine.
She doesn't trust me.
Can you blame her?
No.
Tell Mr. Chase I have a gift for him.
Oliver.
Don't blame me, Mr. Wilson is the one
who gets credit for this trophy.
Slade. You son of a bitch.
I never should've trusted you.
- Are you all right?
- Where's my son?
William? Chase took him, too?
We didn't know anyone else was here.
Okay, what makes you think he's here?
He took Samantha.
He showed me a video of William.
He is on this island somewhere
and we need to find him.
I'd ask if you're okay,
but I don't see how you possibly could be.
Honestly, I...
I don't even know how I feel right now.
Twenty-four hours ago,
I couldn't even think of Malcolm
without wanting to scream,
and now, now I miss him?
- Is that insane? I...
- It's not insane.
He's your father.
He manipulated me, he lied to me, he...
He got me to kill my friend's sister, I...
How can you miss somebody
that you have hated so much?
Yeah. You know I have some experience
with evil dads, too.
My father abandoned me, lied to me,
and then took a bullet for me,
saving my life.
Malcolm was not a good person,
and he was an even worse father,
but in his own way,
he loved you.
Today, he proved that.
God, I don't know,
it's like today I got to see
the father that he could have been,
but he'll never get to be
because he's gone.
"The plane, boss, the plane!"
Reference too dated?
Who's gonna fly the plane now?
Oh, don't worry, between Curtis and I,
we have over 500 points of IQ,
so we'll probably
be able to figure it out...
- No.
- Thanks for the vote of confidence.
No, it's not that.
- Are those antennas?
- Yep.
And that's C-4.
This is way too many antennas
for a remote trigger.
- They must be networked.
- Great, so there's more than one.
Yeah, you could say that.
Wait, there's hundreds.
Way too many to defuse.
All right, let's get out of here.
I think Wilson did something to your head
when he knocked you out.
Curtis worked this up for Dinah.
It's gonna control your canary cry,
but it's also gonna bypass
the sonic dampener.
Oh, I love that Curtis!
This may hurt a bit.
Just sing, Canary.
Actually, it's Black Canary.
The prisoners.
Don't concern yourself with them.
We have unfinished business, sister.
I heard you gave up
the ring of the Demon's Head.
What a foolish woman you've grown into.
It was your selfishness
that forced me to grow up alone.
Our father never would have
passed his mantle on to a woman.
I had to forge my own path.
And you left me,
knowing I would suffer at father's hand.
And you wish to settle the score now?
I stand with my friends.
You ally yourself
with our father's murderer.
He'd be ashamed of you.
Father was always ashamed of me.
No.
Do not interfere.
Do it.
Father would have wanted you to.
- You're late.
- But they are not.
He was only pretending to screw with you?
I needed a way
to get Curtis' device to Dinah.
Have you seen my son?
I've searched. Your son is not here.
We gotta get my gear, and we gotta move.
We find Chase, we find my son.
Not so sure about that, hoss.
Hello, Oliver. Welcome back to purgatory.
Where's my son?
I love this.
Even now, at the end,
you're still ten steps behind.
Where is my son?
William, good name.
Sort of a sweet kid, actually.
You sure he's yours?
Adrian! Where is my son?
If you wanna get your son back,
you know what you have to do.
I know what you want me to do,
and I won't do it.
I'm not gonna kill you,
no matter what you do.
That is never going to happen.
Never say never.
You said nothing ever really dies.
You're going to.
Do svidanya, Konstantin.
My men overheard your conversation
with that traitor, Knyazev.
The boat he's arranging will be here soon.
I don't have to kill you, Oliver Queen.
I only need to make sure
you never get on that boat.
You thought you could replace me?
That's cute.
- You didn't have to do that.
- Oh, I did, for so many reasons.
Oliver, do you copy?
Are you sure you can't defuse these bombs?
Well, I can with my equipment back
in Star City,
but with this teeny-tiny, little tablet
all I can do is try
and locate the trigger.
- Okay, but you can try, right?
- Yeah, I can try.
Okay, good, you do that. And, Curtis,
you just, you work on the comms, okay?
- How?
- I don't know,
you're the genius, all right?
You both are,
so, we need you to do this.
So you guys just gotta,
both, do this right now.
There's the killer
that I know and love.
Maybe you stronger
with that hood of yours.
Tell me where my son is!
"Pain is fascinating, isn't it?"
I told you I was gonna make sure
that you were dead this time.
Do it, Oliver.
You know you want to.
Adrian, tell me, tell me where my son is!
Never.
You're not gonna make that boat.
This island
will remain your prison forever.
It's all over, but only if you do it.
Do it, Oliver, and show everyone,
show yourself who you really are.
No!
It's who I was.
That's who I was, before!
It's not who I am now.
You can blame me for your father's death
for the rest of your life.
Lam done blaming myself for mine.
I knew it would come to this.
Your son is dead, Oliver.
I don't believe you
because you're a liar.
You're lying to me, to manipulate me
into doing what you want.
But, Adrian, here's the thing,
if you are telling the truth,
if you killed my son,
I am never going to be
the person you want me to be.
Not ever.
Oliver? Oliver, do you copy?
- Felicity.
- You can't kill Chase, did you hear me?
What are you talking about?
He's rigged the entire island
with explosives.
They're remotely linked
to some sort of dead man's switch.
If he dies, it detonates all the devices.
He wants you to kill him
so it kills all of us.
Oliver! Oliver, are you okay?
It's okay, I'm fine.
John, you need to get to the plane,
and make sure that everyone's safe.
- Felicity can talk you in.
- Oliver, what the hell is going on?
Chase has put explosive charges
all over the island.
You need to get to the plane,
and you leave when you get there.
- What are you gonna be doing?
- I'm going after my son.
What if Chase is telling the truth?
I don't believe him. I can't believe him.
But either way, Adrian Chase
is not getting off this island.
Where is William?
Hmm.
You really love that kid, don't you?
Adrian!
For an absentee father,
your devotion is impressive.
Here you are, worried about your kid
when everyone else that you care about
is on an island
about to get blown up sky high.
My friends and my team
can take care of themselves.
By using my plane to escape, right?
I can't start the engine.
John's right.
There is definitely something wrong.
With the plane or with the pilot?
No offense.
None taken. I'm no ace,
but I know how to start a plane.
Whatever this was, it's not pilot error.
Either way, we're not going anywhere
without Oliver, or his son.
Actually, we're not going anywhere at all.
I found this ten feet from the wing.
Please don't tell me
that's what I think it is.
That depends on if you think
that's an on-wing hydraulic system.
- Can we repair it?
- With what tools?
So we're stuck here,
is that what you're saying?
We have to tell Oliver. Now.
Oliver, do you copy?
- I'm here.
- Chase sabotaged the plane.
We can't get off the island.
There's an A.R.G.U.S. supply ship
on the eastern shore.
That's on the other side of the island.
Slade knows where it is. Go now!
They'll never make it in time.
Besides, we're not finished here.
Oh...
Don't do that. Even if you had a shot,
you've already told me
that you wouldn't kill me.
Or have circumstances finally changed?
If I die, everyone you care about dies.
Except your son.
But if you don't kill me, I kill him.
You son of a bitch.
William, or everyone else.
You choose, right now.
Either way, it proves me right, yeah?
Either way, it's exactly like I told you,
everyone around you,
everything you touch, dies.
William! Come here! Hey, are you okay?
Are you all right?
Did he hurt you? You all right?
- He's gonna be fine.
- Don't you talk to him.
Don't even look at him!
Hello?
Hello? Who is this?
Mom, it's...
It's Oliver.
My son has been dead for five years.
Please don't call here again.
Mom, Mom, please!
Just listen to my voice.
It's Oliver.
I did not die on the Gambit,
I'm alive, I'm okay.
Oliver?
Oliver, is that you?
Yeah, Mom, it's me.
Just please don't hang up, okay?
Oh, no, no. No, no, no, I won't.
- Oh, my beautiful boy.
Is... ls your father alive?
No.
No, he and, uh...
And Sara didn't make it.
Oliver, sweetheart, I can't imagine
what you've been through.
Where are you?
I...
I'm not entirely sure, but I'm...
I'm on a boat.
I love you and I'm coming home, okay?
I love you!
Oh, Oliver, I love you so much.
You won.
Your son has his father back,
and he learned exactly who his father was.
Just like you learned who your father was,
right here.
On these very same waters.
- What?
- William's younger than you were,
so he's gonna be fine, you know.
And you have each other.
What did you say?
Which is good. Oliver, that's good.
Because it's gonna be lonely
without Mom, and Felicity.
No, Adrian!
English - SDH