Previously on Arrow...
I'm the one
who's testifying against you.
In a shocking fall from grace
the Star City council has voted
to impeach Mayor Oliver Queen
and remove him from office.
I'm thinking about moving up your trial.
And I got a lot of friends
at the courthouse...
Speculation that the former
mayor is secretly the Green Arrow
has multiplied in recent weeks,
after his decision to terminate
two city officials investigating him
led to his impeachment.
If convicted, Oliver Queen
could face a life sentence.
His fate now rests
in Star City's justice system.
- John?
- I'm getting you out of here.
What the hell are you doing here?
I need your help.
In Star City.
Mr. Queen, what happened
to your face?
Mr. Queen, do you know who the Flash is?
Mr. Queen,
how long will this trial last?
Will you be acquitted?
And the media wonders
why everyone hates them.
Thank you, Officer,
you can wait outside.
I'm right where Mr. Diaz wants me.
I need to have a privileged
conversation with my client.
Nobody's stopping you.
Since you fired
District Attorney Armand,
the DA's office has brought in
outside counsel to prosecute.
Okay, well, that could be a good thing.
I mean, someone who's not
in Diaz's pocket.
Have you heard of Alexa Van Owen?
Should I have heard of her?
She took down Intergang
and Bruno Mannheim.
She's prosecuted
CEOs and serial killers,
and she has CIA-caliber investigators
that say they can find
anything and everything.
Her conviction rate is 99%.
She called me last night
and she offered a plea.
Single count of
first-degree manslaughter...
That doesn't sound so bad.
...with a 15-year minimum sentence.
That sounds bad.
We're not taking that, right?
We're not taking any deal.
Look, Van Owen isn't in Diaz's pocket,
but we have every reason to believe
that Judge McGarvey is.
I mean, this whole system
is against you.
No deal.
Get me an acquittal.
I'm not doing it, Rene.
I'm not playing make-believe with you.
It's a mock trial, not make-believe,
and we got to get our story straight.
Well, I'm planning
on pleading the Fifth.
Did you have a different
amendment in mind?
We can't plead the Fifth
without looking guilty.
We are guilty. We are vigilantes,
and we know Oliver is the Green Arrow.
Which is why we gotta lie
through our teeth.
And we gotta be convincing.
We gotta have our story straight.
Hoss, you wanna weigh in on this?
You've been real quiet.
Why?
It's not like I'm gonna have to testify.
Curtis, please don't tell me
you have FOMO
because you weren't subpoenaed.
Yeah, I have major FOMO. Don't I rate?
You know, maybe you're just
so much better
at maintaining your secret identity
than the rest of us.
Guys, can we be real for a second here?
I mean, Oliver's facing life in prison.
Yeah, and I guess I'm just
a little bit surprised that you care.
Not that I think you actually
want Oliver to go to prison, Rene,
- but come on...
- Oliver's a jerk.
My position on that hasn't changed.
But what also hasn't changed
is the position that he's in
right now.
He's in it because of me.
You're right.
And I think we can all agree,
no matter what our feelings are
about Oliver,
none of us would want him
to go to prison.
Am I right?
Damn right.
From where I'm sitting,
it's pretty simple.
They've got the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen isn't the Green Arrow
any more than I am.
And for the record,
I'm not the Green Arrow.
There appears to be
a fair amount of evidence
to suggest the former mayor is guilty.
What evidence?
That photo from several months ago?
That was doctored.
And I don't know
who they're going to find
to say Oliver's the Green Arrow,
but they'll be lying.
- You sound pretty sure of that.
- I am.
I'm the guy that arrested Oliver
six years ago, remember?
I watched him pass a polygraph.
- He's not the Green Arrow.
- Do you know who is?
I got a few guesses.
- Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
- You're welcome.
Oh, hey.
Sorry, they told me
I could come in here.
No, that's fine. Right? We're finished.
Actually, maybe we could just
get some B-roll.
As the Black Canary, you have to know
who the Green Arrow is.
I do.
And I'll testify to it
if they subpoena me.
Happy? Got your sound bite?
Good.
This looks bigger than the O.J. trial.
How would you know?
You were in, like, fourth grade.
Yeah, but I watch American Crime Story.
I guess John decided not to show.
I knew he was pissed,
but I didn't know he was that pissed.
Guys.
Hey, thank you so much for coming.
Well, you know, they were subpoenaed...
But we also wanted to show our support.
- Yeah, we have your back.
- Thank you.
Really, thank you.
- Hey.
So many reporters outside.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
- You okay?
- I always thought
the worst thing
that could happen to Dad is...
- He'd get hurt.
- I know.
Okay, he's been through something
like this before. I mean...
Not exactly like this,
but something, and...
It's gonna be okay.
All rise.
Docket number 11-19-41-73,
The People v. Oliver Jonas Queen.
Status of the parties?
Ready for trial.
Then let's begin.
Oliver Queen is a hero.
He is.
He's saved this city more times
than anybody can count.
But he's done it all from behind a mask,
so that he could take the law
into his own hands.
In fact, he's taken as many lives
as he's saved.
So, yes, Oliver Queen is a hero,
but that doesn't mean
he's not also a criminal.
Three weeks ago,
Oliver Queen was mayor of this city.
In that time, he has gone
from being under indictment,
to impeachment, to being on trial.
How?
How could everything go wrong
so quickly for him?
I think intuitively you know the answer.
Corruption.
It runs through this city like a cancer,
compromising some city officials
while discrediting others, like...
Like the defendant.
Even the anti-vigilante law
that he is being charged under
is the work of the corrupt men and women
who are holding our city in their grip.
This may sound like a conspiracy theory,
but at the conclusion of this trial,
I'm going to ask you
what is most likely.
That our city's government
has been compromised,
or that we elected a superhero
as our mayor?
Ms. Van Owen,
please call your first witness.
The people call John Diggle.
Where is he?
A bench warrant will issue
for Mr. Diggle.
If he's not made to appear
within one hour,
he'll be held in contempt of this court.
Is your next witness ready?
Yes, Your Honor.
Please state your name
and occupation for the record.
Dr. Eliza Schwartz.
I'm an attending physician
at Starling General Hospital.
Thank you, Dr. Schwartz.
And you've had an occasion
to treat the defendant?
- Yes.
- For various suspicious injuries,
is that correct?
I can't say without violating
doctor-patient confidentiality.
I understand.
Then let me direct your attention,
please, to an incident
when Mr. Queen was not a patient.
On the night of April 6th, 2016,
the Green Arrow
brought in the Black Canary.
And according to your records,
she had been stabbed...
Objection. Is there a question
in our future?
Yes.
That night, you were close enough
to the Green Arrow
to determine his identity.
So my question is whose face
did you see that night?
I was focused
on saving Ms. Lance's life.
I wasn't the least bit concerned
with who the Green Arrow was.
Concerned or not,
whose face did you see
underneath that mask?
You know, it's not bad.
Oliver might just pull this one off.
You want to put money on that?
Diaz wants Oliver in prison.
You'd think he'd want to kill him.
I mean, at least try.
What, so the Green Arrow
can become a martyr?
Diaz is smarter than that.
I have to go.
Diaz yank your leash?
Something like that.
You know, you don't have to go.
First step to standing up to him
is to stand up to him.
Sounds like the first step
to getting myself killed.
Not for nothing,
but apart from your face,
there's one thing
you got in common with my Laurel.
And what's that?
Neither of you would let
somebody else tell you what to do
or have you running scared.
You think your Laurel
would stand up to Diaz?
I know it.
Well, maybe if she were a little smarter
she wouldn't have gotten herself killed.
It's been one hour.
Mr. Diggle having not yet appeared,
he is hereby in contempt of this court.
I'm sorry I'm late, Your Honor.
I had some business to take care of.
Out of town.
Oliver Queen is not the Green Arrow.
I can't make it any plainer than that.
How can you be so sure?
From 2012 to 2016,
I was his personal bodyguard.
If he was running around
with a bow and arrow,
I would have known it.
- But would you admit knowing it?
- Why wouldn't I?
Because you were aiding
and abetting a vigilante?
I absolutely was not.
In fact, I had very limited
interaction with Oliver Queen.
How can that be?
You were head of his security
at City Hall.
And my job was to keep him safe.
And that included
not jumping off of rooftops.
Mr. Diggle, you can't even keep
yourself safe.
I mean, in the past four years
you've been abducted by Damien Darhk.
Your own child was also kidnapped.
You were hospitalized for nerve damage
caused by severe trauma.
Mr. Diggle,
either you travel in some
very dangerous circles,
or you have the worst luck ever.
Who was Sean Sonus?
- Objection. Relevance?
- Overruled.
- Your Honor...
- I said overruled.
Answer the question.
He was a drug dealer I investigated
while undercover in the
Central City Police Department.
And he was shot and killed
in Hub City last year.
Your Honor, I renew my objection
as to relevance.
Well, if Ms. Drake is a murderer,
it would certainly undermine
her credibility now, wouldn't it?
Objection overruled.
Again. Sit down, Ms. Loring.
So, you were not with
the Central City Police Department
when Mr. Sonus was killed.
Is that correct?
- That's right.
- Did you murder him?
- Your Honor!
- Answer the question.
I'm exercising my Fifth Amendment right
against self-incrimination.
You beckoned?
I saw something interesting on TV.
And I'll testify to it
if they subpoena me.
Is there a problem?
Not yet, there isn't.
You know, this would move a lot faster
if you would stop talking in circles.
You were given
the gift-wrapped opportunity
to say that Oliver Queen
was the Green Arrow.
You didn't do it, baby.
I wasn't aware I was supposed to.
Well, that's why we're here,
having this little meeting.
So we can set expectations.
The prosecution is holding you
as a rebuttal witness,
so when they call you,
you're gonna be the final nail
in the coffin.
If I go in and try
and convince a courtroom
that I'm Laurel Lance,
I'm gonna get made.
Maybe you're right.
You don't have a poker face.
For example...
The way you've been acting lately,
ever since I torched Federico
on that rooftop...
You've been keeping
your distance from me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's okay.
You're okay.
I just want to be a little clear.
When you take the stand,
I want you to give the jury
a much better performance
than the one you're giving me.
You know what I'm talking about now?
Good.
That's a good girl.
Gotta go to the courthouse.
It's not going too good, is it?
Hey, no, it's going fine.
It's fine. That was just
the prosecution's turn,
so when it's our turn,
we're gonna kick some major ass.
That's a legal term.
Why don't you go
and get yourself something
that's not too unhealthy
from the vending machine, okay?
Okay.
What will happen
if Mr. Oliver goes to jail?
He's not going to jail, Raisa.
He's not the Green Arrow.
I think we both know better.
I tanked it. I did exactly
what you said not to do.
Lawyer's good, D.
Don't worry, I'll bring it home.
How? We got immunity
from the prosecution.
If watching every episode
of Law & Order ever
has taught me anything,
it's that you can't plead the Fifth.
If you get cornered
and you refuse to testify,
- you go to jail, Rene.
- Well, then I'll go to jail, hoss.
But I'm not screwing Oliver over again.
Hey, guys, the clerk just called
the court back into session.
I worked in the Mayor's office
close to a year.
Side-by-side with Mr. Queen
every single day.
If he was running around
pretending to be Robin Hood,
- I would have known.
- And did you know it?
Mr. Ramirez...
Did you have occasion to determine
whether Oliver Queen
was the Green Arrow?
Rene...
He's the Green Arrow.
Oliver is.
And you know this
because you were a member
of his vigilante team, weren't you?
Yeah.
Did you ever see the defendant kill
or maim anyone as the Green Arrow?
Yeah.
How many people did he kill or maim?
- I don't know.
- Ballpark it for me.
I don't know!
It's too many to count.
Order.
Order!
The prosecution rests, Your Honor.
Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
He picked me up from school.
He was with a police officer.
They said you were hurt.
He was here and we just let him walk?
We're not letting him walk.
Let's get outta here.
Hey, look at you.
Maybe you don't care about people
finding out the truth about you.
That's right. I don't care.
Whatever it takes to stop you.
How about taking on
the entire police force?
How does that sound to you?
You want us to light them up, boss?
That depends on them.
My man.
What do you want us to do with them?
Nothing.
If they had an accident
after testifying...
Could be awkward.
Hey, smile.
It's your lucky day, baby.
Okay.
Is this as bad as it looks?
Arguably worse.
Can we prove that Diaz
was putting pressure on Rene?
No, no, no. I mean,
even assuming we could,
the jury has no idea
who Ricardo Diaz is.
Conventional wisdom says you never
ask a client if they are guilty,
because the more I know,
the more it might tie my hands but...
I am gonna ask...
Are you the Green Arrow?
Yes.
Then I'm going to propose
a new strategy.
- Okay.
- Jury nullification.
- Hmm?
- You're going to admit
to being the Green Arrow.
We are then going to highlight
every single thing you have done
for this city,
all the times you have saved it.
We will argue you do not deserve
to go to prison.
This is a legitimate chance, Oliver.
- I can't do it.
- Why not?
I'd be putting a target on my back.
I'd be putting a target
on my wife and son's back.
I have been the Green Arrow
for six years.
I didn't plan on doing it forever.
I thought that one day
my mission would end,
and I would finally,
after all this time,
get a chance to actually live my life.
That will never happen,
if I tell the whole world
that I'm the Green Arrow.
You don't have to testify.
- Jean doesn't have to call you.
- Yes, she does.
And I want to testify.
I don't want you in a position
where you perjure yourself
because of me.
Well, let me just add it
to the long list of felonies
I've already committed for you.
Look, John has something planned.
You don't have to take the chance.
I will take any chance,
if it keeps you from being taken away
from me and William.
Court is back in session.
Here we go.
I graduated summa cum laude from the
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
with master's degrees in cybersecurity
and computer sciences.
From 2015 to 2016, I served as
the CEO of Palmer Tech Incorporated.
Thank you.
Defense moves to have Ms. Smoak
accepted as an expert witness.
I don't see the point of this,
Ms. Loring.
I want the witness to testify
to the validity of this photograph.
Fine, but make it quick.
Ms. Smoak,
this appears to be a photograph
of your husband, Oliver Queen,
- dressed as the Green Arrow.
- Yes.
The key words being "appears to be."
This photo has been doctored.
A pixel level analysis will show
almost undetectable light shifts
and resolution inconsistencies
that would not be present
in a natural photo.
Objection, Your Honor.
What is the point of showing us an
allegedly doctored photograph at all?
The better question would be,
who and why would they doctor a photo
to make Oliver Queen
look like the Green Arrow
if he were the Green Arrow?
I mean, which he's not.
He's my husband, I would know.
No further questions.
When was Mr. Queen arrested?
November 21st, 2017.
And when were the two of you married?
- November 28th.
- Just a week later?
Yes.
Is it possible that you
rushed the wedding
so that you could claim
spousal privilege,
just in case you had to testify
against Mr. Queen?
I've been in love with Oliver
for six years.
Trust me, it felt anything but rushed.
Let's change the topic.
Your father's Noah Kuttler,
the alleged Calculator...
- Objection.
- Overruled.
- He's reformed.
- But before he was,
did you know that he was a notorious
computer hacker and cybercriminal?
No, I had no idea.
Doesn't say much about your ability
to see criminality in people
close to you, does it?
- I would...
- And under the heading,
"Apples falling from trees,"
have you yourself ever engaged
in cybercrime?
No, I haven't.
Good luck proving otherwise,
Ms. Van Owen.
Roy Harper is not a vigilante.
He sacrificed himself
to protect the identity
of a man that the city at the time
referred to as "The Hood,"
or "The Arrow."
I've since come to learn
that the Green Arrow
is the same person.
- But that's not you.
- It's absolutely not me.
And do you know who it is?
Yes, I do,
but I will not reveal his identity.
Not even if it sends me to prison.
Pass the witness.
Well, that's convenient.
You're not the Green Arrow,
you know who is the Green Arrow,
but you're not saying.
Well, I keep my promises, Ms. Van Owen.
When did you meet this mystery man?
Shortly after I returned to Star City.
As you know, I was marooned
for five years on an island
named Lian Yu.
This photograph was taken
during that five-year period.
I'm just curious, why does Lian Yu
look a lot like Russia?
- Objection.
- Overruled.
We obtained this photograph
from a reporter
by the name of Susan Williams.
I've not been entirely forthcoming
about that period of time in my life.
Parts of it were spent in Hong Kong,
and, yes, parts of it
were spent in Russia.
So, you lied,
repeatedly and publicly?
You lied about being on Lian Yu,
and you lied about
five years of your life,
which begs the question, Mr. Queen...
What else have you lied about?
Quiet.
Quiet or I'll clear the courtroom.
Please state your name for the record.
Thomas Merlyn.
"Tommy" is fine if you want.
Mr. Merlyn, you were declared dead,
May 15, 2013.
That night, my father destroyed
a large portion of the city.
With the heightened scrutiny
on my family,
I took the opportunity
to fake my own death
to protect my identity as The Hood.
Three years ago,
Roy Harper confessed to being The Hood.
To protect me.
And then he was attacked in prison.
I have lived with that guilt
for three years.
I am not about to let Oliver
take the blame for me
the same way that Roy did.
And that's why I'm here.
To set the record straight.
Thank you.
Your witness.
If you're the Green Arrow,
how come Rene Ramirez testified
under oath that Oliver Queen is?
Well, I would suspect
that he was being pressured to.
Are you saying he perjured himself?
Well, I don't know. I'm not a lawyer.
I'm just the Green Arrow.
And I am telling you I am the only man
that has ever worn this hood.
Mr. Merlyn,
you're under arrest
on suspicion of murder,
assault, and violation
of the Anti-Vigilante Act of 2017.
The bailiff will remand
Mr. Merlyn into custody.
Objection, Your Honor.
It's the People's contention
that Mr. Merlyn here
is not the Green Arrow.
Be that as it may,
I can't just let him walk out
of my courtroom.
You know, if it's any consolation,
my team is going to extract me
before I ever get to prison, so...
Get him out of here.
Your Honor, defense moves
for a dismissal.
Nice try,
but it's the jury's job
to sort out this kind of mess,
and that's what I'm gonna let them do.
Guys, on the way to Iron Heights,
do you think we could stop
at a drive-thru?
- I am starving.
- We're not going to Iron Heights.
Mr. Diaz really wants to meet you.
All right, so where did we land
on the drive-thru? It's my treat...
You know, six against one,
it's not really a fair fight.
You should have brought backup. I did.
You're cutting a little close there,
aren't you, John?
What's your exit strategy?
Sitting right there.
Well, let's go.
- Thanks for doing this.
- My pleasure.
I always wanted to say,
"I am Spartacus."
- It's Christopher Chance.
- Rene Ramirez.
I think I bought you
a perjury charge back there, Rene.
Small price to pay
for a clear conscience.
You think it worked?
At the very least, we've created
some very serious reasonable doubt.
Yeah, let's hope so.
When you said I didn't have
to take the "chance" of lying,
- that was a pun!
- I don't do puns.
Well, that was Christopher Chance
I did just see in there, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry that I couldn't loop you in.
We had Officer Parks listening
to every word that we said,
and I...
I didn't know Chance
was gonna use Tommy's face.
Well, yeah, I mean, I guess they were
thinking what's more compelling
than a testimony from a dead guy, right?
Excuse me.
- Mr. Mayor.
- We've got a problem.
Not anymore.
- Chance just saved our bacon.
- Laurel told me.
She also told me
that Diaz is making her testify
as a rebuttal witness.
He's sending her in there
with Chance's entire CIA file.
She will be telling the jury everything
about what you guys
just pulled in there.
Or Diaz is going to kill her.
How does Diaz even know about Chance?
'Cause Diaz has access to everything
that Cayden James learned from his...
It's the bug in the bunker.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
We'll think of something.
I'll give you guys some room.
Okay. Okay, so...
Okay, what's the something
that we're gonna think of?
Jean suggested that I just admit
I'm the Green Arrow
and we go for some sort of
jury nullification.
But I explained to her that
I would like to have a life
after being the Green Arrow,
but more importantly, I...
I cannot put a target
on you and William.
Let me worry about me and William.
Let me at least take that
off your plate.
That's not how wedding vows work.
We didn't exchange vows.
But if we did,
"exchange" means "go both ways."
And we fight
for each other, Oliver.
We protect each other.
We're gonna save each other.
I can't save anyone from behind bars.
We'll get you out
just like we got John out.
I can break out of prison, Felicity,
but then what, you know?
I'm not abandoning the two of you.
I can't make the two of you fugitives.
We're gonna be okay.
John and I have been talking, and...
If I go to prison, I need
you and William to go into
A.R.G.U.S. protective custody.
We're not there yet.
We cannot live in denial.
All right, we have to have a plan.
I can handle losing my freedom.
I cannot handle losing you and William.
I solemnly affirm to
tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
Ms. Lance,
the defendant here
has publicly acknowledged
that you were the vigilante
known as the Black Canary.
Is it fair to take Mr. Queen
at his word?
On that, at least.
And being that the Black Canary is
a known associate of the Green Arrow,
is it fair to say
you know his true identity?
I do.
I know who the Green Arrow is.
Good girl.
Over the course of this trial,
we heard Rene Ramirez testify
that Oliver Queen was the Green Arrow,
but a man calling himself
Tommy Merlyn claims that identity.
Ms. Lance, if you would,
please, just help me out here.
Who's telling the truth?
I got an idea, hoss.
- Help me out.
- Let's go.
Ms. Lance,
who is the Green Arrow?
Tommy Merlyn.
Oliver Queen is not the Green Arrow.
Testimony being closed,
we'll take a short recess
and resume for closing arguments.
No comment.
No comment!
Back up! Give her a break, please.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
- Are you okay?
- Until Diaz gets a hold of me, yeah.
I thought you said
you were gonna bury Oliver.
- That was the plan.
- What made you change your mind?
You did.
The first step to standing up to him
is to stand up to him.
- You can't stay in town.
- Don't worry.
Thanks to you, I now know exactly
what I have to do.
Earlier, Judge McGarvey said
it fell upon you, the jury,
to sort out what he deemed to be a mess.
True, we have contradicting witnesses,
and, yes, we have
conflicting testimonies.
But that is not a mess,
ladies and gentlemen.
That is the textbook definition
of reasonable doubt.
Fifteen minutes
after being taken into custody,
Tommy Merlyn was freed by members
of the Green Arrow's team.
Now, you might take that as evidence
that he is in fact the Green Arrow,
but I would like to offer you
a much more plausible explanation.
And that is, Oliver Queen has people
and resources at his disposal
to do whatever it takes
to keep his secrets.
And don't think that doesn't mean
someone falling out of the sky
into this courtroom with a false face
and a made-up story,
because Tommy Merlyn
is just another Roy Harper.
He's just another man
willing to go to prison
to cover up the crimes
that that man committed.
Don't let him get away with it.
Not again.
Not ever again.
What happens now?
It's up to the jury.
Yeah, but...
What if Diaz got to them too?
Dad!
Hey.
William, I love you very much.
I love both of you very much.
And whatever happens,
nothing is gonna change that.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that
the man who wants me in prison
controls the judge,
and we think it's a pretty good bet
that he has
a strong influence over the jury.
- What does that mean?
- It means...
I might be going to prison.
Okay?
If that happens,
Felicity has assured me
that she is going to make sure
you grow into the man
that I know you can be.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go, either.
Okay, I don't...
I wish it was up to me but it's not.
You are strong like me.
Stronger even.
So, whatever happens,
and wherever I am...
You need to know that I am always
right here with you.
- What is it?
- Jury's back.
We have a verdict.
Will the defendant please rise?
Please publish the verdict.
In the matter of
The People v. Oliver Queen,
on all 26 counts of the indictment,
we find the defendant...
Guilty.
Members of the jury, the court
thanks you for your service.
You're dismissed.
Defense moves for judgment
notwithstanding the verdict.
Ms. Loring, as you know,
the standard for granting a JNOV
requires a verdict that no
reasonable jury could arrive at.
I find such a circumstance here.
Your Honor...
The evidence presented
was so conflicting
that it created reasonable doubt.
The defense motion for judgment
notwithstanding the verdict
is granted.
Mr. Queen, see Probation,
then you're free to go.
Oh, my God, how is this possible?
I don't know.
Congratulations, man.
Thank you.
I'm surprised Judge McGarvey
had it in him, you know.
I totally thought
he was in the tank for Diaz.
I absolutely am.
And Mr. Diaz isn't the forgiving type.
Surprise.
Wait, wait...
- When did you...
- During jury deliberation.
You know, the Judge can argue
that he got rolled,
but no one's gonna believe him.
Thanks again, man.
I owe you another one.
Yeah, well, after Kasnia,
let's just call it even.
Chris...
- Thank you.
- Yeah, always happy to help.
Just try not to need me again,
for at least another year.
Okay?
That was a brilliant move. Thank you.
Well, I wish I could take the credit,
Oliver, but...
It wasn't my idea.
Dad, you might wanna close your eyes
for this part.
That was just one time I was scared.
That's not cool.
That's not cool at all.
Go to your room and lock the door.
Is it the guy from the courtroom?
I said go now.
You can take a shot at me
if you want to.
Just, it's gonna ruin me
saying thank you.
Can't be too safe.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
When I rolled over on you last November,
I was thinking about my kid,
even though I knew it meant
it'd take you away from yours.
I'm really sorry.
Apology accepted.
Look, I'm sorry if I
made you feel like you
couldn't come to me
when Watson put you in that position.
I'm very sorry for everything
that happened afterwards.
I'd never do that! It's me...
It wasn't me, I swear.
The only law that I abide by
is following through on my word.
You failed at that.
So what would you have me do?
Two men, they broke into my chambers,
they knocked me out...
The legal system in this country
is going to hell.
You really must be stupid,
showing your face
after the crap you pulled in court.
No.
I'm smart enough to know
there's no place I can run
where you can't find me.
I'm so sorry, Ricardo.
Fool me once...
Couldn't get it out in time.
Come on.
I had a plan.
Get Oliver Queen
discredited, imprisoned...
I worked for months to make that happen.
I'm so sorry to disappoint you.
Oh, I'm not disappointed, baby.
I'm moving on to plan B.
Killing Oliver Queen,
and anyone and everyone he cares about.