Previously on Arrow...
Russia is your home. Let me go save mine.
People are gonna wanna know
where I've been for the past five years.
It's easier if I'm just a simple castaway.
I'm afraid you're going
to miss your boat home.
What's so funny about my father's legacy?
He was going to disown you.
With help from the Green Arrow
and his team,
the Throwing Star Killer
is now behind bars,
and our streets are a little safer.
Former District Attorney Adrian Chase
faces multiple counts of capital murder,
among other charges.
SCPD spokesperson Alison Rou
credits the Green Arrow
with bringing the man known as
the Throwing Star Killer to justice.
Well, it looks like the Green Arrow
is a hero again. Whoever he is.
Yep. And the mayor
ain't doing too bad, either.
The Sentinel's got your approval rating
back up to 70%.
What? Was it ever that high?
No, it was wasn't.
Um, anyway, listen, if you'll excuse me,
I gotta go find Rene
and remove his head from his ass.
- Wait, what?
- He missed a hearing
about possibly getting his daughter back.
- Hey, Quentin?
- Yeah?
If you need any help with that,
just let us know, okay?
Yeah, thanks. Yeah, will do.
Oh, by the way, um,
I'm sorry I almost forgot.
Happy birthday, Mr. Mayor.
Thank you.
We should go get a drink tonight.
We haven't celebrated your birthday in...
I can't remember how long.
Remember the last time
we celebrated yours?
Oh, God, we decided
we would never talk about that again.
Four years?
You've changed a lot, Speedy.
We both have.
Just not sure I have for the better.
I'm sure.
Look, Thea, uh,
being happy doesn't mean
you don't have issues.
It just means that you're working on them.
When did you become all Zen-like
and well-adjusted?
We should celebrate that tonight,
as well as your birthday.
I appreciate that,
but I already have plans.
With who?
Please say "not Susan Williams."
Um, it... NO, uh, with Felicity.
As in a date?
As, uh...
As in I don't know if it's a date.
But you're hoping that it is?
It's dinner.
People go to dinner.
See, I don't believe you,
but I find it incredibly cute.
- Surprise!
Happy birthday. Everything hurt.
Everything hurts here.
Yes!
I love the cake,
where did you get it?
Lord Mesa Bakery.
What's up with number six?
Is that for the number of members
of the team?
- It's cool.
- Actually, I ordered the cake
for a six-year-old because I wasn't sure
that I could order a Green Arrow cake
for a grown man.
Well, hey,
Oliver's a child at heart, right?
That is the concussion talking,
yep, for sure.
I'm really sorry about that, Curtis.
No, that's okay. But you should know
that if I'd had my T-Spheres,
I would have...
Would've what?
Would have still been on the floor.
I'm very sorry.
Mmm.
I was worried
this might've got hurt.
What is it?
They are sound modulators
that I've been working on for Dinah.
Not only will they be able to
focus her canary cry,
but they will be able to override
any kind of sonic dampeners.
- Yes.
- She's coming, right?
Yeah. She said if work didn't go too late,
then she'd swing on by.
Thank you.
- Cake. Here you go.
- Yes!
Lyla couldn't make it?
She and J.J. are visiting
her sister in Chicago.
- Oh.
- We're good, man.
We'll patch things up.
I'm late, aren't I?
That's all good. Didn't miss much.
Just Oliver flipping Curtis
over his shoulder.
I told you a surprise party
wasn't a good idea.
How's Rene?
He's not home.
There's a couple of days' worth
of newspapers
piled up outside his apartment.
- You're worried about him.
- Yeah, well, you know,
Rene may come across
as an irresponsible idiot,
but that's... No, it's just 'cause
that's what he wants
people to think of him, you know.
Yeah.
- Hey.-
We're gonna do a toast in
about five minutes. So, champagne, and...
- Club soda.
- All right, you got it.
Really nice wrapping.
Thank you.
Thank you all so much
for doing this. Cheers.
Cheers.
I almost forgot what it was like
to celebrate a birthday.
That's because we're usually
saving the city from being destroyed
this time of year.
Uh, it's like summer break for you guys.
What are you gonna do, huh?
I've always wanted to see Florence.
The city in Italy,
not the woman or her weird machines.
I'm gonna teach J.J. how to fish.
Few days with my son on the water,
that'll be heaven.
I was thinking the Pacific Crest Trail.
For a night. For, you know,
just one night under the stars,
and then definitely
a manicure-pedicure afterwards.
What about you, Oliver?
We know you got City Hall and all, but...
Yeah, it keeps me busy.
But I need to buy some socks.
Everybody has their thing.
I need socks bad.
Socks it is.
Hey, we all need socks.
Uh, well, I think we could all use
another piece of cake, right?
- Yeah, sure.
- You know, actually, I'm good.
Had about three or four slices myself.
- You need cake, son.
- Oh, okay.
- You need to go.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I need that, yeah.
Oh.
That was subtle.
So subtle.
I guess since the dinner
at Chez Marta was a ruse,
they think we deserve some alone time.
Do we?
Well, I mean, I didn't know if it was a...
We can take it one step at a time.
I would like that very much.
This is hard for you, huh?
Hypothetically dating my ex-fiancée?
No. It's...
Wow, no, I meant summer vacation,
as they are now calling it.
It's incredibly hard.
It's borderline impossible.
We won.
Oliver, we won.
Just take a step back, you know.
You can put your feet up,
no matter the state of your socks.
You could just, God forbid, relax.
Yeah.
My government heard rumors of this place.
An island prison built by the Chinese.
It's incredible that you should lead me
here of all places.
I killed you.
Almost.
But nothing ever really dies.
There are always echoes.
You'll learn that soon enough.
The KGB call this the Red Death.
It's an interrogation drug
meant to break men
by inducing psychological anguish.
It's why you followed me
halfway around the world?
Torture?
Murder creates intimacy between men.
So, I'd appreciate an honest answer.
If your intention was to return home,
why leave from here?
Honestly?
Go to hell.
That's an interesting response.
If my Chinese is correct,
this place is called purgatory.
You know the Catholics
consider purgatory to be
the immediate state
following physical death?
Konstantin...
When I kill you this time,
I'm gonna make sure you're dead.
When we're done, the only person you'll
want to kill is yourself.
I'm just saying, you could've taken
a big knife
and cut the tension between you two.
And by tension, I mean sexual tension.
Yeah, I know what you meant, Curtis.
And then the way you guys dressed up
for each other? Ooh! Sizzle! Sizzle!
Okay. Can you please stop?
You're worse than a shipper
on a soap opera.
Okay, well, look, I'm here.
I hope Dinah's still up,
I think her neighbors are asleep.
That's the whole point
of this modulator anyway.
- Oh, no.
- "Oh, no" what?
- I think she was robbed.
- Do you need backup?
Yeah, probably, but I'm here now,
so I gotta make sure she's okay.
Hello?
Dinah?
If there's someone in here,
you should know that I know martial arts.
Curtis, what's going on?
On, my God.
Curtis? Curtis?
Curtis?
Clear.
We got Curtis' phone
but no Dinah and Curtis.
Okay, well, if Curtis and Dinah
are missing,
I guess we can presume that Rene
didn't skip out on his daughter.
Whoever did this is good.
We know who's doing this.
It's Chase.
He's picking us off, one by one.
Not to state the obvious,
but Chase is currently under surveillance
24/7 in an impenetrable glass box.
There's no way
he got out to do this.
Look, he had to have help.
I hate to say this, but what if this was
Chase's plan all along?
Get himself caught, lull us to sleep.
Yeah. Well, consider me officially woke.
Okay, Chase has worked
with Evil Laurel before,
but she's currently locked up
at A.R.G.U.S.
and there is no way
that Evelyn is doing this all by herself.
John?
Isn't that League?
It's Talia al Ghul.
Contact Thea and Lance,
we need to get them some place secure.
There's an A.R.G.U.S. safe house
across town we can use.
Okay, you get them there
and then meet me at the bunker.
Where you going?
It's time to talk to Chase.
Where are they?
- Adrian, where are they?
- Who?
- You know damn...
- You know damn well who!
You're right. I do know.
Just like I know your every move,
while it seems like you know none of mine.
Tell me where they are.
Or what?
We've already established
that you think you won't kill me.
Kind of weakens your leverage.
I'm gonna find them
and I'm gonna get them back.
Is that what you came here to tell me,
or are you just wasting time?
See you later.
Oh, pain. It's fascinating, isn't it?
Some men will do anything to avoid it,
others will embrace it.
Even revel in it.
Like you.
That's why you're so formidable.
Pain is not a new experience to you.
Then stop wasting my time.
That was my epiphany for true retribution.
I couldn't merely cause you pain.
I had to wake you up.
Open your eyes, make you see.
The pain you suffer is still with you.
This drug will help set it free.
Every cut, every bullet, every wound,
like you're feeling it all
for the first time.
Am I still wasting your time?
Freeze, jerk-wad!
Sorry.
I knew it was you, but what if
it wasn't "you" you. You know?
Multiple Earths, evil twins, et cetera.
Et cetera being the scariest thing
I've said all day.
I hate this thing. Oh.
I'm a little on edge.
I'm actually really looking forward
to being holed up
in an A.R.G.U.S. safe house.
I don't want you in the safe house.
I want you down here with me.
- What? No. Why?
- I can run comms remotely.
Okay? And if Malcolm Merlyn
has proven anything,
it's that when it comes to
the League of Assassins,
locks are more like suggestions.
I can handle Talia al Ghul
and whatever acolytes she's fighting with.
Where I need you is down here with me,
so that both of us can try to stop Chase.
Is this...
And this might sound
a little self-serving,
but is tactic the only thing
behind me staying down here?
- Honestly?
- Yeah.
Of course not. Okay?
The thing that's clear, though,
to me right now is that I...
I let my guard down. And I shouldn't have.
No one could have
seen this coming, Oliver. No one.
I saw it coming.
I knew something was wrong.
I knew it. Here. And I ignored it.
And then I second-guessed myself, and now,
everyone that I love is in danger.
Including, maybe...
- My son.
- No. I couldn't find him.
There's no way they're going to.
Not Chase. Not Talia al Ghul.
William's gonna be fine.
I appreciate that.
But you can't know that.
You can't.
William is the purest part of me.
And now he's in danger,
maybe because of something
that the worst part of me set in motion.
- How'd it go?
- Thea and Quentin are not happy about it,
but they're secure.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
- What's going on?
I had A.R.G.U.S. triple-check
on Black Siren, she's not in her cell.
That's not a coincidence.
Quentin doesn't know about her.
It's why Chase will send her right there.
We need to get the safe house
on the phone now.
God, you know what the worst part
about a safe house is?
It's not being able
to use your cell phone. That's just...
That's barbaric.
Well, yeah, normally I'd chalk that up
to millennial nonsense,
but I know what you mean.
I'm chomping at the bit to speak to
that judge on Rene's case right now.
Well, what could you say?
That Rene was kidnapped by some psycho
that's in jail? That...
I gotta do something, Thea.
I know what it's like to lose a daughter,
and hell if I'm gonna
let that happen to Rene.
Right.
Agent Kosinski. Hello?
Hey, Sharon, we got a problem
with the comms in the...
Stay here.
Yeah, well, I don't know about you,
but I'm sure as hell
not staying here waiting.
You read my mind. Let's go.
It's a tranq dart.
Stop right there!
Stop, turn around slowly. Turn...
Hi, Daddy.
No, it can't be.
It can be. Daddy, it can.
Don't worry.
I'll explain everything.
Just don't take your gun off her, Quentin.
Thea, Thea...
You know it's not what it seems.
Okay, Ollie told...
I'm so sorry, Daddy.
What do we know?
You mean besides this being
the horror version of Groundhog Day?
Look, the security camera footage
is grainy,
but it's good enough to see Black Siren
giving her best Laurel impression.
We know there was
a second attacker. Who do we think it was?
Well, the A.R.G.U.S. agent
that gave Black Siren
her "get out of jail free" card
said that he was blackmailed by a woman
wearing black, so could be Talia...
It was Evelyn.
Agent Kosinski got a positive ID
before he got tranqed.
So these kidnappings are what? Payback?
Before Chase tortured me,
I told him that the team was my strength.
He's trying to take it away.
So his lady friends can come after you
instead of him?
That doesn't sound very satisfying.
Chase doesn't think I can game out
what he's planning, but it's obvious.
Yeah. Obvious to a murdering psychopath.
And present company excluded.
He's trying to leverage our friends
to make me set him free.
That's crazy.
Which would be consistent for Chase.
- You two have to leave the city.
- What?
You gotta leave the city.
You gotta leave the state.
And you can't tell me where you're going.
Oliver, we're not leaving.
We're not going anywhere.
We're not abandoning you.
I understand
that you're not abandoning me.
You're doing
what I'm asking you to do, because...
Chase knows how I think.
He knows that if he puts
the two of you in danger,
and he's gonna try to, that my instinct
will be to pull you close.
So do something he's not expecting.
Split up.
No, that's...
What about you?
If I don't have to worry
about the two of you,
then I can put my focus
towards finding the others.
You get this son of a bitch, Oliver.
I will.
KOVAR". You're strong.
Like a piece of iron.
You think you can resist any pain
because you have.
But the worst pain is up here.
Locked away, deep inside.
That's what the drug is for.
To show you everything. Your sins.
Your failures.
I think you made your choice.
No!
Your guilt.
Oliver! No!
Your bloodlust.
Your inhumanity.
That gun, it only has one bullet.
You can waste it on me,
but I think we both know
who's responsible for your pain.
I've seen the strongest man
resist for up to 12 minutes
before ending his suffering.
Such is my respect for you that I...
I think you can last for, uh...
14 minutes.
Do svidanya.
You're going to do it, aren't you?
Because you are not strong
and you know you deserve to die.
Let me help you understand.
I'm not going to kill you.
I am never going to give you
the satisfaction of being the man
that you think I am.
You're never getting out of here.
Not today.
Not tomorrow. Not ever.
Do you understand?
No, I don't.
But only because you're wrong.
I told you, Oliver. Everyone in your orbit
suffers as the price for your sins.
And the only way to keep them
from paying that price is to let me go.
I'm gonna find another way.
Find it quick.
They're transferring me to Idaho tonight.
And once that happens,
this offer's off the table.
I don't want to see that happen, Oliver.
Like I told you,
I think that you're one loss away
from getting destroyed.
Who would it be, I wonder?
Thea or Felicity?
Maybe someone else.
I mean, look. I don't understand,
all right? But that was Laurel.
No, Quent, it wasn't.
It looks like her and it sounds like her...
No, that was my baby girl, all right?
She's back. Just like with Sara.
Listen, there...
It is hard to explain, but there are
these other Earths, okay?
Parallel universes.
You're talking crazy. Listen to yourself.
I know.
I know how crazy it sounds, trust me.
But it is real.
It's real.
Just as real as meta-humans and aliens.
So, that wasn't Laurel?
It was a Laurel.
It's just not the one that we knew.
Okay, now, look. She's very convincing.
And I need you to remember that,
because that is exactly why
Chase has brought her here.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
That's a surprise.
Felicity, I already have major anxiety.
You going silent on me is not helping.
You know,
my mom's really big into intuition.
Like, stars, signs, horoscopes,
Ouija boards, even.
I always thought it was
either stupid or ridiculous.
Never really took it seriously.
Until now, right?
Yeah. I have this really bad feeling,
like right in the pit of my stomach.
What's it telling you?
We never should have left Oliver alone.
I agree with you, Felicity.
Leaving Oliver feels wrong,
but maybe that's why
it was the right thing to do.
You do realize
how backwards that sounds, right?
I do realize that, but this is Chase
we're dealing with, remember?
Yeah. I know. But what if we overthought
it and now Oliver's vulnerable?
I see your sense of hospitality
remains intact.
You are not welcome here, Malcolm.
Do you aim to cut off
my other hand, Oliver?
Maybe.
You gonna tell another person
about my son?
Last time I was down here,
I saved your life.
Do you really think that gives you a pass
for serving up William to Damien Darhk?
I'm sorry about that.
I wasn't thinking clearly.
I let my emotions get out of hand.
That is all in the past.
The only thing I'm concerned about now
is saving my daughter.
What's that?
Angry woman with two swords.
You getting major Isabel Rochev
flashbacks right now?
- Yep.
- You remember how we handled that, right?
Yep.
We gotta get out of here.
That worked better with Rochev.
Digg.
Told you I had a bad feeling.
John? Felicity?
They're gone, Oliver.
- Damn it!
- They were taken alive. Focus!
I would've thought you would have tagged
your, your pets by now.
They're my friends, Malcolm, and Curtis
did put tracking nanites in Felicity,
but they were rendered useless
when Chase set off an EMP.
Well, I'll give him this much.
He's 50 moves ahead.
But the question is, to what end?
He wants to leverage me
into breaking him out of prison.
And my daughter?
Your sister isn't sufficient leverage?
You've blackmailed people, Malcolm.
How often have you kept up
your end of the bargain?
And quite frankly, I am surprised
that someone like you is willing
to give in to a man like Chase.
I will give in to someone
if it gets Thea back.
The fact that she hates me
doesn't make her any less my daughter.
Something you learned last year,
friends are one thing,
but family is family.
And your child?
You would do anything,
absolutely anything, to keep him safe.
A little while ago, I worried that John...
That the personal connections that I had
were making me vulnerable.
Because as long as there are people
in my life that I care for,
I have to be something else
to protect them.
That's something
that I can't leave in the past.
I admire you, Oliver.
It takes a special kind of idiot
to actually get dumber with time.
Lam not in the mood, Malcolm.
Human connections are what keep us human.
And it's sad that
it's a sociopath
who's gonna have to point this out to you.
You can't live on an island.
You've already tried.
But you are always gonna
have people in your life, Oliver.
And they will always need you.
Better or worse, baggage and all.
And if you can't accept that,
well, your past is gonna stay your anchor.
- Yeah?
- Mr. Queen,
the marshals are here
to transfer the prisoner.
You said you wanted to know.
Thank you, I'm on my way.
I'm going to ensure that
Chase's prison transfer goes smoothly.
We're very capable people,
and we're gonna find a way
to rescue everyone.
You're not real.
I am as real as your conscience.
Remember? Survive.
My dying wish for you
after I gave my life for yours.
But you squandered my sacrifice,
and now my daughter,
my dear Shado, is dead.
Yao Fei, I'm so sorry. I'm so...
Apologies won't bring her back.
And it won't bring the others back.
Please, stop.
Taiana, Akio, Sara...
Everyone you've lost
over the past five years.
And all of those you have yet to lose.
This isn't real.
It's not real, you're in my head.
And who better
than you knows the truth?
What truth?
That those closest to you
are fated to suffer for your sins.
But you can save them, Oliver.
By making the same sacrifice
I made for you.
I love what you've done
with the place.
You got shipping containers
as nice as this on Earth-2?
Everything's exactly the same
as it is here, Dad.
Don't call me that.
You're Laurel, but you're not my Laurel.
- Is that too tight?
- You care?
You think this isn't hard for me?
Doesn't much look like it.
I owe my freedom to Adrian Chase.
In exchange, I give him my help
and his assurance that you won't get hurt.
Chase's assurance?
My Laurel wouldn't be that stupid.
I know.
You loved her, and I know you lost her,
and I know how
it makes you feel seeing me.
You've got no idea.
Don't worry, sir. If custody's threatened,
we have orders to shoot on sight.
Tick-tock.
You're not pulling my strings
anymore, Adrian.
At least you admit that I have been.
Hey, but just so that we're clear,
the moment I get on that transfer chopper,
my friends have orders to kill yours.
We'll see about that.
Think you're about to get a phone call.
Hello?
Somebody help me.
Please help me.
Please, please.
I need the van!
Sir, what are you doing? Stop!
He took your son, didn't he?
How'd you know?
Like minds. Here.
Something funny, nut-bag?
Not yet, but soon.
See what I mean?
This would be easier
if we could kill them.
Then it's not gonna be easy.
We're compromised.
Take the prisoner out!
They're targeting Chase.
Go, I'll cover you.
Really!
Chase!
Thanks for the assist, pal.
Where is my son?
No! No! That wasn't the deal, Oliver.
That wasn't the deal.
I said you let me go,
and I keep your loved ones safe.
But I'm not gone yet.
Why did you involve William?
That's my boy.
He's an innocent.
So was my wife, man, but you involved her.
I already told you, Oliver,
everyone that you care about suffers.
Everyone.
I'll see you on the boat.
Okay, Chase's helicopter flew to an
abandoned airfield in Dawn Valley, Utah.
Then five minutes later,
this aircraft took off from the same field
at a vector of two-seven-zero.
Due west.
That would take him back to Star City.
Chase seems smarter than that.
I'm trying to track this plane,
but it's not easy without Felicity.
Back before the Undertaking,
some of my associates,
especially those who were
on the wrong end of your bow,
thought that The Hood had computer skills.
I had good hardware
and a specific purpose.
Chase turned off the transponder
on the plane.
Luckily, Felicity has access
to a keyhole satellite
that can track the heat signature
of any aircraft in the world. Which...
Impressive.
Just got lucky.
- You expecting someone?
- Yes, I am.
Because Chase is working with
at least Black Siren, Evelyn Sharp,
Talia al Ghul, and whatever army
she's currently controlling.
So you called in reinforcements?
If I wasn't such a confident individual,
my ego might be bruised.
Malcolm, your ego is what I'm going to
need you to keep in check.
Why'?
Who did you reach out to?
Husband.
Mr. Merlyn.
I assume you still have no title.
- No.
- Malcolm...
- I will not work with her.
- I told you.
I'd sooner slice her throat.
Try to, you mean.
Malcolm, you said you were willing to do
whatever it takes to get Thea back.
So, here we are!
Fine.
But does she know?
Know what, Mr. Merlyn?
One of the people we are up against
is your sister.
Nyssa, I wanted to explain it
to you in person.
We have Chase at C-one-thirty.
Flew out over the coast
banked southerly 12 degrees, which...
Which means...
What does it mean?
I know where he's taking them.
Why would your adversary
bring them here?
For that matter,
how did he even know about this place?
Talia.
She researched me.
Probably told Chase everything.
Ironic.
When I was a little girl,
my father told me to visit this place.
It's where I found Sara.
Please, don't.
I'm sorry that I have to.
But it's better for everyone.
This is the only way
to make sure that...
That I don't infect everyone that I love.
But we love you in return for it, Ollie.
We need you home.
Please come home to me, Ollie.
To Thea, and your mother.
Please, we need you.
If you don't, then your father
and my sister will have died for nothing.
- Diggle! Felicity!
- We're okay, you okay?
We're fine.
Little north of pissed off, though.
- Rene, Dinah, where are they?
- Not with us.
Relax.
Enjoy the weather.
Miss Smoak.
Anybody ever tell you
how much you suck at life?
No.
Care to be the first?
Why are we here?
So you recognize this place?
That's good.
Oliver's gonna come for us.
Yeah, I'm counting on it, sis.
Sounds like Chase is using us as bait.
He wants to draw Oliver out.
Numbers aren't exactly in his favor.
He faced worse odds before.
Yeah.
With the help of you and John.
Roy and Laurel. Thea.
The rest of us.
Curtis is right,
Oliver can't do this alone.
I need your help.
Hey, kid.
I'm glad you came back.