My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
I'd like you to work with me
on the Vigilante investigation.
Thank you, sir!
It's just beginning.
In six months,
the organization's vision
of what this city should be
will be complete.
Thousands of innocent people
will be dead
and you'll feel nothing.
That's not true.
I'll feel a sense
of accomplishment.
So...
How can we be of assistance?
Malcolm Merlyn. I want
you to kill him for me.
These black arrows
aren't consistent with his M.O.
Something
doesn't add up.
We're dealing
with a copycat.
What do you mean, the chopper's
about to touch down?
The flight log doesn't have them
due for another 20 minutes!
Then lock down
the heliport!
I've just landed
in Starling City.
We agreed--
half on arrival, the other half
when the job is done.
Gracias.
Don't worry.
The man's as good as--
Guillermo Barrera.
You have failed this city.
You've built quite
a reputation.
And you should have
stayed overseas.
I thought about it,
but then I remembered--
I've got
a reputation, too.
♪ Arrow 1x16 ♪
Dead to Rights
Original Air Date on February 27, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Ahh! Ow!
Now the trick
is to keep your weight
evenly distributed.
I thought the trick was
to avoid getting into fights.
Yeah, well, Starling City's
not the kind of place
where you can talk
your way out of trouble.
Besides, if you're going
to be working with us,
I'll sleep a lot easier knowing that
you can handle yourself...
At least a little bit.
How'd it go?
Badly for him.
Who's him?
An assassin for hire
with an affinity for knives.
His name was
Guillermo Barrera.
Was?
So we can't ask him
about his intended target?
No.
Which is why I need you to
hack his phone.
Barrera's world class.
He kills high
profile targets.
And whatever job
he was hired for
isn't finished.
We need to figure out who
he was here to kill, and fast.
They are probably
still in danger.
Ok?
Yeah.
I have to meet McKenna.
Good thing she didn't meet you
at the heliport.
May not be a good idea
to fall for the cop
that's hunting you down.
Well, it's slim pickings
for us vigilantes.
Four.
Well, I'm more of a runner.
Why the sudden
desire to work out?
What else is there to do?
Well, we can try to think of
another way off the island.
There is no other way.
If there was,
I would have found it.
We can't just sit here
and wait for Fyers
to come and kill us.
I did have one idea.
If you go into the forest
and gather as much bamboo
as you can find...
Yeah?
We could build ourselves a boat,
like they did
on "Gilligan's Island."
That's broken.
It got busted
during the crash.
Did you try
to get it to work?
I'm better at pulling
things apart.
My father was a pilot
and he used to do
his own maintenance.
So you're hoping
aircraft maintenance is genetic?
No, I used to help him
and I liked it.
Then I got
pretty good at it.
So maybe I can make
the radio work.
You should be training
for the inevitable fight
that's looming.
I think I have a better chance of
making the radio work.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
No, I am. I just got
caught up at the office.
Me, too. Wow.
You look nice.
Ooh.
We should go inside.
We should.
We don't seem to be
going inside.
Welcome.
Happy Birthday, buddy.
Thank you.
Oh, this feels like
a Chateauneuf de Pape.
It's going to taste
like one, too.
You are a true friend.
Thank you.
Tommy, you remember
McKenna Hall.
From back in the day.
And back again.
Ollie.
Hi.
Laurel, this is...
McKenna Hall.
We know each other
from the court house.
How are you,
counselor?
I'm well, Detective.
I'm going to go crack this open.
Come in.
Such a nice apartment.
So much space.
Oh, this is adorable.
How old are you here?
That's actually
my sister Sarah.
Oh, I am so sorry.
No, no, it's ok.
I don't know why my father
bought her that canary.
That thing chirped
night and day.
Drove us all nuts.
A toast.
To the first birthday
that I have enjoyed
in a long time.
I got my best friend back.
And...
I have finally
figured out why poets
have been in business
for the last few thousand years.
Happy Birthday, baby.
Thank you.
Cheers.
I think that's the food.
Oh, ok.
Oh, thank God,
she didn't cook.
Amen.
Mr. Merlyn.
Laurel.
Can I come in?
Oliver.
Mr. Merlyn.
I've been trying
to get in touch with you.
What are you
doing here, Dad?
Happy Birthday, Tommy.
Just give us
a second.
Of course.
We're about to eat.
I can't stay.
Well, that works out
because you weren't invited.
I'm being honored by the
Starling City Municipal Group.
They're bestowing me with
their annual Humanitarian Award.
What, they ran out of actual
humans to give it to?
I would like you
to be there, if you could.
I am 100% certain
that I'll be busy.
You might not
believe this,
but all I ever wanted
for you was happiness.
If it will allay
this tension between us,
I'll turn
the switch back on.
Save your money, Dad.
I don't need it anymore.
I'd still like you
to come to the event.
It would mean
a lot to me.
You know what, Dad?
Sometimes the people
that you want there the most...
Aren't.
You taught me that.
Multiple times.
Hello, Lawton.
I see your edge has dulled.
Oh, I knew
you were there.
I just didn't care
if you killed me.
What do you want?
My organization
has been contracted
to eliminate a certain
high profile individual.
A very well-guarded target.
Well, forget it.
Look, I'm retired.
To drink and smoke
your life away?
We all got to die
some time.
I need someone to die
at the right time.
And no one does it
better than you.
My vision...
ain't exactly
what it used to be.
No.
It's going to be better.
So...
Who needs two bullets
in the chest?
Moira.
Is it happening?
Yes.
The Humanitarian Award ceremony.
Isn't that
a little public?
No one will expect it.
I have very welcome news
to share with all of you.
Thanks to Queen Consolidated's
Applied Sciences Division
and their recent acquisition
of Unidac Industries,
the Undertaking
which we set for ourselves
is only months
from fruition.
There's hope on the horizon
for everyone in starling.
We won't fail this city.
And I think I speak
for everyone here
when I say we're all
with you, Malcolm.
Jeez, this is one
paranoid assassin.
Barerra's got cobalt-level
encryption on his phone.
It's not going
to be easy to break.
But codebreaker
is my middle name.
Actually, it's Megan--
Felicity, can you get
anything off of it?
Just the last number
he dialed.
Which was?
A restaurant in China town.
A Jade Dragon.
I guess even hired killers
enjoy the city's best chow mien.
Yeah, Jade Dragon
is a front
for the Chinese
mafia.
Call the restaurant, make
a reservation for two for tonight.
You need to decrypt that phone.
I'm kind of in the mood
for Chinese now.
Hmm.
That is--that is
one big fried fish.
I was told this was the most
authentic Szechwan in town.
Whatever. I wanted to make sure
that your birthday celebration
got its due celebration.
It was a little bit, um,
tense last night.
Well, trust my dad to run
all the smiles out of the room.
He did come by,
and it seemed like
he was trying
to act a little bit dad-like.
Dad-like, that sums up
my father perfectly.
I know the two of you
have never been close,
but it couldn't have been
easy for him
after your mom was killed.
Yeah, I guess he forgot that there
were two of us in that club.
I'm not defending him, Tommy.
It's...
With everything
I've been through,
people that I've lost...
I know how hard it can be.
You probably don't
remember this.
Ahh...
We were eight.
But after her funeral,
he left for like
two years.
And when
he did come back,
he was...
he was so frickin' cold.
We barely spoke.
And that's why I spent so much
time at your house.
From the outside,
it always looked
like I had a father.
He paid my bills,
he lived in the house,
he bailed me out.
But your dad took me
to my first hockey game.
Your dad taught me
how to fly fish.
Your dad took us
to our first R-rated movie.
Your dad taught me
but he wasn't perfect.
My dad made mistakes.
And...
We haven't talked
about this.
But I have a lot
of anger towards him.
But still, I would give anything
to have him back,
because...
At the end of the day,
your dad is...
Your dad.
I meant what I said
last night.
I'm...
really glad
that you're back.
I got to hit the restroom.
Check, please.
I hope you like
barbecue.
Well, don't fall over
yourself thanking me
for spending six hours up a tree
so you can eat.
What?
Great. I'll eat later.
You've been on that for days.
Give it a rest.
It's because I can do this.
Sure, kid. When pigs fly.
You're kidding me.
Can you clean this up?
I don't know. I don't know
how I got this far!
Continue
approach. Big jet 365.
Mayday,
mayday, mayday.
This is wedgetail 325.
Pilot
and passenger down.
Big jet 365, cleared to land.
Runway 2-7 right, wind,
2-7-0 degrees, 10 knots.
I repeat--pilot
and passenger down
on the island
of Lian Yu.
Request
immediate rescue.
Cleared to land,
runway 2-7 right.
Big jet 365.
Damn!
They can't hear us,
and we can't call out.
We're still trapped.
Lance.
The Triad have hired
a contract killer.
Yeah? You mean the one
you put in the morgue?
Congratulations, you're the talk
of the station again.
They hired one,
they're going to hire another, Detective.
Who's your target?
I'm trying to find out
but I'm hitting dead ends.
I need you to put
your people on it.
My people don't work for you.
And come to think of it,
neither do I.
It's not about you
and me, Detective.
It's about
saving a life.
Call me back
when you got a name.
Hall.
Yes, sir?
You and me.
We're going to catch
that Vigilante.
There are five exit routes
from the main floor
that need to be cut off.
Once the fire alarm goes off,
we'll have less
than 30 seconds
to disable Merlyn's
private security
and force him outside
with the others.
Once he's outside...
The rest will be
up to Mr. Lawton.
Roger that.
You look handsome!
I try not to.
It just keeps happening.
What's the occasion?
I decided to go
to my dad's thing.
Really?
Are you sure?
Oh, mostly.
Did you want me
to go with you?
No, no, no, I know
you have work to do.
I promise
I will be fine.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
If you're free,
maybe after the ceremony,
we could have dinner
and talk like we used to.
I'd like that.
That's my cue.
I've been trying to avoid
him all evening.
If we didn't show,
it'd look suspicious.
How can you talk
to him that way?
As if nothing's
about to happen?
I've been living this life
for five years.
Five more minutes won't matter.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Now tonight's honoree
needs very little introduction.
It's neither his wealth
nor his name
that we celebrate here tonight.
But it is his efforts
in making Starling City a better
and safer place to live.
So please help me welcome
Starling City's
humanitarian of the year,
Mr. Malcolm Merlyn.
And so that's a stage, right.
Most nights we'll have a band.
Somebody cool.
Is Fallout Boy still cool?
They broke up.
And never.
So somebody else
will pick the bands.
Something
bothering you?
Don't say no, 'cause you're
a terrible liar.
Really?
I thought I was
getting better at it.
Mm-mmm.
What's wrong?
There's a lot of stuff
going on in my life.
Work.
Friends.
And I'm having a...
difficult time figuring out
how to fit it all in.
I've been struggling
with some of those
thoughts, as well.
Do you have any good ideas?
I think we just have
to be really honest
about what's going
on in our lives.
Think you can do that?
Come on.
I'm in! Yes!
Yes! Yes, way to go,
Felicity Smoak.
You don't happen
to speak Spanish, do you?
Arabic.
Oh, le sigh.
Oh, my God.
You know
I'm there for you.
Excuse me, Mr. Queen.
The I.T. department
has that item that you requested.
One sec.
Ok.
You find the target?
Oliver, the target
is Tommy's father.
At the awards ceremony?
Tommy's there.
Um, McKenna, Mr. Diggle
is going to take you home.
I have some unexpected business.
It's ok.
Lance.
Target is Malcolm Merlyn.
Establish a perimeter
but keep your distance.
I don't want the police
caught in the crossfire.
The true humanitarian
in the Merlyn family
was my wife Rebecca.
Many of you here
knew her.
She tirelessly
devoted herself
to helping those less
fortunate in the glades.
I like to think that if the men
who murdered her
knew her;
knew the work
that she did,
knew the person
that she was...
He would have helped her to her car,
made sure she was safe,
instead of stealing her
purse and shooting her.
The truth is, I haven't done
enough for this city.
My city.
I failed it.
But I promise you--
I am not finished yet.
I promise you
that this city
will be better
for all of us.
And on that day,
I will look
at this beautiful award
and feel that I have earned it.
I thank you.
Oh!
Mr. Merlyn, you should
head for the exit--
Tommy!
Merlyn's not taking the bait.
Change of plans.
I don't like improvisation.
Drive him upstairs
to his penthouse office.
I need to switch
vantage points.
Tommy!
Come with me.
There's an exit
on the second floor.
I wasn't leaving
until I knew you were safe.
Go somewhere safe.
I'll hold them off.
Go now!
Come on!
Where are we going?
Up.
Who are those guys?
I don't know.
They're trying to kill you!
Seems that way.
And we're going up,
without any of your bodyguards?
Dad! We need
to get out of here.
Tommy, take a deep
breath and trust me.
Upstairs in my office
is a panic room.
We get there,
we seal it off.
Merlyn's headed
to the penthouse.
Why do you want
Malcolm Merlyn dead?
I'll settle for you.
Wait!
Go!
You killed him!
Surely as he would have
killed you.
Move, move, move!
Electromagnetic locks.
What if they
cut the power?
This floor is on
an entire separate grid.
The glass?
Lexan. Bulletproof.
It's over.
How did you know
how to do that?
What?
Fight.
Kill.
Dad?
Freeze! SCPD.
Put the bow down.
Tommy, you ok?
Dad!
Dad?!
Turn around slowly.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm ok.
Damn it.
You're bleeding.
I'll be fine, Tom.
No, no, no, Dad!
Dad!
No!
Stay back.
I'm not here to hurt
you or your father.
I said stay back.
Curare.
Don't come any closer.
Your father's
been poisoned.
An assassin named Floyd Lawton
laces his bullets with curare.
I've dealt with this before.
We need to dilute the poison
in his bloodstream.
I said stay the hell back!
In three minutes
he's paralyzed.
In four minutes,
he suffocates.
If you don't let me
help you now,
he's dead before
anybody gets here!
Help. How?
Fresh blood buys him time
to get to the hospital.
A blood transfusion?
That's insane!
It's the only way.
He needs your blood.
You're out of time.
You need to make
a decision right now.
Why should I trust you?!
Because you always have.
Oliver.
Ok. Ready?
Do it.
Hold his arm.
Come on, come on, come on.
You're the Vigilante.
Why?
Later.
He's still going to need
medical attention
to fully clean out
his system, you understand?
Ok.
Thank you.
Tommy.
I'm right here, Dad.
What did the Hood
say to you?
He didn't say anything.
You let a homicidal
maniac talk you into
a homemade blood
transfusion
instead of calling
the paramedics?
My father's life
was at stake.
So first the Hood rescues you
and Queen from those kidnappers,
now he saves
your old man.
But he's taking down every
other one percenter out there.
Is this guy a friend
of yours, Merlyn?
I don't know
who the hell he is.
If they can't hear us,
then what's the point?
Wait!
You still might have
done us some good.
0500 hours from my mark.
Final deployment
is five by five.
That's Fyers!
I'm tuned into
the soldier's frequency.
Scylla is in route.
ETA 0600 hours.
At the southwest bay.
I'll call you when Scylla
is in my possession.
Fyers out.
Who was Fyers talking to?
I don't know.
Sounds like someone
off this island,
maybe his benefactor.
More importantly,
who or what is Scylla?
The Scylla and Charibdis.
It's "The Odyssey," from one
of the four nightmare chapters.
Scylla was a monster.
I want to meet
this monster.
Am I going alone?
So how's it feel
to save a one percenter?
Looks like Malcolm Meryln's
going to be ok.
They took him
to Starling General.
Good thing he was wearing
a bulletproof vest.
He's not in the hospital
because he was shot.
He was poisoned
by curare.
Lawton's alive.
I'm sorry, John.
This Lawton kick his dog
or something?
No.
He killed his brother.
What?
What is it?
You were right.
Scylla is a monster.
A Russian-made S300
anti-aircraft
missile launcher.
It can simultaneously track
up to a hundred targets
while engaging
with at least a dozen.
I mean, from here,
they could shoot down
a commercial airliner,
or start a war.
Hey, you're here.
Yeah.
Walk with me.
Mm-hmm.
I heard you were
there, are you ok?
I'm fine. Fine.
Listen, McKenna, I'm--
I'm really sorry that I had to run
out on you like that.
Don't worry.
Five more minutes,
and I would have had
to run out on you.
Our lives
are complicated.
But I'm willing
to figure us out.
If you are.
Willing and able.
Hey. Hey, Dad.
Dad, Dad.
Take it easy.
You were shot.
The bullet was
laced with poison.
I should be dead.
I gave you
a blood transfusion.
Actually it was...
the Vigilante's idea.
He saved you.
He did?
I was worried I was
going to lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
You said that
after mom died.
But you left.
I wasn't a very good father
to you after your mother
passed away.
I was so lost.
You never told me
where you went.
I found myself in a place
called Nanda Parbat.
I met a man there.
He helped me
make sense of things.
He helped me to find
a purpose for my life;
to make this city
a better place for everyone.
Especially for you.
How are you going
to do that?
Malcolm?
Tommy.
Could I talk to Moira
for a minute?
Thank God
you're all right.
We have a traitor
in our midst.
I want you to find out who.
He just made his last mistake.
My dad's going to be ok,
thanks to you.
It's thanks to you.
No one's asked you what happened
to you out on that island.
You said "a lot."
That doesn't quite cover it.
Tommy...
I saw you
kill those guys
who kidnapped us when you
first got back, didn't I?
I...
I know you have
a lot of questions.
Yeah.
Yeah, but for now,
just the one.
Were you ever
going to tell me?
No.
Tommy, I just saw it
all on the news.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
Bye.
Hello, Laurel.
Mom?
What are you doing here?
I need
to talk to you.
About what?
I know
I've made mistakes.
Yeah.
Yes, you have.
Look, I have to go.
Why don't you send me an email
or a postcard some time?
I have something important
I need to discuss with you.
What could be so important
after all this time?
It's about Sarah.
What about her?
I think
she may be alive.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==