Previously on Arrow:
Tonight, we rise all as one
and take back this city.
Slade's got 20 guys just like him,
and we have no way to stop him.
Mirakuru, we're gonna
use it to make a cure.
Slade promised me City Hall.
And he delivered.
I understand he made you a promise too.
There is still one person who has to die.
- There's too many of them. We can't fight.
- We're not going to.
Laurel?
Laurel!
You killed me?
Let me return the favor.
- You can't kill me.
- You're not invincible.
Close enough.
Laurel!
Oliver.
Are you okay?
The tunnel collapsed.
I'm trapped.
And it's...
It's getting really hard to breathe.
You are gonna be okay.
I need you to tell me
everything that you see.
Rocks, and water and...
And your bow.
Do you see my quiver?
No.
Wait. Yeah. Yes, I have it. I have it.
- How many arrows are in it?
- There's a bunch of them.
There should be one with
a metallic head that's
bigger than the rest of them.
You see it?
Why do I need this?
Because it's an explosive arrow.
And you're gonna fire it.
Do you wanna save me
some time and energy...
and tell me where I can find
Felicity Smoak?
I have been aching to put a bullet
in her smug little face...
ever since the day...
Oh, I really thought the airbags
were gonna go off.
Thanks for the help. Any word from Oliver?
Dig?
- What do you think? Hit her again?
- Go, go, go!
Get down! Get down!
Reports are coming from
all over the city.
Starling General is preparing
for possible casualties.
- Power is out south of Harbor Boulevard.
- Governor.
Governor. Sending in the National Guard at
this point will only cause mass hysteria.
Trust me and my police force.
We have this situation under control.
- Mr. Mayor.
- DA Spencer.
What is going on? There are men in masks
tearing through the city.
Yes, I know. And we're doing everything we
can. The S.C.P.D. have already mobilized.
No. The police force,
they're not equipped to handle this.
You don't understand. I have never
seen anything like this before.
These men in masks, it's...
It's like they're not human.
Not human?
Kate, do you even hear yourself?
Look, I know you're scared
but you need to pull yourself together.
Starling City needs both of us
thinking clearly right now.
How are you so calm?
Officials are
urging all citizens to stay inside...
and off the streets.
Because I know
we're going to get through this.
And when we do, Starling City will
be stronger and better for it.
Can I count on you?
I need you with me on this.
- Mm-hm.
- Good.
Then let's save the city together.
Are you far enough away from the debris
to avoid the blast?
I don't know.
What if I can't shoot that far?
The bow is a hybrid compound, Laurel.
It's gonna do all the work for you.
All I need you to do...
is just aim at the middle of the debris.
Take a deep breath.
Center your feet.
Left hand on the bow.
Place the arrow on the drawstring.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right?
I want you to pull back
on the drawstring...
and keep your left arm straight.
Okay?
I'm gonna count to three...
and then you just let go.
You can do this.
One, two...
three.
Nice shot.
- Dig, are you there?
- Go, go!
Yeah, Oliver, we hear you.
We're coming up.
Sara's gone.
Slade must have taken her.
- What's that?
- It's sonar.
I was monitoring the Amazo.
She's moving.
We have one torpedo left, right?
Can you rig it to fire in a straight line?
I'm discovering capacity to do many things
I never thought I would do.
I need you to get the sub close enough
to the freighter that I can swim over.
Well, then what do you need torpedo for?
If Sara and I aren't back in an hour...
you're gonna sink the Amazo.
Freeze.
Who are you?
I'm her father.
- Dad.
- Laurel. Oh, thank God.
Are you safe?
I am now. I'm with the Arrow.
Well, that's... That's good.
Now, listen, something tells me
he's got work to do.
- I want you off the streets.
- Yeah.
Laurel, please, keep low.
Keep out of sight, alright?
Dad, I know.
You don't have to worry about me.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You?
Isabel attacked Dig so
I hit her with the van.
Slade's army.
He has at least 50 men
out there, all like him.
They're everywhere.
- We need to stop them.
- We might have a way.
S.T.A.R. Labs called. They have a cure.
There's a courier en route.
Where is it?
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Felicity Smoak. Where are you?
Fourth Street, I think.
I don't know what happened.
Some guy in a hockey mask came out of nowhere
and attacked my car. Please help me.
Stay where you are.
I don't think I could
move if I wanted to.
I think my leg's broken.
You should go.
Laurel, I'm not leaving you
out here in the middle of this.
The precinct is in the other direction.
I'll be fine.
Laurel, no.
I don't need you right now.
Everyone else does.
So go.
Go save the city.
Hey, are you still there?
Yeah, I'm here. I pinged your phone.
We're on our way.
Please, hurry.
Find him.
In the last five minutes, S.C.P.D.
has had over
200 reports of masked
men attacking the city.
I should've gone with Laurel.
Made sure she got to the precinct.
She'll be with her father. She'll be fine.
She will, Oliver.
All right, we are 10 meters away
from the freighter.
Still, this is sumashedshiy crazy.
You cannot even be certain
that Wilson has her.
You're a good man, Anatoli.
If this is goodbye, be safe.
- I will see you soon. You and Sara.
- I meant what I said.
If we're not back in an hour, you sink
the freighter and get yourself home.
I think maybe I prefer Bahamas.
Oliver.
I don't know if we will
see each other again.
But know that you have
made friend for life.
If there is anything you need,
it does not matter what...
you have only to ask.
Prochnost, my friend.
I also teach you to speak Russian.
Crazy...
Listen up.
We're gonna establish a
perimeter with checkpoints
at Fifth and Adams,
Second and Kingsley.
- We gotta create a safe zone.
- Who the hell are these guys?
These guys are the enemy.
They're attacking innocents at random,
creating mayhem and chaos.
- We need to put them down.
- Lieutenant.
Now!
Listen to me, these guys,
have you seen them? Huh?
You see these guys?
They do not go down.
We gotta call in the
National Guard.
That's a call for the mayor.
And he hasn't made that yet.
And he won't.
Mayor Blood let this happen.
- What?
- Trust me.
Blood's behind this.
Look, even if I believe you,
I don't have that kind of authority.
Well, in an emergency, the chief of
police does, so get him on the line.
The chief's dead.
Well, there's only one more guy
we could call.
You're not gonna like it.
- The vigilante.
- The Arrow.
Lieutenant, I know
he's breaking the law.
But what we're up against
is not about the law.
It's about survival.
We got masks tearing our city to pieces.
And we're gonna need a mask to stop them.
Make the call.
- Okay, let's do it.
- One more thing.
You know more about what's going on
over everyone else I got.
I need you making decisions
and leading these men.
Detective.
No!
Follow me. I can get you to safety.
Sara.
We lost contact
with our reporter on the streets.
But we have over two dozen
confirmed sightings...
of masked men attacking
numerous municipal locations.
Officials are asking that you stay indoors
while they try to get...
Wait. Stop.
- No, no, no.
- Enough!
- This isn't part of the plan.
- Sebastian?
I am mayor of Starling City
and I order you to let her go.
No.
I don't take orders from you.
Let's go. Come on!
Any word from Thea?
Is she safe?
She decided to leave Starling
before the attack started.
Just over two miles to the bridge
and the courier.
It's for you.
What is it, detective?
- How can we help?
- We?
Starling City Police force
is standing with you on this one.
We need help containing the soldiers.
We're working something and it may
stop them, but we need more time.
We can do that.
Whatever you're doing, good luck.
For all our sakes.
This is the street that
feeds into the bridge.
Floor it.
Hold on!
Dig?
- Diggle?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Ah. Yeah.
- Is she breathing?
Felicity? Yeah, yeah.
- We have to get out of here.
- Yeah, I'm on it.
Thea.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Why should I believe you?
You're a murderer.
A terrorist and psychopath.
I don't expect you to understand
what I've done.
Not now.
Not without more time to explain.
How are you even alive?
- Why are you here?
- I heard what happened to your mother.
I needed to make sure you were all right.
I needed to see my daughter.
I am not your daughter.
You're nothing to me.
And I want nothing from you.
Do you understand?
Yes. But right now, you need my help.
My protection. You have no idea,
Thea, how dangerous it is out there.
The city is falling.
At least let me take you to safety.
They say Nero sang...
as he watched Rome burn.
Now I understand why.
If only Shado were here to witness this.
- Who's Shado?
- What the hell is going on?
One of your juiced-up jackboots
just killed my entire office staff...
and snapped the
district-attorney's neck.
- And?
- "And"?
And I never agreed to this.
- You were supposed to call off your dogs.
- That was your plan, Mr. Blood, not mine.
We had a deal.
And do you feel
that I've not lived up to my end of it?
Those are innocent people.
Dying out there.
- You do not need to kill them.
- Yes, I do!
I made a promise to someone once,
and I will uphold it.
So this really is all about you
just trying to hurt Oliver Queen.
I vowed to him
that I would take away everything...
and everyone he loves.
- And he loves this city.
- But this city...
it's mine too.
Not anymore.
As of tomorrow night,
it'll be nothing but rubble, ash and death.
A land only good for one thing.
Graves.
Sara.
Where have you been?
It doesn't matter.
Why did you come back?
I don't know.
There isn't anything here for me.
Your family's here.
You don't know, Laurel, about me.
About who I am and who I've become.
I know you're a hero.
I'm not a hero, Laurel.
I am the furthest thing from it.
I am Ta-er Al-Sahfer. That was my new name.
Because the woman that I was...
the girl that I was...
was gone.
I'm not gonna pretend that
I've been through anything that you have.
One thing that I've learned in the
past year is that these things...
they don't break us.
They make us who we are.
And what I am...
is irredeemable.
What was that word you said before?
Ta-er Al-Sahfer.
What does that mean?
It means "the Canary."
If you're so far gone...
and so irredeemable...
then why would they know you
by such a beautiful name?
Ollie. Ollie. Ollie. Thank God.
Ollie. Ollie. Ollie.
- Come with me.
- Okay.
All right. Stay with me.
The sub is right alongside the freighter.
You just need to swim. Okay?
Okay. What are you doing?
- I can't leave yet.
- Ollie, come on.
- The cure.
- No.
I can't... I can't leave Slade behind.
I'm not just gonna...
Not just gonna write him off.
We injected him with the Mirakuru,
but it was me, all right?
I chose you over Shado.
Ollie, I just wanna go home.
I just wanna see my family, Ollie.
Please, I don't wanna die. Please, Ollie.
Come on, please.
I need to do this. I
need to save my friend.
I need to at least try.
Get to the sub.
Get safe.
Not without you.
- Sara.
- Come on.
It's Dad.
- Hello?
- Laurel, baby, where are you?
55th and Alfred. There
are a few roadblocks.
- But you're okay?
- Yeah. Sara's with me.
Uh, right. Okay. Listen. Stay there.
Both of you. I'm on my way.
- I can walk now.
- Where is he?
His cell-phone GPS says
he should be within a 500-foot radius.
I'll call him.
- Hey. Where are you?
- We're here. Where are you?
- Honk your horn.
- Cool. Hold on.
Wait, I can see your feet.
You're right outside my car.
That's not us.
Oh, no.
It's gone.
The situation has intensified
as officials struggle to contain...
this historic assault gripping our city.
Mr. Wilson. Is this
what you're looking for?
Yes, it is.
We just got off the phone
with Cisco at S.T.A.R. Labs.
The cure they sent us was all they had.
They used all the Mirakuru
that we gave them.
So they can't make more.
We can't stop Slade's men without the cure.
- We'll find another way.
- There is no other way.
Foundry's been compromised.
We need to get Roy out of there.
I'm on it.
I didn't know, Felicity.
Five years ago, I was a completely
different person, and I had...
no idea that something
like this was even...
possible. I couldn't have imagined.
When you and Diggle
brought me back to Starling City...
I made a vow to myself
that I would never let anything...
like the Undertaking happen again.
- What's happening now is not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
I have failed this city.
Yao Fei.
Shado. Tommy. My father. My mother.
All that I have ever wanted to do
is honor those people.
You honor the dead by fighting.
And you are not done fighting.
Malcolm Merlyn. The Count.
The Clock King. The Triad.
Everyone who has tried to hurt this city...
you stopped them.
And you will stop Slade.
- I don't know how.
- Neither do I.
But I do know two things.
You are not alone.
And I believe in you.
Where's Dad? He should be here by now.
We should get to a better vantage point.
Please, anybody!
- Please help!
- Stay here.
No!
Someone help!
Please help!
Someone help! Please!
Are you okay?
My daughter is still inside.
I couldn't get to her.
- Aah!
- Don't. It's too dangerous.
- Laurel.
- Dad.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Dad... Watch out Dad. Dad.
Delta Charlie 52 to Central. Copy.
Delta Charlie 52 to Central.
Please copy me now.
- Delta Charlie 52 to Central...
- Dad. Dad.
It's okay.
She's fine.
Right here. Here you go, your daughter.
Who was that?
That's the Canary.
Thea, please. Come with me.
I don't want anything to do with you.
I don't even see you.
Stay behind me.
You're out of arrows.
You're not.
Oliver.
This is your phone.
- What do you want?
- The same thing you do, Oliver.
- To save this city before it's too late.
- It's already too late.
You were right about Slade Wilson.
I should have listened to you.
- But I'm here now and I can help you.
- Why should I trust you?
Because, Oliver, I have the Mirakuru cure.
How much venom do we have
to keep him under?
Two hours, maybe.
Let's go.
Hey.
I need you to stay with Roy.
Okay.
Oliver. John.
Maybe this is obvious.
But are we sure this isn't a trap?
- No.
- I'm just saying...
if you guys don't come back alive,
I'm gonna be really pissed.
As a young boy,
I was plagued by nightmares.
Every night, I'd wake up in a cold sweat
frightened and alone.
It was my father's face that haunted me.
And this is how I saw him.
The embodiment of desperation and despair.
I made this mask to conquer my fears.
And to remind myself why I fight...
every day...
to give this city's
most desperate a chance.
All I've ever wanted to do
was help people, Oliver.
Help me believe.
- Where's the cure?
- Slade Wilson will not rest...
until he honors the promise
that he made you.
I won't be so easy to kill
once we level the playing field.
He's not interested in killing you.
Not until he's taken away everything
and everyone you love.
After he murdered my mother...
he said one more person had to die.
Whoever you love the most.
I hope you can beat him with this.
For all our sakes.
And when this is
over, I promise you,
I will do everything in my power
to rebuild Starling City.
And I won't just make it what it was.
I will make it better.
- Like I always planned.
- You really think...
after everything that's happened...
after what you've done...
that they'll still let you be mayor?
Why not?
No one knows that I've done anything
except try to save this city.
And if you tell anyone about my mask,
I will tell them about yours.
Do what you have to, Sebastian.
All right, sweetheart. I
gotta get back to it.
Hey. You guys okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
You won't believe it.
A blond in a mask ran out of a burning
building with a kid in her arms.
It was the bravest thing I've ever seen.
That woman's a hero.
You gave it to him, didn't you?
I did what I felt was necessary.
Don't worry. I'll tell Slade.
Does he still have the cure?
No.
- Slade, you betrayed...
- Goodbye, Mr. Blood.
I loved this city.
Why does every secret formula
have to be color?
What ever happened
to good old-fashioned clear?
Alright, so if we inject one
of Slade's soldiers with this...
According to S.T.A.R. Labs...
- it will counteract the effects.
- Assuming they got the recipe right.
- We need to test it.
- We can't.
- Treat Roy like some kind of lab rat?
- Felicity.
What if it doesn't work?
What if it kills him?
- What if he wakes up and kills us?
- We need to know. One way or the other.
- Go lock the other door.
- Okay.
So where does Ivo keep his safe?
It's, uh, by his books.
Oliver.
What are you looking for, kid?
This?
Detective Lance.
Yeah.
What's going on?
What is it?
We are watching
live footage of an Army convoy...
arriving on the outskirts of the city
to restore order.
Looks like the cavalry's here. Finally.
- Maybe.
- What do you mean?
They're taking up positions
at the bridges and tunnels.
Those are the only ways into the city.
- Yeah. And the only ways out.
A buddy of mine in military intelligence
once told me the Army isn't always the Army.
But it's clearly the military.
The trucks. The uniforms.
Except the nearest Army base is at Monument
point, which is 300 miles from here.
So how could they mobilize
to Starling City so fast?
Okay. So if that isn't the Army,
who the hell are they?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
It's Lance.
- Detective.
- You near him?
- Yes.
- You near a TV?
- Turn it on.
- How did you get this number?
- Amanda. What are you doing?
Not sure what you mean, Oliver.
Amanda, the troops taking up position
at the city's exits, they're not Army.
They're A.R.G.U.S. Those are your men.
So you tell me what you're up to.
Amanda.
Slade's followers
are a clear-and-present danger.
I cannot allow them to escape the city.
They need to be contained.
By any means necessary.
You can't.
There's a drone en route carrying
six GBU-43/B bombs.
Enough firepower to level the city.
There are over half a million people
in this city.
Five hundred, seventy-six thousand.
None of whom deserve to die.
But I have to think about the people
in every city.
You once told me that Mirakuru
made a man virtually unstoppable.
What could happen to this country,
this world...
if I don't end this here and now?
Listen to me.
I have the cure.
I can stop Slade and his men.
I can't take the chance
you'll fail, Oliver.
Amanda, I just need more time.
I'm sorry.
You have until dawn...
then Starling City is a crater.
If you're gonna use that,
you'll wanna click the safety off.
I'll shoot you. I will.
I can see it in your eyes.
My eyes.
They're just like mine.
Both of them filled with pain and anger...
because those we loved
were ripped from us.
I lost my name, my wife.
- Tommy.
- Shut up.
You're all I have left in this world.
And you've lost everything too, Thea.
But you still have a father.
You still have...