Previously on Arrow...
Ms. Mayor,
as of today, Mr. Queen
is officially working
for the SCPD.
You sure you're
good with this?
Hiding the truth
from Oliver and Felicity? No.
We need your help.
This is a plan
to level all of Star City.
These are the bomb
schematics we found
in Felicity's
hideout.
We have got to go
to the cops.
The SCPD are a joke.
We go to The Glades.
I guess it's time to
pay my dad a visit.
Woman, Voice-Over:
The world is not a fair place.
Innocent people die
while the guilty go free.
The system is broken,
filled with corruption, greed,
and apathy.
The people who are supposed
to protect us are failing us.
Woman, Voice-Over: Criminals
continue to walk the streets
because no one is willing
to stop them.
The world may not be fair,
but everyone deserves justice
and someone looking out
for them.
And in other news
from city hall,
today marks the dawn of
a new era for Star City,
an unprecedented partnership
between the SCPD
and the recently unmasked
Oliver Queen,
now a deputized member of
the police force.
You expecting someone?
If anyone from my
organization caught me
talking to you, it's
lights out for Marco.
This will calm your nerves.
It certainly does.
Did you find
William Glenmorgan?
Not exactly.
We've used Glenmorgan for
a few sensitive jobs.
So have the Bratva,
the Irish,
and anyone else rich
enough to pay him,
but no one has seen
his face.
So how do you hire him?
Through the online
black market,
but he's very careful.
Glenmorgan might not
even be his real name.
Word is he's in town
contracting
for talis global.
That will get you into
the talis server room.
You'll have to find your
own way into the building.
Hey.
What'd this guy do
to you anyway?
I'm not paying you
to ask me questions.
Freeze!
I said, freeze!
Get on the ground.
Show yourself.
Nobody has to get hurt.
I need your help.
Holy crap.
I got you. I got you.
Game time, rookie.
You ready?
It's not my first
crime scene, Dinah.
No, but it's your first
one as an SCPD deputy,
so try not to screw
it up, huh?
Kidding.
The new Green Arrow has
been dropping felons
at my doorstep
almost every night,
but this is something
different... a b & e.
Uh-huh.
It doesn't look like
it ended well.
Don't touch that.
This is a crime scene,
and at a crime scene, we
follow proper procedure...
Mm-hmm.
A concept that is clearly
alien to you.
My apologies.
I'll take that, please.
Yes, captain.
So not everyone is
excited
about our new
partnership, I see.
It's gonna take some time
for them to get used
to the Green Arrow
wearing a badge.
But, hey, this is
the best lead we've had
on finding out who's
under that hood.
It shouldn't
take too long
to analyze the blood.
By not long, you mean
at least a week.
My crime lab is buried
under mountains of evidence.
There's another option.
Dinah,
why is the SCPD working with the Green Arrow
if you are not going
to use my resources?
Please.
OK.
Thank you.
Careful. It's gonna be sore.
Not bad.
Well, the Navy didn't teach
me heart surgery or anything,
but I can handle
a few stitches.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
So you want to tell me
what happened out there?
OK. How about your name?
I appreciate the help,
but I'm not looking
to make new friends.
- Looks like you could use some.
- I work alone.
But you came to my place.
And I'm starting
to regret
not taking my chances
at the hospital.
Well, I guess stubbornness
comes with the suit.
Look, you're doing
a lot of good out there,
and you obviously care
about The Glades.
Let me help you.
You have no idea
what I care about.
If Oliver Queen
knew anything,
it's that you can't
save the city alone.
I'm not
Oliver Queen.
Zoe, you're supposed to be at the
mayor's fundraising breakfast.
He knows
I hate those things.
It still doesn't look good
when his chief of staff
shows up late.
He loves schmoozing
donors.
20 bucks says he
didn't even notice.
Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen,
esteemed donors
and beneficiaries.
It's my honor
to introduce the man
who single-handedly
cleaned up The Glades...
my friend and your mayor,
Rene Ramirez.
Thank you, Keven.
And thank you all
for coming out today.
Many years ago,
we came together for
a common purpose...
to improve The Glades
when no one else would.
And look at us now.
The Glades have
never been stronger,
but our work's
far from over.
And I promise you
if I'm reelected,
I will keep fighting
to make sure
The Glades remain
the greatest place on Earth.
Afternoon,
Mr. Diaz.
I have to say,
the accommodations here...
a lot more comfortable
than slabside.
You can thank me
by telling me
everything you know
about
the terrorist financier
known as Dante.
Three days you keep on
asking me the same thing,
and I keep on telling you
I don't know anything.
Then why did he help
pay your debt
to the Longbow Hunters?
You must be really desperate
to be reaching out to me.
Is that your husband on
the other side of the glass?
How you doing, Johnny boy?
Keep Stonewalling,
Mr. Diaz,
and watch how fast
those accommodations
you're enjoying
disappear.
You'll see just how
uncomfortable a place
A.R.G.U.S. can be.
Or we can send you back
to slabside,
let you rot there.
Let me be...
Real clear.
For the cheap seats,
screw you.
I want my lawyer.
You belong
to A.R.G.U.S. now.
No one knows
you're here,
and no one
ever will.
So I suggest you
cooperate.
I got nothing more to say.
DNA match...
Oliver Queen.
Whoo! DNA signature
confirmed.
I knew you were here before
you even walked in the door!
How's that?
- That's good work.
- Thank you.
Aren't you
a working man now?
Shouldn't you be at
the SCPD?
Uh, they need a little
help from Team Arrow...
Specifically you.
- Cool.
- You need to analyze this DNA.
It belongs to
the new Green Arrow.
Some husbands bring their
wives home flowers,
and mine brings me blood
from a crime scene.
They say romance
is dead.
Any idea on who it could be?
Nope.
Oh, you're no fun.
You don't think it could
be Roy, do you?
Oh. We are not even on the
same continent as Roy.
Yeah. Well, let's find out
who our mystery man is,
shall we?
Ooh!
Well, shame on us for
being so sexist.
Our mystery man is
actually a woman.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey.
Can you sit down?
Why?
'Cause the, um...
well, before you ask,
I mean, no, it's not,
it's not Thea...
the DNA match is on
your father's side.
I'm sorry. Say again?
The vigilante is
your sister.
No!
Get in! Get in, boss.
Go! Go! Go!
What the hell
are you doing?
You mean besides
saving your ass?
I knew that sniper
was there.
I told you, I don't
need your help.
Well, it looked like you
were gonna kill that guy.
I was gonna take him
alive
to get some answers.
Talis global is no joke.
They recruit Navy seals,
mercs, assassins,
not the kind of folks
you want to mess with alone.
This is my mission.
It's personal,
so stay out of it.
The next time you
get in my way,
I'm putting an Arrow
through you.
No hits
on the state birth index,
no hospital records.
As far as the government
is concerned,
your mystery sister
doesn't even exist.
Well, my father was
always very good at
Burying his secrets.
Yeah.
Hey, you OK?
You know, this has
to be a shock,
not as big as
a shock as maybe
becoming the flash and then
fighting alongside batwoman,
but still a shock.
I have come to terms
with the fact that
my father kept things
from us.
Yeah.
Hey, maybe you should
reach out to her.
I feel like if she
wanted to talk to me,
she would've come
and talked to me.
Oliver,
she's running around town dressed like you.
I mean, I'm no therapist,
but I'm pretty sure
the technical term for
that is cry for help.
She has to have a reason.
Yeah.
I don't feel comfortable
just barging into her life,
not without knowing more.
I need answers.
Well, luckily for you,
your wife is
very talented at finding
invisible people.
Some even call her
a genius.
So one thing we know about
your father is that he loved
a good old-fashioned
paper trail.
He used an offshore
account to handle
some of his more sensitive
financial transactions.
Yup, recurring payments
to m & h storage
in orchid bay,
and the good news is
the account is still
active.
We need whatever's in
that storage unit.
We need it here immediately.
OK. Copy that.
And...
One more thing.
Just one more?
The account is not
registered to your father.
It's registered
to your mom.
There he is...
The man himself.
You think you're
gonna be the one
to get me to talk?
Let me make one thing
clear, Ricardo.
You will tell us exactly
what we need to know.
A little good cop...
heh... bad cop.
I've beaten that game
before.
I'm not here to play
any games with you.
I'm here to offer
you a deal.
John, what are you doing?
Deputy Director Bell.
What are you doing here?
The Pentagon sent
me to help deal
with the situation
brewing in kahndaq.
Imagine my surprise
when I heard
a rumor that you had
taken Ricardo Diaz
into A.R.G.U.S. custody.
Clearly not just a rumor.
What kind of deal?
It's simple, really.
You give us Dante,
you go free.
Are you serious?
Those are the terms.
Mr. Diggle,
a word.
You think about it.
Ricardo Diaz
was just arrested.
Now you two want
to set him free?
What the hell
is going on here?
My apologies for not
looping you in sooner, sir.
Director Michaels and I
were in the process
of reinstating
the ghost initiative.
And Mr. Diaz here was
our first potential recruit.
What's that?
A defunct A.R.G.U.S.
program that employed
expendable criminals
for covert operations.
It was scrubbed
shortly after
my predecessor died.
And you think it's a good
idea to bring it back?
Are you questioning
my decision,
deputy director?
Of course not,
madam director.
That kind of radical,
out-of-the-box approach is
exactly the shot in the arm
A.R.G.U.S. needs.
I'm sure the Pentagon
will be very excited
to hear about this.
Nice work, agent.
Looking stronger
in the ring, peanut.
Just got to work on your
right cross a little more.
Guess the new
Green Arrow needs
Wild Dog's help
after all.
I'll be fine,
dad. Go.
All right.
So I'll see you soon. OK?
OK.
How you feeling?
Must have been
a nasty bug
for you to miss
3 days of work.
It was, but I'm better now.
Good. Because
the education initiative
is coming to a vote
next week,
and councilman Roberts still
needs some hand-holding, so...
actually, dad, there's
something else
I need
to talk to you about.
Mm-hmm.
Someone's planning
an attack on Star City.
Zoe, please tell me you
haven't been talking to Dinah.
They're planning
to set off multiple bombs.
And we need
to find out where.
I want you to give
the SCPD access
to the Archer Program.
You want me to use
our security system,
the very thing that
keeps us safe,
to help Star City?
You're out of
your mind.
You're the mayor.
You have a responsibility...
don't you dare talk to me
about my responsibility!
When The Glades
needed help,
no one came to
our rescue.
Dad, if this bomb
goes off,
thousands of people
could die.
How could you turn
your back on that?
The Archer Program wiped
out crime in The Glades
and helped it
thrive.
You do remember
what happened
when it fell in the
wrong hands once.
And we barely
recovered.
Oh. So I'm the wrong hands?
You know that's not
what I meant.
You know what I know is,
is that you used to stand up
for anyone in need.
It didn't matter which part
of town they were from.
You were a hero.
What happened to you?
I want to know why.
You're gonna have to be
more specific.
Why do you want
to help me?
'Cause we're the same.
I doubt that.
You said your mission
is personal.
So is mine.
I watched as my wife
got shot to death
by a drug dealer
from these streets.
And for a long time,
all I saw was red.
Then I met Oliver Queen
and the team,
and they helped me
channel my anger
into a fight
for a better life.
I just want
to pay that forward.
That can't be all.
OK.
Ever since Oliver went
to prison...
I've been alone.
My friends, my team...
they... they moved on, found
another way to be heroes.
And I've been running around
the city helping you.
You can trust me.
Follow me.
If I knew there were
this many boxes,
I wouldn't have had them all
delivered to our living room.
This feels like
a waste of time.
Hey, you call this
a waste of time?
I don't know. You
were pretty good.
You clearly weren't too happy
about Thea being born, though.
Yeah. But she grew on me.
What's that?
This is a letter
to Walter Steele...
From my dad.
I always forget that Walter
and your dad were friends
before Walter and your
mother, you know?
What does it say?
"Dear Walter,
"as you know, I haven't
always made
"the best choices,
"and if you're reading
this letter,
it means I'm gone."
"I need your
help to right one last wrong."
"There's a woman...
"Kazumi Adachi.
"I loved her.
"We had a daughter.
"And I treated both of them
unfairly.
"I abandoned them.
"I'm not proud of what I did,
"but I'm trying to make
it right.
"You're the only one I trust
with this.
Please take care of Emiko."
Are you OK?
No.
I don't know
what to think.
Emiko
and her mother were
supposed to be
taken care of
in the event of
my father's passing.
It clearly
didn't happen.
The secret identity of
your unknown sibling
has been locked in
a storage unit for years.
Your mother made sure of it.
God. You must have
so many questions.
This answers
most of them.
I mean, it'd be one thing
if my father had...
An affair.
He had a second family.
He... he had a woman
that he wanted
cared for,
he had a child that
he wanted protected.
That he loved.
How am I supposed
to believe that he's
ever loved anybody
but himself?
How... how could he
abandon them
in the first place?
I don't think moira gave
him much of a choice.
I worked...
So long and hard
to redeem
my family's name
after the terrible
things
that they've done,
but abandoning this woman
and a little girl?
It's unforgiveable.
What do you want to do?
You put all this
together alone?
People can't let you down
if you don't let them in.
Spoken like someone who
knows what that feels like.
My father gave this
to my mother
the last time he saw her.
When I was a little kid,
we used this quilt
to build play forts.
We'd play so long that
sometimes,
we'd just fall asleep there.
And before we closed
our eyes,
we always hoped for
the same thing...
that we'd wake up in
the morning, go upstairs,
and my father would be
waiting for us.
I'm guessing
he never was.
Mom and I struggled,
but we got by.
We had each other
no matter what.
But last year, there was
a fire in the apartment.
And the fire department was
nowhere to be found
because who gives a damn
about some tenement
in The Glades?
By the time
they finally arrived,
there were no survivors.
Your mom was in there.
It wasn't the fire
that killed her.
He did.
She was dead before
the fire even started.
He put a bullet in her head,
a very specific
kind of bullet.
You tracked a bullet?
Why would he kill your mom?
That's what I've been
trying to figure out.
I know these guys.
The arms dealer who
provided the rifle
and the arsonist who tried
to destroy all the evidence.
Your mission
is about revenge.
It's about justice,
which has always been in
short supply in The Glades.
William Glenmorgan is
my last stop.
And you need help
taking him down.
I need to finish this.
Let's go get that
son of a bitch.
You lost your edge.
What the hell do you want?
I want your access codes
to Archer.
So you have been talking
to Zoe.
If you've gotten her mixed
up in your canary business...
she's not a kid
anymore,
and that's not
why I'm here.
We found this in Felicity's
base of operations.
She's a criminal.
Criminals like
to blow stuff up.
Felicity's dead, Rene.
She was murdered.
And we think the person
who killed her was
behind this plan.
Like I told Zoe,
whatever happens in
Star City isn't my problem.
Well, the old Rene would've
made it his problem.
Jeez.
Do you have any idea
how much you've hurt
your daughter?
She used to idolize you.
At least as mayor,
I'm actually getting
things done,
not wasting my time
running around the city
with a hockey mask,
pretending that it mattered.
It did matter!
And it still matters.
We made a promise
to always keep fighting,
to be there for each
other no matter what...
all of us...
you, me, Roy, Diggle,
Oliver, and Felicity.
We owe her this.
The next time
you come back here,
I will have you arrested.
And you stay the hell away
from my daughter.
For Zoe's sake, I do not
want to hurt you,
but I'm not leaving here
without those codes.
The last time we fought
each other,
it didn't end so well
for you.
Hey. You are
still upset.
Damn right.
You had no right
to make that call.
You're right. It is way
above my pay grade,
but it worked out
for us.
Is that your version
of an apology?
Hey, Lyla,
you have to admit,
I actually did help.
I'm the one who shut down
the ghost initiative.
And I swore never
to reinstate it.
You knew that.
I know that,
but you would have
absolute oversight
and zero accountability.
This is the perfect cover
for our operation.
Lyla, we had to do something
to get Diaz to play ball.
Which you did by
undermining my authority
and forcing my hand.
And here I thought I was
the one in danger
of becoming
Amanda Waller.
Glenmorgan is holed up
in his compound
outside Star City.
I spotted at least
10 bodyguards.
So the killer's surrounded
by even more killers. Great.
And he's got a bleeding edge
security system.
Bypassing security system's
is gonna be a piece of cake.
You guys have cake?
I mean, I don't want cake,
but if you got a cake,
I would have a piece.
But if you don't have it,
don't worry about it.
You don't have it, right?
OK. Anyway, it's... yeah, hi.
This is Curtis.
Curtis, this is... you still
haven't told me your name.
Emiko.
I'm a huge fan
of your work.
This was not the deal.
I know, but you agreed
to letting people help you,
and if we're going
to get to Glenmorgan,
we need a guy in a chair.
Person in a chair.
Fine.
Does this mean what
I think it means?
Suit up.
It does mean what I
think it means. Heh!
Surveillance feed
coming through now.
Oh, yeah. That's a lot of
bad-looking dudes with guns.
I see why you guys
needed me for backup.
Can you disable the alarms?
I can do you one better.
I can knock out
the whole system... cameras,
motion sensors,
the whole shebang.
But it's up
to you guys to deal with
that army of
terminators yourself.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
And here we go.
We got a situation
out here, boss.
Then why are you talking
to me about it?
Deal with it.
Let's move.
Ow!
Teamwork makes
the dream work.
Go ahead.
You go get him.
I'll take care
of them.
If you want something
done right...
Kill 'em yourself.
Whoever you are, you
just made a big mistake.
I dare you
to do that again.
You come into my house
to kill me?
You'd better have
a damn good reason.
Kazumi Adachi.
You shot and killed her
last year in The Glades.
I've killed
a lot of people.
Tell me why you did it.
I didn't.
Guns aren't really
my thing.
Liar! The bullet that
killed her was yours.
It wasn't. Someone
must have set me up.
I've been on a covert
mission in Santa Prisca
for the last two years.
I just got back into
the country last month.
I swear.
It wasn't me.
You did it. You got him.
Glenmorgan
didn't kill her.
What?
I failed my mission.
I failed my mother.
You must really hate
that book.
Go home to your
daughter.
I did. She told me
to come here.
I'm sorry things didn't go
the way you hoped for
last night.
Glenmorgan's alibi
checks out.
He really was in
Santa Prisca
the night my mother
was murdered.
I spent months working
through that list,
thinking I was getting
closer to answers.
Now I'm back to square one.
The bullet's
still a lead.
Someone purposely sent me
down the wrong path.
I'm gonna find out why.
Yeah. We are.
You're not alone in
this anymore.
I'm still not
looking for a team.
OK, fine.
Then how about
a partner?
You'd be breaking the law.
Hmm, never stopped
me before.
What about your daughter?
Again, her idea.
Archer access codes
as promised.
How long
will this take?
William wrote us
a targeted search algorithm.
If you got the codes,
that means my dad
decided to help us.
Not exactly.
I forced him to.
I thought seeing you
would make him remember
who he used to be.
Hey.
Your dad may have lost
his way,
but deep down, I still
believe he's good.
Don't give up
on him yet.
Access granted.
We're in.
This is feed
from yesterday,
but we now have
unfettered access
to the Archer Program's
entire security interface.
Let's find those bombs.
Yesterday was a bigger
success than we anticipated.
You had them eating out
of your hand.
A shoo-In for reelection.
That's not why I
called you in.
Last night, one of
the canaries
paid me a visit.
She has the plans.
Maybe there's another way
for us to achieve our goal.
The Glades is the future.
We've always agreed on that.
My mission to build up
The Glades
never included wiping out
the rest of the city.
Well, Star City's a cancer.
The only way to get rid of
a cancer is to destroy it.
The canary also said
Felicity Smoak
was murdered.
You wouldn't happen
to know
anything about that,
would you?
Ms. Smoak was becoming
a liability.
She had to be dealt with.
Is that a problem?
Of course not.
Good. I would hate to think
that you're getting
cold feet, Mr. Mayor.
Psst.
You OK?
Dumb question?
No.
You know, even after
everything that I've learned
about my father...
I just never expected
anything like this.
He ruined Emiko's life.
Just abandoned her.
Well, you don't have to.
You said you didn't want
to barge into her life
without knowing
more about her,
and now you do, so
what's holding you back?
I just think that I'll
make things worse.
Oliver, you became
the Green Arrow
to right your father's
wrongs.
What your parents did
to Emiko and her mother
is beyond wrong.
You are a better man
than your father
ever was.
Don't make the mistakes
that he did.
Reach out
to your sister.
Make things right.
When I agreed
to this deal,
no one said
anything
about sticking a bomb
in the back of my head.
Didn't we?
Do it.
Tracking is activated,
and the subcortical
incendiary is armed.
So this is your
failsafe.
You are, which
is why we need
to take every precaution
to keep you in line,
because the second you
step out of it...
Boom.
You'd better
hope so, lady,
'cause if it doesn't...
I'm coming for you.
Emiko, Voice-Over: People say that
revenge corrupts the soul...
That if you go down that path,
you'll never come back.
But sometimes, embracing
the darkness is
the only way to get
justice.
My name is Emiko Queen.
I will get justice
for my mother,
and no one will stand in my way.
Hello, Emiko.
Greg, move your head.