My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
You are not going to be Bratva Captain
for much longer.
Susan Williams. She's suspecting
that Oliver's the Green Arrow.
What are we gonna do?
Hack into her computer,
and find out what's there and delete it?
- She has...
- Everything.
Apparently, I have been plagiarizing
my stories for the past two years.
And my laptop is filled
with incriminating evidence.
But now, I've been thoroughly discredited.
Did you hack Susan Williams' computer?
Thea asked me to put a few things
on Susan's computer and...
Wait. Wait, wait, wait. Thea asked you?
The Mayor's Office ordered
the falsification of autopsy reports
to protect the identity
of Detective Malone's killer.
If any of these allegations prove true,
it would likely trigger impeachment
proceedings led by the Mayor's...
This might be
the end of my administration.
When did you learn
the Green Arrow killed Detective Malone?
Why did you protect the Green Arrow?
We have no comment at this time,
but we will have
something for you shortly. Thanks.
I've called in every favor I could.
I still don't know how this got leaked.
We know how it got leaked.
It's Prometheus.
He sent the ACU after me
as the Green Arrow,
and now,
he is coming after me as the Mayor.
For something he set you up for
in the first place.
Nobody's saying the guy isn't smart.
We're just gonna have to be smarter.
What's the plan, boss?
We don't have a plan yet,
but if we lose this office,
then Prometheus wins.
I just realized,
am I allowed to be in here?
Usually, the detail stands outside.
Better go blend in.
Okay, well, on the political front,
I think the plan should be to deny,
deflect, obfuscate...
- That's just gonna confuse people...
- Yeah, but that's the point.
What if we tell the truth?
A version of the truth.
"The Green Arrow is a good guy
and I gave him the benefit of the doubt."
You know what, it worked on Pike.
I'll tell the vultures
you're gonna be making a statement.
Okay, do you want me to write you a draft?
No, I'll write it.
I need you to handle something for me.
Okay.
- You need to make things right with Susan.
- Ollie...
You got her fired
under false pretenses, Thea.
Only because I was trying to protect you,
which is what I'm doing now.
- Yes, Adrian.
- Mr. Mayor.
What's this?
My letter of resignation, in which I take
sole responsibility for the cover-up.
- No.
- The cover-up was my idea.
I approved it. I'm the Mayor.
And if this impeachment proceeding
goes the way that I think it will,
not for long.
The Council has broad powers to run
impeachment hearings as it sees fit.
It calls its own witnesses,
enters its own evidence,
they take a vote, majority rules.
But Oliver can't defend himself?
It's not a criminal trial.
The Council needs a pound of flesh,
and I'm volunteering.
- And I've already said no.
- Yeah, I'm persistent.
I have a better idea.
Be my lawyer at the hearings.
- Mr. Mayor...
- It's "Oliver".
And I'm not your boss anymore,
I'm your client.
I have many reasons for killing Anatoly.
Biggest is his poisoning Bratva
with American scum.
Fine.
What?
Take them.
What'd you do?
Extend our lives by length of good movie.
All right, lady, do your thing.
That was not your thing.
Boss is getting impeached
and you're down here playing marbles?
Actually, this was your idea.
You're the one who encouraged me
to lean into
the strengths with my tech, remember?
You said that.
We were walking down the alley,
you were like,
"Lean into your strengths..."
- You literally said that!
- I didn't...
Anyway. These are two inventions of mine,
two autonomous mini-drones.
One with offensive,
and the other with defensive capabilities.
So, what,
you can't handle yourself on the field,
you've gotta give yourself
a pair of balls?
That was... That was too harsh, wasn't it?
You think? Yeah, it was,
but, you know what? You recognized it.
- Yeah, 'cause I'm trying to work on...
- Yeah, that's progress.
Anyway, Paul's big problem
with me being Mr. Terrific
was the fact that he was worried.
But now, he doesn't have to worry
with these bad boys in my arsenal.
Sounds like you got
the emotional logic all figured out.
L do.
Now, if I can just get
these damn things to work.
News of the cover-up sent shockwaves
through City Hall,
forcing Council members into enacting
a rarely-used impeachment clause.
Mayor Oliver Queen's administration
might be over.
That woman never reports good news.
It'll work out.
I'm just waiting for my opening.
There's that optimism again.
Chase is representing me,
so I'm gonna beat this.
How are we doing with the
data pull from Prometheus' mother's house?
The sniffer pulled about
a petabyte worth of data,
it's like looking for
a needle in a haystack,
- but I am working on it.
- Good.
There's something else
that I could use your help with.
- Okay.
- Susan Williams.
- Oh.
- She's not returning my calls.
Am I really the best person
to come to for love-life advice?
She's not returning my calls
since you and Thea got her fired.
Well, in my defense, I didn't know
that was gonna be Thea's play.
I know, but I still need your help
because Thea is not budging.
Look, I know how severely problematic
what I'm about to say is,
but Susan is your girlfriend,
so, if anyone is going to fix it,
- I think it has to be you.
- I'm trying,
but like I said,
she's not returning my calls,
and you may have noticed,
I'm sort of facing an impeachment
this week.
- Okay. Yeah, I'll do my best.
- Thank you very much.
Um...
For what it's worth,
and everything I know about politics
I got from Keepin' it 1600,
but I do think
you're gonna beat this thing.
What makes you so sure?
To Star City,
Mayor Oliver Queen is a hero.
Bang.
This marks only the second time
in the 140-year history of this city
that a mayor has faced impeachment.
In 1898, Mayor Prescott
was removed from office.
We'll see what fate awaits Oliver Queen,
who's stepping into the building now.
Hey, I'll catch you up there, all right?
- Hi, Susan.
- Sorry, busy reporting for my new blog.
I'm sorry, I've been trying...
My first entry will be about
how you never took this job seriously.
As Mayor, you've just phoned it in.
You'll only ever be that other guy.
But, of course,
I can't write that
because no one will believe me
now that you've trashed my credibility.
I had nothing to do with that,
but I am working
- to make it right, I'm...
- Whatever. You deserve today.
Hey, so, what do you think
Oliver's chances are?
Come to order.
We're about to find out.
We recently learned
that Detective William Malone
was murdered by the vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
It appears
that the Mayor knew some time ago,
and actively worked to hide the fact,
even from the SCPD.
Today, the Council considers
two grave questions.
Did Oliver Queen's actions
violate the oath he took faithfully
to serve Star City?
And should he therefore be
removed as Mayor?
- Hell to the no!
- What he said.
It's Paul. Should I take it?
I'm not gonna take it.
Maybe I should take it.
No, no. Okay, I'll take it.
- Hey.
- This is so completely unfair.
Yeah, that seems to be
going around lately.
So, you got Oliver's girlfriend fired?
He told you? Of course he told you.
Well, did he also tell you
it was a mistake?
- I mean, on my part at least?
- Felicity.
I'm putting the toothpaste
back in the tube, okay?
- And how is that going?
- Well...
- Felicity, what's going on with you?
- What do you mean?
This week it was Oliver's girlfriend.
Last month,
he tells me you're getting involved
in some stuff
you shouldn't be involved in?
Well, that is a matter of perspective
considering that that "stuff"
helped get you out of prison,
- and General Walker's gun-sights.
- What're you talking about?
"Pandora"?
It's a data cache compiled
by a group of hacktivists called Helix.
They collect electronic dirt
on literally billions of people,
including General Walker.
So, when I asked for it
to get you off, they...
That's a bad choice of words.
They gave me the whole package.
And you're still in bed with these people.
What? You make it sound like
it's a bad thing.
Pandora's just a tool.
Sounds to me like this could be a weapon.
Okay. And is there a problem if it is?
- It depends, Felicity.
- On what?
On how you use it.
My autopsy showed that
mortal injury on the deceased
was consistent with the edging of
the arrowheads used by the Green Arrow.
I have here,
your original Cause of Death Report,
in which you conclude
that the Green Arrow killed Malone,
but this report,
it was never included in the case file.
Why is that?
The DA came to me, and I...
You're referring to Adrian Chase?
That's correct.
He instructed me to revise the report
to indicate
that the Throwing Star Killer
was responsible.
This report.
And you went ahead and signed it,
even though you knew it was fake,
and then passed it along to the police.
Is that the case?
- Yes.
- Why?
Did Mr. Chase threaten you?
He didn't have to.
He said the request came
from the Mayor himself.
The Mayor?
Yes, he told me
the Green Arrow killed Detective Malone.
And did Mayor Queen say why?
He said the Throwing Star Killer,
a man we've been calling Prometheus,
manipulated him.
Did he say why this Prometheus
would wanna orchestrate
Detective Malone's murder?
No.
Standing here today, do you believe
what Mr. Queen has told you?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
He's clearly been determined to protect
the Green Arrow for his own purposes.
I think the question here is, why?
Coming through.
Who's most in our corner?
- Pollard, believe it, or not.
- That's not surprising.
She can't call in the marker
I owe her for helping
with the gun reform if I'm impeached.
I'll touch base with her,
see if I can get her to call you
to testify in your own defense, okay?
Okay, well, I...
I have a very political idea.
I'm listening.
Like Adrian said, the Council needs
somebody thrown to the wolves,
and I think it should be Malone.
- Thea!
- What?
Half the SCPD is corrupt,
so, it's not hard to believe.
And he is no longer with us,
so, he wouldn't really mind.
That way, the cover-up is
no longer about the Green Arrow,
it becomes about protecting Malone's
reputation for the sake of his family.
Now you're gonna
destroy his reputation. No.
- But, Ollie...
- Thea, it's not even a question.
Okay.
How do we think the Council's gonna vote?
It's a pretty even split
with Kullens as the swing vote.
Hold on!
My target's the Mayor and his corruption.
He surrenders,
I'll let the rest of you live.
Good man.
Good woman.
Hey, hey, get to safety, get to safety.
- Quentin, the driver!
- Yeah, yeah, I'm on it.
You want me? Come on!
Lucky you. You get one more day.
Okay, all right.
Look, I appreciate what you're doing,
but I'm fine.
Mr. Mayor, all due respect,
your head's bleeding and our concussion
protocol's even stricter than the NFL's.
Well, I'm the Mayor, so I'm suspending it.
The, uh. Your driver, he's okay.
Yeah, he took a hit on his shoulder,
and he's got a bump on the head,
but he's fine.
And before you ask, he didn't see you turn
all Bruce Lee back there.
- Where's Dinah?
- She's doing her job, working the scene.
All right, I gotta get to the Bunker, l...
- Oh, boy.
- Easy, Ollie.
You know
there's a concussion protocol, right?
Yeah, so I've heard.
- This was Vigilante?
- Yeah.
Apparently, because of the
impeachment hearing, I'm a criminal.
- You okay?
- Oh. Never felt better.
Hey, so, I made sure the unis keep
all the press behind the cordon.
Trust me, you don't want them
snapping shots of you in an ambulance.
Yeah, no ambulance.
But I'm tougher than I look.
I'm gonna get back to the office.
Where have I heard that before?
Hey, look, while under threat
of the impeachment,
you can't exactly amend by-laws,
so that concussion protocol?
Yeah, it's a thing.
It's okay, Ollie,
I can go back to the office
and tell everyone
we're gonna be working overtime.
Plus, I'm never getting into a limo
with you again.
Oliver's on his way to Starling General,
but don't worry, he'll be fine.
I heard shots were fired on the motorcade.
Yeah, flipped our limo in the air.
- Cool.
- Not "cool," more like "ow,"
and Oliver might be concussed.
But in the meantime,
there's still the Vigilante out there.
Okay, Rene and I
are gonna hit the streets,
see if we can't muscle the Vigilante's
whereabouts out of some people.
Curtis, let's check the Key Hole satellite
and CC thermal cams.
Actually, hold on. I need a favor.
Okay, if this is about Susan Williams,
I'm already on it.
No, it's about the impeachment.
You said that Pandora
has dirt on a lot of people, right?
Yeah, if by "a lot of people,"
you mean "everybody," then, yeah.
What about Councilman Kullens?
Last time I checked,
he's part of "everybody."
- Why?
- You know why.
Oh. Oh!
You wanna blackmail him?
No. It's not blackmail, it's politics.
In the wake of the attack,
Councilman Kullens
has called a brief recess
to the impeachment hearings.
If the Mayor is medically cleared,
the Council will vote tomorrow.
Okay.
Well, sounds like you need a note
from your doctor, Mr. Mayor.
This is ridiculous,
I know what real injury feels like.
I can only imagine, given your other job.
And you're right, your CAT scan is clear.
- Good.
- Uh-uh-uh. Not so fast.
Look, I can't discharge you without
a few more hours of observation.
Doctor Schwartz...
People can withstand only so much strain.
And being both Mayor and him,
it's unsustainable.
I assure you, my body can handle it.
I'm not talking about your body,
Mr. Queen.
I'm talking about this.
The mind needs rest,
or at least someone to take your thoughts
off all the evil you face each day.
Doctor Schwartz,
are you prescribing me a girlfriend?
Or just a friend.
Hi, this is Susan.
I can't come to the phone...
"Demand an exam"?
Yeah, it rhyme better in Russian.
Spros dopros is Bratva way
to call Pakhan to account for actions.
Captains all listen,
maybe Pakhan lose position.
That's good news!
That's good. That means we can
overthrow Gregor without a fight.
No. Everybody knows about
Gregor's deal with Kovar.
No, no, we still end up dead.
Men who call, vote, are killed
if Pakhan keeps position.
Anatoly, why bother?
I did not want to die
in hospital basement.
That's... Fair.
Look, all we have to do is find evidence
that Gregor's deal with Kovar
benefits him and not the Bratva.
Yes, but where are we going to find that?
I have to go.
Code says you have one hour to finalize
personal affairs before Spros dopros.
I can do that.
But you must have Captain with you,
who is not me.
I'll lose him.
I'm really good at losing people.
I've got bullet fragments and casings
coming out of my ass,
but nothing new.
All right, I'll catch you back downtown.
Hey, Johnson,
gotta make room for a tow truck.
- Anything?
- Nada.
Peeps on the street are actually
more afraid of the Vigilante than us.
What about you?
Vigilante changes artillery supplier
every week.
Every lead goes cold.
We could really use
a break right about now.
I think I got something.
Yes! I totally manifested that!
What do you got?
When my sonic cry hit Vigilante,
it knocked off a small piece of his visor.
It looks like it's lined
with some kind of circuitry.
Well, that means it's manufactured.
Maybe I can link to back
to where he bought it from.
I think I can do you one better.
My T-Spheres can actually track the tech
to the individual user.
Except they won't be ready
till the iPhone 16 is released.
- Ye, of little faith...
- What's a T-Sphere?
Curtis' balls.
They're something really fascinating,
and of my own personal invention.
I realized that quantum computation
- could be used to...
- All right, yeah, forget I asked.
I'll bring you guys the visor, okay?
Copy that, we're here.
Curtis, this is on you now.
Challenge accepted.
Hey, seriously, man,
what's up with your balls?
I mean, you were literally gonna
throw those things in the trash.
Paul called, asked me to dinner.
Like, a date.
Like, I'm gonna get my man back.
I told you, hoss,
some piece of tech ain't gonna...
Look, I know Paul,
he wouldn't be asking me to go out
to dinner if he wasn't ready to reconcile.
Personal call?
Uh, yeah, I had a family emergency.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. Family's important.
Hey, why don't I log that in for you?
So you can handle your emergency.
Uh...
Don't worry, I'll take good care of this.
And, uh, I hope everything's okay
with your family.
- Oliver Queen is mine.
- Not if I kill him first.
Yes.
I'd like to report a sighting
of Vigilante.
This is District Attorney Chase.
Hey, Oliver's out of the hospital,
headed to City Hall.
Any word from Dinah?
Um, she's at the precinct, trying to
recover that piece of Vigilante's visor.
What about you, Felicity?
And don't tell me that it's traffic cams,
we both know they're on autopilot.
I sent Thea something
to sway Councilman Kullens.
Apparently, he's the swing vote
on Oliver's impeachment.
Pandora?
Officially, his wife died in a car crash.
Unofficially, she crashed the car
on purpose.
- Suicide?
- He used his clout to cover it up,
so I'm guessing
he's not gonna want it uncovered.
And you are okay with this, right?
I think the city needs Oliver
to keep being Mayor.
Felicity, Kullens is not a criminal,
he's a human being.
He's a politician,
that's hardly the same thing.
A human being that went through
a very tragic accident,
a very private one.
Come on, this isn't you.
Well, it pretty much is.
Okay, do you know what your superpower is?
- Computers?
- Empathy.
Big, reflexive, pure empathy.
- Well, maybe I'm fresh out.
- Because of Billy.
It's a dark world.
And for the past four years,
I have watched you and Oliver
and Laurel and Thea and Roy,
I've watched all of you
use a little darkness to fight it.
That's true.
Sometimes, we do fight fire with fire,
but every time we do, Felicity,
every single time,
we risk being burned.
Well, some days, I can't help but feel
as if this city
wants to collapse in on itself,
and all we're doing is
delaying the inevitable.
No, we're preventing it.
We're the good guys,
don't you forget that, all right?
Whack-a-mole.
We got Prometheus, the Vigilante.
And the one wild card I thought
maybe might be on our side,
just murdered a cop.
- Nah, the Green Arrow got played.
- I don't know.
What I do know is
the next Mayor owes me a raise.
Yeah, I'll put in a word with Mayor Queen.
He's not impeached yet.
All right.
Please tell me you didn't send it.
The thing with Kullens' wife,
he doesn't deserve that.
- Felicity told you, didn't she?
- Thea...
I haven't sent the email, okay?
Ollie, don't look at me like that,
it's politics!
There's about to be a vote,
so it's time to play hardball.
This isn't hardball, this is cruel.
What would be cruel is
the people of this city
not having you as the Mayor.
The Anti-Crime Unit,
low-income housing,
commonsense gun legislation.
Ollie, in the short amount of time
you've been doing this,
you've done a remarkable job.
Please, just let me do what I have to do
to help you keep doing that.
Felicity told me about this Kullens thing
because of something
that John said to her.
Thea, when you fight fire with fire,
you are probably gonna get burned.
I won't. It'll be fine.
Like it was with Susan?
You destroyed her career,
now you've graduated to blackmail.
Where does it stop?
Magic hands.
The magnetic resonance frequencies
within Vigilante's tech
are now communicating with my T-Spheres.
Great. So what does it mean?
Can we catch the Vigilante, or not?
Well, cross your fingers
and your toes.
It's working!
The T-Sphere's picking up on the signal
from the piece of visor!
Yeah, but the other one's still wonky.
No, no, it's not.
It's actually tracking
the rest of the visor.
- Let's take down this SOB.
- Without Oliver?
If Vigilante gets to him, we'll be
doing this without Oliver permanently.
- Let's suit up.
- Suit up!
Oh. Sorry, I thought since Oliver's gone,
I would, probably...
But it makes more sense probably for you...
I'll make sure I'll work on
the timing there. Promise.
- Balls.
- My. T-Spheres. Don't call 'em "balls."
You speak with Pollard?
She won't call you to testify
without Kullens' blessing.
We're not gonna get that.
And the Council hearing directly
from you
is only one of two ways
I can see us winning this thing.
- What's the second way?
- You won't like it.
Does it involve
offering up a sacrificial lamb?
Either me, or Detective Malone.
Oliver, this impeachment
is about punishing someone,
and if you don't offer up a name,
this'll be the last time
you're looking out that window.
If the Council is not gonna let me
testify at the hearing,
then I need to take my case
directly to the public.
- A press conference?
- Yeah.
Mind filling me in on
who you're throwing under the bus?
The Green Arrow.
Right here.
And, stop.
- Dude, we got him?
- I think so.
- Oh. This is bad.
- Why is that?
The building that
you just stopped in front of?
Well, City Hall is located
directly behind it, offering
perfect line-of-sight to where
Oliver is giving his speech.
It's the Vigilante's Book Depository.
Felicity, we need you
to check the blueprints.
Yeah, already on it.
Okay, the sixth floor is under renovation.
Dollars to donuts...
That's where he'll be.
Yeah. I'm listening.
Yeah, copy that.
Vigilante is across the street.
Sixth floor.
He's gonna take you out as soon as
you walk outside into the open.
- Is the team on site?
- Yeah.
Then it'll be fine.
Good evening, everyone.
I'd like to thank the City Council
for conducting these hearings
with honesty and integrity.
Simply wish that I could've done the same
with regards to the Green Arrow's
murder of Detective William Malone.
- Terrific, where is he?
- This way, this way!
What's so funny?
I think I just found
a new use for my T-Sphere.
Your what?
When I took the oath of office,
I promised to be honest and forthright.
I never wanted to be a politician
who relied on dirty politics
or underhanded tactics.
Now, that's what I'm talking about!
Oh, no.
And in the spirit of that transparency,
I think I owe everyone an explanation
as to why
I covered up what the Green Arrow did.
I did it in a misguided attempt
to protect everyone from the tragic news
that the Green Arrow
had become a cop killer.
What?
That a man we had put our faith in
had failed this city.
I didn't think that we could afford
to lose another hero.
Hey, Vigilante!
I got two of these.
- Nice aim.
- That's the thing, they aim themselves.
Awesome!
You're awesome. That was badass.
- That mean no more ball jokes?
- Hell, no.
Remind me to thank Cisco
for that upgraded Kevlar.
- You guys all right?
- Yeah, but what about Oliver?
But the truth is more important,
and the truth is that
the Green Arrow has gone rogue.
We must disavow him, we must hunt him,
and punish him for what he has done.
Green Arrow is not a hero.
He is what's keeping Star City from being
the best that it can be.
Thank you very much.
They're still deliberating.
Well, that's taking longer than I thought.
Yeah, well,
you gave them plenty to think about.
So, how's it feel, huh?
Making yourself into a villain like that?
Susan Williams is here.
You want me to say you're busy?
No! No, I'd like to tell the truth
for the rest of the day,
if at all possible. Please send her in.
All right.
Susan, please.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're here.
- Susan, I'm very sorry.
- I got my job back.
An anonymous hacker confessed
that the plagiarism story was fake.
Said they were just messing with us.
My boss apologized.
Well, that's good news.
Still though, I'm really sorry.
Are you? What I mean is,
you didn't know about this
beforehand, did you?
No, I had no idea.
But once you did,
you made them make it right. Right?
- Are we off the record?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
So, what happens next?
You mean, what do I do with your secret?
I keep it.
I care about this city,
and you're working double-time
to make it a better place.
I do appreciate that, but I meant,
what happens next with us?
Uh...
Sorry to interrupt,
but I think you'll be happy that we did.
Council voted
against impeachment.
Thank you so much, Adrian,
I could not have done this without you.
Are you kidding me? No thanks needed.
You're not just my boss, Oliver,
you're my friend.
I'm gonna go give Thea the good news.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hey, no need to pack up, we won.
We both get to keep our jobs.
Yeah, not...
Not both of us.
Look, Ollie, you... You were right. I...
I am getting deeper and deeper
into the mud lately,
and it's like my bloodlust last year,
except instead of arrows and swords,
I've replaced it with
politics and slanders, so I am...
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
that you have to quit, Thea.
- I need you here...
- Ollie, please.
Please don't ask me to stay,
because I will.
I will for you.
But I am broken. Okay?
I need you to let me go.
Let me go, so, I can try to fix myself.
Well...
- Your resignation's accepted.
- Thank you.
My resignation letter's on the desk.
When I signal,
you must align with Anatoly,
who called Spros dopros,
or Gregor, our incumbent Pakhan.
Now, let's get this over with quickly.
Hey, stop!
Mr. Queen, you do not have floor.
Just give me 10 seconds,
listen to what I have to say,
and if you don't like it, shoot me.
As you wish.
This laptop contains
80 million rubles in transfers
from Kovar's accounts
to accounts that Gregor controls.
Yes, we know this,
to spread among Bratva captains.
It also contains 40 million rubles worth
of bank transfers from Kovar
that Gregor hasn't disclosed.
Open it. Ask him if it's true.
Is this true, Gregor?
40 million rubles. So, it's true.
If anybody wishes to cast a new vote,
please do so now.
It seems that
you are deciding vote, Viktor.
What say you, my friend?
We have a new Pakhan.
This is most disappointing.
I liked many of you.
- Council isn't impeaching.
- Yes!
- Still the mayor.
- Whoo!
Yet, the Green Arrow is
Public Enemy Number One.
We've dealt with
the police on our backs before.
Not like this, one of their own is dead.
Dinah's right.
And now we know just how much the police
can interfere with our work here.
Can I go?
I'm kind of
getting back together with Paul.
It's a big deal.
- Can I leave? Can I...
- Yes! Yes, of course. Go.
Have fun.
Everyone should have fun tonight.
Just quickly though,
I might have buried the headline here.
You all saved my life.
And five months ago,
I never would've thought
that was possible.
Thank you for working hard,
thank you for banding together,
thank you for being...
Sorry. L...
I mean, thank you for saying thank you.
Wow. Man to man, that means a lot,
but I'm really late to see Paul, so...
- Give Paul my best.
- Thank you!
- Good luck.
- Good luck!
Oh. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, we were stopping an assassination.
Can you believe
I stopped an assassination?
Wow.
So, on the way over here,
I rehearsed what I would say to you.
How I would win you back,
tell you I love you.
You know, I just started with...
That was definitely not
how I planned on opening,
but can I start again? I'ma start again.
When I came to...
It's nice to see you, Curtis. I mean that.
As much as you're going to think
that I don't.
What?
Are you divorcing me?
I'm sorry. I really am.
- Felicity!
- Hi!
Lam so glad you got in touch.
- Though I am a little surprised?
- Yeah, me, too.
Well, "surprised" isn't actually
the right word to describe
how I'm feeling.
What's the right word?
Ready.
A good friend of mine
told me that if you're gonna try
to fight fire with fire,
you're gonna get burned,
but then another friend of mine
came through something
pretty scary tonight
because he had backup,
a team.
You're accepting the invitation
to join Helix?
Yes. Full throttle.
Susan.
Oh. Hey.
- I thought we could talk.
- About?
An exclusive.
Can we set up the meeting tomorrow?
I'm late for a dinner.
The thing is that this story,
it's important.
You could call it life or death.