My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will
fulfill my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Next time your daughter
calls the Vigilante,
we'll be able
to listen to every word.
I know you swore to bring
this guy down, detective,
but using your own
daughter as bait,
that's stone cold.
Where'd you get it?
From your stepfather.
And where
did he get it?
Belongs to your mother.
Mmm.
Hi, George.
Vanch...
Surprised to see me?
I imagine you would be, seeing
as how you botched my trial,
and from what Viv here tells me,
protecting my interests.
There were contingencies
that couldn't be anticipated.
Yes, Vivian told me.
The head of the Triad
getting ventilated,
Bertinelli getting collared,
and, uh, this archer.
Exactly.
What am I supposed to do in
the face of something like that?
Absolutely nothing, Georgie.
Tell you what.
All is forgiven.
Give us a hug.
Come on.
You know, I could use
a place to stay
while I'm getting my sea legs
back under me, George.
And you got a nice place here.
What do you say? George?
George?
Ahem.
I hope George
has been food shopping.
I'm famished.
So this book contains
a list of the names
of the guys you've been hunting.
And this book,
your mother's,
has the same list of names.
It's identical.
So where'd your mother
get her copy, Oliver?
For that matter,
who gave it to you?
Felicity Smoak.
She said that Walter found it
in their bedroom.
And now he's missing.
She's my mother,
Diggle.
She's not the kind
of person who would--
Have her husband disappeared?
Because that's really
the question, isn't it, Oliver?
I understand why you would believe
your mother over your stepfather,
but I tend to believe the innocent
party is whoever's missing--
and presumed dead.
Twitch, and I will
open your throat.
How many more with you?
What?!
You have ten seconds
to tell me something I believe
before I cut out
your voice box.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yao Fei sent me here,
and I'm pretty sure
it wasn't so you could kill me.
What?
Yao Fei.
He gave me
directions to your...
plane.
Frank, you got be
kidding me.
You can't throw me
another assignment now.
It's Lieutenant,
and I'm pretty sure
that's what gives me
the authority.
I'm drawing in
on the Hood investigation.
I am going
to get this bastard.
Have you considered
the possibility no one wants you to?
What?
He saved the Christmas hostages.
He took down an arsonist
and armored car thieves,
and just last week, he busted
the Vertigo drug ring when we couldn't.
What was urban legend's
becoming heroic.
If this man's a hero,
I don't know what my life
in this city as a cop means.
Let me suggest you find meaning
in following orders.
Frank, listen!
I'm close.
If my lead comes
to something more...
Come to me with something real,
Quentin, and we'll talk.
In the meantime,
I'm assigning you another case.
Hey.
Heading out?
Oh, yeah,
it's a meeting
with the financial
planners.
Are you all right?
There was something
that I wanted to talk to you about.
I want to talk
to you about Walter.
Right around Christmas,
when he...disappeared,
he gave me this.
This is your
father's notebook.
He kept a list
of all the people in Starling City
who owed him favors.
I had...no idea
there was
so many of them.
I've just been researching
some of those names
online, and, um,
they're not good people.
Oliver, I have no idea
what your father
was involved in
or with whom.
And you and your sister
both now know
that he wasn't exactly
honest with me.
Then we need to find out--
no.
If what you say
is true
and this list is filled
with bad people
and Walter was looking
into it, and now he--
the only way to keep
this family safe
is for everyone in it to stop
asking questions,
including you,
Oliver.
Promise me.
So this is really happening.
498 hours
of community service to go.
499. This orientation
doesn't count.
Tell me how this is not
cruel and unusual punishment.
Anastasia, I'd like you
to meet our new intern,
Thea Queen.
Interns get school credit.
I'm more like
a court-ordered slave.
Oh. I can relate.
Anastasia is on
a one year pro-bono
sabbatical
from her law firm.
And apparently
from my six figure salary.
The experience of helping others
is its own reward.
I have yet to see
any evidence of that.
And speaking a lack of evidence,
Cyrus Vanch was released
from Iron Heights.
We represent a victim's
advocacy group
who's trying
to keep Vanch locked up.
I'm calling Kate Spencer.
I already did.
She said there's nothing
the D.A.'s office can do
without further evidence.
Well, then I'm going
to her office.
And then she also said
not to show up at her office.
Vanch is connected
to human trafficking,
drug running,
racketeering,
and at least 52
different homicides.
Ok, so what's the play?
Because unless you have access
to some private police force,
Vanch will stay free
to roam the streets.
I have to get this.
Hello?
How does a night with me
and a dozen famous chefs sound?
Like an episode
of "The Bachelor".
I'm auditioning potential chefs
for the club tomorrow night.
I've arranged a tasting,
and I could use
an extra set of taste buds.
I'm trying
to figure out how to get
a vicious criminal
back in jail. I can't.
It's perfect.
It sounds like hungry work.
Tomorrow night?
Maybe, if we could
do it early.
Look, I got to go.
There's someone
I have to call.
I'll see you later. Bye.
You don't find that
a little convenient,
her just so happening
to have burned the book?
She did it out of concern for
my safety, Diggle.
Or her own.
Oliver, you said it yourself.
Whoever compiled that list is
involved in something very dangerous.
And if your mother
is lying to you...
And she didn't know
any of the names on the list.
She said she didn't.
You don't have to take
her word for it.
Oliver, if this were anybody else,
you'd be hooded up right now
on your way to having
an arrow-side chat with them.
This isn't anybody else.
This is my mother.
And I know her.
What's that?
That is the phone
that I gave to Lance
so that he could
contact the Hood.
Is he asking
to turn yourself in?
He gave it
to Laurel. Hello?
I need your help.
That's why you have the phone.
Cyrus Vanch was just released
from prison on a technicality.
Living large
in his lawyer's house.
Who is now missing.
There's no evidence
of foul play.
But I know he's just
Vanch's first victim,
and he won't be
his last.
What
about the police?
They can't move on him
without evidence
of new criminal
activity.
Laurel, obtaining evidence
isn't what I do.
Vanch is dangerous.
Hold on to the phone,
I'll call.
Laurel needs my help.
Oliver, are you running
to help her...
or away from the truth
about your mother?
I have work to do.
Hey, Detective?
I'm busy, Kelton.
I'm pretty sure you're going to
want to hear this.
The bug I put in that phone
from the Vigilante just lit up.
Your daughter's playing
Maid Marion to Robin Hood again.
Where you going?
Lieutenant Pike's
office.
If she's meeting
with the Hood,
there's going to be
a task force there when she does.
♪ Arrow 1x13 ♪
Betrayal
Original Air Date on February 6, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
See, we got to look at all this
as an opportunity.
The Triad and the Bertinelli
organization are leaderless.
The giant sucking
sound you're hearing
is the current power vacuum
in Starling City,
the one that
I plan on filling.
How are you going to convince
the Triad and Bertinelli's crew
that they should
sign up with you?
Well...
that's an excellent
question.
I need to do something.
Something spectacular.
To get their attention
and earn their respect.
You know what
I learned in prison?
If you want to be
respected,
you find the biggest guy
and you put him down permanent.
I think I just found
the biggest guy.
This is going to be fun.
I even wore
my fat pants.
I don't want to know
what those are, do I?
Nope.
Ohh.
This is work.
It'll just
be a second, okay?
Hello?
It's me. I have something.
Can you meet?
Yeah, where?
Rooftop, Winick building.
30 minutes.
Good work, Kelton.
Okay, everybody.
Rubber bullets.
This is my daughter here.
She cannot come
to any harm.
But outside of that,
you do whatever
needs doing
to bring that
archer down.
You sure about this?
Look, she knows I'd do anything
to catch this bastard.
And this is the best--
it's the only option I've got.
Look, I want to get this guy
just as badly as you do.
I just don't want to see
anything come between you two.
I warned her. I said stay away
from this lunatic.
She didn't.
You don't think that turns
a knife in my back?
I hope she sees it that way.
Mmm, put those
puppy dog eyes away.
Something's
come up at work.
That can't wait
until tomorrow?
It'll only be an hour.
I can meet you at the club.
One hour.
An hour and a half.
Tops.
Ricky has been driving me
for six years now.
I can't remember
the last time he missed a day.
Thank you for offering
to fill in, Mr. Diggle.
It's my pleasure, Mrs. Queen.
Believe me.
Are you sure my son
won't miss you?
He said he was staying
in for the evening.
And you believed him?
It's been my experience
when your son wants
some alone time,
there's not much I
can do to stop him.
Hmm. Much to my chagrin.
You can stop just up ahead.
No need to escort me inside.
I'm fine on my own,
Mr. Diggle.
Of course, Mrs. Queen.
Mrs. Queen.
I was just, uh,
looking for the restroom.
Excuse me, ladies.
Happy Birthday.
Hello, Laurel.
Thank you
for helping.
I couldn't do much.
Vanch's position
is too heavily fortified.
But I did get this.
Evidence he's trying
to take over the positions
vacated by Frank Bertinelli
and...
and the Triad.
What's wrong?
We're not alone.
What?!
SCPD!
Get down! Hands
where we can see 'em!
Dad!
Do it now!
You so much as leave
a bruise on her,
and I swear I will
drag you down to hell myself.
Laurel, I'm sorry.
Quentin, don't!
I don't know what's worse--
the fact that you lied to me
or nearly got me killed!
You were
completely safe.
I was on a rooftop
with an army of men pointing
their guns in my face!
Well, you shouldn't have been
on that roof in the first place.
No! You wanted me
on that roof.
Wasn't that the whole point
of your little trap?
I'm trying
to catch a killer.
You manipulated me.
Manipulated?
You practically ran to this guy.
I told you, I said stay away from him
and you did not.
That was before you gave me the phone!
What?!
That's before you realized
that you could use me as bait.
Your own daughter.
Yeah, but you wouldn't
listen to me!
You are so blinded
by your hate for him
that you don't
realize the damage
that it's doing
in your own life.
To your family.
So what happens
when you catch him?
What happens then, Dad?
You're going to find
another criminal;
somebody else to blame
for mom leaving?
For Sarah dying,
for your drinking?
That's enough,
Laurel.
Yeah, you're damn right, it is.
Laurel!
The phone.
Give me the phone.
Laurel could have
been hurt, or worse.
And I suppose
that was Lance's fault.
What's your point, Dig?
Just that you don't really see
straight when it comes to Laurel.
Or your mother.
This is not the time
to bring
this up again.
Ok. Ok.
But there's something
I should tell you
and it's better
I tell you now than later.
I'll be driving your mother
around for a few days.
You're spying on her?!
Just doing my due diligence,
Oliver. See if she meets with
anyone we might be interested in.
She's not a suspect.
She's my mother.
Which is exactly
why someone needs to take
a close, objective
look at her.
Oliver, something's going on
in this city. You know it.
That doesn't mean
she's involved.
Then there's no harm
in me driving her around
for a few days, is there?
I still can't believe it.
He used me as bait!
Who?
My father.
He was trying
to catch the Vigilante.
He eavesdropped on my phone
conversation with him
and then lied in wait
with his jack boots.
This was tonight?
Yes.
While you were working.
This was work.
So you met up with the Hood guy?
Knowingly?
He's contacted me before.
He helped me
with the Declan case
and Joanna's arson
investigation.
The Declan case
was months ago.
I know, Tommy, I've been
wanting to tell you.
Laurel,
he's a murderer!
God.
You sound like my father.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but he's right.
Are you seriously
taking his side?
He's been lying
to me for weeks!
Yeah, it feels like
crap, doesn't it?
Tommy!
A sting operation to catch
the notorious Starling City vigilante
wreaked havoc last night.
Despite the police's
failed attempt
to apprehend the Vigilante,
police have continued to insist
that their warnings remain.
This archer is to be
considered armed and dangerous.
Should you find yourself in
harm's way, always always,
call 9-1-1.
Interesting.
Using deception
and intimidation
to make a name
for himself.
This guy
stole my move.
I have news.
From my friend
in the police department.
I think I've figured out a way to
get the Hood out and into the open.
Huh.
Astonish me.
Remember that attorney?
Laurel Lance?
Now what's wrong
with this picture?
You look like
you're...working.
I'm going
over résumes
for the Chef's position
at the nightclub.
This guy looks pretty good.
He won "Top Chef" Season Six.
At this point,
it is basically
a culinary prerequisite
to be on that show.
Ohh.
Can I talk to you
about something?
Tommy...
Every time you want
to talk to me about something
and that something is Laurel,
you look like you're about
to tell me you have
a terminal disease.
She's been working
with the Hood guy.
What?
You're letting her work
with that crazy person?
She could get hurt, Tommy.
I'm not "letting"
her do anything, okay?
I only just
found out about it
because she accidentally
slipped up
on one
of her many lies.
She's lying to you?
That doesn't sound like Laurel.
Lying, keeping secrets
about who she's spending time with--
does that remind you
of anybody we know?
Me, in every relationship
that I've been in.
Me, too.
Except this one.
There's some sort of infatuation
thing going on here.
I...
We both know
that she has
a pretty strong
track record
of being attracted to
guys who are dangerous,
who break the rules.
Show me a more dangerous
rule breaker than the Hood.
I just think you need to have
an honest chat with her.
Find out the real reason
she's keeping secrets.
I just can't
believe that Laurel,
of all people,
would lie to my face.
I guess that's
the way that it is
with the people
that you're closest to.
I know.
But talk to her anyway,
and fix this.
Before it becomes
something that's unfixable.
Shéngcun.
It's Chinese.
It means sur--
Survive.
What do you think he meant,
besides not getting killed?
There's an airfield
10 clicks from here.
It's key off this island.
Yao Fei and I had been
observing it for months,
familiarizing ourselves
with their operations.
We were supposed to get off
this island together.
But then Yao Fei
was compromised,
and we were separated.
What's this for?
I think Yao Fei sent you
because he knows
I cannot take the airstrip alone.
Sounds like Yao Fei.
He is a softer judge
of character than I am.
If you're going
to have my back,
I need to know
you can cover it.
What are you doing?
Fight back.
Keep your blade up.
Always stay
behind your sword.
You have no skill.
No strength.
No training.
To say you fight like a girl
would be a compliment.
I told you--
I'm not a soldier.
I was shipwrecked here.
I killed the guy
that was wearing
this uniform by accident.
Where was Yao Fei?
He told me to run.
And I did.
Hey, it's Tommy,
hit me on the beep.
Hey, it's me again.
Please call me back.
I think
we should talk.
I was just
leaving you a message.
I love a girl who can take
care of herself.
But can't block a taser.
Oh, no need to get out
of the car, Mr. Diggle.
It's just my accountant.
The only threat is boredom.
Well, it's no
problem at all,
Mrs. Queen.
It's my job.
Yes. Well, then,
take the night off.
I'm quite all right.
It's taken care of.
I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard will not be
a problem anymore.
Given your propensity
for squeamishness,
I'm assuming that Mr. Ballard
remains in good health.
I made it clear
to him persuasively
that his plans endangered
the undertaking.
I didn't have to make
the usual threats.
Excellent.
Now, one more matter
to attend to.
I need you to have
to contents of this address
removed and disposed of
thoroughly.
The warehouse where
you're storing the remains
of "the Queen's Gambit".
I already told you, I knew
Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
And I don't think it serves for
anyone to find evidence of that.
Do you?
What the hell
are you doing?
Nothin'. Just hangin'.
I work for Mrs. Queen.
And I work security for
the man she's meeting with.
I guess that means
we're on the same team.
I don't think so.
And I'm going to need to see
what you put
in your pocket just then.
What are you, man,
the police?
Show it to me.
Do it now.
Right.
Just thought I could come in
here and ruin my lungs a little bit.
I know,
it's a filthy habit.
Laurel, it's me.
Can we talk?
Laurel?
Make sure this message
finds its way to the Vigilante.
Do it fast,
because at sunrise,
I'm going to leave pieces
of this girl all over Starling City
unless he pays me
a little visit.
You know, gives us a chance
to get to know each other better.
What do we do?
Can your CSIs,
I don't know,
can they track this
or trace it or something?
How did he know
about Laurel?
What?
How does this guy know
Laurel is connected
to the Hood?
I have no idea.
I only found out about it
myself last night.
She--she said you knew.
Well, just me and...
Mr. Lance,
this maniac has got Laurel!
You got to call in
posse or something,
I don't know, SWAT teams.
I can't.
Detective Lance...
I got to go
make a call.
Thanks for coming.
It didn't seem like a good idea
to talk about this at your house.
Yeah, it would have been
a little awkward
for you to explain to my mother
that you're spying on her.
No, man.
Awkward part's
coming up.
You bugged
my mother?
Just listen.
It's taken care of.
I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard will not be
a problem anymore.
Given your propensity
for squeamishness,
I'm assuming that Mr. Ballard
remains in good health.
I made it clear
to him persuasively
that his plans endangered
the undertaking.
I didn't have to make
the usual threats.
Excellent.
Now, one more matter
to attend to.
I need you to have
to contents of this address
removed and disposed of
thoroughly.
The warehouse where
you're storing the remains
of "the Queen's Gambit".
I already told you, I knew
Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
I'm sorry, man.
The yacht was sabotaged.
Somebody tried
to kill my father.
And your mother
was involved somehow.
You do not know
that she was involved, Diggle!
What I do know Oliver,
and so do you,
is that she kept this a secret.
Why would she do that if she
didn't have something to hide?
Is that...?
Yeah!
You have three seconds
before I have this line
permanently disconnected.
It's Laurel.
She's been kidnapped.
Listen, whoever this is,
he's going to kill my daughter.
Please believe me.
Sorry.
It's nothing personal.
The airfield was a very
heavily fortified position.
I've been there.
And I cannot
take it on my own.
So--so what?!
Huh? You're just
going to kill me?
Like I said...
It's nothing personal.
But if you're alive,
they will find you.
And if they find you,
they will torture you
until you give up my location,
and I cannot allow
for that to happen.
Hey, don't leave! No, please don't
do this, all right?!
I'm not going to say
anything to that--
Don't make it
more difficult upon yourself.
I can do this
in a way
that you will not
feel it at all.
Ahhh!
Steve Wilson.
Oliver Queen.
Well, Oliver Queen...
There might be a fighter
inside of you after all.
Detective.
If this is another trick,
you will not like
the consequences.
I'm not particularly
happy right now.
I hate you.
I hate everything you stand for.
But this lunatic
has my little girl.
He left this behind
as some kind of ransom note.
His name is Cyrus Vanch.
Jeez...
He'll kill her if he
doesn't get to you.
He'll kill her anyway.
So why come to me?
It's a pretty tight
circle that knows
about you and my daughter
working together.
If Vanch knows, it's because someone
at the precinct talked.
There isn't anybody else
I could trust.
Vanch is holed up
in a mansion.
It's a heavily
fortified position.
I was there. I can't
take it by myself.
I need your help.
Then I need yours.
Time's running out.
And still no visit
from your friend.
I might have overestimated his
fondness for you.
Assault with intent.
And kidnapping.
You're going to rot in prison
for life this time.
That's assuming
your hooded BFF
saves you.
And his chances
of survival are not so great.
He's going up
against trained men
with their fingers
on the trigger
of guns that fire up to
600 rounds per minute.
Now, I'm no Einstein,
but that is a lot
of bullets.
And even if he were
to take them out,
I have two sharpshooters
on the roof.
And even if he were
to get by them,
what's he going to do against
the veritable army
of sons of bitches
I've got waiting for him?
Now, as I said,
I'm no Einstein.
But I can count to 24.
And in case
you're wondering--
I was so I studied up
on my news footage--
24 is the exact number
of arrows he carries in his quiver
and flechettes
around his forearm.
Lose the bow,
Merida.
Ventilate him.
My daughter!
My little girl!
I'm the Vigilante.
You're the cop.
That doesn't mean I have to read
the bastard his rights, though.
Laurel, are you ok?
Yeah.
I'm ok.
All right,
you're good to go.
I'll, uh, I'll take you
home now.
I can take a cab.
Laurel, you had a trauma.
I'll drive you home.
No.
What?
I'm going to need you to keep
your distance for a while.
Laurel...
Dad, I love you.
I'll always love you.
But what I can't do right now
is trust you.
I was just doing my job.
I thought you'd understand
at least that.
That part I do understand.
But lying to me,
using me...
It's going to take longer.
Are you all right?
What would you think if I said
I didn't know?
That you were being honest.
My father
has the phone now.
And I don't think he'll be
giving it back any time soon.
Maybe that's good.
I didn't see how
it would put you in danger.
I'm a big girl.
I knew the risks.
Now I know them.
And I'm not willing
to take them with you.
What does that mean?
It means good-bye.
Laurel!
Laurel.
Oh, my God, Laurel.
Laurel, tell me
you are okay, please.
No, no, I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm so sorry.
No, no,
it doesn't matter,
just as long
as you're okay.
You know, this does not
change anything
between you and I.
It takes two men
to take the air field.
And if you compromise
my getting off this island,
I will kill you.
You've had
your second chance.
You need me
just as much as I need you.
So what's our next step?
Turning you into something
that won't get us both killed.
Choose a weapon.
We're starting now?
That's mine.
You are the lunatic
who tortured me?!
No, that was another guy.
Bull!
This mask, it's my
operational equivalent
to a balaclava.
My partner
and I wore them
to keep our identities
classified during our missions.
You're lying.
Fyers told me this nutcase
is a prisoner on the island.
He lied to you.
My partner and I came
here to free Yao Fei
and get him
off this island.
We're A.S.I.S.
Australian
intelligence.
Now.
You are going to find
your silver weapon.
Have you considered
a sword?
I like swords.
I made it clear
to him persuasively
that his plans endangered
the undertaking.
I didn't have to make
the usual threats.
I've listened
to this 15 times.
It's definitely her
voice, Diggle. I just...
I can't believe
it's her.
We all have blind spots
when it comes to family.
Yeah. Laurel's almost
got her killed tonight.
Vanch never would have known
about her connection to me
if Lance hadn't
have lied to her.
I guess the lesson here
is blind trust can be dangerous.
I made it clear
to him persuasively
that his plans endangered
the undertaking.
I didn't have to make
the usual threats.
What's the undertaking?
I don't know.
But with all this
talk about threats,
it can't be good.
You warned me that
if she was lying
would be to cover up her
involvement in something dangerous.
I need to know what
The Undertaking is.
What are you going to do?
I need to have another
chat with my mom.
I'll need the Unidac merger
finalized by the end of the week.
We're on something
of a clock here.
Moira Queen,
you have failed this city.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==