Previously on Arrow...
- Lyla.
- We need to talk about John.
He's back in the country.
And he's in prison.
We are gonna break him out.
Hey, John.
I'm not saying you shouldn't do
your penance.
But do it as Spartan.
Church is planning something.
Something big.
You're talking about the Trust.
At least we definitely know
where Church is now.
We gotta put him down.
Go. Do not die.
- Get him to safety.
- But...
Go!
Don't kill him. He may have his uses.
We are not gonna write off Rene.
We're gonna find him.
We're gonna bring him back.
Wherever he is.
The Trust goes
to the Brace, 04 in 72.
How you feeling, my friend?
You can keep
going with the foreplay,
but I'm never giving you what you want.
You remind me of this other guy
I once tortured.
Maybe bigger,
a little more muscle on the frame.
Look, I was conversing
with this son of a bitch
just like you and I have been
conversing for the past...
What, 20 hours or so?
My knuckles hurt.
Even with the brass. I needed a shower.
My lady was waiting for me.
And this guy
would just not give me what I needed.
Not unlike you.
So I said to myself, "Tobias,
"make this guy feel pain
like nobody who's ever lived."
And then it clicked.
It's not the pain that breaks people.
It's fear.
Fear of that pain.
Of what that pain brings.
Of what happens next.
You not gonna finish your story?
Huh?
Oh.
I got what I wanted from that guy.
So you might wanna think about that
the next time I ask you a question.
Tobias Church. Where is he?
Don't know. Even if I did,
whatever you're gonna do to me,
he's worse.
How sure are you about that?
Ahh!
Hey, you're a lot cuter
than the green guy.
Aww, you're kind of cute, too, in a
"I feel sorry for you" kind of way.
- Where's Church?
- Yeah, who wants to know?
The green guy.
Where is Church?
Look out!
You Okay?
I'm better than this schmuck.
Church. Address. Now.
I heard he's somewhere northwest of here,
maybe by the water.
Half the city's on the water.
I swear, that's all I know.
Come on.
How's it going?
I would punch this monitor
if I didn't know how much it cost.
Also, it'd probably really hurt.
Can you get off your feet, please?
Oliver told me that you were back to work
a week after you were shot
by the Clock King.
Shot in the shoulder.
Not a knife in the back.
I don't need you to remind me.
I have excruciating agony to do that.
Who's that?
Hmm? Telemarketer.
Tell me you've had better luck
than I have had.
We might have narrowed it down
to the northwest part of the city.
Yeah, so now we're looking for a needle
in a slightly smaller haystack.
I'll run an algorithm cross-referencing
traffic cams with probable locations.
Wow. This place just got really crowded.
He'!-
Do people just walk into
your secret base of operations?
- Yes.
- This is...
- Spartan.
I'm guessing.
You guys must the new kids on the block.
We're more like the Backstreet Boys.
It was funny in my head.
This is Rory Regan and Evelyn Sharp.
John Diggle. And you are missing a man.
Rene Ramirez.
Lyla called in A.R.G.U.S. for the search.
Unfortunately, she's turned up nothing.
It's going around.
We are going to find Rene,
and we're not gonna give up hope
while we're doing it.
I have an early meeting at City Hall,
I will check in with everybody soon.
Is it just my imagination,
or did Oliver just seem...
Optimistic. That's not usually a word
I'd associate with his demeanor.
- Thank you.
- Rene?
- Slow.
- What about the ACU?
Too many cops on Church's dime
keeping him five steps ahead.
And with Conahan gone
and Church's assault on the ACU,
I'm thinking we gotta bring
more men into the fold.
Well, do we have enough guys
that we can trust?
Pike says that a bunch of his men
have volunteered since the attack on ACU.
So, if you want, I can vet 'em,
and I could,
you know,
make sure there's no bad apples.
Please. Let's get that done.
Look, I know
this is one of the last things
you wanna be dealing with right now,
but the re-zoning vote is in a few days.
Allowing us to expand
low-income housing in Orchid Bay?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, well, we need
a four-fifths majority vote
from City Council in order to pass
the ordinance and...
Who are the hold-outs?
Only one that really matters.
Councilman Kullens.
Yeah, he is decidedly anti-residential.
I was gonna say,
he's the most stubborn man in the city
compared to you, but that works.
Let's get into it.
Anatoly, what is this?
It is time, my friend.
English will suffice, Viktor.
Fine.
What does Bratva mean to you,
Oliver Queen?
Brotherhood.
Brotherhood is family.
Who are yours?
My father is dead.
- My mother and sister...
- Both dead.
Bratva only know their brothers.
Do you know what I mean by this?
I have no family.
I have no home. I have no name.
We're at the latest probable, Overwatch,
but it's another dead end.
Try not to use that phrase.
Look.
- Is that...
- Blood? Looks like.
Scratch that. We think this is where
Rene was being held.
- "Was"?
- Blood's still fresh.
They must've just moved him.
KH-Ten shows a panel van moving
from that location 40 minutes ago.
Can you track it?
I have been able to every other time
somebody asked me that question.
- Got it.
- Where?
This is a little awkward,
but Oliver made me promise that if we got
our location on Rene,
I would only share it with him.
That's actually not surprising at all.
Lest I forget.
So you can pay the ferry.
Why, man?
'Cause you pissed me off.
NO. Why this city?
Why come here?
And why are you asking me that now?
'Cause, if I'm gonna die tonight,
it'd be nice to know why.
From what I heard, you were popping
in Blüdhaven, in Hub City.
Why you messing with us?
For your water access.
Seriously.
Through Star City's docks
I can move thousands of tons of heroin,
Slam, Vertigo.
I'm working on the biggest
consolidation of drug enterprises
anybody has ever seen.
Only thing I'm waiting for
is for Green Arrow
to get out of the picture.
Little man,
that grave ain't gonna dig itself.
So how about you do the digging yourself?
Oh, you think I'm afraid
to get my hands dirty, huh?
Hey, you okay?
I thought Church would put up
more of a fight.
Probably realized he didn't have to.
What do you mean?
I was hurting so bad
it got so I couldn't even see straight.
I barely even remember telling him...
Telling him what?
Who you are.
He knows you're Oliver Queen.
I should've been out there
with you tonight, Oliver.
Digg, you said you needed time.
Don't be afraid to take it.
And tonight
would not have made any difference.
Church didn't want to fight.
He wanted to run.
That's because he knows killing the Mayor
is a lot easier
than killing the Green Arrow.
What? We were all thinking it.
I told Rene to stand down and recover.
Evelyn and Rory are going to watch
Thea and Quentin
in case Church tries to get at me
through them. How's Curtis doing?
He says he wants to get back at it.
Then let's get him on Lyla and J.J.
Good. I'll have Felicity's back.
Oliver, I know you have a security detail,
but you might as well have a bulls-eye
painted on your head.
I can't disappear again.
I'm still dealing with the
fallout from not being around
when the ACU was attacked.
And there is actually a re-zoning vote
that needs my attention.
What? Wait. Doesn't a vote
take a backseat to finding Church
before he tells every criminal in the city
who you are?
I have security, I'll be fine.
Have you ever... Has he ever actually
said that and it turned out to be true?
You agree with her?
Well, I know I said I thought it was
a good idea for us to start a new team,
but what do we have?
A Laurel Lance wannabe,
a weird rag-guy, a lunatic and Curtis.
Curtis just wasn't who I pictured.
They have potential.
One of them got themselves captured
and gave up your name.
- And I'd like you to debrief him.
- Debrief him?
Church told Rene
that he's planning something.
Something big enough
to involve five cities.
So Church just gave up his master plan?
He thought Rene was gonna be dead
five minutes later.
Church is trying to consolidate
the drug trade through Star City,
but he was waiting for the Green Arrow
to be gone before he made his move.
Okay. Well, if that's true,
I think I know a way we can turn
this to our advantage.
I'm all ears.
Oliver, I know a guy.
Very specific skill set.
I think he could be here in 24 hours.
Did you get my message?
Yeah. Quentin and I
can take care of ourselves.
Still doesn't hurt to have a shadow.
Is Councilman Kullens in there?
Yes. He is waiting in your office
with Susan Williams.
Thank you very much, fellas.
I didn't agree to an interview.
Yeah, well, she's shadowing him
for some type of profile.
And I already tried to get her kicked out,
but he was adamant
about having her in there.
Any advice?
Don't screw it up.
Councilman Kullens, hi.
Miss Williams,
it's a pleasure to finally meet you.
Really? Have you watched any of my pieces?
I have, and I think you're off the mark.
In certain instances.
Is that on the record?
If you wanna get an actual quote,
Miss Williams,
you can go through
all the proper channels.
This meeting is strictly
about the re-zoning ordinance.
Yes. Councilman, as you know,
I ran on a platform of unity,
but it is difficult
for a city to be united
when so much of the zoning within it
remains exclusionary.
We need to open it up.
Allow for more affordable housing,
give the people the chance
to start over and rebuild.
The second the money starts rolling in,
those families get squeezed out.
By crony capitalists.
That's not going to happen here.
Hard to believe,
considering your family's history.
I'm sorry, Councilman. I don't follow.
Well, the type of re-zoning
you're proposing
happened downtown 25 years ago.
But instead of affordable housing,
we got sky-rises.
One of them became
the offices of Queen Consolidated.
Is that true, Mr. Mayor?
I'll consider that a "no comment."
I can tell, you have good intentions.
But politics is the art of the real.
I'm sorry. I'm not changing my vote.
Okay, maybe
you should just put an arrow in him.
That was a bit more than I expected
to get done on my lunch break.
Is this a normal Wednesday
afternoon for you?
Well, I had to make up for last night.
I hate canceling last minute.
I got a feeling I'm gonna be
the one canceling on you for a change.
I got a promotion.
I signed on with the ACU.
Oliver's Anti-Crime Unit?
This isn't gonna be weird, right?
- Hmm?
- Me reporting to your ex-fiancé?
Yeah, what could possibly
be weird about that?
- Felicity?
- Mmm-hmm.
Does Mayor Queen
know that we're seeing each other?
It really doesn't help if you call him
"Mayor Queen."
Felicity...
Definitely. Yeah, he's definitely...
Definitely aware of you.
Love what you've
done with the place.
It's not much, man, but it's home.
And it's safe, especially
now that Felicity's teched up the place.
Thanks for coming out.
No problem, man.
Let's just get this over with.
But I gotta tell you.
There's nothing you could tell me
that I haven't already told myself.
I'm torn apart over this.
Is that what you think this is? A lecture?
What I deserve is a beat-down.
When's the last time
you looked in the mirror?
But maybe something good
can come out of this, man.
Like, I don't know,
maybe you saw something,
heard something
that can help us bring down Church.
I already told Oliver
everything I remember, man.
I know,
but traumatic events have a way
of doing funny things to the memory.
And if you think what you went through
was not traumatic, again I say, mirror.
My dad taught me how to take a beating.
I know, Rene. You're tough.
I get that, man.
But this isn't about being tough, okay?
It's about...
Look, man, I've been where you are, okay?
And I know it's not easy,
but if we talk about this
and go through it step by step...
Look, I said I don't know.
I should be out there trying to fix this.
Not in here with you, playing therapist.
- Oliver says stay put.
- And I'm staying put.
But I don't remember anything.
CHURCH". Yeah, yeah, sure.
Just make sure the AmerTek gear
gets to the Brace.
I want everybody locked and loaded.
No, he's not gonna be a problem.
The Green Arrow'll be dead by then.
Louis, I'm gonna need to hit you back.
You like this place?
I'm getting a penthouse built.
Gonna let me see the whole city.
I told you to stay away
from the Green Arrow.
I don't work for you.
And the Green Arrow found me.
You kidnapped his protégé.
A serendipitous encounter.
And your last.
After getting threatened by a freak,
I hired one of my own.
This was your second warning.
There won't be a third.
I thought you hired me
to kill the Green Arrow.
Nope. You're gonna kill the Mayor.
What is Susan Williams
doing in your office?
I agreed to an off-camera interview.
Okay, come here.
Okay. So, did you go out last night
as the Green Arrow and get hit
really hard, in the head?
Susan Williams is in our lives.
Thea, if we don't make her an ally,
then she's gonna remain an enemy.
Okay, but she's poison.
Well, it turns out that if you ingest
small amounts of poison over time,
you can develop an immunity.
Good morning.
When I got your call last night
I thought someone in my office
was playing a prank on me.
Well, I thought
Thea made a good point yesterday
when she suggested
that you go through the proper channels.
- Hmm.
- Please.
The interview I had in mind
was going to be on camera.
Baby steps. May I ask you a question?
I don't think you understand
how this interview thing works.
Have your attacks
on my administration been
personal or are they just good ratings?
Don't see why they can't be both.
Why are you asking?
Because I'm trying to figure out how hard
I'm gonna have to work to win you over.
You seem like a nice guy.
But you're not a real politician.
I am underqualified.
Vastly. And the city,
my home, is suffering because of it.
I appreciate
the fact that I haven't earned your trust.
Yet. But, Susan,
as someone who professes
to care about Star City,
I think that you owe
it to the people of Star City
to give me an opportunity
to earn that trust.
And I promise you
I can't do that
if I'm spending all of my energy
dodging all of these grenades
that you're lobbing at me.
So, here's my idea.
You give me one month with no attacks.
Let me show you what I can do.
And if I don't deliver,
it's open season.
One month.
- What's this?
- My personal cell.
Why would I need that?
I think you can figure it out.
To survivors of Amazo.
May we experience as much sorrow
as drops of wine
about to be left in glass. Prochnost.
Prochnost.
I get us more drinks.
Something stronger.
All right.
It's a party, Viktor.
Let me get you a drink.
You may have passed all the tests
and said all the right things,
but I do not believe for a second
you are Bratva.
Then you weren't paying attention
during the ceremony, I guess.
Look around you. These men are here
because government men like Kovar
have taken everything from them.
The Bratva is means to bring justice
for all those crimes.
Justice is why I'm here.
Yeah, some American castaway
will never understand.
So you can say all the words
that Anatoly feeds you.
But you'll never be one of us.
And you should know by now
what we do to outsiders.
Viktor, come to toast our new brother?
Yes. Of course.
Congratulations, brother.
What was that about?
That was nothing.
- What is this?
- Best not ask, just drink.
How long are you gonna be staying here,
man?
I'm a fugitive, Rene. I live here.
And until you heal up, we're roomies.
So, you feel much more like talking?
Why don't we talk about the time
you were tortured?
Sure.
It was about a year ago.
My brother, Andy, did it.
- You got tortured by your brother?
- Mmm-hmm.
He was working with Damien Darhk.
Oliver said you re-enlisted. That why?
Partly.
That also why you sidelined yourself?
That too.
- Hmm.
- So, you ex-Navy, right?
- Dishonorably discharged.
- Reason?
You know something, man,
you don't have to tell me.
We were transporting a prisoner,
one who had information we needed.
Intelligence officers
couldn't get it out of him, so...
I tried to do it my way.
You put a beating on him.
I've been thinking a lot
about that decision.
Particularly since you've been on
the other side of that beat-down, right?
Because I screwed up. Again.
That's my life, man.
And now you're asking me
to relive my latest and greatest.
That's right, Rene.
If you wanna help us.
If you wanna give us anything
that can bring down Church,
I'm afraid you're gonna have to.
Okay.
What do I do?
Councilman. Thank you for coming back.
I'm afraid
you're just wasting both of our times.
After you educated
us on Queen Consolidated,
Thea and I thought
we would do some of our own research.
Yeah, we were very curious to find out
where our family's business was located.
You would not believe
how surprised and delighted
we were to find out that
you were one of those, um...
What was...
What was the term the Councilman used?
"Crony capitalists"?
Right. That you were
one of those crony capitalists
who pushed poor people
out of those neighborhoods.
Hiding behind a shell company, of course.
The same company who owns controlling
interest in a real estate developer.
Who just filed for permits to redevelop
Orchid Bay for commercial uses.
Your opposition to this re-zoning,
it's not political, it's personal.
I get it.
You're trying to protect an investment.
Susan Williams
isn't shadowing you at the moment.
But, to me,
this feels like a story she would like.
So, should I call her?
She actually gave me her number
this morning.
Are you blackmailing me, Mr. Mayor?
Well, Councilman, it's like you said.
"Politics is the art of the real."
Well, that was fun.
You made Kullens squirm.
The guy's a career politician. Just need
to know where to apply the pressure.
How are you so sure
about all this?
I'm the mayor of Star City, Thea.
This is what I do.
Thea, get in the car!
Get in the car, get in the car!
It's my sad duty to inform you
that at 1:23 a.m.,
Mayor Oliver Queen
was pronounced dead at Starling General.
In his too-short life,
Oliver Queen experienced great hardship.
But he came through the other side
with a passion for service,
committed to making Star City
a safer place for us all to call home.
Well, he really didn't say anything
that nice about you when you were alive.
Probably didn't deserve it.
Sorry about the suit.
We haven't been properly introduced.
Heads up.
God!
Christopher Chance.
John referred to you as the
"Human Target."
Well, that works better as a job
description than it does as a nickname.
This is so weird.
You have failed this city.
How's Thea?
She's a little shaken. You know,
I didn't get a chance to tell her
what was gonna go down until right before.
She is gonna be so pissed at you.
And, like, the whole city.
They're gonna find out though, right?
I mean, you can't stay dead forever.
No. Just until Church makes his big move.
That's what you're
betting on now,
that the Green Arrow/Oliver Queen is dead.
That's the hope. Now we just need
to figure out what he has planned.
I do not understand you, Oliver.
You become brother,
but you still act like you carry
weight of world on shoulders alone.
That is what your brothers are for.
I'm just thinking about why I came here.
Because this best bar in town.
Actually, only bar.
No. No, I mean why I came here.
After Lian Yu.
Yes. Yes, you already told me.
Something about old promise.
I thought I told you,
time to move forward.
She has a family. I haven't...
I haven't spoken to them.
Oh, this is about woman?
Now I understand.
There is old saying in Russian.
Okay, maybe not Russian,
but it still works.
"No problem beautiful woman cannot fix."
Now go talk to her before I do.
Oliver! Where are you going?
Party just start.
Figure I'd get some air.
You sure? I think I heard
Anatoly was looking for you.
I'm sure. I'll be fine.
So, thanks for doing this.
Being killed is basically my job.
But, uh, not just for taking the bullets.
I heard that you got Kullens to cave.
Yeah. And scored you
a very pretty girl's phone number.
I heard that too.
Yeah, but the truth is, you did that.
I was under the impression
that I've been down here all day.
I don't just put on faces, Oliver.
I become my target.
And to do that, I've got to learn
everything there is to know about them.
More than they know about themselves.
- I've got to become them.
- My apologies.
What for? Man, you've got a great life.
You're the mayor.
But you'd still rather
be The Hood than Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen has...
Has never really been my better half.
See, nobody moves forward in life
when they're hiding behind a mask.
Trust me.
You know,
it's why you're struggling as mayor.
And it's probably
why you won't call that girl.
That's not the reason.
Listen, I'm the last person
to give dating advice,
but Felicity moved on. You should too.
You didn't know? Sorry.
Uh, earlier today, I met with a detective
who just joined the ACU.
Uh, Billy Malone. He casually mentioned
that he was seeing Felicity.
Seemed to think that you knew.
Hmm.
You're safe, Rene.
Nothing can hurt you.
Is this gonna be one of those hippy-dippy
meditation things?
Eyes closed. Breathe.
Don't try to remember.
Just go there. Get a picture.
I was starving. My wrists hurt
like hell from the zip ties.
What else? Sounds? Smells?
Couldn't smell anything. Nose was busted.
What about people? Who else was there?
Muscle. Los Halcones. Triad...
It's not the pain
that breaks people. It's fear.
- But there was something else.
- What?
The Trust goes to the Brace, 04 in 72.
I know what's happening.
- Hey!
- Hi.
Um, thanks for letting me swing by.
I know it's late.
You do remember that this apartment
has a front door, right?
Uh, front doors are more for people
who haven't just faked their own death.
Good point. So, what's up?
Your message sounded cryptic.
Sorry. I wasn't sure
if I should say anything at all, actually.
That couldn't wait till tomorrow?
Why didn't you tell me
that you were seeing someone?
Well, maybe on some
crazy sub-conscious level
I was worried you'd show up on my balcony
in the middle of the night.
Sorry.
Snark probably isn't appropriate here.
I'm totally fine
that you're seeing someone.
But I'm hurt that you didn't tell me.
I'm sorry. I meant to, and then
every time I went to go bring it up,
I just sort of...
Like... I just chickened out.
Why? Were you...
Were you
keeping the door open for us, or...
No! Course not.
No, it's just,
you and I work together and I just...
I didn't wanna make it a thing, you know,
until it was something real.
Is it real?
I don't know.
It's John and Rene. They have something.
"The Trust goes to the Brace, 04 in 72."
Could that be any more obscure?
"04 in 72," could be the time and date.
4:00 a.m., 72 hours after he held Rene.
Yeah. That's soon.
And "the Brace"
is what the guys in my hood
used to call a private airstrip
outside Pennytown.
Halpin-Brace Airfield?
That's the one. And this "Trust"?
I think it's the heads of the
crime families that Church controls.
That's a bigger leap than
Curtis took at the Beijing Olympics.
When he had me dig my own grave
he talked about bringing this
"Trust" together.
That's his big play, man.
- 04:00 a.m.'s in 20 minutes.
- Mmm-hmm.
Wake up the team. We don't have much time.
You're all geared up.
Oliver didn't bust me out of prison
for me to warm the bench, right?
So, what's up? You ready to move out?
Decided not to go.
Last thing any of you need right now
is me screwing things up again.
When it comes to guilt and recrimination,
the line forms behind me.
I didn't think I was ready to face
what I had done.
But I'm wearing this suit again because
I think it's a path to redemption.
And it could be for you, too.
Good flight?
Everyone's very interested in hearing
what you've got planned, Tobias.
It's called the largest drug enterprise
on the Western Coast.
Shipments 24/7.
In a city where cops are afraid
or on our payroll.
And as an added bonus,
the Mayor's an alkie.
Sentry reports movement on the perimeter.
I thought you'd taken out the Green Arrow.
Nah, it's not him. It's the JV squad.
Chill out, damn it! Deal with them.
Spartan is such a badass.
The baddest.
You were right.
Fear of pain is what's worst.
You afraid yet, bitch?
Never.
I lost Church.
Got him. Moving southwest.
I've got these two. Go back up Mr. Church.
You guys all right?
Good to see you again, brother.
Yeah, you too. Nice helmet.
Target is secure. You guys all right?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
You survived. I guess
I'll just have to kill you again, Oliver.
You mind if I call you Oliver?
Yes, I do.
Get up.
You're done, Church.
You got much worse coming,
and you don't even know it.
He calls himself Prometheus,
and he's gonna end you.
First of all, I would like to apologize
for perpetrating
a deception on this scale.
The ACU had intel that we may
be able to catch Mr. Church,
but only if his plan moved forward.
Which would only happen if he believed
the Mayor of Star City was dead.
In my mind, this was a worthwhile gamble.
And it paid off. Mr. Church
and his underlings were apprehended
as well as the heads
of organized crime enterprises
in Blüdhaven, Hub City,
Keystone and White Holland.
One more piece of good news.
I've just received word
that the City Council passed an ordinance
re-zoning for low-income housing.
And with Church in custody,
I take it that your identity is safe?
Well, I hope so. Thanks for the assist.
And the personal insight.
Just part of the service.
Ah, speak of the devil.
Oh, am I the devil now?
That would definitely be my cue to leave.
Take care.
Sorry to drop by unannounced.
It's not like you need an invitation.
Yeah, no, I know. I just...
Just between us,
things have been a bit complicated.
Wait, complicated is probably not
the right word.
It's not the wrong word.
I want you to be happy.
And in the spirit of that,
I think that you owe it to yourself
to find out if what you have
with Billy is real.
And I owe it to myself
to embrace whatever's next
for me when I'm not...
- Yes.
- The...
Yeah.
It's funny,
that's what I came here to say to you.
We're usually on the same page.
About a lot of things.
All right. Uh, mmm, yes,
I will see you later.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- You don't need to thank me.
Yeah.
I care about you.
And I will always care about you.
It's a mortal lock.
Viktor wanted to give you a proper gift.
Guessing that's not you.
That's a nice knife.
Maybe I keep it after I kill you.
This doesn't concern you.
Actually it does.
Have a nice night?
You can tell your boss I expect
the other half of my fee within the hour.
Oliver, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Anatoly, what the hell is going on?
Viktor clearly sent those two to kill me.
Then some other guy shows up
and kills them. And...
Yes, yes. My way
of handling Viktor problem.
I know he wanted you dead.
You didn't think
it would be a good idea to tell me that?
We cannot kill Viktor. He's too connected.
I hire special man.
- Come on.
- Anatoly, what did I get myself into?
Yeah, a most interesting question,
my friend.
I thought we agreed
the last time was the last time, Susan.
I know. But then I remembered
my money was still good,
and you still like
gambling a bit too much.
What do you have for me, Ian?
The guy who took the bullets for
Mayor Queen was Christopher Chance.
It felt like his work.
I think I figured out
how Queen knows him.
Really?
I went through the database
looking for details on Chance's past ops.
Came across this little beauty.
You recognize your boy?
That was taken five years ago.
When Oliver Queen was supposedly
stranded on a deserted island.
Heading northbound.
Those cops riding protection
aren't on your payroll, buddy.
Nobody's breaking you out.
It's not what I'm worried about.
You guys should've flown me
to Iron Heights.
Yeah, I heard you liked helicopters.
What's got you spooked?
All right.
Don't go out there.
Why? So I can protect your ass in here?
So you don't get killed.
I knew we'd be having this conversation.
Just hear me out.
You want the Green Arrow.
I can give him to you.
I can give you his name.
You would be the only person who knows.
It's Oliver Queen.
So, we cool?
Yeah, we are.