Oliver: My name
is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I'm Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am...something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
I killed Sara.
Malcolm gave me something
that made me
susceptible to suggestion.
What happened wasn't
your fault, Thea,
because it wasn't
your decision.
Malcolm? He's going
to face justice.
He's gone. Malcolm Merlyn
will never be seen again.
Welcome to Nanda Parbat.
When I told you
that Malcolm killed Sara,
he wanted her dead,
but I am the one
who fired those arrows
into her chest.
I promised you your vengeance.
So take it.
Kill me.
But spare
John Diggle's life.
Let him go.
I will beg for it.
You've shown
tremendous strength,
fortitude,
and power.
No, Mr. Queen...
I don't want to kill you.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
Ra's is a title greater
than any one man.
Wing ta Lao wo chey.
Am I supposed to understand
what that means?
No. It is from a dialect
no longer spoken.
Said to me by a man
whose place I took.
Contemplating the same offer.
And what it means is,
a tale to be told...
begins thus.
Ayy!
[All grunting]
[Ra's speaking Arabic]
Don't let your footing
betray you.
Let your power come not from
the strength of your attack
but from the ground
that holds your feet.
All men seek guidance,
a purpose.
The means to live
without pain.
Those who journey here have given
such an exchange
for their fealty.
You mean they have
to kill for you?
No, Mr. Queen,
they have to die for me.
Is all of this supposed
to impress me?
No.
It's to inform you.
Surely men have
branded you a murderer,
a torturer.
But see, I would never
shame you with such bluntness.
Because I see it
in your eyes.
The struggle you have
with your dual identity.
Oliver Queen and the Arrow.
Neither are giving you
what you crave.
But becoming
Ra's al Ghul will?
Oliver Queen is a man
destined to be alone.
He loves a woman
he knows he cannot have.
You don't know me.
But I know the Arrow.
"Al Sahhim."
You will never be
anything more than a vigilante
for those whose lives you save
at the risk of your own.
And the city will turn on you,
and your closest allies
within the police department
will call you a criminal.
You will be scorned
and hunted,
and then killed.
Dying as you began
your crusade...
Alone.
♪ Arrow 3x16 ♪
The Offer
Original Air Date on March 18, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Your brother attempted to have me
believe that he killed Sara.
Your confession
is even less convincing.
I don't have
any reason to lie!
Except to protect your father.
Why would I
protect Malcolm
when I turned him
over to you?
He gave me a drug
called Votura.
I put three arrows
into her chest,
and I had no idea
what I was doing.
He used me.
Someone she trusted.
So I don't deserve
to be living
any more than
Malcolm does!
There would be no justice
in killing you.
I killed Sara!
Kill me.
Do it.
The blood debt ends
with Malcolm's death.
Which, I can assure you,
my father has taken care of already.
Laurel: Thea!
Roy: Get away from her!
Nyssa, no!
[Breathing heavily]
Are you ok?
How the hell...
Did she get out?
It's League training,
probably.
What were you doing down
here in the first place?
I just wanted
to pay my respects.
It was Herodotus
who first wrote of these waters.
And Ponce de Leon traveled
the earth in search of them.
And their discovery by Al-Khidr
is chronicled in the Qu'ran.
And they have permitted me
to live way beyond my time.
You don't seem too fazed
by what I've told you.
I've seen things that
have helped me to believe
that this world is a much bigger place
than people realize.
As I told you
on the mountain, boy,
man can only evade
death for so long.
The waters' powers
are losing
their effect on me.
My time is almost over,
but my legacy won't be
just ash and bone,
it will be history.
And you think that I'll help you
secure that legacy?
You survived my sword.
Your resurrection wasn't a gift
from these waters,
rather by force
of your own will.
And what better heir
to immortality
than someone who has already claimed
victory over death?
I didn't defy death
just to become an instrument of it.
We are justice.
Isn't that what
you've dedicated your life to?
Then why confine your crusade
to a single city...
When I can give you
a whole world to save.
By executing anyone who
stands in my way?
You would command resources
that you cannot even fathom.
Numbers greater than any army.
And more loyal.
Now, if you wish for them
to renounce killing as you did,
thy will be done.
[Scoffs]
I doubt that.
It's called
the League of Assassins
for a reason.
The League's reason
would be your own.
You would be Ra's al Ghul.
And what if I say no?
Then you are free
to leave.
With your compatriots,
as a gesture of good will.
All debts forgiven,
and all blood oaths waived.
Let's go home.
[Door opens]
Really need to stop having these
"thank god you're not dead" reunions.
I agree.
[Laughs]
- I'm working on it.
- You look ok.
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
Not even a scratch.
How is that
possible?
How did you get him back?
Doesn't matter.
What matters is,
you didn't kill him.
No, I wanted Ra's
to kill him.
And I still do.
Thea...
He's not staying here.
You and I both know
there's nowhere else I can take him.
If you think I feel bad for him,
you're wrong.
I'm not asking you
to feel bad for him;
to forgive him.
Just let him heal.
I have to go.
[Door opens]
John: How did Thea react
to her new house guest?
Fine.
That bad, huh?
Did she ask how we
made it back from Nanda Parbat alive?
Well, I didn't
get into it with her.
Well, how about me,
Oliver?
Like I said,
Ra's had a change of heart.
Ra's Al Ghul
doesn't have a heart.
Two months ago, he kicked you off
the side of a mountain
and put a sword through you.
Now he's giving you Malcolm Merlyn back
all gift wrapped?
Diggle, we're back.
We're alive.
Let's just be
grateful for that.
What's the Chinese
word for ok?
Or, how do you say
ok in Mandarin?
"Hao ba."
Ok, everything
is going to be "hao ba."
I want to go home!
Yeah, I--I know,
buddy,
but home's not
really safe right now.
Because those men
tried to hurt us?
Yeah. Because
of those men.
In fact, Akio,
we shouldn't
even really
be out in open.
[Akio yells]
Akio!
Akio: Oliver?
Hey, look, you cannot
disappear like that!
I thought I saw
my father,
but it wasn't him.
Look, I--I--I get it,
I get it, and I'm sorry.
We--we can't get separated.
- The botanical gardens!
- The what?
Mother and father always
told me to go there
if we ever got
separated.
Ok...
Come on!
Well, thank God.
You know, just because
I'm furious with you,
that doesn't mean
I want you dead.
What about Malcolm?
I mean, I know Laurel
wants him dead, I mean, is he?
Nope.
We got him back.
Well, I suppose
congrats,
and why, oh, why,
did you do that, are in order.
Laurel: Oliver.
[Beep]
Oliver, what are you doing?!
You're free to go.
My father would never trade
my life for yours.
And he certainly wouldn't do it for
Malcolm Merlyn's.
He didn't.
If no bargain
was struck,
then how are you
still alive?
Go home, Nyssa.
Ok. Well,
I don't understand
anything anymore.
Why did Ra's Al Ghul--
it doesn't matter.
Let's focus on what does.
Somewhere, there is someone
that needs a reminder
that we are still
watching over this city.
Well, there is
a robbery in progress
at the Kingston
Property depot on Third.
New shipment just arrived.
I'm assuming whatever it is,
it's worth a lot of money.
Ok. Suit up.
Oliver...
Suit up.
I just want to get
this shipment done.
Excuse me. We're looking
for the Catoca shipment.
Maybe you could help?
The Catoca shipment.
Where is it?
I don't know!
Sorry.
Boss says
check the crates
for a Catoca manifest.
Drop it!
Roy: Look out!
You still need
training.
When are you going
to stop telling me that?
When you no longer
need training.
Arsenal.
The head guy got away...
With these.
[Exhales]
Ran into a new player tonight who
dropped some bodies.
I need a name.
One of these four
will give him up.
Yeah.
Well, when he does, you can
read about it in the papers.
Detective?
It's captain now!
When were you going
to tell me, huh?
Or were you going to tell me?
You really going
to stand there
still pretending like you didn't know
my daughter was dead?
Uh, Captain Lance...
My whole career,
my whole life,
even when I knew nothing,
I at least knew
right from wrong.
And I knew
vigilantism was wrong.
The day we take the law
into our own hands is a day that we--
we become outlaws.
And that idea--that idea
was precious to me.
Almost as precious
as my own daughters.
I threw that all away
the day I threw in with you.
You know why?
'Cause I trusted you.
But I see the man
under the hood now.
He lies,
and he keeps secrets.
All so he doesn't
have to carry around
the weight of his decisions.
And I'm done with him.
[Door opens, closes]
What would you say
if I told you
I just connected the virtual TCP to
the open source sensor?
I would say you only
think you did,
because I've been trying to figure
that out for over two weeks.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
I have been trying
for at least two full minutes.
Ah! Let me see.
Oh, you don't
believe me.
Well, no, I'll just, uh,
make sure you did it right.
Oh, and if
I'm right?
Then I will take you
to the best steak dinner
you've ever had.
Hmm.
Which, I'd probably do anyway.
Well, I hope it's better than
that fusion place you took me to,
where I needed this microscope
to find the food.
[Ray chuckles]
[Knock on door]
Oliver, hey.
What are you doing here?
I mean, it's nice
to see you here.
Nice to see you again,
Mr. Palmer.
Likewise.
And please,
call me Ray.
Ok. Ray.
May I speak with Felicity
for a few minutes, please?
- Uh, absolutely.
- Thank you.
Should have called.
No. I'm sorry,
I should have told you earlier
when you got
back.
You don't owe me anything.
That's not true.
You're one of my
closest friends.
[Inhales, exhales]
We went up against
a new crew last night.
One of them had his
lips sewn shut.
Is that
a real thing?
Apparently.
Ugh. If only I had known
I have that option.
[Sighs] Ok.
Michael Amar?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Street name's "Murmur"
because of the whole lip stitch thing.
Practitioners say it focuses
the mind like meditation.
You ok?
I handed some of Amar's men
over to Lance.
He knows the Arrow
knew about Sara, didn't tell him.
What did Lance say?
Some variation
on "Go to hell."
Oliver, he just
needs time.
No, he's right.
I lied to him. For months.
Kept something from him,
and he had every right to know.
Are you ok?
I mean, besides Lance
and the whole
me and Ray thing?
I mean, it just seems like there's
something else going on
underneath all that.
I'm fine.
Thanks for help
with Amar's name.
[Knock on door]
Oliver's not here.
Actually, I came by to
see how you were doing.
He told you that
Malcolm was here?
Go ahead.
I'm the last person
to stop you from killing him.
My last attempt to do so
didn't exactly work out.
That's kind of why
I'm here.
I'm worried
about you.
Everyone's so interested
in saving my soul these days.
Look, no one wants
to see Merlyn dead
more than me.
But Oliver was right.
You wanted your own
father killed.
Yeah, and how
messed up is that?
You know, I wish that I never learned
Malcolm was my father.
Everything since then
has just...
[Sighs]
You know,
you're lucky, Laurel.
You have a normal father.
Someone who really loves you.
Yeah, I can't say we're on
the best of terms.
[Malcolm groaning]
You should
probably go.
[Door closes]
How much of that
did you hear?
Enough to know
that I am the last person
you wish to see alive.
I'm not going
to apologize for what I did.
And I'd do it again.
I know.
You asked me
to teach you to be strong.
To make sure
you can't be hurt again.
You learned
your lessons well.
I have learned
nothing from you.
Do you realize
that I'm so messed up,
I was willing
to die last night?
For what you made me do?
You know, I didn't
actually think it was possible
for me to hurt any worse
than I did when I came to you.
You proved to me
I was wrong.
So what was it again
that you taught me?
Show me the knife.
How did you know?
You are my daughter.
Do it like I taught
you--one strike to the neck,
it'll be over
quickly.
[Scoffs]
You're sick.
I love you, and I
want to do what is best for you.
If that were even close
to being true,
you would have stayed
out of my life.
Father.
Oh.
Your safe return
pleases me, my child.
Then extend me the courtesy
of explaining why
Malcolm Merlyn is still alive.
If you're not going
to watch your tongue,
then at least
mind your tone.
Why did you release
Al-Sahfer's murderer?
As a gift
to Oliver Queen.
An advance for him
becoming my heir.
You've selected an outsider
over your own daughter?
He survived my sword.
[Scoffs]
Sara...
You're punishing
my love for her.
At least do me
the courtesy of admitting it.
- You never approved.
- I never approved
of you allowing
weakness into your life.
And even in death,
your devotion to her
pollutes
your judgment.
[Sword clangs]
[Speaking Arabic]
Target's name
is Michael Amar.
Yeah, got him here.
Got out of Iron Heights
two months ago.
Did he escape?
No, released. Turns out
he was serving a sentence
based on a coerced confession.
Cops beat it out of him.
He confessed to a crime
he didn't commit?
I might sew
my mouth shut, too.
He's not innocent anymore.
What was he after tonight?
His crew made off with a couple
of crates, all containing these--
industrial grade diamonds.
But word on the street
is this shipment was loaded
with high end jewels they didn't take.
Why would he steal
worthless diamonds?
That's the million
dollar question.
Actually, street value's
only worth a couple thousand.
We could use
Felicity on this, Oliver.
She's
pre-occupied.
I know a couple of fences
from my less socially responsible days.
I could talk to them,
see if I can find out
where Amar is trying
to move these diamonds.
That's a good idea.
[Sighs]
You want to tell me
what's going on now?
[Chuckles]
Ra's predicted this.
He said that the city
would turn against me
and I would die alone.
And we come back,
and the first thing that happens
is Lance is shutting me out,
and...
I see Felicity with Palmer.
It's like he looked
into my future.
Sounds to me like
Ra's is playing with your head.
Question is, why are
you letting him?
He wants me to take his place
in the League of Assassins.
That's why he let us go.
As a sign of good faith.
Is there even a world
where he can imagine you saying yes?
He said that I can do more
as the new Ra's
than I could ever do
as Oliver Queen or the Arrow.
That I would have
unlimited resources.
That I could make
a difference, not just a dent.
You're not really
considering this.
Just because
Captain Lance is angry
and Felicity
is momentarily unavailable.
It's more than that.
I just...
John, tell me honestly...
What have we accomplished?
[Sighs]
Oliver...
All the people that
we put away, John, they got out.
The city is no better off.
The Arrow is not...
Is not making a difference.
And if I just
can't be me...
And the Arrow
isn't enough...
Oliver...
Then maybe I should
be Ra's al Ghul.
[Door opens]
Is Malcolm still alive?
In my head, I've already slit his
throat seven times.
Broke his neck twice.
Sorry that I had
to bring him here.
Been trying to remember
who I was before mom died.
Before Malcolm...
And I don't recognize her.
I couldn't even fathom
killing someone, and...
in the last month,
I've held a gun
to Slade Wilson's head
and nearly took
my father's life twice.
But you didn't kill
either of them.
You know why I didn't
kill Malcolm?
Mom.
I thought what
she'd think about
her daughter becoming
a murderer just like him.
Thea...
You're nothing like him.
There's something
broken inside of me
just like there's something broken
inside of him.
Nothing can change that.
Where are you going?
To go buy
my evil dad some soup.
[Groans]
[Door opens]
One big,
happy family.
What did you do to her?!
I encouraged her
to kill me.
My version of being
a supportive father.
- Yeah, you really are insane.
- Perhaps.
But I'm not the only one.
Or do you doubt
that Ra's would release us both
without conditions?
No conditions.
An offer.
To take his place.
You don't seem surprised.
I don't put much
stock in augury.
But there is a prophecy.
The man that doesn't
perish at the blade of Ra's Al Ghul
will become
Ra's al Ghul.
[Cell phone beeps and vibrates]
Ra's al Ghul doesn't
offer, he orders.
Oliver!
Don't delude yourself
into thinking you have a choice.
Hey, what are
those bamboo things called?
Hey, Akio, come on,
all right, it's ok.
"Hao ba."
You need to remember
that you're strong, right?
Just like my sister.
- You have a sister?
- I do!
And I miss her just
as much as you miss your parents.
Why aren't you with her?
Well, I told her that I had to hang out
with my good buddy Akio.
Really?
Yeah. We used to go
to botanical gardens
just like these
in Starling City,
except she didn't
know the...
plants as well
as you do.
Oliver?
What's wrong?
Run!
Hey.
Where's Diggle?
He's out with Roy.
They're on their way back.
Thanks for coming.
Where else would I be?
It's not rhetorical.
Ray and I may be a something,
but that doesn't change
my commitment to what we're doing here.
Good.
What about your commitment?
[Chuckles]
John might have
told me about your employment
offer from Evil Incorporated.
He also might have told me
that you may be considering it,
which is, by the way, insane.
There's a League
of Assassins.
That is not the name
of a nice group.
I've been an assassin.
There is more than
one path to justice.
There are a lot of different
ways I can answer that.
All varying on the theme
of you're crazy,
but I'm going to go with,
what makes you think that you're
not already on the right path?
Ok. Ok.
'Cause it's been
over two years.
You tell me.
What have I really
accomplished?
My mother's dead.
Tommy, Sara.
Crime's not down,
and my sister
is in ten different
kinds of pain right now.
So you leave.
Then what?
All the people
you've lost,
all the sacrifices
you've made,
it would have been
for nothing.
I don't know why
I'm doing this anymore.
I can't answer
that for you.
Yes, Captain Lance
is shutting you out,
but I don't believe
you're the Arrow
so that people can
say "thank you."
And, yes, you and I
are not together,
but that was
your choice.
When we thought
you were dead,
each one of us
had to figure out
why we were
doing all this.
Seems like
it's your turn.
Roy: Are we
interrupting something?
What do you have?
Just talked to a friend
of mine who used to run
a munitions depot back
when I was in Afghanistan.
I think I know why our guy
is so interested
in low grade diamonds.
The type of diamonds
Amar and his crew are interested in
is used to make
diamond-tipped bullets.
They can go through body
armor like tissue paper.
Ok. So who wears
body armor?
The police.
The guys who beat that false
confession out him,
who put him
in prison.
He's going
to get payback.
Ok. Roy, suit up.
Dig, I need you to secure
the perimeter of the station.
Felicity--
Call Captain Lance,
I'm already on it.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Hi.
Peace offering.
I already ate.
Right.
You know, it's funny...
A friend of mine is having trouble
with her father.
The son of a bitch
is barely human, but you...
You know, history
has taught me
that you'll give me
the cold shoulder for a while,
and then you'll move on
to blowing up at me,
and then finally,
you'll let it all out
at a dinner that I've dragged
you to after days of pleading,
but my point is,
is just let me have it!
I deserve
every minute of it.
And I am ready
to take it, but...
don't you think
for one second
that I am giving up on us.
[Sighs]
When you were
a little girl,
you used to wait up for
me when I was on nights.
You couldn't fall asleep until I
walked through that front door.
- I remember.
- Yeah.
You were always the protector
of this family, of everyone.
Laurel Lance...
Always trying
to save the world.
You can't save this.
Dad...
You don't know
how hard I've tried
to forgive you for lying to me
the way you did?
I'm not proud of it.
You're my daughter,
I'll always love you,
but I don't know if I'll ever be able
to forgive you.
[Gunfire]
[All yelling]
Kill them all!
Police band is filled with reports
of gunfire at the precinct.
Oliver: Any luck
getting to Lance?
Still trying.
I'll lay down cover fire,
you haul ass for the exit.
I'm not leaving you!
Just because you think
you're some kind
of hero now doesn't mean
I'm not going
to protect my daughter.
Now on my move, you run!
Go, go, go!
My father's
back there!
Officer: Hey!
[Both grunting
and groaning]
What, are you waiting around
for a thank you?
That's not why I do this.
[Whistles]
Nice work.
Not without
a few casualties,
but Amar is in custody.
So that's a no on the whole victory
dance thing, then?
You know me.
I don't dance.
But I do occasionally
say...thank you.
You're welcome.
And you were right.
Ah, a "thank you"
and a "you were right."
I should really
be recording this.
I started all of this
because of my father,
to...right his wrongs.
It became
something more.
But I never stopped
to think about it
or about why...
until you asked me to.
And what was
the answer?
Tonight at the precinct,
the only thing
that I could think about was...
those police officers,
and how their families
were counting on me,
and Roy, and Diggle,
to get them home safe.
That's why I'm doing this.
So...
that means a pass
on becoming the most handsome
Demon's Head ever?
It means I'm not ready
to give up on what we're doing here.
You know, you're
always saying
how you just want me
to be happy...
You know,
the thing is,
as long as you're
in my life, I am.
[Cell phone rings]
[Ring]
It's Ray.
I should probably
take this.
Who are those men?!
I-I don't know.
Then why are we
running away from them?
Shado?
Nyssa:
Are you all right?
What are you doing here?
Looking for you,
actually.
I missed your sister.
I suppose I wanted
something to remind me of her.
Now's really not the best time.
Are you...
having problems with your father?
I have some
experience in that area.
Do you want
to talk about it?
With you?
You know what?
I could use a reminder
of Sara, too.
Dinner's on me.
During the fighting,
your technique
was competent?
Why do I feel like that's your idea
of a compliment?
Could certainly
be improved.
Is that an offer to teach me?
I have nowhere
else to go.
It is not customary
for one to wait so long
before accepting
a great honor.
I'm not
accepting it.
Wing ta Lao wo chey.
"The tale
to be told begins thus."
Maseo, this story,
it's over before it begins.
You misunderstand.
It does not mean the tale
is yet to unfold.
It means Ra's
has already written it.
The choice has been made.
No.
I will always be grateful
for what you've done for my family.
For what you meant to Akio.
But if you insist on pursuing this
path of resistance...
There will be consequences.
Is that
a threat?
It is the will
of Ra's al Ghul.
[Knock on door]
Yeah, who is it?
Hello?
Thea. Are you ok?
What's going on?
I--I don't know what
I'm doing anymore.
I don't know
who I am.
Can I just stay
here with you?
Yeah.
Cops believe they've won.
But still got what,
how many rounds of those
armor-piercing
diamond bullets?
[Laughter]
You tell everyone
who will listen
what you've seen.
Go.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man