My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Hi, Ollie.
SCPD!
His name is Vincent Sobel.
He's my old partner.
We have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
The police are coming. You should go.
Will you marry me?
Yeah.
You're the very best part of me.
I'm a better human being
just because I've loved you.
No matter what life throws at us,
our love can conquer it.
Oliver Jonas Queen,
Felicity Megan Smoak,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Please, kiss your bride.
There he is. Hey, buddy.
Aunt Thea said
I could have some champagne.
I said a sip,
and only during the toast.
Mom and Dad used to let us do that.
That's just fine.
Yeah, and we turned out all right.
I think that they would be
pretty impressed with this party,
and the groom.
- Think so?
- Yeah. Of course.
Why, is everything okay?
Felicity was supposed to be here
by now, so...
What's there
to be nervous about, Ollie?
You guys are already married,
and it's not like you invited
anyone but John to the ceremony.
Well, uh,
you were still in the hospital,
and it was
just a little last minute, okay?
- Yeah, I know. I know.
- Hey, you.
Hey.
Lyla apologizes
for not being able to make it.
A.R.G.U.S. missions
do not stop for weddings.
Well, she was hoping that
it would for this.
Congrats, man.
- So where is the bride?
- I don't know.
Donna said that
she had a plan, but...
Mom insisted
that we make an entrance
since we didn't have
a traditional wedding,
which I'm sure
I'll never stop hearing about
for the rest of my life.
- Welcome to the family...
- Oh.
Son.
- I can call you that now, right?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- Great.
I want you to know
that I have forgiven both of you
for running off
and eloping.
And for waiting to
propose to my daughter
until you were under indictment.
Oh, actually, Felicity proposed to me.
Come on, Donna,
let's let them have their day.
They did have their day,
and we weren't part of it, remember?
I guess she's keeping
the tradition of the Smoak women
not having traditional weddings.
What are you talking about?
We had a wedding.
No. Getting married by
a Tom Jones-impersonating rabbi
isn't exactly traditional.
- You love Tom Jones.
- No, I don't. You love Tom Jones.
You know what?
At least we had a Jewish wedding.
Seriously, you guys, would it
have killed you to get a rabbi?
Or a chuppa?
I'm gonna steal Felicity
for a moment.
- Oh, yes, of course.
- I'll bring her back.
Those whack jobs
are already your in-laws.
So, if you're having second thoughts,
it's too late for you.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
You really do love me.
I always knew you guys
would end up together.
- Didn't I say that, honey?
- She did.
Even when I saw on the news
that your engagement was off,
I kept telling this one, "Adam,
"Felicity and Oliver
are meant to be together,
"they're going to work it out."
Didn't I say that, honey?
- You did.
- I did.
Well, we're so glad
you guys could make it.
It's great to see you again.
Well, I'd tell you guys
to move back to Ivy Town,
but I guess being mayor of Star City
would make that kinda tough, right?
We love Ivy town, but...
Star City is our home.
Best part about weddings,
free booze. Salud.
Mmm!
Paul and I had, um,
specialty cocktails
made at our wedding.
Hopetini and Peach Paul Sangria.
We also wore matching white tuxes.
Can I have
a glass of champagne, please?
You okay?
Me? Oh, yeah, of course.
Just because I'm divorced
doesn't mean that I can't
handle celebrating
people getting married.
Well, I'm not
that into weddings, either.
Shocker.
Well, the idea of
spending the rest of your life
with one person seems
pretty unrealistic, and, uh,
also pretty boring.
It's probably why I've had
so many busted engagements.
- Say what?
- What?
I'll be right back.
But you're just gonna leave
on that bombshell,
- that's what you're gonna do?
- Mmm.
Is it me or has she been
acting weird lately?
Oh, no, she's definitely
been on upswipes.
She's been secretly
texting with somebody for weeks now.
Good for her.
You know, maybe you should
start dating, too.
Oh... Yeah.
- I date plenty.
- Oh, really, who?
Mmm-hmm. "Who?" Oh, man, you know,
- so many guys.
- Wow.
There's one guy in particular
who I'm dating... Uh...
His name is Dom Pérignon.
He is smooth, and expensive,
and he's really nice.
Uh, but there's like other guys, too.
I'm not trying to be
tied down right now.
You know, I'm trying to live
my best single life.
Yeah. Who, like Tom Collins, Rob Roy?
I'm not actually a gin guy.
Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.
Come on, Quentin,
it's "Oliver" tonight.
Matter of fact, it's always "Oliver."
Well, I got a little something
for you, Oliver.
Yeah, I know,
it doesn't look like much.
But, uh, my dad gave that to me
on my wedding day.
Quentin, I can't accept this.
It's not like I got anybody
I can give it to, is it?
And besides, it's not right
you don't have a parent here tonight.
Thank you.
This means a lot.
Right here, right here,
right here. Here we go.
- I got it, I got it, I got it!
- Yes!
Love...
What is love, really?
It is not tangible.
So, who's to say
it's not just made up?
I mean, there's no hardcore proof
that it actually exists.
I mean, look,
I love a lot of things.
Sweaters, math, coffee,
but, you know,
I'm not gonna marry that stuff.
What is marriage anyway?
Like, what is it? Like, is it...
As a paper, it says,
"Oh! I won't leave you ever."
No, I could leave, like that.
So, what is marriage, really,
what it boils down to, I...
And everybody give Curtis
a round of applause.
Thank you, Curtis. Thank you.
Um, I think what my friend
is trying to say is,
true love is...
So special
that we all dream about it.
And when I look at
Oliver and Felicity,
I'm reminded of
how I felt about my wife
on our wedding day.
We were so in love.
And we would do
anything for each other,
I mean, no matter what.
And that is the epitome of
Oliver and Felicity.
Yeah, I mean, you guys
have had your struggles,
but you always work through it.
These are
two of the most genuine people
in the world,
and they deserve
all the happiness,
and I'm so fortunate
to call them my friends.
So, please raise a glass
to true love.
Oliver and Felicity.
To Oliver and Felicity.
It's time now
for the couple's first dance.
This is only a courtesy dance
because your speech was so sweet.
I have my moments.
You okay?
Yeah. You know, just, um...
Thought a friend might've come,
would've been nice to see him.
Oh, it's a "him"?
I'm guessing he's more than
just a friend then.
Weddings make you nostalgic
for the ones you love.
I definitely miss my wife
and my family.
You know, for what it's worth,
I did see the DJ checkin' you out.
No, no, no. I don't do DJs.
I had this thing once,
it did not work out.
Can you believe
our daughter is married?
- Oh, my God.
- I really can't.
Thanks for letting me back
in her life.
I made a mistake
asking you to stay away.
Seriously, Felicity needs her father
in her life.
And just for the record,
I think Tom Jones is actually...
He's pretty good.
- I kinda like him.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry, this is awkward.
- You two know each other?
- No, it's, um...
We...
Well, then this is awkward.
I'll go get myself a drink.
Wow, you look, um...
You look...
- Really good.
- You mean I look sober.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, the last time I saw you...
You were going through a nightmare.
Ah, it's Jean Loring.
This is Oliver's lawyer.
I gotta take this. I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure, sure.
I was never the girl who dreamed
about her wedding,
but I have to say
this was the perfect evening.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Uh... I'm so sorry. We got a problem.
I think I jinxed it.
Come on.
- What's going on?
- Well, listen,
I really did not want to
do this right now.
But Jean Loring just called
and she said
I got to tell you right away.
It's okay. What's happening?
I told her you were in the middle of
celebrating your wedding...
Quentin, what's going on?
The prosecution's smoking gun
is a witness who is willing to
testify that you are the Green Arrow.
- Who?
- That information's still under seal.
But it's someone on the team.
I can't believe
this is happening again.
Okay, hold on a second.
We do not know
this is an
Evelyn Sharp situation yet.
It's a betrayal.
I never should've trusted them.
It's not a "them," it's a "one."
A one who wants to out you to the FBI
that will lock you away for life.
That's an awfully long time.
I'd wait for you.
Hey, I just got your message.
Usually, the bride and groom
like to be alone
on their wedding night, what's up?
Somebody on the team gave me up
to Samanda Watson.
That's impossible, Oliver.
No one would do that.
Lance got it from Jean Loring.
Jean Loring got it
from District Attorney Armand.
I'm running surveillance on
Curtis, Dinah and Rene
and I have worms crawling through
their texts and e-mails.
- So you're spying on them?
- I'm not spying on them.
More like keeping tabs.
Oliver, why not just
confront whoever this is
and give them a chance to come clean?
What makes you think
they're gonna be forthcoming?
How do we know that this isn't
just the surface of this betrayal?
I mean, look, John,
I don't want to spy on them.
If you have a better idea...
I'm all for it.
If someone goes somewhere suspicious,
we'll know.
Felicity, we were all
just at the wedding.
The most suspicious place they can go
is out for late-night pizza.
John, either Curtis, Dinah,
or Rene gave me up.
We need to know why,
we need to know who.
Otherwise, when you
put the hood back on,
you could be next.
All right, all right.
Where do you want to go,
bathroom or couch?
Hey, hey, I am perfectly capable
of walking myself.
That was not because I was drunk.
That is just because
I am very clumsy.
Wow! This is the doghouse.
Woof!
It's actually way cleaner
than I thought it would be.
Oh, look, you have flowers.
Why do you have flowers?
Are you seeing some lady friend
or something?
It's not like that.
You know who I'm going to see
when I get to my place
in the morning?
Some hot dude?
Myself.
In the mirror.
Alone.
Do you think
it was the vigilantism
that drove Paul away?
Or did I just lose my charm,
or did...
Do you...
Do you ever feel like
life would be easier
if there was never a Team Arrow?
Only all the time.
You know what, though?
Oliver and Felicity
got their happy ending.
Which is all that matters.
To Oliver, at least.
That's just the booze talking, hoss.
All right?
I mean, you're gonna find
someone new,
but until then, you got all of us.
That's what I get for being nice.
You have to stop contacting me.
I've done all
I'm willing to do for you.
I'm not here to ask for a favor.
Then what do you want?
I miss you, D.
That dress
reminds of the one you wore
from the Guzman op.
Don't do that.
Don't try to dip me in nostalgia.
I don't even know
who you are anymore, Vince.
The man I knew would never,
could never kill an innocent person.
The people I've killed
weren't innocent.
Oh, no?
Well, what about that cop
you accidentally shot last month?
- Collateral damage.
- What?
Are you trying to tell me
that there hasn't been any in the war
that Green Arrow's fighting?
No. No, there hasn't.
Sounds like I'm not the only one
who's changed.
The Dinah Drake I knew
was never this naive.
Oliver brought me back
from a very dark, very bad place.
He stopped me from becoming you.
The only difference
between him and me
is that I don't lie to myself
about what I'm doing.
Look,
I may not be a saint,
but I do know this.
I care about you.
I always have. And always will.
Don't contact me.
Leave town.
And if I catch you
out in the field again,
I won't let you get away
a second time.
You didn't have to walk me
all the way home, Quentin.
You know I can take care of myself.
You are still recovering from
six months in a coma, Thea.
Let me be
a little overprotective here.
Hello, Thea.
Congratulations on
not being comatose.
Cayden James
would like a word with you.
- Get away from him.
- Thea.
You just got out of the hospital.
Are you so eager to go back?
Thea!
Laurel, you...
Next time, I'll put you
back into a coma.
Speedy.
Could we get audio on this?
No, I tracked her to this location,
then accessed street cams.
Guess we know how Vigilante
skipped the cops last month.
There's no way we can tell
what she's saying to him.
It doesn't matter
- She lied to the team about this.
- Oliver...
What else has she lied about?
Let's not get paranoid here.
Well, it's not paranoia
if it's a legitimate fear.
I mean, Vigilante
tried to kill Oliver last year,
he wants to out them
to law enforcement,
he's virtually doing the same thing.
It puts him away for life.
Okay. I don't think
Dinah would do this,
she cares way too much
about this team.
Oliver, listen,
she supported me through my injury.
- And as the Green Arrow...
- I know and I appreciate that.
But after what happened with Evelyn,
we need to protect ourselves.
Thea, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine. It's okay.
What happened?
Evil Laurel. She took Quentin.
I tried to stop her, Ollie,
but I'm not strong enough anymore.
It's okay. It's fine.
I'm just so glad you're okay.
Yeah,
but how are you all right?
Not that I'm not glad
that you're okay,
but it's not like Evil Laurel
to leave loose ends.
She needed a messenger.
What are the chances that
that's gonna ring like, right...
Fantastic. That's not creepy at all.
Hello. This is Cayden James.
Where's Lance?
Now, why would I tell you that?
What do you want?
A nano aluminum amplifier.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, that's all right.
I'm sure you can research it.
And when you do, you'll find
that it's secured at A.R.G.U.S.
Deliver it to me,
or Quentin Lance dies.
Last time we spoke
you vowed to destroy the city.
I'm guessing this amplifier
gets you one step closer
to completing that goal.
So why should I help you?
I did float the concept of
Mr. Lance dying, didn't I?
Now, you listen to me...
At nightfall tomorrow
I will text an address to this phone.
You'll be there with the amplifier,
or Quentin Lance
shuffles off this mortal coil.
Oh, and please don't breathe
a word of this
to your friends at A.R.G.U.S.
It's safe to say
there are no good reasons
that Cayden wants that amplifier.
- It sounds like a trap.
- He has Quentin.
It doesn't matter, he has leverage.
Can you and Curtis make
a replica of this thing,
a fake to pass off to Cayden James?
No. I mean, we're good,
but we're not that good.
It's one of a kind.
Isn't this guy
some type of genius hacker?
He knows it's at A.R.G.U.S.
Why doesn't he just
hack in there himself?
A.R.G.U.S. is 100% air-gapped.
I mean, you can't access
their network unless you're on site.
And I doubt he wants to
cross paths with A.R.G.U.S.
since they held him prisoner
for eight months.
He's using us instead.
A.R. G. U. S. isn'tjust gonna
hand over this amplifier.
They have a longstanding policy
of not negotiating with terrorists.
- Let's bring in Curtis and Rene.
- No Dinah?
Until we know
where her loyalties lie, she's out.
Oh, Dan, I can't tell you
how much I appreciate this favor.
I know it's not exactly protocol
letting me in here,
but I wanted to leave this
little surprise for Lyla
for when she gets back.
I'm not letting protocol
get in the way of romance.
Yeah, well, thanks for
helping keep the flame alive.
I, uh, forgot my card.
It's back at security. I'm an idiot,
I'll go get it.
No, no. I'll grab it.
Don't need everyone to
see you roam around
without clearance.
Good idea.
Overwatch...
You're up, talk to me.
Okay, guys. I'm working on
locating the amplifier.
Just stand by.
Oh! Okay, guys, I got it.
It's in the east wing.
I'll shut down security
when I access
the panel, does everybody copy?
In position.
Still don't understand
why the brown guy's
gotta be the janitor, is all.
Janitor is
a very honorable profession.
They clean up after you puke, which
is something I might do very soon.
Why the hell isn't Dinah here?
Is it possible that she could be
more hungover than I am?
- Definitely not.
- Guys, focus!
Overwatch, I'm in position.
How long until security is down?
That depends on Curtis.
We're clear.
Also, leaning over,
not a great decision.
You're not throwing up.
I'm already spending my honeymoon
in a garbage can,
I'm not wearing your puke.
- She slapped me.
- Oliver,
I can only buy you 60 seconds
before the security
around the amplifier turns back on.
That's more than enough time for me.
The floor's
still pressure sensitive,
if you touch it,
it will re-trigger the alarm.
Copy that. On your count.
Three, two, one. Go.
Almost there.
Guys, you're about to get company.
We need more time.
Oh!
I got it.
Clear. In three, two, one.
How you guys doing?
Good news is
this is exactly what Cayden wanted.
- Bad news is...
- It's exactly what Cayden wanted.
- Yeah.
- At least now we know
what he's gonna use it for.
What, he didn't want to
supercharge his Christmas lights?
Remember the thermobaric bomb
that Cayden stole?
Well, this will multiply
the blast radius 20-fold easily.
That's the entire city and then some.
Look, I wanna save Lance
as much as anyone,
but he wouldn't want this.
I mean, he wouldn't want us to
just hand over something so dangerous
to some psycho.
Yeah. Well, that's exactly
what we're going to do.
Curtis is gonna sabotage.
Curtis is gonna do what, now?
The amplifier doesn't have to work.
We just need Cayden James
to think that it works long enough
for us to get Quentin back.
I could back-channel a path
into the circuitry.
If you hide it
behind the existing border,
it might buy us enough time to
get Lance, get the hell out of there.
Hi.
Did you guys
just get back from the field?
Why didn't I get a call?
We should speak in private.
That's a bit dramatic, don't you think?
Okay.
I know that you've been
meeting with the Vigilante in secret.
- You followed me?
- I did.
Whatever business I have with Vince
is none of yours.
It is when it threatens to
put me in prison
and keep me away from my son.
What the hell are you talking about?
We're talking about being arrested
off the statement of someone
who knows my identity.
Somebody on this team!
And you think it was me?
What, because I didn't tell you
about Vince?
I think you have given me
no reason to trust you.
And you, what about you?
You don't trust me either, John?
Dinah, I'm sorry.
Wow.
No. No, no. Hey, I'm the sorry one,
you know.
I'm the sorry one
for having your back all those times.
- Screw you guys.
- I'm not finished.
- I am.
- Hey, guys...
Can we all just please calm down
for a second?
Look, I know everyone's stressed
because Cayden's threatening to
blow up the city,
and Lance is kidnapped,
but let's just all
just take a breath.
Now I'm not saying that it's me,
but it can literally be
any one of us.
Dinah, you are the only one
who has something to hide.
Everyone else checked out.
- What does that mean?
- Yeah,
what does that mean, John?
It means we had you
under surveillance.
- All of us?
- Yeah.
And by "all of us" you mean
all of us.
So, just the newbies.
We're out there risking our lives
just like the rest of you are...
Stop.
Dinah isn't the witness, Oliver.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Because it's me.
I'm the one
who's testifying against you.
Agent Watson came to me.
She said she had proof
that I was Wild Dog,
and that she was gonna
use it against me
to make sure
that I never saw Zoe again.
She said she had a solid case
against you,
and that she was gonna arrest you
either way.
You were going down.
I just couldn't make
the trip with you.
You should have told us, Rene.
We could have figured something out.
There was
nothing to figure out, hoss,
right? There is no other way.
And now we'll never know.
Rene...
Get out.
Oh, good. You're awake.
I wanted us to
have a little daddy-daughter time.
Because of what happened on Lian Yu?
You make it sound like
I should be over it by now.
You shot me and left me for dead.
You seem to have bounced back.
Yeah, thanks to Cayden James.
He sent someone for me.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake
shooting you.
I'm glad you're okay.
- Then you're an idiot.
- You're probably right.
You're probably right.
Listen,
when you, uh, look at me,
do see your own father
at all?
No.
Because my father died
when I was 13.
What happened?
It was my 13th birthday.
And he left
to go get my birthday cake
like he did every year.
And then the phone rang.
There was an accident. A drunk driver
ran through a red light.
Head-on collision.
I'm sorry.
I used to pick up Laurel's cake, too.
Yellow with chocolate frosting.
From her favorite bakery.
Carly's.
I'm sorry you didn't get to
know your father.
I guess you're stuck knowing me.
Okay, it's time.
Remember, if Green Arrow
reneges on our deal, you kill him.
How can you eat this?
You ask me that every time.
He means at a time like this.
Stress makes me hungry.
So does guilt.
I just...
I screwed up,
you know, Oliver was right
to kick me off the team.
You were in
an impossible position.
Yeah, and when you're in
an impossible position
that's why there's a team, D.
Just like Dig said.
You're uncharacteristically
quiet, hoss.
I'm just hungover.
Doing some processing. I'm actually
doing a lot of processing.
Oliver spying on us, you mean.
I'm not gonna pretend
there's not a difference between
the three of us
and the three of them,
the original three, but...
Spying on us? I mean, come on.
That crosses a line.
Yeah. And I just don't like the way
that it makes me feel.
Now I'm stressed.
Wow.
It's good. It's real good.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Felicity told me what happened.
Yeah.
I would ask if you're okay, but I
think I already know the answer.
Thinking about what Rene did.
What do you do, really?
He kept a secret,
and he put his daughter
ahead of the team.
And I feel betrayed.
How can I feel betrayed
by somebody doing
the exact same things that I've done?
Because you've never
sold anyone out on the team, Ollie.
And if you're convicted,
you could end up spending a really
long time in jail.
But having said that,
you're doing
the right thing looking
at things through his perspective.
And having done that...
Maybe you can see
your way to forgiving him.
Seriously?
Well, Rene is a...
A very desperate guy
who just did a
very desperate thing.
But he's also the same guy
who, just last night,
was giving such
a heartfelt sweet speech,
and calling you his friend.
And I really think
that he meant that.
It was a betrayal, no question.
But since you've been able to
see things
from his point of view,
you should also be able to
see your way to forgiving him.
Listen to you.
Quentin needs the team
right now, Ollie.
But he needs the whole one.
It's almost nightfall.
Let's have the team suit up.
John...
- The whole team.
- Copy that.
Thanks for having me back, man.
Let's get our friend back.
This is where Cayden James wants to
make the exchange?
Yeah, it's a no-brainer
he picked this place.
It's a digital black hole.
There's no cameras, insulated walls.
Once you guys get inside,
I'm totally blind.
Well, that means so is he.
- Did you get the amplifier working?
- I hope so,
'cause otherwise we'd be
handing a crazy psychopath
the means to crater the entire city.
I mean, yes. Yes, it's ready.
I'll handle the exchange.
You three will be my eyes and ears.
The priority is extracting Quentin,
but if we get a chance
to take Cayden James into custody,
we take it.
Whatever we're going through,
whatever issues we have,
let's put it aside
and get the job done.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
Agreed.
Okay. Let's go.
So we meet again.
Where's Lance?
Oh. Somewhere handy.
I'll be taking that amplifier now.
You will be telling me
where Lance is.
A fair request.
Equally fair, lay down your bow.
I'll let you speak with him.
I am a man of my word.
If I wasn't, there wouldn't be
much point in
vowing to destroy this city.
Would there?
No sign of Lance or Laurel.
We can't see anything from up here.
Let's search the building.
Green Arrow said stay put
until he makes the exchange.
What, we're his eyes and ears
and we can't even look around?
Guys, we need you as backup.
Well, maybe if you'd bugged Lance
like you bugged us,
we'd know where he was.
Whoa! We didn't bug you guys.
We tracked your GPS.
It's totally different.
You're bugging me now.
You know I can hear you
through Wild Dog's comms,
you know that, right?
Screw it.
I'm not gonna sit around here
and wait for Oliver to
decide to trust us again.
See? Wasn't that easy?
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Accommodations could be nicer.
But yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah, well, sit tight.
I'll be there soon.
Yeah, just don't compromise
the city's safety for me, all right?
Now there's
a dedicated civil servant.
I wish there were more like him.
Proof of life, as requested.
Your turn now, I think.
Take what you wanted.
Mmm.
I think not.
You see, what I wanted was
a nano aluminum amplifier.
One that hasn't been sabotaged.
He knows.
That makes no sense.
How could he know?
I'm disappointed.
Though not nearly as much, I imagine,
as your friend Mr. Lance.
Kill him.
And kill him.
Team, everything's gone south.
Back up Green Arrow.
Wild Dog, Terrific,
where are you guys?
- We're on our way.
- On your way?
Why weren't you in position?
Don't got time for that now, hoss!
We got eyes on Lance.
James is gone.
His men are down.
Where the hell is everybody?
I've got Lance and Laurel.
They're exiting
the north side of the building.
I'm on my way.
Laurel's getting away with Lance.
We've got company.
Okay. One last stop.
Run.
Laurel.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Thanks for coming to get me.
- Can I get a sitrep?
- Is everyone okay?
Yeah. We're good here.
- How's Lance?
- He's fine. Sleeping it off.
Any sign of Cayden James
or Black Siren?
Nada. They're completely
off the grid.
But we got Quentin back.
- That was the objective, right?
- Right.
You and Rene were
supposed to be backup.
- Where'd you go?
- We were looking for Lance.
And from what I can tell,
we found him.
Moving off of your position,
was that
your call or Curtis'?
- Look, I was right there beside him...
- It was my call.
And it turned out to be right one.
You got lucky, Rene.
It doesn't make it the right call.
Look, man,
I know you're pissed at me
and I don't care.
Because you left us blind out there.
And I wasn't gonna let Lance die
just because you didn't
trust us enough
to go off leash and look for him.
When you are in the field,
there is a clear chain of command.
Plain and simple.
I've been the same guy tonight
that I've always been
- since you brought me onto this team.
- Rene, yes, that's true, you have.
- Sometimes you go your own way.
- That's right.
And I put up with it
because I trusted you.
What's that supposed to mean?
You got a second chance tonight,
my friend.
And you broke our trust again.
You don't get a third.
You're off the team.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
It's been real, y'all.
You know, I hate to say it,
but Oliver is right.
We're a team,
we need to trust each other.
We need to believe in each other.
I don't believe in you anymore.
- Dinah.
- Don't.
It's too late.
I'm out, too.
Guess we should both be glad
I didn't leave town like you said.
Oh, thanks. That's really
what I needed right now,
an "I told you so."
Are you okay? You don't look it.
I really don't want to talk about it.
Then why'd you reach out?
'Cause I had no one else to call.
I'll try not to be insulted by that.
I really needed someone who
believed in me.
I needed a friend.
Friends?
I can do that.
Sunflowers. My favorite.
Well, I wanted it to feel like home.
I'm not gonna have to
leave again, am I?
Hey.
I won't let anyone
split us up ever again.
I promise.
I'm just gonna say this.
I don't think there's
anything that has been said or done
- that can't be undone.
- I don't think I agree, John.
I agree with Felicity.
We need to move forward.
Sorry I'm late.
I think I probably
might still be a little hungover.
I've also been thinking about
a few things.
Oliver, you and Dinah were right.
No trust, no team.
You all spied on me.
Invaded my privacy.
Now, whether you couldn't
trust me or not,
it means that I can't trust you.
Curtis, what's that supposed to mean?
I'm still a part of
Helix Dynamics, Felicity.
That's separate.
But...
This...
I'm done.
Like I said, we need to move forward.
- Oliver...
- Cayden James knew
that we sabotaged the amplifier
last night.
We need to find out how.
When you had me raid their bunker
and plant that mini-cam
two months ago...
Is this the outcome I had in mind?
Quite so, Ms. Lance.
Although I must confess,
things have worked out
even better than I anticipated.
Hardly impressive.
Left to his own devices,
Oliver Queen will always push away
those closest to him.
So we've got 'em fighting with
each other instead of fighting us.
Please tell me
that isn't your whole master plan.
Oh, not at all, Mr. Diaz.
In fact, I think it fair to say
that this
is only the beginning.