Previously on Arrow...
I have a village, too,
run by a government strongman named Kovar.
You will go to Russia and find my parents,
and tell them what happened
to me and Vlad.
Taiana, I'm sorry.
Tell me who this "Prometheus" is.
I guess you know
what I've been up to, huh?
Remember, I'm always ten steps
ahead of you.
- What's going on?
- Chase is gone.
- So is Oliver.
- We have to assume Chase has him.
Just make sure he suffers.
That was always the plan.
PROMETHEUS". Did you hesitate at all
- when you killed him?
Or was he just another name
you crossed off your list?
If you kill me,
you'll only really be killing yourself.
Five, four, three, two, one...
Hundred and forty-five seconds.
That's how long my father struggled
under the water before he died.
According to my father's autopsy,
your arrow pierced his aortic arch,
but it didn't kill him.
No, he was still conscious enough
to feel his lungs filling with water
for 145 seconds.
And here you were
bragging about a plan
more intricate than torture.
Did you ever think about
why I chose the name Prometheus?
He challenged the omnipotence of the gods.
See, because like you,
they play judge, jury and executioner.
But Prometheus took away their power.
If that's what you're gonna do to me,
you'll need to come up with something
better than whatever this is.
I did.
And the only way for you to stop it
is to confess.
- I killed your father.
- Nothing so pedestrian.
I want you to tell me your secret, Oliver.
I want you to confess to the one thing
that you've been afraid
to admit to yourself.
How many times am I going to tell you
that I don't know
what you're talking about?
Fine.
You'll come around eventually.
Now, where were we?
One forty-five, one forty-four,
one forty-three...
Bandages and water will not help me.
Before you die, tell us what you meant.
You said if we kill you,
we kill ourselves.
Why'?
You will find out soon enough.
You're gonna tell me now
or I'm going to dig that
bullet out of your arm.
Go to hell.
Oliver! Oliver!
What are you doing?
He will never tell you truth
in that much pain.
Does this has to do with your deal
with Kovar, yes?
Samovol'shchina.
If you know what it was or what is coming,
you will beg Kovar to spare you.
And you are no one's hero.
Everything
and everyone that you love,
will wither
and die at your touch.
Da.
Good riddance.
What do we do about Kovar?
What does it matter?
Our Pakhan is dead.
We must swear in a new one.
ANATOLY". There are men loyal to us,
and men loyal to Gregor,
all without Pakhan.
How do we choose a new one?
Pakhan is determined by seniority.
Why is he doing that?
It's for journey to afterlife.
Makes good gift in heaven,
but even better bribe for Satan.
Da.
You can get in there, too.
You're one of us.
AY-.
Viktor, I think he cut into tendon.
I don't think he's very happy
you're Pakhan.
You think? I know.
I wish there was less painful transfer
of power in Bratva.
What are we gonna do about Kovar?
You're asking for yourself
or you're asking for Bratva?
Anatoly, Gregor made it sound like
all of us were going to be killed.
Samovol'shchina.
"Do as you will."
But he made it sound like there was some...
Some deeper meaning? Yeah, it comes from
Russian Revolution, 1917.
Why is he quoting the Russian Revolution?
I can't think of any good reason.
Maybe ask Kovar when I talk to him.
What?
You can't meet with Kovar.
Kovar had deal with Gregor.
Gregor is dead.
As new Pakhan, I have to meet with him,
he will suspect something is up.
- I could try to talk to Galina.
- To who?
- I told you about Taiana.
- Oh, yes.
Galina is her mother
and she works for Kovar.
Maybe she heard something.
Oh!
Your boss, you work for Konstantin Kovar?
- He said you were enemy.
- No, no.
- A bad man.
- No, no, no.
I'm friends with Taiana.
My precious Taiana?
Well, we're friends.
And I could use your help.
- With some things...
- Mmm-hmm.
Wait, I'm not gonna hurt you,
I'm not gonna hurt you. Listen to me.
When Kovar hears about this,
you cannot say you saw me,
do you understand?
You say you saw me, he'll hurt you.
All right? All right.
KOVAR". My father once told me,
"Do not have 100 rubles,
"but have 100 friends."
Fortunately for us,
we have both friends and money.
Yes, I assume your presence here means
that our arrangement has borne fruit?
The shipment was routed to this location.
The BIC codes are inside.
All you have to do is retrieve it.
And as for my compensation,
I think that...
Unidac Industries, yes.
I will make sure you get
the information you desire.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some other business to attend to.
My apologies.
Malcolm Merlyn,
CEO of Merlyn Global Group.
Anatoly Knyazev, gangster.
You undercut your new station,
Mr. Knyazev.
Pakhan of the Solntsevskaya Bratva,
it's...
It's no small feat.
Nor is samovol'shchina.
One of Gregor's last words.
And, uh...
Were his other last words
about who killed him?
He called the man Kapiushon.
- Hood.
The reports of man with a bow and arrow
are disrupting business,
Bratva and otherwise.
It's interesting.
I heard some reports of my own...
Of you having trouble with Gregor
because of his deal with me.
I questioned it, yes.
Now that I am Pakhan,
I'm obligated to live up to commitments
that he made.
Such as samovol'shchina?
You study history, Mr. Knyazev?
When the Soviet Union was dissolved,
many thought that
the capitalist opportunities will
give rise to a more stronger,
a more united Russian people.
But then powerful men at the KGB,
Communist Party,
the Komsomol, they decided to
cash in on their privileges.
And, uh...
Russia became not stronger,
but diseased.
And samovol'shchina was the cure once.
It could be so again.
Right, what does that mean?
It means Kovar is planning something
very big and very terrible.
What is he gonna do?
Oliver, maybe time is best
for you to go back to America.
Anatoly.
We're brothers.
What's happening to you
is happening to me.
Kovar is going to overthrow
Russian government.
Samovol'shchina is coup.
And, I mean, he just told you this?
Before I got there, he was making deal
with American businessman.
Some secret, sensitive shipment.
Do you think it's a weapon?
Kovar has many men,
but not enough for a coup.
But with weapon...
Luckily, I got a chance to see
the file they're working on,
Orekhovo-Zuyevo.
It is a shipyard in Moscow.
Then we go to the shipyard.
We stop Kovar from retrieving it.
Seeing you take bullets out of Gregor,
I saw him again.
Face of the monster.
This place, it's not good for you, Oliver.
Go home.
I didn't save you from Gregor
to stand by while you're murdered
by Kovar.
This isn't over for me.
So be it, brother.
Do they look familiar?
Do you even remember their faces?
These are your victims.
They were people who did terrible things.
They had victims.
And husbands. And wives.
Daughters.
Sons.
Confess your secret, Oliver,
and all of this ends.
I'll give you a gift, and you can walk out
that door and go back home.
Adrian, you're sick
and you're a hypocrite.
There is nothing that I've done
that compares with you.
Murdered your own wife...
Cecil Adams.
You knew him by his street name,
The Count.
You put three arrows in him.
He was gonna kill a friend of mine.
Felicity Smoak, yeah.
Confess or you get the same three arrows.
Go to hell.
I've already been there, Oliver.
And I've come back with a message for you.
- Are we all clear?
- Clear.
See how easy it is to think first,
and kill people later?
What is that?
Sarin gas. Enough to kill thousands.
What's next?
You said something
when I brought you here.
About how your friends are your strength.
Now...
She didn't even know
I was in her apartment.
Oh, I swear to God, if you hurt her...
You'll do absolutely nothing.
Because you're here.
You see, until you confess
your secret, Oliver,
everyone that you love is at play.
Even your son.
You're bluffing.
He's in hiding.
I don't even know where he is.
Because you haven't really looked.
But for me,
we both know it's just a matter of time.
Confess.
I don't know what you want me to say.
Then I guess I should leave you here
to think about it.
And wonder who I might kill
while I'm gone.
Adrian! Adrian, please!
All you have to do is say the words.
I...
That's what I thought.
See you soon.
We have incoming.
The truck!
Kovar has the Sarin gas.
Then we are all going to be dead men.
- How's Anatoly?
- Recovering.
Which is more than I can say for our men.
- The sarin gas get him?
- Da.
Where were you?
I was keeping Overwatch,
like Anatoly ordered.
You have something to say to me, Viktor,
so just say it.
It was your idea to go against Gregor.
Because of Kovar,
with your vendetta against him.
- Now look at the mess we're in.
- Well, do you have a better idea?
We should be honoring Gregor's pact
with Kovar. Not this.
The moment that Kovar
overthrows the government,
he is going to wipe out the entire Bratva.
Where are you going?
We have one of Kovar's men
and we need to know
where the gas is gonna be used.
Why would he tell you anything?
He won't be talking to me.
Please, I don't know anything.
There's no need to hurt me.
Quiet.
A friend of mine recently showed me
the skinning technique
used by hunters of Mongolia.
They remove all the skin
of things much larger than you
in less than five minutes.
Which means,
you don't have very long
to tell me what your boss is planning.
I don't know anything.
I was kind of hoping you would say that.
What is this monstrosity?
You should be resting.
I woke up with headache.
I came to find you,
I was not expecting this.
This is not human.
Anatoly, I told you.
Putting on this hood,
it helps me direct
the darkness inside of me.
And it worked, by the way.
I know what Kovar is planning.
But at what cost?
You're a fool to think a piece of cloth
can separate man from monster.
Dividing yourself in two
will only make monster stronger,
until it is stronger than you.
You knew what I was capable of
back on Lian Yu.
Yeah.
But this man I see now
bears more resemblance to Slade Wilson
or Anthony lvo.
Tough man.
Clearly withstood a lot before breaking.
He gave up pretty quickly.
The rest was me practicing.
Practicing to become what?
Something else.
Kovar's inviting key members
of the government,
politicians and military mostly,
to the opening of his casino.
And kill them with sarin gas,
even the innocents?
It's not good for business.
Yes, but being in charge of whole country
is good for business.
We need to get into that casino,
and we need to stop the attack
before it happens.
Place will be fortress,
increased security
for president and generals.
Impossible to break in.
Then what do you suggest we do?
We sneak in.
Without the help of someone
working for Kovar?
I know someone.
Well, if you're thinking about house lady,
last time it did not go so well.
Give me a second chance.
And if second chance doesn't work?
Mrs. Venediktov?
He's fine.
Well, he's unconscious, but... Look,
I'm sorry that I scared you
the other night.
I just, I need to speak with you. I...
Well, it's like I said,
I knew your children Taiana and Vlad.
Do you know what happened to them?
I'm sorry. They're dead.
But Mr. Kovar say
he's still looking for them.
Kovar is lying.
Before she died, Taiana,
she told me that he was a monster.
And she made me promise, she made me swear
that I would bring him to justice.
But even what you say is true,
what can I do?
Taiana told me that...
"The same hammer that shatters glass,
"forges steel."
I say to her as a child
to make her grow up strong.
Well, she did.
And she helped me grow strong, too.
Would you please,
please help me keep my promise to her?
This gets me into Mr. Kovar's buildings.
Thank you.
Make it right for them.
Uh...
Tell me,
who killed my children?
A monster.
What did you do to her?
I made her more compliant.
Get up.
Give yourself a chance.
I'm...
I'm not gonna fight her.
I don't want you to fight her.
I want you to kill her.
I'm gonna leave now.
When I come back,
either she's killed you and I let her go,
or you kill her and I let you go.
No. Neither one of those things
is gonna happen.
If you don't kill her,
you're gonna watch me snap her neck.
Adrian, what is the point of this?
You seem to be having a little bit of
trouble figuring out what your secret is.
I thought this might remind you.
Good luck.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
I can't take another day in here.
I think it's a...
Canisters are in a storeroom.
Southwest corner. Second floor.
Copy that.
Okay, if you'd be so kind
to let us in now, please?
- I'll meet you at the target.
- Da.
I took you into my home.
I gave you food and shelter.
This is how you repay me?
Now where?
I studied the map.
I know a shortcut. Here.
Are you sure this is the way?
Almost there.
Should be at the turn up ahead.
You sold us out.
We're in a casino, Anatoly.
I like to think of it as
playing the hand I was dealt.
Evelyn? Hey, look at me, listen to me.
I need you to bring the knife over here.
I want you to get me out of these things.
When he comes back...
We will ambush him.
No, we can't beat him.
I didn't know what I was buying into
when I sided with him. I...
It's okay. I forgive you. I, uh...
I just, I think that together,
we can get through this.
I'm dead.
That's all he kept telling me. I'm dead
because I was a part of your life.
Will you bring me the knife?
Will you bring me the knife,
and I can save us?
No!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
Come on!
Are we serious?
Oliver, what are you trying to prove, man?
Evelyn betrayed you,
you've killed people for less.
I'm not gonna kill her,
I won't, just let her go.
You're forgetting what I told you
- would happen if you didn't kill her.
- No!
- Adrian, will you please, okay?
You have made your point.
Confess, Oliver. Tell me your secret.
I don't know what you want from me!
I want you to tell me what you've been
too afraid to tell your sister,
Felicity, Diggle.
Tell me!
I don't know! I don't.
Wrong answer.
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Finally, we're getting somewhere.
Confess.
Oliver, we've been betrayed! Viktor, he...
KOVAR". I'm so very proud of this casino,
and what it means for our country.
Well, that's why it saddens me
to tell you that
there was an attempt
by Solntsevskaya Bratva
to crash these festivities,
and assassinate every one of these
government officials here tonight.
But don't worry,
we have them all in custody.
Yes.
I'm told they planned
to stage a gas attack
in this very room.
But, uh, sadly for them, even though they
were successful in launching the attack...
It backfired and
killed every single one of them.
Well, at least,
that's what the newspapers
will report in the morning.
Good evening.
Confess.
You killed my father
because he was a name on a list.
But that's not really true, is it? No.
It's too late, Kapiushon.
The gas has only done its work.
The list was just an excuse.
The hood, the disguise, just an excuse.
The idea that all of this is
some heroic crusade, is just an excuse.
Excuse for what?
- Huh? Tell me!
- You tell me, Oliver.
You tell me.
Kill him.
Oliver Queen.
Who could have imagined?
I know what's going on
through your mind, Oliver.
You're thinking that you can get
yourself free from those chains,
lay me to the ground and snap my neck,
just like I did to Evelyn.
There it is.
There's the look I've been waiting to see.
But it's not just about stopping me,
is it?
No, there's something else in there.
Confess, Oliver.
When you see Taiana in the afterlife...
Give her a kiss for me.
- I'm going to finish this.
- No!
Are you going to let your Pakhan finish it
for you, Mr. Queen?
You don't have to do this, Oliver.
We both know that I do.
You don't have to, Oliver.
The man will face justice, I promise.
You're right.
He'll face justice.
You've told yourself you kill
because you have to.
Confess, Oliver.
You don't kill because you have to.
So, why...
- Why do you do it?
- Because I wanted to.
What?
I wanted to.
I wanted to!
And I liked it!
How's it feel?
Knowing that I saw the one thing
you couldn't admit to yourself?
WOMAN". I knew he'd break.
Just like you said he would.
It's because I know him
better than he even knows himself.
Give us a moment alone, would you?
I told you, Oliver.
You infect every life you touch.
Now do you realize why?
It's because your crusade
was based on a lie.
You used your father's memory
to justify a killing spree.
There's a price to be paid
for that, Oliver.
Your mother paid it.
Your friend Tommy paid it. Laurel.
Do you really want to tell me
that John Diggle and Felicity Smoak's
lives are better having known you?
You promised to let me go.
And I'm a man of my word.
But first, I have a gift for you.
This tattoo of yours.
To be an American
and named a Captain in the Bratva,
you must have done
something extraordinary.
When you look at it, it must...
It must remind you of such a victory.
Now when you look at it,
you'll think about our time here together.
And the secret that you confessed to me.
Whatever pain I caused you...
I'm sorry.
I believe you, Oliver.
I just don't care.
You know, I've decided.
You are my favorite American.
How many Americans do you know?
You and joking are not exactly
made for each other.
But that looks like it does.
Anatoly, why make me a Captain?
I'm not staying in Russia.
Because now anywhere you go in the world,
any Bratva you meet will know
what kind of man you are.
Come, I have another gift for you.
Here,
I recovered it from the casino.
Thank you.
You remember the first time
we met on Amazo?
I was performing surgery on myself.
That's kind of difficult to forget.
Yeah. What was it I said to you then?
"Living is not for the weak."
I cannot believe scared boy
in cell beside me
would be one to kill Konstantin Kovar.
Well, that wasn't me.
- That was him.
- That is a lie you tell yourself.
An excuse that allows you to kill.
But you kill because you like it.
That's not true, Anatoly, I hate it.
And I think maybe you've had
a bit too much to drink.
Well, that is entirely possible.
But in this case, lam right.
This deal you've sold yourself on,
like this hood is going to keep
this monster of yours at bay?
Someday it's going to fall apart.
And when it does,
you're not going to like the man
you see underneath.
Well?
It will take weeks
until he's back on his feet.
But he'll live. He gives you his thanks.
Just out of morbid curiosity,
who did this to him?
That's his business.
Well, whoever it is,
I'm glad I'm not him.
- How much longer?
- "How much longer?"
We've literally had to re-route
the electro-optical digital imaging
from every reconnaissance satellite
I could gain access to.
Then we had to capture data
in a four-dimensional array
which could then be parsed
using a real-time algorithm.
Basically, solving cold fusion
would have been easier.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Just been at this so long
I don't know which way is up.
And Oliver's been gone for six days and...
And, and what?
- Oliver? Oh, my God!
- Oliver?
Chase had me.
And he let me go.
Go slow, man.
It's over.
Oliver, we're gonna get this
son of a bitch for whatever he did to you.
John, it's...
It's over for me.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
I'm shutting everything down.