Previously on Arrow...
You would be remiss in forgetting
the thermobaric explosive that remains
in my possession.
What do you want?
Vengeance for my son.
- What'd you find?
- Video of his son's murder.
This is fabricated. It didn't happen.
Whoever planned this
knew exactly how Cayden would react.
Which means that person
has to be close to Cayden.
Do you trust me?
I need you here for a
rather important assignment.
- What's that?
- Rooting out a traitor.
- Baby, please wake up.
- He's gone, D.
We're clear.
All right. Keep moving.
I guess Cayden James and friends
knew we were coming.
Oh, yes.
Once I learned of Mr. Sobel's treachery,
I had to assume
this location was compromised.
Speaking of which,
I didn't appreciate your alliance
with him.
Made me think we no longer have
an understanding.
- You need to know something.
- Many things, I'm sure.
But I doubt very much that
you're the man to teach them to me.
We almost have proof
that I didn't kill your son.
A desperate gambit.
Cayden, give me more time.
Time, I'm afraid,
is a commodity you and your city
have run out of.
Mr. Sobel's betrayal convinced me
that there's little good
in delaying matters further.
Accordingly,
I will be detonating
the thermobaric bomb
over Star City at midnight.
My son will find justice in the ashes
of your beloved city.
ARROW
Cayden is going to detonate the bomb
in four hours.
Where are we with the video?
Well, we're running
a photographic analysis algorithm
to reveal the original footage.
- How long will that take?
- As long as it takes.
The algorithm Felicity and Curtis wrote
works wonders on a still image
but this is 24 fps video
we're talking about here, so...
Right. Cayden just told us that
we're running out of time.
There's something you should consider.
You're putting all of your chips down
on a bet that he'll spare this city
if he thinks you're not responsible
for his son's death.
That's because that's
the only play we have, Alena.
I'm just saying you might be
trying to reason with a man
who's beyond reason.
As you are well aware,
Arclight is now in its final phase.
And now it's time for us
to take our leave.
Words much appreciated.
But how are we to get out of city?
Stay close to your phones.
You'll be airlifted from the city
before the bomb goes off.
After it does,
your individual shares of the ransom
will be wired into offshore accounts
that have been set up for each of you.
Sounds fair.
Lucrative.
Indeed.
Thank you for helping
to see this project to fruition.
I don't think I need to stress
how personally important
this has been for me.
Thank you for all you've done
to get justice for my boy.
Mr. James.
Just as Alexander reigned destruction
on Persepolis,
so do I now,
on Averwood Pharmaceuticals.
$50 million
from illegal black market drug deals.
And I just made it all
disappear.
You must be our new recruit.
Kojo Sledgehammer, if I recall.
I am...
I am so stoked to be here, Mr. James.
This is just...
You are an absolute legend.
It's been a pleasure meeting you.
I'm sure we'll all do
great things together.
Owen.
See you guys tomorrow.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hey, that was quite a game.
Please don't lie, okay?
I could see you weren't in the stands.
Mom told me you didn't show.
Where's your mother now?
She and Jim went to have dinner
at some fancy French restaurant.
Jim got a promotion.
He said he wanted to treat her.
That's considerate of him.
So sorry I missed the game, Owen.
I got delayed at work.
Is that what we're supposed to call
your weirdo hacker group?
The work we do is important.
It benefits people
all over the world.
Yeah. Work you won't even tell me about.
As I've said,
that's for your protection.
Look, I know I'm not
the easiest person in the world
to talk to.
But,
I do want to be a bigger part
of your life.
I truly do.
You can't have it both ways, Dad.
You can't say you want to be a part
of my life
and keep me out of yours.
When are the finals?
- Tomorrow night.
- I will be there.
I can't share with you
all the details of my work,
but I vow to do a better job
of sharing your life.
And that begins tomorrow.
Yes. Yes, exactly. Please.
Listen. We need SCPD radios linked
with emergency services right now, okay?
Now.
Where the hell are you?
Did you get my message?
Yeah. I'm okay. We rallied the troops
and everyone's panicking a little.
Gather a list of essential personnel
clergymen, doctors, as many people
as you can mobilize.
How... How are we gonna explain
how you have access
to the Arrow's bunker?
We have bigger problems right now,
Speedy. It's...
Besides, this is the only place
in the city I can think of
that can possibly withstand that blast.
You have eyes on...
- William. Of course. I've got it.
- Thank you.
Do you have to keep doing that?
Keeps me calm.
Do not worry.
Cayden James will not let
his friends die with the city.
You're damn right.
And I'm not gonna stick around
to find out.
Where are you going?
Some place I won't get blown up.
Two of you haven't noticed,
the airlift that Cayden promised,
it's more than a little late.
I hate to say it,
but I think he's right.
I notice that Dinah didn't show up
for work today.
Well, after what happened to Sobel,
you really expecting her to?
No. I just...
If from what Oliver told me, I...
I don't really think that
she's exactly just grieving.
You think Oliver would just... What?
Let Dinah kill her?
No. I...
I just don't think that
that's what's on his mind right now.
Right.
Well, you know, if it comes down
to Laurel against Dinah,
Laurel's not the one I'm worried about.
Tell me where I can find Black Siren
or the next bone I break is your neck.
Lady, if I knew
where any of those guys were going,
I'd be with them.
I guess that's one way
to not get information.
What are you two doing here?
Looking for you.
SCPD says you weren't in today.
We were wondering if you were
gonna do something stupid.
Guess we were wrong.
I'm looking for her
to get justice for Vincent.
Why do you say justice
like it's cold-blooded murder?
I know you're hurting, D.
But Felicity called.
We've got till midnight before James
lets his bomb do its thing.
As much as we feel for you,
that seems like the priority.
He's right. Now's not the time
to go off the deep end.
I can't let this go.
I'm sorry.
D.
I love you both,
but stay the hell out of my way.
We need to consider
the A.R.G.U.S. airlift option.
Oliver, we've already talked
about this. James will see it coming.
We need to consider something.
- Got it.
- What?
I've seen this. It's bogus.
You said you had something.
Yeah. The whole thing was
a massive deception.
Owen was never collateral damage
like Cayden was made to think.
He was the real target the whole time.
Who is that?
Facial recognition just picked him up
as Carl Iskoff.
Paid assassin.
- With bow and arrow?
- Bow and arrow is not his usual MO.
I'm guessing it was a special request
by whoever hired him
- to kill Cayden's son.
- All to set you up.
We need to have a conversation
with this Iskoff.
Find out who hired him.
He's dead.
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The assassin was assassinated
not long after Owen Post.
We need to know where Cayden James is
right now.
Got him.
I'm guessing Cayden doesn't care
about people knowing his location
now that his bomb is about to go off.
He's almost on the I-86.
He's psycho but he's smart.
I mean, he doesn't wanna be anywhere
near the boom
when the bomb goes boom.
We'll never catch him.
I have an idea.
We need to talk.
Questionable judgment, Mr. Queen.
If you wanted the bomb to go off
before midnight,
you'd be hard-pressed to come up
with a better way
than taking me into custody.
Watch this.
Would that be the proof
that you alluded to earlier?
Just play the video.
No. I'm not watching this again.
No, Cayden.
You're not.
You're watching the real video
for the very first time.
Oliver didn't kill your son.
Which means someone else did.
The assassin's name is Carl Iskoff.
He was instructed
to use a bow and arrow,
so the video could be manipulated,
and they could make it look like me.
It's the same tech used to out Oliver
as the Green Arrow, four months ago.
Someone's gone through a lot of work
to put you two on a collision course.
Oh, yes.
Someone within my organization.
How do you know?
The metadata on the forged video file
confirms it as the
work of the same person
who manipulated that photo in October.
You lost a man a month ago.
Killed by the traitorous Mr. Sobel,
but I highly doubt it was Mr. Sheck.
- That leaves Laurel? Diaz?
- And Anatoly?
I'd like to speak
to my former colleagues.
And that's where the two of you come in.
No.
We're not rounding
them up to be executed.
No, I just want a pointed conversation.
Bring them to me. All three. Alive.
Otherwise, I'll have no choice
but to stay the course.
I still have a very powerful bomb.
And I'd be perfectly happy
to take out Star City
right along with whoever orchestrated
the death of my son.
You gotta be kidding me.
Please tell me you're kidding me.
The only way to stop James
from destroying the city
is by delivering him these people.
Lead them to the slaughter, you mean.
- We won't let that happen.
- Right now, that's our only option.
You don't even know for sure
that one of them did it.
I mean, none of them
were working for Cayden
when he received the video.
They were working for him
when he received the doctored photo.
It has to be one of those people, Alena.
It is either Diaz,
Anatoly or Black Siren.
You hope. What if Cayden is lying?
Well, we've got
bigger problems then that.
I mean, what makes you think that
we can find Cayden's BFFs,
if he can't?
If they're smart,
they're out of the city by now.
They're smart, but so is he.
He grouped them together by promising
to fly them out before the blast.
Thank goodness for small
favors and gullible bad guys.
By now, they're worried that James
might not make good on that promise.
Raisa wanted to go
to one of the city shelters,
so she could be with her family.
What's going on? Why do we have
to leave the safe house?
We'll talk about it later, buddy.
You promised
you won't lie to me anymore.
Cayden James is threatening
to detonate a large bomb
in Star City
and this is the safest place for you.
That is the truth.
- Alena.
- Yeah. We're running facial recog
and Cayden gave us
back satellite control.
Our usual tricks aren't working.
Oliver, we need the rest of the team.
Agreed.
- Where are you going?
- Need to go look for a few people.
Let me come with you.
I need you to stay here.
I wanna stay with you.
It is too dangerous out there.
Bottom line.
I'll be back as soon as I can be.
You have any luck?
Did you think I would?
She was pretty clear about
where she stood, hoss.
So, basically the city
is gonna get destroyed
and our friend is gonna commit murder
and there's not a damn thing
we can do about either?
- Well timed, D.
- Different kinda D, Hoss.
Sorry, John.
We've gotten some
place with Cayden James.
He won't detonate his bomb, if we
bring back Anatoly, Diaz and Laurel.
Alive.
So, no honor amongst thieves?
Well, let's just say
he has a good reason
to think at least one of those
is responsible for his son's death.
We can use your help finding them.
If we do it,
we should go after Laurel first.
Dinah's after her.
If she gets to her before we do...
D's gonna kill her.
And if she does that,
she might be killing the whole city.
Vince told me
you had a to-go bag stashed.
Took me a little while
to figure out where.
You can't stop me.
This ends tonight.
You end tonight.
No.
You stay out of this.
I can't let you hurt her.
Hi, Daddy. Missed you.
I told you.
This ends tonight.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
What are you doing?
I had her.
I'm saving the city.
I cannot believe you are working
with Cayden James.
It's not like that, D.
He wants Anatoly, Diaz and Laurel.
- Alive.
- Or boom goes the city.
Just saying, that's
a pretty good reason to not kill her,
besides, you know,
all the other good reasons
like, killing is bad.
I can hold off for a little while.
Dinah.
- We do not just execute people.
- No.
You just let them die.
Can we continue this later?
Anatoly and Diaz are still in the wind.
Correction.
Ricardo Diaz was in the wind.
Cayden's satellite just picked him up
headed south.
Our team can take down Diaz.
Okay. I'm sending you
the GPS co-ordinates now.
I'm staying here.
I'm not letting her out of my sight.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
So, what? We're letting the foxes guard
the hen houses now?
Quentin, Canary,
you keep eyes on Black Siren.
Wild Dog, Terrific, you go after Diaz.
Overwatch, let us know when you
have eyes on Anatoly,
and Spartan and I will be ready to move.
Put me through to Cayden.
Mr. Queen.
Have you fulfilled my request?
We have Black Siren.
Where do we take her?
The last time I checked,
it took more than one songbird
to make up a trio.
Cayden, we don't have time for games.
Then I suggest you find
my former compatriots
as soon as you can.
Owen, before this night is over,
I promise to you,
we will render our judgment.
Where's my phone?
Ah.
- Are you heading out, Cayden?
- Yes, Alena.
Prior engagement. Must attend.
Well, are you sure that's a good idea?
Whatever do you mean?
Oh, uh...
I'm... I'm sorry. I just assumed
somebody would have told you.
I... I picked up some chatter
on your hacked A.R.G.U.S. responder
a few minutes ago about your takedown
of Averwood Pharmaceuticals.
My point being, it's just...
If A.R.G.U.S. has your scent,
maybe going out right now
isn't the best idea.
Probably not. But I'll take precautions.
Can't afford to break this date.
Leaving town?
You like that?
We got this off another pair
of doppelgangers.
You know, I have to say,
I was surprised.
Your boyfriend and his little magical
healing abilities.
You know, I thought it would be
harder to take him down,
but it wasn't.
What's going on?
I'm counting down the minutes.
What? Before you try
to kill my daughter again?
That is not your daughter.
That is a monster.
You gave your monster a second chance.
After he worked his ass off
to redeem himself.
And after he gave his life
to stop Cayden James.
You seriously wanna compare Vince
to Laurel? I...
I know. I know what she's done.
I'm not an idiot,
but no one deserves to die.
Not even her.
You're wrong.
And once this is all over,
if Cayden James doesn't kill her,
I sure as hell am gonna take my shot.
Where's my dad?
He said he'd be right back.
Um, yeah. I know.
And he will.
It's just that...
Things didn't really go
as he planned tonight,
the way any of us had planned, so...
Just taking a long time.
He's gonna be okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I've got eyes on Anatoly
and a few of his friends.
Looks like they've got themselves
a helicopter.
Next time I come back to City,
I hope it is ash.
Kapushon!
Show yourself.
City is about to become crater.
You want to put me in prison? Fine.
Just... Out of town, please.
Bomb's not going off, Anatoly.
Because I'm gonna deliver
Cayden James the truth.
You.
You have finally snapped.
Took few more years longer
than I expected.
You set me up.
Photo.
The doctored video.
I already told you.
That was not me.
Well, forgive me if I don't wanna
take you at your word.
Overwatch, we got him.
Curtis and Rene got Ricardo Diaz.
That makes us three for three.
William, give that to me.
Call James.
I was beginning to think
you'd forgotten about me.
We have all three.
Where do you want 'em?
Meet me at the abandoned theater
on Jefferson Avenue.
I'm on it.
- I'll call Curtis and Rene.
- I got Quentin.
I'll keep an eye on Cayden.
Prodigious timing, gentlemen.
It's almost midnight.
- Not here to play games, Cayden.
- Yet, here you are.
- And what of Mr. Diaz and Ms. Lance?
- They'll be here.
And what of this young man?
I don't believe your son
was invited, Oliver.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanna be with you. I'm scared.
- William, just listen to me...
- It's just like on the island.
Just like when my mom died.
I don't wanna lose you too.
- Please, I want to stay with you.
- Come here. Come here.
It's all right.
You stay right here.
It started with my son.
Yours should be here for the end.
It's a beautiful symmetry,
don't you think?
He has nothing to do with this.
I don't disagree.
But it appears your son has other plans.
Hello, William.
My name is Cayden James.
You're the guy who wants
to blow up the city.
I suppose.
It's a long story.
And it concerns my own son.
Where is he?
Passed away, I'm afraid.
Cayden James.
I was told to expect you.
Warned, in fact.
Mr. James, we're here to remand you
into custody
for multiple violations of federal law.
I strongly advise you not to resist.
My only son is playing in this game.
Could I perhaps watch it
before you take me in?
That's not how it works.
Just asking for few moments.
Little compassion here.
I strongly suggest
surrendering peacefully
to avoid a scene.
There's no need for that.
I'm gonna get a lay of the land.
She better be here when I get back.
I don't think she likes me.
Well, you haven't given her
much reason to, have you?
Fair.
She's right, you know.
- About what?
- I'm not like Sobel.
I'm not gonna change.
I'm not gonna just wake up one day
and... And be your Laurel.
No, no. You'll always be you.
But you can be better.
Why would I?
We live in an ugly world
and the only way to survive it is...
Is to be ugly right back.
- You're wrong, okay?
- Hey.
Has it ever occurred to you
that I like who I am?
That when I killed Sobel,
I actually enjoyed it?
And all those pictures that you
showed me of your daughter, this...
This... This woman
that I don't even recognize,
they made me sick.
She was soft and naive.
And that's why she's the one who's dead.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I don't ever wanna
find myself enjoying killing you.
Perimeter's secure.
- Let's move.
- Yeah.
Quite a brave young fellow
you have here, Mr. Queen.
Brave and foolish.
- Much like his father.
- Wait, wait. What's he doing here?
None of your concern, Mr. Lance.
Ah. And the rest of our guests
have arrived.
These two freaks say that you think
one of us killed your boy?
In point of fact, Mr. Diaz,
I know that one of you killed my boy.
I intend to find out who.
You believe people in masks,
over people you do business with?
I'm with the Russian.
I think these guys would do anything
to save their precious city.
I don't trust anyone's word, Mr. Diaz.
I put my faith in data.
Information.
Ones and zeros never lie.
This is digital proof that
one of you has betrayed me.
Come on, William.
Please just get out of there.
None of you know
what it feels like to lose a son.
A piece of yourself, gone.
It's like a phantom limb.
No. It's worse than that.
It's like a piece of your soul, lost.
As if it had never been there. No. Stop.
I keep reminding myself that...
I have not lost my son.
He's been taken from me.
Hey.
You're losing it.
Your grief,
it's making you crazy.
What if it has?
Just look at him. He wants to kill
everyone in this room.
- Just be ready to move.
- Okay. Screw this.
It was me.
I did it.
Surprise.
I'm the one who did it.
I killed your stupid kid.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
For the past three minutes,
Cayden's detonator has been emitting
a 76 GHz field.
- Now it's spiking.
- Okay. What does this mean?
It means there's something wrong
with the bomb.
It's a shame really. He was very cute.
Signal's fritzing again.
Closer Cayden gets to Laurel,
the bigger the frequency spikes
on the detonator.
No, it's not the detonator.
Aren't you gonna ask me why I did it?
No.
I know you're lying.
You're not nearly as callous
as you portray yourself to be.
I saw, Ms. Lance.
When I ordered you to execute
Mr. Sobel, I saw you hesitate.
You didn't wanna do it.
Oliver, you need to get Laurel
away from Cayden, right now.
His detonator is interfering
with her power-dampening collar.
Well, well, well.
Now this is interesting.
Laurel!
Guys, are you okay? Do you copy?
Overwatch, we're fine.
Okay, thermal imaging reads
everyone's still inside,
but they've gone
in different directions.
I'm good. Find Anatoly.
I've got Diaz. Go!
Sure thing, hoss.
- Knew this would happen.
- What?
We work with Oliver, we get in trouble.
The guy's a walking death trap.
Who do you think taught him about traps?
- Stop!
- God, you're persistent.
It's annoying.
Son of a bitch.
Dinah! No!
No!
Laurel! Laurel!
William?
William, back away, son.
Your son wouldn't want you to do this.
The person responsible
for his death is in the vicinity.
And I intend to drag them
to hell with me.
I owe it to my son.
Look at me.
You don't be afraid, all right?
I'm right here with you.
I love you very much.
William.
I had an obligation to protect my son.
It's a father's job
to protect your child.
But I failed.
I failed him, utterly.
All this time,
the man responsible for his death
was me.
Don't you move.
I can't believe he was ready
to blow up the whole city.
Yeah.
He lost his boy.
I don't even wanna...
Yeah.
What you did was very dangerous.
I know and I'm sorry.
I am never gonna let
anything happen to you, William.
Ever.
And I am promising you,
that I will do everything I can
to make sure nothing happens to me.
- You can't make that promise.
- I can make that promise.
I just did. I am. Right now.
Kiddo, I've been doing this a long time.
So trust me.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
I gotta go talk to the others,
all right?
Okay.
Where are we?
If by "we" you mean Anatoly,
Diaz and Laurel...
Completely in the wind.
- Again?
- Again.
Well, Quentin's walking Cayden James
to booking right now.
Look, I know what you're all gonna say
but I think finding Laurel
needs to be our first priority.
Don't make this personal, Dinah.
Or you know, more personal.
You heard her.
She is the one who had
Cayden James' son killed,
she was the one who set
all of this into motion.
- You don't know that.
- She confessed.
She was pushing James' buttons, D.
How did she manage
to blind all of you this much?
You're the one who's not seeing clearly,
if you ask me, Dinah.
I didn't.
Hey. Hey.
You're better than this.
- I guess we're leaving now.
- Yeah, we're leaving now.
Just to be clear, whatever happened
doesn't change anything.
Yeah, we're glad
we took down Cayden James,
but we're still doing our own thing.
Please try and keep Dinah in line.
No promises, hoss.
In case you haven't noticed
we're not having a lot of luck
with that right now.
Well, we saved the city again
and got Cayden James.
Yeah. Why doesn't that feel like we won?
I must say this visit
is somewhat predictable.
Well, I needed to look you
in the eyes, Cayden.
I need to know that
this surrender of yours
isn't some sort of ploy.
I've had bad luck with that tactic.
You prevented from doing
the unspeakable last night.
I'm sure Owen
would have been ashamed of me.
But then he always was.
These are my best guesses,
as to where you might find
my former allies,
along with the account number
to a bank in Corto Maltese
where I placed all the money
I embezzled from the city.
Thank you.
I would ask one thing in return,
permission to visit my son's grave.
I can arrange that.
Be a better father than I was, Oliver.
If this is another feeble attempt
to extract information from me,
I warn you, I will continue to invoke
my Fifth Amendment protections.
I'm very sorry
to have to tell you this, Mr. James,
but your son Owen
was found murdered last night.
No.
He's 18!
No!
Who would wanna hurt my boy?
I'm afraid we don't know.
I am truly very sorry, Cayden.
Hey.
What's your story, morning glory?
I used to say that to you
when you're a little girl, you know?
The other you.
- I already told you.
- I know what you told me.
What you told me was a lie.
James said it.
You hesitated when you killed Sobel.
So what if I did?
It means there's a piece,
maybe just a small piece
but it means that there is a piece
of my daughter in you, somewhere.
And I'm gonna get it out,
whatever it takes.
Didn't think we'd end up here.
SCPD custody.
You know, I saw this playing out
in a lot of ways.
But I gotta tell you
I wasn't expecting this.
I assume it would be foolish to think
that this is a rescue operation.
You're always the smartest guy
in the room.
You thought you always had
everybody pegged.
You've put everyone
in your little boxes,
you always understood
what they were thinking,
how they'd react.
But you're realizing now,
you didn't really know anything.
I'm afraid I don't take
your meaning, Mr. Diaz.
Is that so?
You're supposed to be the smart one.
You made some moves,
then I made some moves,
Queen is under indictment now.
His team is fractured
into million pieces.
And this city,
oh, this city,
it's prime for a takeover.
You see, guys like you
never understand these things.
Why destroy a city
when you could take it over?
I suppose this accounts
for your presence here.
The new police captain,
she's on my payroll,
along with a few other city officials.
Arclight
was a big help in thinning
the herd for me.
I suspect you're not done
thinning the herd.
You were always talking about
how much you missed your son.
I guess you didn't know
I'm the one who had him killed.
Tell your boy
I said hello.