Previously on Arrow...
There was a fire
in the apartment.
Your mom was
in there.
It wasn't the fire
that killed her.
Your mission is
about revenge.
- Dante's a person.
- He is the financier
behind dozens
of terrorist attacks.
Deputy Director Bell.
We're in the process of
reinstating the ghost initiative.
Restoring the program is the
only way we can get Dante
without A.R.G.U.S.
oversight.
We were able to backtrace
the number Diaz called.
It belongs to Dante's
contact Virgil.
Blackstar's our only lead
on finding those bombs.
Felicity's still
alive.
You're not
gonna shoot me.
My name is Mia Smoak.
I'm Felicity's daughter
and your sister.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Where are you?
I can't find you!
Oh, oh, aah!
I'll always find you...
Both of you.
You stay away from me.
You stay away
from me and my family!
You can't protect
your baby.
William, it's your dad again,
and I don't know if you're
getting my messages, buddy,
because you're not
returning my calls.
I tried... I tried
calling the house.
Look. I know that I'm not
your grandparents' favorite,
but Felicity and I,
we just want to know
how you're settling in, and we
would love to hear your Voice
because we really miss y...
The mailbox is now full.
Good-bye.
He's still not
answering your calls.
No.
Zoe froze me out
when I first lost custody.
Don't worry.
He'll come around.
You just got to
be patient.
Patience is not really
my thing, Rene,
but thank you.
Any word on when Dinah
is coming back?
Well, she's already
tried to check herself
out the hospital
a couple of times.
Patience is also not
really her thing.
- Working a new case?
- Not exactly.
It's for your
sister. Yeah.
That's still weird
to say out loud.
OK, Rene, look.
Our team has been deputized
to work with the SCPD.
She hasn't been.
She shouldn't be out there
as a vigilante,
and I would actually really appreciate
if you didn't
encourage her.
Do you really think
I could stop her?
Stubbornness runs
in the family.
Besides,
this is personal.
Why?
This is the bullet
that killed her mother.
Her mother
was murdered?
- She didn't tell you?
- No.
Look. I'm not trying to get in
the middle of any family drama.
Too late.
Her mother was murdered
over a year ago.
- Ohh.
- Emiko's been trying to find
the killer
ever since,
but all she's found
were dead ends.
This bullet is her
only legit lead.
Does she have any reason
to blame my family
for her mother's death?
Y'all did become
Starling City Royalty
while she and her mom were left
to struggle in The Glades.
All I'm saying is
there's a difference
between trust
and trust fund.
- She trusts you?
- That's because I had to prove
to her
that she could.
OK. I'll prove it, too.
Just like
my father taught me.
He should have taught you
how to aim, boy.
You'd be lucky
to break skin.
Do you two
ever stop talking?
Oops.
That is enough.
You're supposed to be training,
not trying to
kill each other.
Aww. Why you
got to ruin all the fun?
The op in Cairo
was a bust.
Dante's emissary Virgil
managed to evade us.
Virgil was
our only contact to Dante.
All that effort to trick Diaz
into giving up the number,
and we're back
to square one.
Not completely.
We still have the records
from Virgil's phone.
That could lead
us to Dante.
Meantime, Dante is
wreaking havoc,
financing terrorists
all over the world.
I was hoping to be done
with this group by now.
I know. The only thing anyone
knows about this operation
is that Diaz is a part
of the ghost initiative,
but the longer this
takes, the more likely
A.R.G.U.S. brass is to
find out the real reason
for the ghost initiative
is to go after Dante.
It's time to tell
Oliver and Felicity.
Our position now is
riskier than ever.
The less secrets we have,
the better.
My sister?
No. That's not possible.
I wish it wasn't,
but here I am.
Now, get the damn gun
off me.
He will when
you stop lying.
It just doesn't
make any sense.
We all knew Oliver
and Felicity.
They never had
a daughter.
Guess you didn't know
them as well as you think.
Is this true?
Is she their kid?
Hey. Whoa. Let him go.
He doesn't know who
my parents are.
I never told him.
She's telling
the truth.
Look, Mia,
Mia, my dad told me
to keep a watch on you
and keep you safe,
so I know who
your father is.
Your dad
knew, too?
Who the hell
is your dad?
John Diggle is
my adoptive father.
- A vigilante.
- Mia...
so you've been lying to
me this entire time?
Well, now that we're
all acquainted,
what the hell are you
doing down here?
She's looking
for Felicity,
who's apparently not dead.
How do you know?
Because she's done
this before.
She's just hiding somewhere,
being paranoid like always.
Figured it
might be here this time.
So you're just
going on a hunch, huh?
No. I am going
on an entire lifetime
of dealing with her.
Did you even bother
checking into her murder?
Of course we did.
She died
in an explosion.
Did you actually see a body?
OK.
So where do we start?
Yeah. I'm not looking for any
kind of family reunion here, bro.
Oh, I'm sorry, sis,
but I have come too far
to get sidelined now,
so we're helping each other
whether you want to
or not.
The ghost initiative sounds
a lot like task force x.
Didn't Lyla shelve
that years ago?
She did,
but there's now
a more immediate,
more dangerous target
that the brass at A.R.G.U.S.,
even above Lyla,
is preventing us
from pursuing.
We're using
the ghost initiative
to go after
this target
without their
oversight.
Well, I love
a spontaneous ota moment
as much
as the next person,
but you didn't really
come here to tell us
about resurrecting an old A.R.G.U.S.
defunct program, did you?
It's not
about the program.
It's about
who's in it.
- Ricardo Diaz.
- Ohh.
You have to be joking.
You're working with the man
who threatened
and tried to kill
my entire family?
I think it's important that
we hear what John has to say.
Working with this monster
is a small price to pay
for bringing down
a much larger threat.
Diaz was the only one we could
use to get close to this guy,
and I promise you he is
a million times worse.
So Diaz is just walking around free
right now in exchange for intel?
He's not free, Felicity.
He has a bomb in his head.
If he makes one misstep...
We are taking
every precaution.
Well, I understand
why Curtis left.
Hey.
You can't really be
OK with this.
No, but i... I trust John,
and I believe
that he would only take
a step like this
if he had
no other choice.
There was
no other choice,
and I hate that
it came to this,
but Lyla and I
believe that using
the ghost initiative is the best
way to take down this threat.
You realize that this is
the second time you have
prioritized your job over
keeping your friends safe?
Working with A.R.G.U.S.
does keep you safe
because it makes
the world safe.
You can keep telling
yourself that.
Meet Virgil,
an intermediary
for the terrorist
financier known as Dante.
- Diaz should be familiar.
- Nice guy.
Your job is to meet
with Virgil,
convince him that he should
be in business with you.
You get through Virgil,
you get a meeting with Dante.
So our first mission
is a meeting?
That is way
below our pay grade.
Wait. We're getting paid?
If we can even
get the meeting.
I tried once.
Virgil wouldn't take my call.
He wouldn't
take yours,
but he'll take his.
Diaz is the reason we've
been able to track Virgil.
So what do you say, Diaz?
You want to make that call
for real this time?
I thought you'd
never ask.
OK. Operation blow the
head off the dragon
is officially
a go.
I overrode A.R.G.U.S.'s
security protocols
and accessed the bomb
in Diaz's brain,
which means as soon as dig's ghost
initiative mission is over, one click.
Boom!
That's great.
- High score on candy crush?
- I'm working.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize that being a fake lawyer
was more interesting
that getting revenge
on the bastard
who killed Quentin.
Fine. I'm listening.
Happy?
All you have to do is get
within 100 feet of Diaz,
which should be easy
for the D.A.,
and then just click
this button right here
and activate
the remote detonator.
♪♪ Da da da ♪♪
Won't that send me
straight to the top
of most likely to have
killed Diaz list?
Heh. What do you care?
You've been trying
to kill Diaz for months.
I mean, the only
reason he's still alive
is because we needed him
to get Oliver out of prison.
True...
But some things have changed.
I mean, I'm kind of
good at this D.A. thing,
so I'm not really sure I'm
ready to give it up yet.
Well, I'm not ready to
give up on getting Diaz.
Diaz is in A.R.G.U.S.
custody.
He's not running
around free.
Trust me.
I would be thrilled to see his head explode,
but is it really worth
the consequences?
Yes, it is worth
every consequence.
I have to protect
my family.
By family you mean
you, Oliver,
and your baby?
What, are you
psychic now?
Well, there's no wine
or champagne
and no caffeine
on this mission,
and that... that is
a pregnant lady
amount of chocolates
you just consumed.
I ate that much chocolate
before I was pregnant.
- No one else knows.
- Not even Oliver?
I haven't found the
right time to tell him.
I've been trying to tell him,
so I would really, really appreciate it
if you wouldn't tell...
Anyone.
I won't.
I promise.
Really snap
your wrist next time.
Gives it a bit
more power.
How the hell did you
get in here?
I have something
for you.
- Of course Rene told you.
- Don't get mad at Rene.
I just...
I want to help.
I had Felicity analyze the
composition of the bullet.
- It's made from a...
- a rare promethium alloy,
the kind used by a handful of black
market weapons manufacturers?
I've done my homework.
Do you know it was shot
with a customized rifle?
Specs are
on the drive.
Thanks.
I can help you catch
who made it.
This is my mission.
OK. Maybe we can discuss
your mother.
Rene has
a big mouth.
I'm glad he told me, OK?
I know what it's like
to lose a parent.
I don't want
your sympathy.
I want justice.
Except you're not
authorized to get it.
I am.
Why should I
trust you?
I understand that my parents
weren't exactly the best people,
but... if they taught
me one thing,
it's the value
of family,
which is what
you and I are,
so if someone's hurt you,
you better believe
they've hurt me, too.
I don't know how we're gonna used
this old stuff to find Felicity.
It's like
a tech time capsule.
Here goes nothing.
Whoa.
And we have liftoff.
I thought you
had Archer.
Why do you need all
this old junk?
Because as advanced
as Archer is,
it was designed
for The Glades.
This system was
built for Star City.
So who am I looking
for again?
Uh, some guy.
Paul loiseau.
Scpd has him listed
as the only eyewitness
to Felicity's murder.
I'm guessing she paid him
to say she was there.
Says this guy committed
suicide about a week ago.
Wait. That was right when we started
looking into Felicity's disappearance.
What about the coroner?
Another suicide.
Star City's bad
but not that bad.
Someone's taking these people out,
but why?
So Felicity uncovers
a bomb plot,
but before she can tell anybody,
the party responsible
fakes her death.
Now they're tying up
loose ends.
- So why not just kill her?
- Because they needed her.
You were the last one to talk to Felicity.
What did she say?
Just the usual bull about
how the city's not safe
and she wanted me
to get out of town.
It might not have
been bull this time.
You guys are just junkies
looking for your hero fix.
My mom is the only
person I care about,
and I'm gonna go look for her
myself without any of you.
- Hold on. Mia...
- get the hell off!
That goes
for all of you.
This is my kind
of place.
This used to be
a triad hangout.
Everyone, focus.
The objective is to find Virgil
and get him to agree
to your deal.
Where is Virgil?
Ah, speak of the devil,
and he shall appear.
Ricardo Diaz,
and here I thought the
almighty dragon was in prison.
No prison could hold me.
You should know that.
No bodyguards.
That's a good sign.
Now all you have to do
is convince him.
You know, Mr. Diaz,
I was, uh...
I was happy
to get your call.
My employer would like to know
when he can collect on your debt.
The Longbow Hunters
were not cheap.
We have
a proposition,
and I think it will cover
more than what I owe.
That's intriguing.
Too bad it wasn't made
in good faith, though.
Kill them,
except for Mr. Diaz.
Dante will deal with him
personally tonight.
Don't let Virgil leave!
Unh!
Great. Now we owe
her one.
Move!
Nowhere to run, Virgil!
Treachery earns the worst punishment,
Ricardo.
Dante will make sure you
get what you deserve.
Ha ha ha!
Are the handcuffs
really necessary?
Until you tell us which
one of you tipped off Virgil.
Hey.
We were caught in the same ambush.
In case you missed
the show out there,
we almost died.
Well,
some of us did.
You got something
you want to say to me?
Maybe
"Dante will deal with him personally"
was actually code
for "get Diaz out
before
the bloodbath."
- The phone call to Virgil.
- Mm-hmm.
Diaz must have warned
him somehow.
I'll have the analysts
look into encoded phrases.
Lady, you ain't
gonna find anything
because I wasn't the one
who warned them.
Sure you didn't.
You didn't really
think this one through.
Even if you and Virgil had
ridden off into the sunset,
mommy and daddy wouldn't
have let you get very far.
He didn't think we
would really do it.
You guys, you have no idea
who you're messing with.
You're afraid.
You'd rather have a bomb
explode in your head
than risk Dante finding
out that you betrayed him.
Once Dante figures
all of this out...
and he will...
you all are gonna be wishing
for the mercy of a quick death.
Laurel Lance
entering Queen residence.
No more sad chocolates.
I got you
a roasted turkey sandwich.
It's not deli meat.
I double-checked.
Also, I got you some
fruit and veggies.
Are you on any
prenatal vitamins?
Any Mac and cheese
in there? No?
Clearly, you're having some
kind of weird pregnancy crisis,
and killing Ricardo Diaz
is not going to solve it.
Focusing on killing the maniac who
wants to kill me and my family
might be a little bit more helpful than...
Eating that banana.
One, you need
the potassium.
Two, yes,
you're right.
Your husband's job is to
be the enemy of monsters,
and those monsters are going
to target you and your family
like they always have.
Thank you. That is
incredibly reassuring.
You are more
than capable
of protecting yourself
and your family.
I mean, you built this insane,
crazy security system.
Which didn't work the last
time somebody targeted us.
- So? You'll fix it.
- Yeah. OK.
In half a day, you hacked
into Ricardo Diaz's brain.
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but you're kind of
a badass.
What if it's
not enough?
Look.
There will always
be another Diaz.
- Oh.
- You just have to have faith
that you can handle
the next one
and the one after that
and the one after that.
You know,
this baby's really lucky to have you.
I know it's scary,
but I promise
you've got this,
and if you want to
kill Ricardo Diaz,
I am not gonna
stand in your way,
but don't do it
out of fear
because you have nothing
to be afraid of.
We just finished the
analysis of the phone call
between Diaz
and Virgil.
No obvious ciphers
or patterns.
OK. Well, if Diaz
was telling the truth,
then Virgil must have been
tipped off by someone else.
Probably the same someone who's
been blocking us at A.R.G.U.S.,
and now they know we're
using the ghost initiative
to go after Dante.
We need to catch him before
they shut us down completely.
Any luck figuring out
his next move?
Well, we did manage
to find this.
It's an Italian florin
coin circa 1300s.
Wouldn't have pegged
Virgil as a coin collector.
He wasn't.
It's a fake.
Turns out there's a
microchip hidden inside.
Well, that sounds
promising.
Unfortunately, the data's
very heavily encrypted.
I don't really trust giving
it to an A.R.G.U.S. analyst,
but Curtis did leave us
his decryption algorithm.
Considerate of him.
It's gonna take
a while.
Well, hopefully,
not too long.
If Dante's in town, it must
be for something big.
Um,
the algorithm you wrote to find the weapon
is lagging
a little bit.
Do you... Mind
if I take a look?
The algorithm's fine.
OK.
Do you have to
stand right there?
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
I had to help Zoe
with her test.
Geometry's a bitch.
- How we looking?
- Fantastic.
The weight on these
feels a little strange.
Did you make these
yourself or...
- no.
- I'm just asking because
when I started out,
I made most of my own Arrows,
and I could show you a
trick or two if you want.
What I want is for you
to not touch my things.
And that's a hit! OK.
Andrew Thornton.
Specializes
in promethium-based
customized weaponry.
That sounds like our guy.
Yeah. Now we just
have to find him.
According to that online
chatter right there,
he's doing a deal
tonight
at an industrial plant
in Pennytown.
- Hmm.
- So what's the plan?
Rene's gonna roll with me,
and you need to stay here.
No way. I'm not
staying behind.
You don't have
a badge, OK?
I'm sorry,
but I promise you
we will take care
of this.
Let's go, Rene.
Gentlemen, who's ready
to do some business?
Behold my masterpiece.
Fully customizable
to your specifications.
- Unh!
- Ugh!
I'll handle Thornton!
Copy that.
Ugh!
Thornton's mine.
Hey! What the hell
are you doing?
Taking back my mission!
There's two of you now?!
You're gonna tell me
everything you know
about the murder
of Kazumi Adachi!
Andrew Thornton,
up against the wall!
By the authority of the SCPD,
I am placing you under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm taking him in
for questioning.
No. This is my mission.
I need to question him my way!
You'd be breaking the law,
which you're
already doing!
There's a right way
and a wrong way to do this.
The only thing
I've done wrong
is think that I could
ever trust you.
Hey. Thornton's ready
to be questioned.
Thought you'd be
happier about that.
Yeah. Sorry. I just...
with Emiko.
I need to make her understand
we're on the same side.
I think the problem
is you thinking
you can make
her do anything.
Yeah. I've been doing
this a long time.
She's new,
she's unsanctioned,
and I'm trying to
help her.
But she didn't ask
for your help.
Imagine how you
would feel
if, when you first
started your quest,
someone had basically
ripped your father's list
out of your hand and
taken over your mission.
I see your point.
Emiko doesn't need
anybody telling her
what to do
or how to do it,
and she definitely doesn't
need anyone's protection.
You see that move
she did with the bow
and switched hands?
Yeah. It's impressive.
Ridiculous.
Just be her brother
if you want her to be in
your life and to trust you.
Just...
Just be her brother.
Hey!
It's just me...
your brother, apparently.
What,
you think just because we're related
I'm not gonna kick
your ass out of here?
That was the hope, yeah.
If you're here to
convince me to join
your little merry
band of heroes,
save your breath.
Actually, I was just
hoping that we could
commiserate about how much
our parents suck.
I never had anyone to do
that with before.
What do you have
against our parents?
Seems like you
came out all right.
You're super rich.
Well, let's see.
Oliver, being my dad,
got my mom killed.
Then he and Felicity
promised to stay in my life
after my grandparents
took custody,
and then I never heard
from them again,
and my whole justification
for it, you know,
that it's hard for publicly recognized
vigilantes to raise children,
sort of went out the window
when I found out
they actually had
another kid,
which means that they
just didn't want me.
Being the kid they wanted
wasn't so great either.
If you hate Felicity
so much,
why are you wasting all this time
trying to find out where she is?
- Because of this.
- A rock?
Felicity gave it to me
when I was a kid,
and it's how she sent out
her distress signal...
now nearly
two decades later.
And you held onto it
all this time.
It's actually
really sad.
Thanks.
You know, parents
aren't perfect.
They love us
the best way they can.
Ahh. Maybe I was just
trying to do the same.
My whole life,
my mom told me that our dad was a hero,
but everything in this
city says the opposite,
that all of our problems
today are because of him
and the other
vigilantes.
You knew him
back then.
Was he a hero?
Yeah, he really was,
and, you know,
I'm starting to think
that this rock was
supposed to lead me to you.
Family was always the most
important thing to my...
our parents.
Damn it, you are here to just
talk me into joining you.
Well, did it work?
We have a lead
on Dante's location.
- What's wrong?
- I got a call from the Pentagon.
They want me in front of
the joint chiefs tomorrow.
They're going to ask
for my resignation.
Lyla, I'm so sorry.
I should have never
forced your hand
with the ghost initiative.
I backed that play
with open eyes, Johnny,
and I stand by it now.
Still, I never thought it would
mean you losing your job.
Then we better
make it count.
Dante is within our grasp,
and we may not have another chance.
Now tell me
about that lead.
Well, Curtis' algorithm
absolutely worked.
According to the
microchip in the coin,
Virgil was using it as some
sort of storage device
for all kinds
of data,
including a forged
diplomatic credential
from the quraci embassy.
There's a delegation
there tonight
with a very interesting
guest of honor...
Princess noor harjavti.
Rumor has it
Princess noor is planning
a revolution.
So she needs Dante's money
to fund her palace coup,
which may be the reason
why he's in town...
to make
the deal.
We need to get
into the embassy
and stop that deal from
happening and nab Dante.
Copy that.
Only one problem.
We have no idea
how Dante looks.
- We know somebody who does.
- Diaz.
Which means we have to put
him back in the field.
That's not our
biggest problem.
The ghost initiative
is blown,
and we can't rely
on anyone at A.R.G.U.S.,
and we cannot go in
there without backup.
Maybe we don't have to.
Just got
off the phone with John.
He and Lyla are
gearing up
for a ghost initiative op.
They asked me to be
in the field.
In the field
with whom exactly?
Diaz?
I told John it was
your decision.
Whatever you decide
after the mission,
I will back any move that you
want to make against Diaz.
Oh, you don't
mean that.
You know what?
I know why you've been acting
so strange lately, right?
- You do?
- Yeah.
I was gonna tell you.
There's just been
so much going on. I...
you're planning
to kill Diaz.
Yeah. Uh, so I'm guessing
there is a speech coming.
Felicity, I think
there's a better way.
I... I think that,
but that's my choice.
I have no right
whatsoever to make yours.
Right after I got
out of slabside, i...
I didn't realize
or totally understand the...
the pain that
you were dealing with.
I just want you
to get closure
because I want us to be
able to move forward.
I hope you change
your mind,
but if you don't,
I swear I will not
stand in your way.
- Thank you.
- I have your back
no matter what.
Tell John you're
coming on the mission.
And so am I.
Harbinger's in position.
Sitrep?
I count 11, 12 guards
in this room alone.
We have to move
on Dante after the meet.
Agreed. You copy
that, Diaz?
Sure thing, boss.
Can't wait for you
to meet Dante.
Joke all you want.
Just remember,
we're only keeping you alive
so you can I.D. Dante.
After that,
all bets are off.
Overwatch,
what's your status?
The feed is live, but 5 of the cameras
are down in the souTheast corridor.
One guess as to why.
That's where we'll find
Dante and the Princess.
They don't want eyes
on the exchange.
Hold on.
What the hell is Director Bell doing here?
Son of a bitch.
He's Dante's source.
Looks like somebody
owes me an apology.
The Princess is here.
Everyone head
to the south corridor.
Your highness.
Princess noor,
at last we meet.
That must be him.
Diaz, can you
confirm? Diaz?
His signal is offline.
His last location was the
auxiliary room to your right.
I've got it.
Stay in position.
Forgive me.
Virgil couldn't make it.
I wasn't expecting
other company.
Not company.
More like proof of concept.
Mr. Bell works
for A.R.G.U.S.,
one of the many we've
installed at the agency
that now work for you.
My god.
Diaz must have used a defibrillator
to short the chip out.
That's why we lost
his signal!
Dante.
Excuse me.
Mr. Diaz.
No.
You owe me a debt.
This is the payment.
It's a setup.
Please.
Unh!
Forgive me, Princess.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Dante's headed for the south exit.
Everybody move in.
What about Diaz?
Dante's the objective. Go!
Leaving so soon?
Nah.
Don't miss.
Hey!
You don't get to
go free.
Honey, didn't we go
through this already?
You don't have
what it takes.
I do,
and I'm not
scared of you,
and I am stronger
than you are,
which is why
I'm not
going to kill you.
I thought Dante
was the objective.
He is the objective,
just not the priority.
Not this time.
You made a big mistake.
Stand down!
This is over.
For now.
He's gone.
Well, Diaz will be
taken back to slabside
for reneging on his
side of the deal.
This time,
he'll stay there.
Still need to think
about Dante.
He's not gonna forget
what happened tonight.
I won't either.
You could have gone after
Dante, but you chose Diaz.
Last year,
I had the opportunity to catch Diaz,
and I let it slip
through my fingers.
I wasn't gonna make
the same mistake twice.
Well, what about Dante
being the greater threat?
When I knew there was a
choice between catching
Diaz or Dante,
all I could think about was
what letting Diaz go meant to you last time,
Felicity,
so in that moment,
I decided that
sometimes the best choice is
to just protect your family,
and that's exactly
what you two are.
I just got off the phone
with the Pentagon.
We'll give you
some privacy.
OK.
Agent bell will be getting
a hero's funeral.
The official story is
he was at the embassy
on a covert assignment
that went awry.
Right. So it's
a cover-up.
OK. What about
the ghost initiative?
- It's being suspended.
- Well, that's some good news.
That's all the good news.
We lost Dante,
and I lost my last chance to get him.
You didn't lose
your last chance.
I'll be the one
to resign.
Look. We will tell
them that I took out
the ghost initiative
without your consent
and without your
knowledge.
No. This is
my responsibility.
Lyla, listen
to me.
We have no idea how far
this conspiracy goes.
If you step down
as director,
we may never
find out the truth.
Being terminated
for an opsec violation
will ruin your career.
But you'll still
have yours.
Let me take
this fall
for the family.
Hey.
Glad you called.
Thought you were
done with me.
Yeah, I did, too...
Until I got that.
Yeah.
Thanks for having Rene
bring that over.
I'm sure it's not
SCPD protocol
to release
interrogation records.
- Uh-uh.
- Yeah.
Least I could do,
though.
It is your mission.
It's... been
hard for me
not seeing you as him.
Him being our father?
I just assumed
I shouldn't trust you.
That's why I've been keeping
so much distance between us.
Then you give me
a chance,
and I, of course,
immediately overstep.
Pretty much.
I've lost a lot
in my life.
People,
you know, but...
With you,
I lost time,
so you gave me a chance,
and I immediately saw it
as an opportunity to
get some of it back,
but there was
no excuse for the way
that I behaved when I was
coming aboard your mission.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
Oliver Queen did apologies.
Well, I mean,
I didn't, but I've...
Grown a bit
over the years.
So? Fill me in.
What do you guys
have so far?
The same bomb plans
you have,
plus a map of tunnels
into The Glades.
Cube in a cube.
- You know it?
- Felicity used to
force this stuff
on me.
Little, uh,
mother-daughter bonding time
before I wised up.
There's another solve.
Cube in a... Cube...
In a cube.
No way. Huh.
What is that?
I think it's
a mini-cassette.
My grandparents had an answering
machine that used these.
What's
an answering machine?
It's not important.
What is important is the
message that's on this tape.
Can you hack it or...
no. You can't
hack this. Heh.
It's encryption
through obsolescence.
It's pretty genius,
actually.
Yeah, so genius,
you can't listen to it.
- We'll figure it out.
- I hope so...
Because this could be the
key to finding our mom.
Green Arrow
entering Queen residence.
Hey! How'd it go?
- Pretty good.
- Good.
I feel like we're
getting to a good place.
- Mint chip.
- Hmm. You want some?
I'm good.
Just needed a little
comfort food
after the night
we had.
A night that could have
ended very differently.
You want to know why
I didn't kill Diaz.
I wanted to.
I was ready to.
Then I realized
killing Diaz
wasn't going to
prove anything.
The whole reason
I wanted Diaz dead
was to protect
our family,
and... what our family needs
is a fresh start,
one in the light
just like you're doing.
I want our children
to know
that they are the most
important thing to us
and that we would
do anything...
Anything for them.
Ahem. You said,
"children."
I'm pregnant.
Ha ha!
Impressive.
You shouldn't be here.
Is that any way
to greet an old friend?
I hear you and Oliver Queen
are getting along quite well.
- He trusts me now.
- Good.
The timing couldn't
be better.
It's time for you
to come home.
What are you
doing here?
Unh!
Greg, move your head!