Previously, on "Arrow"...
Why didn't you
tell me about Sara?
Every time I bring her up,
you end up evading it.
You killed Sara.
And I don't want you
to tell anyone about this,
especially Laurel.
How could you
have done this to me?
- Please do not do this--
- Just stop!
I will work with you
to stop Ra's,
but never again will
I be your daughter.
Oliver Queen
is still alive.
Somehow, Taer Al-Sahfer's killer
still yet breathes.
Yes, I know.
He has returned
to Starling City, apparently.
Why did you not
tell me?
I had a right to know that justice
has not been done!
Because Oliver Queen
did not murder Taer Al-Sahfer.
Do you not believe his own confession
because you doubt his motives
or because you don't
approve of my grief?
- Sara was your beloved.
- And you've never approved.
I knew Sara would leave us.
Leave you.
One way or the other.
I didn't approve of the love that
I knew would end only in heartbreak.
Whether Queen
killed Sara or not,
he challenged you.
He defied you.
For that alone,
he must die.
♪ Arrow 3x15 ♪
Nanda Parbat
Original Air Date on February 25, 2015
[All grunting]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Coordinate your attacks.
If you don't
fight in unison,
your numbers
become my advantage.
[All grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
You both have
a long way to go.
Particularly you, Oliver.
You've spent years preparing to bring
a bow and arrow to a sword fight.
That's almost funny
coming from you,
considering you're the reason
the League is targeting us.
John: Thea has the club
closed for renovations.
I've reinforced all the entrances
with A.R.G.U.S. tech.
- We're secure.
- John.
My friends call me Dig.
You shouldn't even
speak to me.
If the club is as secure
as Dig says,
perhaps you and Thea
should relocate here.
We discussed that.
Thea wants to stay in the loft.
I have only been able
to survive in Starling City
because the League has no idea
where in the city I am.
We are not
leaving the loft.
You and your sister
have the same stubbornness.
Clearly it comes from your mother's
side of the family.
It's pretty amazing
how much Malcolm taught you
in such a short time.
Yeah. He's father
of the year.
Your fighting style, it--
it reminds me a bit
of Sara.
That's, um,
probably because
the same people
taught Malcolm and her to fight.
I need to take a shower.
What?
I was going to ask for a favor,
but I'm...
Really more concerned
about you at the moment, Oliver.
I'm fine.
[Exhales]
You've been pushing it pretty hard
with Malcolm Merlyn lately.
When's the last time
you got a decent night's sleep?
I will sleep
when this is over.
We recovered the Omega
from Chen Na Wei.
We stole the Alpha from
the Hong Kong military
and gave it
to Amanda Waller.
Look, no matter how many times
you make me say it,
it's not going
to be any less true.
That's enough.
You're relieved.
Sorry. Waller's a little too thorough
for her own good,
and by "thorough," I think
you know I mean paranoid.
Well, I've gotten
used to it by now.
Where is she,
anyway?
Well, the mop-up of the Alpha/Omega
bioweapons problem
has become a United
States Army operation.
Ms. Waller's
participation is concluded.
I'm sure that comes as a profound
disappointment to you.
Oh, like you
wouldn't believe.
I apologize for the invasiveness
of your debrief.
And now that it's over,
you're free to go.
The Yamashiros
have been released, too.
They're returning to Japan.
You go with them,
and from there,
you can return to Starling
or go wherever else
on earth you wish.
Thank you,
General Shrieve.
After what you did, son...
That's the least I could do.
[Sighs]
This is hardcore.
When Dig said he was
fortifying the club,
I figured there'd just be a few extra
locks and cameras.
[Chuckles]
Are you ok?
No. No, not really.
What's wrong?
Ollie told me
that I can't tell anyone.
Whatever it is,
you have to be able
to talk about it with someone.
Someone who's
not your brother.
I killed Sara.
It was Malcolm.
- He--
- I know.
And none
of you told me?
You know last year when I kind
of went off the rails for a bit?
Yeah...
I was also under
the influence of something.
And just like you,
I killed someone.
A cop.
Roy...
They didn't tell me, either.
And when--when I found out...
You wished that
you didn't know.
Look, I'm not going to lie
to you and tell you that
the feeling ever goes away,
but I can tell you
that it gets easier, Thea.
You don't have to see
that cop's family
almost every single day.
I can't imagine that it's going
to get any easier.
[Sighs]
And I don't think
that it should.
[Doorbell rings]
So he is alive.
There were doubts.
Do you have any idea what happens
to the stock price of Palmer Technologies
when Palmer goes missing
for a week...
Whoa.
It's been a week?
I've been
a little distracted.
I can't get the gauntlet module
to interface with the helmet system.
I've been working
the problem, but I can't--
- Stop!
- Yeah, I imagined you'd say that,
but this is the last step towards
the suit becoming operational,
and a little facial hair
is a small price to pay--
Stop!
This is
a subsonic ionizer.
If you try to use it
on quadband circuitry,
- it could result--
- In a catalytic reaction
that could destroy
the entire building.
Oops.
Oops?
You need to get
some sleep.
I will, once I've
cracked the problem.
Or blow yourself up?
Whichever comes first.
Ray?
When those men
killed Anna,
I promised myself
I would never feel
that helpless again.
So, can you even
imagine how I felt
when Brick's men took a portion of
the city hostage?
Lousy. We all did.
But if you're
punishing yourself--
I'm not--I'm not
punishing myself.
I'm focused on
the task at hand.
Too focused, clearly.
I'm sorry, but I've got
a lot of work to do.
Hey, Dad. It's me. Again.
Listen, I know you're upset
and you have every
right to be, but
it's been over a week, and
now that you know the truth,
neither of us should go through
this alone, so,
please call me back.
I love you.
[Hangs up phone]
Hey. What are
you doing here?
Um, I--I need
to talk to you.
Is everything all right?
No. It's about Sara.
Ok.
Malcolm drugged me.
He gave me something
that made me...
susceptible to suggestion,
and I--
Thea...what are you
talking about?
I killed Sara.
I didn't know what
I was doing, ok?
It wasn't me.
I'm so sorry, Laurel.
If Merlyn
drugged you...
then it wasn't
your fault.
But how could you
work with him?
How could you
stand by his side?
Because of the threat
of the League.
We have to work
with him.
I don't have
a choice.
Yes, you do.
What happened wasn't
your fault, Thea,
because it wasn't
your decision.
If you want to make
this right,
what you do from
now on...that is.
I can't remember
Sara's smile.
It's weird,
isn't it?
I mean, I know
Sara used to smile
and--and laugh,
but when I close my
eyes and I try and picture it,
all I see is the way
that I found her.
You know, sometimes,
the only thing that keeps me going
is the thought of
one day finding her killer.
We will.
I promise.
How do you do that?
- Do what?
- Lie.
Right to my face.
Thea told me, Oliver.
She told me everything.
How could you
keep this from me?
After what you wanted to do
to Lacroix and Merlyn?
Do you really need to
ask me that question?
I'm not so consumed
with vengeance
that I blame Thea
for Sara's death.
I blame Malcolm Merlyn.
I need him.
He murdered my sister.
With the League
targeting us,
he is the only chance
I have of saving mine.
This is how
it has to be.
It's really
amazing...
The way Merlyn
always finds a way
under your protection.
I'm sorry, Laurel.
You know, it's hard
to remember a time...
When I was actually
in love with you.
[Door opening]
[Puff]
I told you not
to tell anyone.
I guess I'm just not as good at
keeping secrets as you are.
Thea, I'm not gonna pretend
that I understand
all the different types
of pain that you're in,
but the threat,
it is very real.
And the only way that
we are gonna survive
is by acting in unison.
Are you really quoting
Malcolm Merlyn to me right now?
Yes. Because he,
better than anyone,
understands the danger
the 3 of us are facing.
We're not
in any danger.
Not anymore.
Not you or me.
But Malcolm--he's going
to face justice.
Thea, what
have you done?
You're clearly not
League of Assassins.
They wouldn't be
this sloppy.
Aah!
[Grunting]
That's right.
I forgot.
Oliver mentioned
you were having
some identity issues,
though he didn't mention
about your delusions of grandeur.
[Grunting]
You killed my sister,
you stupid son of a bitch!
[Both grunting]
Now you're just
embarrassing yourself.
Your sister's teacher
was my teacher.
Did you think you could
really dispatch me with a stick?
No.
[Cocks gun]
I suppose we're gonna
see if being a killer
runs in the family.
[Clang]
Step aside, Laurel.
Nyssa!
This does not
concern you.
We've come
for Al Sa-Her.
[Malcolm grunting]
Nyssa: Uhh!
Uhh!
You swore to me that
you didn't kill Sara.
I never believed you.
[Grunting]
It is admirable of you
to honor your sister,
but you can rest now.
Sara's murder is avenged.
Where is she? Hey!
I told you Merlyn
was off limits.
I know.
And then I realized
that I didn't
really give a damn.
This is why
I keep secrets from you.
Because you let your emotions
dictate your actions,
and it is gonna
get you killed.
Did you really think
that you had a chance
against Malcolm Merlyn?
Nyssa and the League
kidnapped Merlyn.
I know.
Thea traded Merlyn
for safety.
She was able to
contact the League
because they are
in town on the hunt.
Merlyn has a video
of Thea killing Sara.
First thing he's gonna
do is show that to Ra's.
Then we're right back
at square one.
Making that video
was a bluff
to make me
challenge Ra's.
Merlyn loves Thea.
He would never just
serve her up.
[Sigh] We have
to get him back.
What?
Yeah. I'm with
her, because
it just sounded
like you wanted to
rescue Malcolm Merlyn from
the League.
My sister did this
because she is angry.
Eventually, she will
settle down and realize
that she basically just
killed her own father.
There's no coming
back from that.
The guilt will just
eat away at her
until there is
nothing left.
Please.
I'll start with the
private airfields.
No. Oliver,
Merlyn murdered
my sister
and corrupted
yours and now
you want
to save him?
I'm trying to save
Thea's soul.
You're out of your mind.
And you don't need
to be here.
I got something.
Unless it's a big,
fat coincidence
that the security cameras
at Starling City Aviation
just went dark.
I'll handle it.
I'm going home!
We hope you'll
consider staying with us
in Tokyo for
a day or two
before you leave
for Starling City.
Don't pressure
him, Tatsu.
He's been away from
home a long time.
You can stay
with us forever.
I like playing
games with Oliver.
Well, maybe I can send
my family's plane,
and then you and
you parents could
vacation in America.
Your family
owns a plane?
It's more of a jet.
I see it! I see it!
I see our boat!
I hate boats.
Oliver.
What is it?
Hell will be a paradise
compared to what
my father has in store
for you, Al Sa-Her.
Malcolm: Only because
of my Undertaking.
Your father doesn't care
about Sara's death
just as you know
in your heart
that your relationship
with Sara
has cost you
any chance of taking
your father's place.
[Tires screech]
Get him aboard.
I'll deal with this one.
[Grunting]
Your sister told us
Merlyn killed Sara.
Are you so lost
you'd deprive me of my justice?
This isn't justice.
It's vengeance.
Vengeance is justice.
[Both grunting]
Go!
He's gone.
Malcolm Merlyn will
never be seen again.
So, what's the play?
Trade her for Malcolm?
Ra's will not
make that deal.
Even for
his own daughter.
Laurel: What are
you doing with her?
She's a source of information...
And leverage.
I need the room.
Laurel: You're gonna torture
her to find out
where
Nanda Parbat is?
I need the room.
Everyone clear out.
Oliver, listen.
I know what you're doing
and I know why
you're doing it.
But you can't
save Thea's soul
at the cost
of your own.
Laurel was right.
I need to know where
Nanda Parbat is.
Was she also correct you intend
to torture me for that information?
No. Because we know
I won't have to.
You placed Sara's killer
under your protection.
Your every action
has been aimed
towards the frustration
of justice.
I will gladly
tell you
where to find
my home...
Because you
will die there.
It's like "Mission:
Impossible" in here.
Yeah, that's
the idea.
Make it impossible for
the League
to get the drop
on us.
I thought Thea got us
off their hit list.
Yeah, that was
before we put Ra's Al Ghul's
daughter in a box.
Taking prisoners now.
Isn't that crossing a line?
Actually, Oliver
has an entire prison
on Lian Yu.
Maybe I shouldn't
have told you that.
Nanda Parbat is hidden
beneath the Hindu Kush.
That was quick.
She wanted
to tell me.
Thinks I'm gonna
die there.
She's not
the only one.
I understand
facing Ra's
when you were doing
it for Thea, but--
I am doing it
for Thea.
Look, I may
not agree with it,
but I understand
what you're trying to say.
You don't want
Thea to live with the guilt
of getting her own
father killed.
But how is her
brother dying any better?
I don't
plan on dying.
That's what you said
the last time
you went to go
face Ra's,
and how did that
turn out for you?
Oliver, I'm about
as angry with you right now
than I've been with
anyone in my life,
but that doesn't mean
I want you going
on a suicide mission.
You're unusually quiet.
Yeah.
Guys, want to
give us a minute?
So, Thea
served up Merlyn.
You want to save her from
regretting that decision.
Yeah, I get it.
- But?
- But Oliver, I can't shake the feeling
that there's something
more at play here.
It's Thea.
Plain and simple.
Are you sure?
Right now,
it's the only thing
I am sure about.
[Keys clacking]
[Beeping]
What the hell?
Did you get
locked out of
the Palmer
Technologies server?
That's a shame.
You did this?
I just came from
a friend of mine
who has his head shoved so far
up his colon that--
and I'm pretty sure
this is true--
he's literally going
to get himself killed.
Him, I can't do
anything about.
You're a different story.
Great. Why don't you
tell me the story
while you unlock
the atom subroutine directory?
You have two
options, Ray.
Option one--
you can find a way to
break through the
encryption that I used
to lock up your server, which, by
my calculations,
will take you roughly
6.25 hours.
Or you can use that time
to eat a proper meal,
take a shower,
and get no less than
5 hours of sleep, at
the completion of which
I will
give you the password.
I see.
It's your choice,
but I highly recommend
option two, because
this whole situation
has gone from
endearingly eccentric
to creepily not ok.
If I had the energy,
I think I'd be getting angry right now,
but instead...I'll just
take option two.
That's a wise choice.
After your dinner
and a shower,
I am taking you
straight to bed.
Putting you.
[Whispering]
Why do I do that?
[John speaking
baby talk]
I didn't hear you
come in.
Why can something
so small
change the way you view
the entire world?
What did Oliver say?
Did you ask him?
Oliver has other
things on his mind.
Like what?
He's going
to Nanda Parbat.
Cheating death once
wasn't enough for him?
He's convinced he's
doing the right thing.
Is he?
You going with him?
Oliver has to do what's
right by his family.
I have to do
what's right by mine.
Is that why you didn't
go the last time?
Last time, I didn't go
because Oliver wouldn't let me.
And when you thought he died,
you blamed yourself.
I don't want to see you put yourself
through that again.
I can't stop Oliver
from going.
Then go with him.
You might have hung up
the uniform, Johnnie,
but you're still
a soldier.
Standing down while your
friend goes into battle
just isn't in your DNA.
Just get there and back
in one piece.
About that.
You think we could borrow
the A.R.G.U.S. jet?
Thea: What the hell
do you think that you're doing?
Roy told you?
Roy and Laurel.
They both think
that you're out of your mind.
Me, I know it
for sure.
I'm doing this
for you.
If your father dies
because of
something that
you've done,
there's a piece of you
that will go missing
and you'll never be
able to get it back.
That I can live with
but not you dying
because of me.
I am not gonna die,
and the only reason that
you think you can live
with Malcolm's death
is because
you don't really know
what it's like
to take a life.
You're a good
person, Thea.
Both of our parents
are dead because of me.
And that guilt...
That's something that
I have to live with.
I don't want that
for you.
No, please.
Please just don't go.
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
We got a Gulfstream
spinning up
at Starling City
Aviation.
I can't ask you
to come with me, Diggle.
You didn't ask me,
Oliver.
Besides, you don't own
a jet anymore.
Ra's: In 1854,
I encountered an illusionist
in Vienna,
and he was dazzling,
magnificent,
powerful,
and then nearly half
a century later,
I stumbled
upon this man again.
He was withered,
broken,
dying.
You see, a magician
can cheat
many things
except one.
Please.
I was your horseman.
Let me hunt for you
once more.
Allow me to prove
to you
my reborn loyalty.
Al Sa-Her, face
your death with honor.
Or at least dignity.
Please don't
do this.
There is a price
you must pay for your crimes
that can only be measured
in agony and blood,
but know I will take
no pleasure in this.
Take him away.
No.
No! No! No!
[Shower running]
Shut...Up.
Is this an actual
Van Go--ohh!
It's a Vermeer
actually.
I rotate the paintings
out here
with my collection
at Starling Museum.
Yeah. I'm really into the Dutch
Masters this month
for some reason.
You're very attractive.
I mean, they're.
- You were right.
- Hmm?
Food was delicious,
the shower was amazing.
Thank you
for insisting on it.
Well, a deal's
a deal.
Password's inside.
You didn't
have to
blackmail me.
I trust your judgment.
In fact, I pretty
much depend on it.
Well, that would make
you the only one.
You know, I can
be as obsessive and stubborn
as the next
billionaire,
but I do know the value of somebody
calling me on it,
telling me when
the emperor has no clothes.
Speaking of.
Heh.
Right. Uh...
You know what?
Sometimes, I forget
that we work together.
When I'm with you,
just you.
I don't think about work
or the mission or...
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
There it is.
Nanda Parbat.
Centuries old,
never taken by force.
Then why are we
doing this, Oliver?
[Cocks gun]
I mean, why are we
really doing this?
The League will have
sentries patrolling the area.
If they spot us,
we cannot let them get away.
Surprise is
our only advantage.
I'd say they've
spotted us.
What's your count?
6 on the south side,
probably another 4
on the east.
I don't want to go out
like Butch and Sundance,
so what's the plan?
Shoot straighter
than they do.
Cover me.
[Arrows whooshing]
If he gets to the fortress before
we do, we're dead.
He won't.
[Gunfire]
[Speaking Japanese]
One sniper on the roof.
[Gunshot]
They're A.R.G.U.S.
They work for Waller.
Waller?!
General Shrieve said
she wasn't involved
anymore.
Maybe that decision
didn't sit well with her.
We can't stay here!
Delivery truck.
That sniper will take us out
before we get there.
Toss me your gun.
I'll cover you.
Thank me later.
Give me your gun.
Maseo: Go!
I am the prisoner,
yet you look the more tortured.
By now, Al Sa-Her is
in the presence of my father.
His last hours will be
spent in agony,
begging for death.
That doesn't
please you.
I thought it would.
Having Merlyn to hate,
it's...
It's like a piece of Sara
that I can still hold on to,
but once he's gone...
So is another part
of her.
She would want
to be avenged.
Can you remember
the sound of Sara's laugh?
When Sara was
first brought before my father,
the moment he weighed
her apprenticeship or her execution,
she bore witness
to a demonstration of his power,
one that inspired terror
in all who had come before,
but Sara...
Laughed.
It was so innocent,
so genuine.
That was the moment
I fell in love with her, I think.
All I knew,
all I craved was to hear
her laugh once more.
Thank you.
[Speaking Arabic]
This place is humongous.
How do we find Merlyn
in all of this.
The nanites that
I tagged him with 4 months ago,
this can track them.
Down!
Thanks.
Oh, my God.
Oliver: Malcolm.
Help me get him down.
- No.
- What?
Trap. Trap.
[Clang]
Ra's: Mr. Queen,
welcome to Nanda Parbat.
John: Oliver!
Oliver.
Yeah. I tried that already.
Nothing's happening.
We need to get out
of here now.
Yeah. Save your
strength.
I have a feeling
we're gonna need it.
I'm not gonna let you
die down here.
I don't think
that's up to you.
I shouldn't have
let you come.
Also not up
to you, Oliver.
You don't understand.
I think I do.
You forget I know you sometimes
better than you know yourself.
Maybe you could have told me
I wasn't doing this for Thea
before we left.
You are doing it
for Thea...
But, yeah, you're right.
It's not just
about her.
You know, every time
I close my eyes,
all that I can see,
all that I can hear,
feel is...
just the fall.
I couldn't live
like that,
couldn't live knowing
that, uh...
There was someone
out there who beat me.
Yeah, that
makes sense.
No. It's egotistical
and insane.
So is putting on a mask
and jumping off of rooftops, Oliver.
To do that, you have
to be in a certain mindset.
Every soldier
on the battlefield, man,
has to believe
he's coming home.
Otherwise, he's
paralyzed.
Ra's got in your head.
What was the favor
you wanted to ask me?
I don't think now
is the right time.
We're not dead yet.
Now might be
the only time.
I always assumed
if I ever got married again
that Andy would be
by my side.
When I lost
my brother...
I never thought
I'd get another one.
So pretending
for a moment that
we aren't two dead men
chained to the floor...
How you feel about being
my best man?
I feel pretty good
about it.
[Loud thud]
[Door opens]
Oliver, it's time.
[Gunfire]
I counted at least
3 shooters.
Now!
Tatsu: Maseo!
[Screaming]
[Screaming continues]
Go! Get him out
of here! Go!
[Screaming]
Akio! Akio!
Akio!
Really starting to wonder why
I decided to come with you.
I told you I want
to show you
how I deal with the things that
you're going through.
[Sighs]
That's Michelle Vincent
and her son Rory.
He's 4.
Roy, why are you stalking
some random family?
They're not random.
That's them.
That's the police officer's
family?
I give them cash,
bring them groceries.
I even got Rory
a Boba Fett for Christmas.
Don't worry.
They don't know it's me.
You're torturing
yourself.
No. It helps actually.
It helps me
with the guilt.
Look. I appreciate
what you're doing here,
showing me this,
but the cop and Sara...
They're just not
the same thing.
You weren't any more in control
of yourself than--than I was.
I know, not when I
killed Sara,
but when I traded
Malcolm to the League,
when I let him
into my life,
I knew exactly
who he was,
what he was.
He taught me
how to kill.
Maybe I am a killer.
Maybe that's
the real me,
and I deserve
to be punished.
I don't
believe that.
I just tried to have
my father murdered.
Can you please just
take me home?
[Ray sighs]
[Whoosh]
I'm in no mood
for conversation.
You'll want to
hear this.
There's something that
I need to tell you.
I can't live
without you knowing.
The guilt is far worse
than anything you could do to me.
I lied to you.
And you believed it...
when I told you
that Malcolm killed Sara.
He wanted her dead
to put certain things
in motion,
but I am the one
who fired those arrows
into her chest,
and when I made the deal
to give up Malcolm,
I promised you
your vengeance.
[Beeping]
[Thunk]
So take it.
You tasted death,
and you wanted more,
but the truth is
everyone and everything
must come to an end,
even for one
such as me.
Kill me,
but spare
John Diggle's life.
Let him go.
I will beg for it.
You have shown
tremendous strength,
fortitude, power.
No, Mr. Queen,
I don't want to kill you.
I want you to take
my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man