Previously on Arrow...
Mr. Ramirez suffered
a traumatic hemothorax.
I'm recommending he be
transferred to a facility
that can provide
the care that he needs.
- Where's my dad?
- Have a seat.
He's gonna be okay,
but I need to tell you about it.
You wanna keep going,
or are you gonna testify?
We're leaving.
You've seen what having Felicity
in my life has done for me.
You deserve that same
kind of happiness.
I've located
the Heir of Ra's al Ghul.
- So, where are we going?
- Wherever you want.
It's up to me?
I'm the well-traveled man. I've been
every place in the world there is.
But you want to get out of here.
Because if the police know
you're alive, they'll come after you.
The Arrow, too.
Yes. If someone knew where I was,
it would be unfortunate
for both of us.
So, why did you reach out to me?
I don't want to hurt, or get hurt.
Never again.
I can teach you to be strong,
in heart and body.
I can teach you to protect yourself,
so, no one will ever hurt you again.
That's what every father
wants for his daughter.
Malcolm Merlyn's legacy lives on.
This is a new dawn.
Al Sa-Her was going to bestow on us
a new golden age,
and lead us into
the realm of Thanatos.
Yet for what greatness
Merlyn possessed in his soul,
he lost in his heart.
He swore that our great journey
would be nothing
without his blood legacy at our side.
And thus, before he gave up his life,
he made sure this journey
could not commence
until his beloved was ready.
Step forward.
I have to say,
the new uniforms do not impress me.
We've cleansed ourselves
of your father's sins
for our rebirth, which couldn't be
further from your fate,
daughter of the Demon.
I would so relish
slitting your throat, Athena.
One thing we have in common.
Except I've grown a taste
for the contemporary.
Such as plastic explosives.
Oh, my gosh!
You'd be in so much trouble
if your dad saw you doing that.
You're lucky
you have such a cool aunt.
You know,
who approves of bad behavior.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- I'm gonna miss you, too.
Just promise me that you're gonna
watch over your dad, okay?
But he is the Green Arrow.
You know,
before he was the Green Arrow,
he actually used to be
really afraid of the dark
and he needed a night light
in his bedroom till he was what, 16?
It was not a night...
It was not a night light.
I couldn't sleep
with it being pitch-black.
By the way, I did see that.
Go get a fork and a plate,
and get yourself
a reasonable slice of cake.
Yes!
Thank you for doing this.
It's actually pretty cool.
Why do you sound surprised?
I don't know.
I just thought that maybe,
you'd be a little more anti me going.
I'm the one who encouraged you
to go follow your heart.
I know, I know. It's just that,
now, that it's all real, I just...
I thought that maybe, you'd be like
a tad less supportive.
I'm completely supportive
of anything and everything
that makes you happy.
Speaking of which, I did tell Roy
that the two times that I shot him
with arrows would be nothing
compared to what would happen to him
if you end up unhappy.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- Yeah.
- I spy an overbearing big brother.
Again, no, no,
he's never been like that.
Never?
I know we've said it a million times
but we're gonna miss you,
we're really gonna miss you.
You guys have to come visit us
once we find where we're gonna land.
Where do we think
that's going to be?
We don't really know exactly,
but that's kind of the best part.
I mean, we're gonna figure it out
as we go along.
That's so spontaneous and romantic.
As long as we're together, that's
really all that matters, right?
So, how's your new roommate?
She's just as messy as my Laurel,
but surprisingly,
she's a better cook.
You trust her, Lance?
I'm not stupid, you know. I know
who she is, I know what she's done.
But she says
she's trying to get better,
and, well, that intel
she gave you last week on Diaz,
that panned out.
- Yeah. He still got away.
- Don't they always, though?
I'm sensing
a work conversation, so...
Where are we with the SCPD?
Well, Dinah and Curtis,
they are growing a list of
possible cops on the take,
but that could end up being
the least of our worries.
- How so?
- The DA's office refusal
to drop your case
without Roy's testimony,
that doesn't sit right with me.
And who's to say that the SCPD
is the only part
of the city's power structure
that Diaz has got his fingers in.
Yeah. Oliver,
you let me worry about Diaz.
You spend a little more time
with your sister
before she gets out of here.
And you think this guy's gonna
stop worrying about things
all of a sudden?
Well, ever since
he trusted me to take over.
If that's still on the table.
I'm gonna go, grab some cake.
You brought this up last week.
I don't know, man.
I thought we were clear,
you wanted out, I wanted in.
- Has something changed?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's just you and me.
And we don't know
what Diaz has, what he doesn't.
And bottom line, I don't think
that it should be just you.
This is definitely one of the jerks
who beat Roy to a pulp last week.
I wonder what food they're serving
at Thea and Roy's goodbye party.
Pizza, apps,
maybe like some mini-desserts,
that's this new thing.
Like you go to a party
and then they serve you
these desserts like mini-donuts,
and you just dip them in the sauce.
That would be reason enough
to crash a party,
not that I'm saying we crash a party.
I'm not expecting to be invited,
- but Felicity's my business partner...
- Curtis, focus.
We need to find out
how many of these cops are dirty.
- Well, Officer Hester makes ten.
- Yeah, and counting.
The more cops who are dirty,
the harder it is to believe
Captain Hill didn't know.
Who's next?
Nick Anastas.
More like hot Anastas. Wow.
Just because
you've the hots for him
doesn't mean
he's not on Diaz's payroll.
All his stats check out.
He doesn't have any influxes of cash
into his account,
or pressure points for blackmail.
Look, I'm just saying
you never mentioned to me,
that you worked
with such a hot police officer.
Not even once.
I guess I never noticed.
Yeah, just like you don't notice
beautiful sunsets and rainbows.
You just don't. You see, beauty is...
Hey, Z. How's school?
- Good. Hi, Dinah.
- What's up, Zoe?
Feeling like
some mac and cheese tonight?
- Again?
- Can you get sick of mac and cheese?
Definitely getting there.
- Come on.
- Going to my room to do homework.
You two seem to be
getting along well.
Yeah. It's almost nice, having
a little Munchkin around.
I'm sure Rene appreciates somebody
he trusts taking care of her.
Yeah, you know,
he should be starting rehab soon.
Hopefully, he'll be
back to normal ASAP.
- I really, really miss that guy.
- Me, too.
Hey, it's your boyfriend. Anastas.
Homicide, gotta go.
You keep digging. I got to find out
who at work I can trust.
He's not my boyfriend yet.
I'm on it.
I can't believe
we're actually doing it.
Yeah, I can't believe it, either.
Happily ever after.
Yeah, ever after.
- Okay, that wasn't so convincing.
- Hey, I'm thrilled.
I just... I don't wanna jinx it.
Okay, since when
do you believe in superstitions?
Well, ever since I met your brother,
there's not a lot I don't believe in.
Okay, now, I may believe it, too.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Please tell me you've packed
some weapon somewhere.
Follow me! Hurry!
Nyssa, what...
- What is going on?
- We need to move.
- What, are there more coming?
- Many more, these were the scouts.
They look like
the League of Assassins.
No, the League of Assassins
was disbanded, this can't be them.
Nothing stays dead forever.
Your father made sure of that.
Okay, well, I don't care.
I'm sorry, this is not me anymore.
I've nothing to do with this.
Like me, you are
an Heiress to the Demon.
That is something
you can never truly run from.
Hey, what happened?
- Thea, are you hurt?
- No, I'm fine, I'm okay.
I'm doing pretty fine myself,
thanks for asking.
They weren't even out of city limits
and they got attacked.
- It's because she jinxed it.
- Superstition played no part.
I hear you've taken my husband
as your own.
Yeah. Well,
we can talk about that later.
In the League, such talk would take
the form of mortal combat.
What the hell is going on?
Apparently, my dear old dad decided
to recruit some loyalists
- before Nyssa disbanded the League.
- For what?
To start his own. The Thanatos Guild.
Began hearing whispers
about them shortly
after we all returned from Lian Yu.
He couldn't have lived for long
considering he didn't
leave the island.
Moses never entered the Holy Land,
and yet, his legacy endured.
His second-in-command,
Athena, took charge.
A contemporary of mine, and a rival.
Her involvement alone suggests
a very dark purpose at work here.
Why would this Guild attack Thea?
Before Merlyn gave up his life,
he discovered a map that leads
to something ancient. Powerful.
I do not know what it is,
but I do know
that he yearned for Thea
to be at his side
when he unearthed it.
It's really funny
he never mentioned this.
Because he knew you were not ready.
Athena believes Thea to
either be in possession of the map,
or at the very least have knowledge
of its whereabouts.
Well, you have fun
on your treasure hunt, okay?
I told you, you cannot run from this.
Watch me, okay?
Roy and I are getting out of here
and back to our lives.
I need your help obtaining the map.
You cannot deny your father's legacy
any more than I can deny mine.
They will find you.
What do you want from me?
Merlyn had an associate in Star City.
If he shared the map's location with
anyone, it would've been with her.
You haven't spoken to her?
She does not care for me.
But she would not deny
Merlyn's daughter.
Okay, fine.
I'll go with you to talk to her,
we'll help you find your map.
And then, that's it.
I'm done for real this time.
Drug deal gone bad.
Very bad. The man was shot
over a dozen times.
Maybe he pissed off the competition.
I'll take it from here,
Lieutenant Drake.
Captain, this is
a drug-related homicide.
Isn't it a little below
your pay grade?
It's part of a larger
sting operation.
I wasn't aware of a larger...
You aren't aware because it's
above your pay grade, Lieutenant.
Well, we'll head back
to the station, then.
Hey. You can leave the evidence
with me.
Of course.
Now, I see why
you didn't want the boys to come.
That is Tigressa.
Looks like the only thing
she knows how to kill is vodka.
She has over 200 confirmed kills.
One of them being her own brother
because he matched her quote.
Al Ghul.
I should take your hand
for what you did to Al Sa-Her.
I never understood
your affection for Merlyn, Tigressa.
But I always respected it.
- This is...
- His spawn.
You think I wouldn't recognize
Malcolm's own blood?
Your father had much faith in you.
Yeah, well, but that new league
he created running around,
I can't say the same for him.
So, you've met Athena.
She is not the leader
your father desired. You are.
Yeah. Well, I'm sure death has
cured him of his disappointment.
Look, the only reason
why we are here is because
Athena thinks
I can open some map for her.
And with good reason.
Your father made sure
you were the only one
that could actually
unlock its secrets.
Of course, he did.
And that is why Athena needs you.
Your father secretted the map...
Here.
And why didn't you just take it?
I rejected the path of the League
of Assassins a long time ago.
One day, you're gonna have to tell me
how you did that. Thank you for this.
When you find it,
you may not be so grateful.
I was being polite.
We should contact your brother.
There's safety in numbers.
Overwatch, are you sure
we're alone here?
Yes, it's just the five of you.
No other souls for two blocks.
Copy.
Be cautious. Merlyn would have
laid traps to protect this place.
What kind of traps
are we talking here?
Are we talking Raiders
or Temple of Doom kind of traps?
- You okay?
- I will be once this is all over.
Yeah, me, too.
Get down!
A trap. Excellent.
- "Excellent"?
- We must be close.
Thermal imaging is showing
that what we're looking at
is what we've got.
No hallways, no doors.
Malcolm had a secret chamber
in his office.
He might have something here.
Clever.
Iodide diazonium.
A component magnetically attracted
to the same type of steel
my father used to encase relics.
Okay. That's not a map.
The map is inside.
It's an ancient League cipher.
- Does it need a code?
- Try my birthday.
Eighteen digits across,
three alphabets.
Okay, so, it's not my birthday.
Tigressa.
Guys, about you being
the only souls for two blocks.
Funny thing about those ninjas.
I want Al Sa-Her's daughter,
and the map.
I'm always merciful
when I get what I want.
I know you better than that.
Stand down. I'm not gonna ask twice.
Come with us,
and we'll let your friends
continue to draw breath.
Stay where you are,
and blood will be shed.
We'll go with shedding blood.
Except, it'll be yours.
Take this someplace safe. Go.
Exit's kind of blocked right now.
We can help with that.
You've had the same footwork
since you were eight years old.
Thea!
Held my own. Barely. Let's go.
Make your father proud.
Come with us.
Felicity, I know
you were wondering.
It's from Raiders... Kiss the floor.
I've got Thea and the map.
Let's move.
Here, let me help you.
Okay. God, that bitch
has a really powerful kick.
I think she might have broken
one of my ribs.
I assure you, that will be
the last time you have to face her.
Yeah, you'll get
no complaints from me.
This Athena doesn't seem like
the type who'd give up easily.
I intend to take the choice
out of her hands
by taking Merlyn's map far from here.
I know the toll
a father can have on a child.
Even long after he's gone.
This is my burden, not yours.
You didn't tell me that this
was the box from Hellraiser.
Take care of each other.
That was a lot easier
than I thought it would be.
Okay, wait. Now, how're you
gonna open it?
I'll find someone
who can unlock the cipher.
My people invented
mathematics after all.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Not this type of mathematics.
Wait. Look, you can't
go out there by yourself.
Not with Athena's assassins
looking for you.
She said that's what
she wanted to do, Thea.
- Yeah, it's not what I want.
- Speedy.
You made it clear
once I acquired the map,
you'd have no interest
in your father or the League.
And you made it clear that this map,
it leads, to what,
something ancient and powerful?
Okay, you cannot take this on
by yourself.
Plus, we have the world's
greatest mathematician right there.
And the protection
that you're gonna need
to keep that thing safe,
while you try to open it...
I appreciate the gesture.
Can you do it?
Well, in my experience,
anything locked can be hacked.
Usually, by me.
Thea, are you sure about this?
Nyssa's right.
You did say that you wanted
nothing to do with Malcolm's legacy.
I know, okay.
Look, I can't believe
that I'm even saying this,
but after
seeing those assassins, I...
This all just became too real.
Nyssa gave you an out.
I don't know why you don't take it.
I don't know how to explain it to you
right now, okay.
I just... I need you to trust me.
All right, you ready?
To go to prison for stealing
evidence? No, not really.
I'm doing the stealing,
you're doing the hacking.
Something tells me the police
don't make that distinction.
This could be the last time I'm here,
not as a suspect.
Okay, but how long
is this gonna take?
- My worry is 25 to life.
- Come on.
- Okay, keep watch.
- What!
I thought you said
no one else is gonna be here.
We are here, aren't we?
This might take a while.
Crap.
Come on.
This is police access only.
What're you doing here?
Nick Anastas! Hey!
- It has been a while.
- Do I know you?
Yes, of course. Curtis Holt.
We met through Dinah Drake.
She's my friend and your Sergeant or
Lieutenant, or was it just Detective?
Either way,
I'm meeting her here for dinner,
but I kind of got lost
in this new building.
I mean, I really haven't seen
this place since it was blown up.
I can give you a tour if you want,
while you're waiting
for Lieutenant Drake.
She usually doesn't show up
for her shift for another hour.
Totally Dinah. She's a major slacker.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Gotcha.
- Nyssa.
- Husband.
You got to stop doing that.
I do have a wife now,
and she doesn't like it.
But that's the fun of it.
Thea might want you to stay,
doesn't mean you have to.
The point about Felicity's utility
was well taken.
So was her point about wanting
nothing to do with Malcolm.
It's her life
and she must find her own truth.
I think her truth is a new life,
that she's earned.
She's earned your support for
her actions, whatever those may be.
I can understand why she would be
conflicted with Malcolm.
He was her father.
I am not conflicted. He was evil.
And Thea should not be charged
with righting his wrongs.
My father was also evil.
And I've dedicated the rest of
my life to righting his wrongs.
From what I understand,
you've done the same.
But my father asked me to.
With his dying wish, he asked me to.
Back on Lian Yu,
Merlyn gave up his life for Thea,
just as your father did for you.
I believe
Thea owes him the same debt.
Well, it is convenient for you
to believe that.
Because Thea gets you closer
to what you want.
So, do not pretend that
you're selflessly supporting her.
And never ever lecture me
on what I owe my sister.
- If you think I would...
- Nailed it!
I nailed it, I got it.
- You've unlocked the map?
- No.
Okay, so,
what do you mean by "nailed it"?
I figured out how to unlock
the Hellraiser cube,
but I just thought
you should do the honors.
You've heard of the
Fibonacci sequence, right?
Let's assume not.
Fibonacci sequence
is a mathematical pattern
dating back
to Pingala's formula in 450 B.C.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
When you said "ancient,"
you were not kidding.
I never kid.
Except where my marriage
is concerned, apparently.
The Fibonacci sequence.
Every number is the sum
of the two previous numbers,
so, finding the two starting ones,
that's the tricky part.
What are the starting numbers?
- Ten and thirteen.
- Is she right?
1013 was the year
the League was founded.
- And Malcolm's birthday.
- Okay, sit.
Try 10, 13, 23.
- Thirty-six.
- Fifty-nine.
Ninety-five.
- I was always good at math.
- That's right.
Hmm.
What does it say?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Why're you burning it?
She's heating it.
The League writes in hidden text that
can only be revealed through flame.
- You don't remember?
- I don't want to.
I don't know what's going on with
him, but just keep working on it.
- Why isn't the flame working?
- There's two possibilities for that.
Either Malcolm was using
a different type of invisible ink...
Or?
Or there's nothing on this
and we're wasting our time.
What's this?
I thought since old-school wasn't
working, I'd try some new-school.
The scanner can make
a 3-D voxel-based recreation.
I didn't start using a computer
until I was 25.
That explains a lot.
If I can duplicate the map digitally,
there might be some hidden markers
on there that we can trace.
- Sounds complicated.
- It is. Very.
So, it would be really great
to not be distracted, you know.
Very true.
I'll stay here to make sure
you remain uninterrupted...
- Sister-wife.
- Okay.
Okay, so, somebody is grumpy.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to be supportive.
But?
But I don't understand why you think
that this is your responsibility.
He died for me.
Okay? I don't know what it is,
but ever since
I found out about this, I just...
I feel like
I can't run away from it yet.
No, you see,
that's where we are different.
You see this
as us running away from something,
but I see this
as us running towards something.
Something way better.
You know just, I don't know.
I just feel like
recently, you've just been finding
any excuse you can
for us to stay here.
Unlike all my boyfriends in the past,
I do find it kind of cute
when you're being insecure.
I just don't wanna
lose you again, Thea.
That map is not my future.
You are.
I love a good old murder board.
Yeah. Feeling very Alan J. Pakula.
Sometimes, I forget
you're not Felicity.
Now, look. I know this has probably
already occurred to you,
but all Hill did was
take the evidence from your hands.
That's not necessarily proof.
Not to mention,
her name did not pop up...
- She's dirty.
- Are you asking me, or telling me?
You tell me if these drugs
are the same kind Diaz pushes...
If Hill took it off your hands,
that would be pretty damning.
And the fact that so much
of this department is so crooked,
would make a lot more sense
if it was rotten from the top down.
So, are they Diaz's drugs?
I don't know yet.
Maybe we should just try it.
Or we can read the analysis.
- Oh.
- What?
- It's Vertigo.
- Vertigo?
I heard of this back in Central City.
It's a hallucinogenic, right?
Yeah, but the good thing is that
this isn't Diaz's drug of choice.
- So, Hill is clean.
- Looks like.
You actually look disappointed.
Well, because it means
we're back to square one.
Yeah.
Thinking about
taking that thing with you?
One hundred percent no.
- You okay?
- Why wouldn't I be?
I mean, Roy only thinks
I'm gonna leave him
and a bunch of crazy assassins
that my dead dad organized
are trying to kill me,
so, my life is just great.
You know, Thea,
you don't have to do this.
You don't have to leave
everything to Nyssa.
Myself, and John and Felicity,
we will stop Athena.
You can go, you can live
your happily ever after with Roy.
Here, I thought
you were supposed to go live yours.
Felicity, she told me you stopped
being the Green Arrow.
Yeah, that was the plan.
Life interfered.
- John got hurt.
- He did.
But he's not hurt anymore.
I worry that he would be
in over his head,
going up against Diaz alone.
I don't think anything's
over John's head.
You might be right.
I don't know, I...
I gave it up because
I wanted to be a better father.
But William accepts the idea
that I'm the Green Arrow.
Plus, I don't want to give it up.
- I don't know why.
- I do.
Because being the Green Arrow
is what makes you feel complete.
For some reason, when you put that
hood on, it enables you
to become
the best version of yourself.
We're supposed to be
talking about you.
Maybe we are.
I don't know.
Maybe that's the reason why I can't
seem to give this life up. I...
I don't know, maybe I'm hoping that
somehow, I'll get the same thing,
and find the best version of myself,
whoever she is.
Athena's group of assassins,
found them.
- Where are they?
- Star City gas plant.
It holds the city's entire supply.
- At worst, they could blow it up.
- Why?
It's not their MO.
It is if they're using the plant
to leverage us
into giving up the map.
Clearly, Athena
doesn't know you very well.
Yeah, too bad it's not
Ollie's choice. It's mine.
You can't give in to them.
I can't let them hold the city
hostage, okay. This is still my home.
So, what, am I going alone?
Overwatch,
you have eyes on the Guild?
No, not yet, but I'm reading
a frequency spike,
which means
they just activated a bomb.
Athena's way of putting pressure
on our negotiations.
Fan out and find the bomb.
Multiple heat signatures.
Guys, they got you surrounded.
Head on a swivel.
- Where are the new assassins?
- Everywhere.
You want your map so bad? Come out.
Let's talk.
Perhaps your father taught you
some sense after all.
But you're mistaken if you think
that all we want is the map.
The map is meaningless
without spilling your blood.
You're really starting
to piss me off.
Your father spoke often
about you.
He was always ashamed
of your weakness.
Don't forget, guys,
we still have a bomb situation.
There's always a bomb situation.
I can trace the frequency root
of the detonator,
it is 17 feet to your right.
- Lead the way.
- Up.
Merlyn said
he tried to teach you to be strong.
- Clearly, he failed.
- I'm not my father.
This isn't working.
I know. It's a collapsible circuit.
I can freeze it.
I have done it before.
No! No, it's a mercury switch.
That will definitely set it off.
What do I do?
Short-circuit it.
I'm out of electricity arrows
right now at the moment, Felicity.
Green Arrow?
On its way!
Got it.
Woo! Nice work.
Thea!
You've lost. It's as clear
as your imminent death.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I know that you bleed. I win.
You don't want to do that.
Are you all right?
I learned a few tricks from Merlyn.
Wait. Where did she go?
That woman is hard to kill.
Were you really going to burn it?
To ashes.
The other assassins either fled
or they're wrapped up.
I really didn't miss those guys.
Speedy, the map.
They were being literal.
They needed your blood to spill.
That's definitely not "X"
marks the spot.
Where does it lead?
I believe I know where.
Nanolithography, the map
is printed with bacteria.
That's gross.
When exposed to the enzymes
of Thea's DNA, it reveals itself.
Ancient League secret?
No, no.
This is bleeding edge science.
This requires an atomic force
microscope. Leave it to Merlyn.
Nyssa, you said you know
what this map leads to?
These are ley lines.
Great. Ley lines. You've only seen
those with Damien Darhk.
These are different.
I thought they only intersected
on one place on Earth.
- Doesn't look that way from this.
- Indeed. These lines are global.
This suggests the existence of
three intersections
of a kind I thought
only existed on Nanda Parbat.
Right, but what only exists
on Nanda Parbat really?
I mean, besides really
depressing decor.
I know now why Merlyn called
his new league the "Thanatos Guild."
Thanatos
is the personification of death.
- In Greek mythology.
- Exactly.
I believe these lines suggests the
existence of three installments.
The three what?
Your father discovered the existence
of three Lazarus Pits.
Of course, he did.
Thea, come on.
Hey, Roy, just...
Let's give her some space.
Thank you, sir.
Officer.
Nick. Or should I just call you
"Officer" because we're at work?
Nick's fine. You're becoming
a regular around here.
Yeah, well, you know,
I just stopped by to...
See Lieutenant Drake.
To ask you out. To dinner.
Or drinks or like just coffee,
or we can just
walk down the street and talk...
- Yes.
- "Yes"?
- I get off work tonight at 7:00.
- Yeah.
So, should we say 8:00?
8:00 is awesome. 8:00 is perfect.
Yeah, I'll make reservations,
and I'll text you.
- Sounds like a plan. See you tonight.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- What're you doing here?
Getting back on the horse, D.
Back in the game, back in the saddle.
I'm gonna get really
right into... What's wrong?
I checked intake and evidence lockup
for any Vertigo-related cases.
- And?
- There aren't any.
Is that not a good thing?
There aren't any Vertigo cases
because they've all been kicked.
And the evidence released
by Captain Hill.
So, she's dirty. She did it for Diaz.
Ricardo Diaz is pushing Vertigo.
- Hey.
Look, I'm sorry
for storming out last night.
I just really needed some space, but
it really had nothing to do with you.
It's fine.
I'm just trying to figure out if you
packed that bag to come with me,
or Nyssa.
I mean, it's pretty obvious she wants
to destroy the new Lazarus Pits
just like she did
with the original one.
I mean, can you blame her?
What would happen if the League
or the Guild,
or anyone got their hands on it,
how dangerous that would be?
So, you are gonna go with Nyssa?
Look, last night,
Ollie and I were talking,
and we were talking about how when,
you know, he becomes the Green Arrow,
he feels complete.
And I was thinking that maybe
that's because when...
When he puts that hood on,
he gets to right our fathers' wrongs.
And maybe this could be my calling,
this could be
what I've been looking for.
So, you've made up your mind.
You know what,
so have I.
- I'm gonna go with you.
- What?
- No, no, you don't need to do that.
- Yes, I do.
I told you,
it doesn't matter where we go,
as long as we go together.
God, how did I get to be so lucky.
Hmm... I think it has something
to do with a stolen purse.
Please, just
be careful, all right?
And if you need anything,
or if you don't need anything,
just call me.
- Keep her safe.
- You know I will.
You drew them back into this, Nyssa,
that carries with it
a certain responsibility.
Thea is your sister
and the daughter of Malcolm Merlyn.
She's less in need of protection
than you think.
This is a Horchus dagger.
In the League of Assassins,
it symbolizes
the cutting of marital bonds.
I hereby annul our marriage.
Nyssa, as wedding gifts go,
this isn't half bad.
Be well, Oliver.
Well,
this is it.
Thanks for clearing
a few things out for me.
Of course.
- One more piece of advice?
- Sure.
If you're gonna wear the hood,
you shouldn't
string John along anymore.
I thought I was the one who gave
that wise sibling advice.
Nope. That has never been the case.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
You'll be with me the whole time.
Goodbye, Speedy.