Previously, on "Arrow"...
Malcolm: You've heard
of Votura?
Keeping the subject extremely
susceptible to suggestion,
or retaining no memory
of their actions.
I will tell Ra's--
he will still kill her.
She fired the arrow.
Amanda: The bio weapon is comprised
of two components.
The Omega she has is harmless without
its counterpart, Alpha.
I trust my father.
He explained to me
that every name
on that list
has a reason to be there.
A few years ago,
I found a message he left me,
explaining the list.
How was that possible? You were
on a deserted island!
I didn't say that
I found it on the island.
Chen Na Wei
has left Hong Kong.
We've tracked her here.
Where are we--
Welcome home, Mr. Queen.
Did you learn all this
in nine months?
Malcolm's
a good teacher.
[Grunts]
Did he teach you to cheat?
There's
no such thing.
There's only
survival and death.
He's not wrong.
This is good.
What is it?
If I told you
what it was,
you probably
wouldn't eat it.
Is it weird?
You know,
being back here with me?
Well, I've been
back here before.
You know,
in a lot of ways,
this place reminds
me of who I am.
Or, I guess...
who I've become.
It's probably why
Malcolm suggested we train here.
It's kind of cool
that we're here, though.
It's like there's really
no more secrets
between us anymore.
Yeah.
When you were here...
Did you ever think you were
going to see us again?
Get home again?
Chen Na Wei touched
ground in Starling 24 hours ago.
We're still trying to determine
how she made it
into the country,
but we believe she's here
to auction off
the Omega bio weapon
to the highest
bidder.
The Omega's inert without
its counterpart.
Who's going to pay
for a useless super virus?
Rogue nations.
Terrorist groups who believe
they can replicate
the Alpha component on their own.
Why did she have
to sell it here?
There's a corporate
executive in town.
A man on
the Triad's payroll.
He's committed several acts of
industrial espionage
for them over
the years.
His name
is Peter Kang.
Yeah, I know him.
He works
at my family's company.
That guy came
to my house for Christmas.
And, that, Mr. Queen,
is exactly why
you and Mr. Yamashiro
are still alive.
Chen Na Wei chose the one
place on earth where your
continued breathing is still
of use to me and my superior
But have no illusions--
if you threaten
to compromise the mission
by contacting anyone
in Starling City,
I will remove you and Mr. Yamashiro
from the equation,
along with anyone who
discovers Oliver Queen is still alive.
Tracker's in place.
Now what?
Follow Kang
to Chen Na Wei?
No, she's too smart to keep
the Omega on her person.
She'll keep it in a secure
location till the auction.
We'll need
to figure out
where that auction's
going to be.
Kang's on the move.
[Country music playing]
Laurel. Hey.
What you having, sweetheart?
Next round's on me.
Your desk sergeant
called,
wondering why
you weren't on duty.
Yeah. Ah, well,
this is Laurel.
You know,
the daughter that lived.
Is there a bartender
in the city
that doesn't
already know that?
Well, excuse me for seeking
a sympathetic ear.
Takes more than some
fancy corporate law firm job
for some of us to get
over Sara's death.
I love you, so I'm going to pretend
like you didn't say that,
and I'm going
to drive you home.
Not now, sweetie.
Not now. No, please.
Hit me again, Frank.
[Laughs]
[Quentin sighs]
Later, Frank.
I'm sorry
for all the trouble.
Kang's headed inside.
Maseo: A.R.G.U.S. has detected
bursts of data emanating
from Kang's
office computer.
But it's protected by
SHACAL-4 encryption.
Ok, pretend
for a second
like I don't know
what that is.
It means we can't hack
into Kang's computer.
You'll need to get directly on to
the Queen consolidated network.
Maseo, Waller was pretty clear what
would happen to people
if they found out
I'm still alive.
So taking a stroll through
my family's company
is probably not
the best plan.
You'll go in at night. I don't
have time to familiarize myself
with the office floor plans.
Oh, my God.
Who is that?
That's my sister.
Sara...
Hey.
[Gasps] Hi.
- Are you ok?
- Yeah, why?
You kept saying Sara's name.
Oh. Um...
Yeah, well,
I was dreaming.
Why didn't you tell me?
What?
That Sara died?
Laurel told me.
Kind of by accident, but...
Well, I didn't want
to upset you,
and Laurel didn't want
anyone to know.
Why?
After everything that
happened with Slade,
Sara went back
to the League of Assassins.
She had her own
secrets, Thea.
And...
Uh...
Those weren't
my secrets to share.
Was it the League
that killed her?
Where are you going?
I'm going to...
Take a walk,
clear my head.
[Twisting combination lock]
Slade.
I told myself I wasn't
going to come down here.
That I never needed
to see you again.
You'll be happy
to know I was wrong.
Slade: You think
I won't get out of here?
You think I won't kill
those you care for?
Well, I keep
my promises, kid.
I keep my promises!
Thea!
♪ Arrow 3x14 ♪
The Return
Original Air Date on February 18, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Thea: Hey!
The fire went out.
Ollie, what is it?
We need to get off the island.
We're in danger.
What are you
talking about?
- Slade Wilson's here.
- Ollie, that is ridiculous.
It's not. Listen to me.
Slade was--
I was keeping him
prisoner here!
What do you mean, "was?"
[Cell phone beeping]
Malcolm: Hello, Oliver.
You let him out!
You told me you lost
your duel with Ra's
despite your willingness
to kill him
because
you hesitated.
For you and Thea
and even myself
to have any hope of surviving
the next encounter,
you need to regain
that killer instinct
born of a primal
need to survive.
You're sick.
[Scoffs]
Your SAT phone
is going to stop working
after this call.
Ollie!
Merlyn set Slade loose
as an object lesson.
That's insane!
He thinks it'll help me
regain my killer instinct.
If he doesn't
kill us first!
Come on.
The last time I saw her,
she was in pigtails.
Where is she going?
Hi, Ollie. Dad.
Stopped by the office today.
Saw mom talking to Walter.
Starting to think that something's
happening there.
But I don't know...
Queenie.
Your sister's boyfriend?
I--I don't know.
You got my delivery?
You have some of that
inheritance of yours?
Tommy: What
the hell is this?
What are you
doing here, Tommy?
About to ask Jordan
the same thing.
Just paying the family
my respects.
Yeah, and so you did.
Now you're going to stay
away from her permanently.
- Whatever.
- Mm-hmm.
You should be
bringing flowers here,
not looking to score drugs!
What are you even
doing here, Tommy?
I came to thank you
for my birthday card.
And to tell you that
my party tonight's 21 and over.
Well, I think we both know
that that's not true.
Oh, it is. As far
as you're concerned.
You shouldn't
grow up too fast.
Yeah, well,
you're not my brother.
You're right,
no, I'm not.
But I think about him every
single day.
For the first time,
I'm glad he's gone.
'Cause seeing you
like this would break his heart.
[Scoffs] It's funny how Ollie seems
to care more about me
now that he's dead
than he did when he was alive.
Every time I spoke
to his grave,
it always felt
so empty.
That's 'cause he was here
watching over you.
Why did you
bring me here?
To get something we need.
I thought you were
better with a bow.
I am. It's for you.
Just in case.
What is it?
- - He's been here.
[Grunts]
Ugghhh (Crashing)!...
Nice to see you again...
Ms. Queen.
[Gasps]
You ok?
Yeah.
She's unhurt.
I have no desire
to kill either of you.
This time tomorrow, two bodies
will be found in Starling City,
burned beyond
any recognition.
With ample evidence
that Oliver and Thea Queen
have been killed in some
horrible accident.
I'm going to leave you, kid,
the same way you left me.
Alone in Purgatory.
You leave me,
and you let my sister go.
You're lucky I didn't
bury her next to Shado.
Did he tell you about her?
Shado...
Is the reason why
this is all happening.
Why I killed your mother.
He doesn't need to.
I figured out
you're a sick son of a bitch,
all on my own.
Well, of course
he didn't tell you.
Your brother
likes his secrets.
You always have.
That's who you are.
You know, maybe if you told me
what really happened with Shado,
your mother would
still be alive.
- That's enough!
- I agree!
Welcome home, kid.
Slade...
Slade!
Maseo: Are you
in position?
Yeah.
The company
computers are protected
by biometric
encryption.
Look for
a fingerprint reader.
Ok, but why wouldn't they
take me out of the directory?
Why would they?
You're dead.
[Beep]
Yeah. I'm in.
The crawler's programmed to seek out
all of Kang's network traffic.
And it's running.
The program should
take 90 seconds.
What's that?
Maseo: Oliver,
you have to go.
I'm not done.
[Elevator dings]
You have to go.
Someone's coming.
You're cute.
It's too bad you're,
you know, dead.
Which is obviously a lot worse,
for you than it is for me.
[Sighs] I really
need to learn
to stop talking to myself.
According to the information
we took off Kang's computer,
the auction is tonight.
In four hours.
Amanda: Where?
They're still
working on that.
The crawler program
retrieved
2.7 gigabytes of data.
It's taking some time
to crawl through.
You have less
than four hours, apparently.
Where's Queen?
Probably went to check
on our weapons.
♪ You spin my head
right round ♪
♪ right round, when you go down,
when you go down now ♪
♪ you spin my head
right round ♪
Ah. Thanks, Bud.
[Spits]
Yeah, no problem.
Bud.
Nothing like
a rich kid's party
to remind me of what I miss
about being shot at in Afghanistan.
When I hooked up my
big brother with his first stateside job,
I somehow expected
more gratitude and less complaining.
Oh, less complaining.
You sound like Lyla.
You should have
never divorced her.
You big dummy.
Thank you, Andy,
I appreciate that.
♪ You spin my head right
round, right round ♪
♪ when you go down,
when you go down now ♪
♪ you spin my head
right round, right round ♪
Tommy: Do you
like Sushi?
Have you ever had anyone
eat some off of you?
I promise not
to use chopsticks.
Laurel: Are you still
using that line?
Well, it looks like
I scared her off.
Tommy: Oh, that's all right,
she's vegan, anyway.
What are you doing here?
I heard you decided to go
corporate in San Francisco
instead of saving the world
in Starling City.
I realized that maybe the world
can't be saved.
What is it?
I just don't
believe who's here.
Queen.
I thought I told you
this party is 21 and over.
No worries.
I came prepared.
Fake ID.
Laurel, how are you?
I'm handling.
How's school?
Straight "A"
student.
I'm going to go
grab a drink.
Not alcoholic,
I swear.
[Chuckles] Not.
Queenie.
Isn't this past
your bedtime?
Maybe I just need a little
something to keep me awake.
You holding?
[Toilet flushes]
Stay away
from Thea Queen.
Who the hell do you think...
Holy crap.
You're Oliver Queen.
You're supposed to be dead.
People are going to believe--
Stay away
from my sister.
How'd you like
to be dead again?
[Neck cracks]
[All murmuring]
How many people
are in this prison?
Maybe there's somebody
we can call for help?
Well, Slade
killed the guard.
There's one
other inmate.
He's not going
to be helpful.
Then how are we supposed
to get out of here?
This is a Chinese prison retrofitted
by eight A.R.G.U.S. technicians.
There is no getting
out of here.
So what, we're just supposed
to sit here and starve to death?
That's your plan?
I am working
on a plan.
[Sighs]
What did he mean?
- What?
- Wilson.
When he said that you were
still hiding something.
[Sighs] He's insane.
Yeah, I picked up on that.
I also picked up on how
you reacted when he said
that you were
keeping secrets from me.
Was he telling the truth?
I don't think that this is
the right time.
Actually, I think time is something
that we have a lot of right now.
Why didn't you
tell me about Sara?
- Come on, Thea...
- No, now that I know
about your secret, everything has become
a whole lot clearer.
And I can tell when you're hiding
something from me.
Like you are doing right now.
So what is it going to take for you
to stop treating me
like this tiny,
fragile, little object?
Tiny?
What?
This prison,
these...
Cells,
they were made for men.
Fully grown men.
Come here.
[Sighs]
I never thought I would wish
for longer arms.
There's a way
that we can do it.
But it's going
to hurt.
[Sighs]
Just do it.
All good. On three.
1, 2...
3.
[Grunts]
[Groaning]
All right.
Come on.
Up, up, up,
up, up, up, up.
[Groaning]
[Beep]
[Grunting]
Ok.
That's good.
Come here, come here.
All right.
Malcolm would
have told Slade
about the plane
we used to get here.
It's how he plans
to get back to Starling.
[Sirens in distance,
police radio chatter]
Anybody see
who Peter Pan'd him?
Well, a few
witnesses saw someone
head upstairs a few minutes
before it happened.
Male, white or Hispanic,
twenties or thirties.
That narrows it down.
Maybe it's a vigilante doing
some public service.
[Scoffs]
Thea, right?
Yeah.
Aren't you a little
young to be at a party like this?
I invited her.
Oh, well,
you spoiled billionaires
sure know how to throw
yourselves a party.
You got underaged girls,
you got drug dealers,
you even have
dead drug dealers.
If I had have known
he was here,
he never would have made
it past the front gate.
We had a lot of crashers
here tonight.
Yeah, right. I can see that.
What are you doing here?
They asked us to stay
and give statements.
No, I mean,
at this douchebag's party.
Tommy, I'm sorry--
Wow, you really have
a thing for these rich
bad boys, don't you?
I mean, you think
maybe, just maybe,
one of 'em getting
your sister killed
would have gotten
you cured of that.
Dad!
And what about you,
sweetheart?
Dressed like that. It's funny;
I can't figure out
if you're following in your brother's
footsteps or my dead daughter.
Dad, you know what--
I'm just observing how
one little boat trip
can turn everyone's
life to crap.
Laurel: That is enough!
We're leaving.
Right now.
Well, thank you
for that.
I'm sorry,
was I embarrassing you?
No. Yourself.
At least I know who I am.
And I'm not becoming
someone I'm not.
Hanging around with
billionaire playboys
like some kind of
gold digger?
Taking on a sell out job
in San Francisco.
Is that what
this is about?
When Sara died, you said you wanted
to go to law school
'cause you wanted to make
the world a better place.
Wethersby Posner
is one of the most
prestigious firms
in the country.
You said you wanted
to help people.
All you'd be doing there
is helping fat cats get fatter.
You know, maybe this
sermon would have
a little bit more
credibility
if you weren't
so lit right now.
Well, I don't need
to be sober
to see what you're doing
with your life.
I just wish you could, too.
What were you
thinking?
Anyone at that
party could have seen you!
Yeah, I pulled the hoodie
down to cover my face.
That disguise
wouldn't work
even if you smeared
grease paint all over your face.
So, what, you came
to chastise me at gunpoint?
We got the auction location from
the scraper program.
Kang's using a defunct steel factory
owned by your family's company.
I--I don't care.
I'm done with the mission.
- Oliver...
- No, coming back here,
Maseo, has shown me all the wreckage
that I have left behind.
And if I go with you tonight
and I get killed,
then I lose any chance
I've ever had
of fixing all of the things
that I broke.
You don't have that chance!
Waller will kill you--
My family's resourceful; We
have connections in the media.
There has to be a way
to shelter us
from whatever Waller does.
Look, Oliver,
if you want redemption,
start with all the lives Chen Na Wei's
bio weapon could end.
Those people
are strangers to me.
These people...
They're my friends
and my family.
And they will be ashamed of this
selfish choice you're making.
They're already ashamed of me.
Good-bye, Maseo.
[Starts engine]
Hey! Wait, I think
I found a path.
Thea?!
Stop!
[Groaning]
What the hell was that?
It was a booby trap.
What kind of psycho
would put that thing there?
[Groans] Me.
Oh, God.
Ahh!
[Both groaning]
Slade's going to be at the plane.
We need to move.
No, no, no, we need to rest,
we need to rest,
just a few minutes, ok?
Slade gets to--
He will kill us both
if you end up passing out, ok?
Ok, ok, ok.
Couple minutes.
[Groaning]
Why didn't you
tell me about Sara?
Oh, come on.
Every time I bring her up,
you end up evading it.
Because this
isn't the time.
We just need to focus.
Well, I'm not, ok?
Knowing that you're keeping
something from me--again--
it's keeping me everything
but focused right now.
So tell me.
Malcolm killed Sara.
No.
No, he was in Corto Maltese
with me, ok?
He didn't
kill her directly.
He used someone.
He put them under
the influence of a drug...
So she wouldn't know
what she was doing.
She?
She who?
You killed Sara.
[Gasping]
Oh, God.
No, Sara? No, she--
she was my friend!
How could you not tell me?!
Because
you weren't you.
Oh, God.
You had no control
over your actions.
You cannot
blame yourself.
You were right
about Malcolm, ok?!
He doesn't love me!
I'm an idiot.
No, you're not.
This whole thing
with Lian Yu.
This is ridiculous!
And what the hell
are we even doing here?
I ask myself
the very same question...
over and over.
Slade...
Don't.
Oh, yeah.
You've come a long way.
[Both grunting]
I have yet to make good
with my promise, kid.
[Thea grunting]
[Beeps]
Hello, Oliver.
I told myself I was
recording this message
in case I died suddenly,
but I wonder
if it isn't just easier
to say what I have to
say to a video camera.
I'm not the man
you think I am, Oliver.
I didn't save our city,
I failed it.
I did something
terrible,
and in my efforts
to make it right,
I ignored my conscience and
made alliances with terrible people.
There's a book.
A book with a list
of all their names.
And with these people,
I always told myself
that everything I did,
I did for my family.
That's a lie.
Because what good
is a family
without a soul?
You can right
my wrongs.
You...
Can be better
than I was.
You can save this city.
I love you.
Thank you all
for coming.
I promise that
for one of you,
it'll be well
worth your time.
You've read the briefing.
With the proper resources,
you can own...
Armageddon.
[Camera shutter clicking]
The bidding will begin
at $50 million.
55?
Do I hear 60?
I have $60 million.
Going once,
going twice...
Man: 90 million.
Anyone care to make it
an even hundred?
[Sighs]
Just a moment.
I don't like
uninvited guests.
[Speaking Chinese]
I'm sorry I'm late.
Actually, you were
right on time.
Let's go.
Make the call!
Find me the Yamashiros.
They die tonight.
You have a choice to make.
What choice?
Whether or not you want
to keep your hand.
Come on, then.
You've earned it.
- Thea, don't!
- He killed mom!
And he will continue to pay
for his crimes,
but not like this!
You're not a killer!
Yeah, tell that to Sara!
What happened to
Sara is not on you!
What happens to him is!
All this is what
Malcolm wanted.
He freed Slade
to prove that we're killers
because he wants you
to be just like him.
You got to prove to
him that you're not.
[Groaning]
[Gunshot]
Slade: A flesh wound.
You're clearly not the killer
that your brother is, Thea.
Yeah, I wish
that were true.
She's lost,
your sister.
No, she's not.
You can see it
in her eyes.
She's being touched
by darkness.
Was it Merlyn?
He's an interesting man to do that
to his own daughter.
So now you've lost
your father,
your mother,
and now
your little sister.
How's the girl
with the glasses?
What's her name?
Felicity.
[Grunts]
How many people can
Oliver Queen lose
before there is no
more Oliver Queen?
Thanks
for the trip home.
Have a nice flight
back to Hong Kong.
I'm afraid it's not
that simple, Mr. Queen.
The hell it's not.
You have the Omega.
You have Chen Na Wei.
It's over.
I'm sorry to say, that's not up
to either one of us.
This him?
General Matthew Shrieve.
You've done your country
quite a service today,
Mr. Queen.
That said,
I've got some news
you're not going
to want to hear.
Well, General, I'm used
to that by now.
We're going to need
to debrief you.
Back in China.
Once that's accomplished
and the Omega's secured,
I'll make sure you go any place
in the world you want to go.
Sound fair?
[Laurel laughs]
Tommy Merlyn.
Are you stalking me?
Just checking on you.
Things with your
father seemed, uh,
they seemed tense.
Your roommate
told me
you were taking
a job here.
I said that
couldn't be true,
that you were going
to work for a white shoe firm.
Ah, I was.
And then someone reminded me
why I became a lawyer in the first place.
You want to tell me
about it over dinner?
Hey, hey, hey,
it is just dinner.
How many girls have you used
those three little words with?
Those are the only three
little words I say.
Fine.
Just dinner.
- Let's go.
- Maybe drinks.
- Maybe.
- Ok.
Dad.
I didn't know that you were
going to be here.
Where else would I be?
Got to think about a way
to tell your mom about this.
Um...
She already knows.
You weren't worried
about her heart giving out, then.
You know, if you were going
to drink tonight,
you would have
done it by now.
Really?
Are you going to get your mask
and your Billy club
and take it away
from me, huh?
- Black Canary?
- Dad!
When does your shift start,
huh? Shouldn't you be
running around
on rooftops by now?
Hey! Do you remember
when I was going to take
that corporate job in San Francisco?
Do you remember
what you said to me?
You were mad because I wasn't
choosing a life
where I was going
to help people.
It's like you knew.
Already, even then.
You knew that my life was always
headed towards that mask.
Do you think that's what
I'm all torn up about?
The reason why I want
to open up this bottle
and want to crawl inside it is because
of what you did to us.
I loved your sister,
I loved your mom.
So much like each other,
and you know, these wild spirits.
But you and I,
we had something more,
'cause we were the ones
that were alike.
And we had a trust
and we had a bond,
and you broke it.
And I don't know
how you could do that to us.
Look, I'm going
to survive this.
I mean, I got to,
it's my baby girl.
But what you've done,
I don't know how
I'm going to live through this.
Daddy, I think we should
go to a meeting.
Yeah.
I'll go to the one
on Broxton.
You go to the one on Fourth.
[Thea inhales and exhales]
I need a shower.
I need ten showers.
Thea.
I'm fine.
I would be really,
really worried
if that were true.
What do you want
to hear?
Nothing.
And I don't want you
to tell anyone about this,
especially Laurel.
And why is that?
Because she loves you
like a sister,
and it would hurt
the both of you too much.
Does she know
about Malcolm?
No.
No, that would
complicate things,
and despite everything
that he has done...
We still need him.
Malcolm: I agree.
I guess A.R.G.U.S. is
looking for a few guards
to volunteer
for island duty.
You almost
got us killed.
I simply had more faith
in you and my daughter
than you obviously
have for yourselves.
How could you
do that?
To challenge you,
to see if you both could work--
How could you
make me kill a friend?
He should not have
told you that.
I trusted you.
I let you
into my life.
How could you have
done this to me?
Because you are my daughter,
Thea, and I care about you.
Oh, God,
that's sick.
And not even
remotely true!
You do not understand
the danger we face
from Ra's al Ghul!
Just stop!
Stop using him as an excuse.
The only person that I'm afraid of
right now is you.
- Please, do not do this...
- Please, stop.
I will work with you
to stop Ra’s.
Because that's what my brother
says we need to do.
So I will be
your student.
I'll be your partner.
Even if I have to,
I will be your soldier.
But never again will
I be your daughter.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg, move you head!