Previously on "Arrow"...
Got an ID
on your not so secret
but very crazy admirer.
Carrie Cutter.
She's former SCPD.
Love is a bullet
in the brain.
My hero!
I'm Cupid, stupid.
And if I don't help you?
I think I made it
abundantly clear
you don't have
a choice.
Are you working
for Damien Darhk?
I did what I had to do
to keep you safe.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
And who's William?
He's my son.
Oliver, we need
to talk.
I can't do this.
Felicity.
Oh, my God.
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
♪ Let me call you sweetheart ♪
♪ Keep the love-light glowing ♪
♪ In your eyes so true ♪
♪ Let me call
you "Sweetheart" ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
Whatever you're
thinking of doing,
you don't have to.
Just let us go.
We won't tell anyone.
No one. Absolutely
not, right?
Wonderful.
Agreement...
the mortar that holds
together the bricks of love.
So how much
do you love each other?
With everything that I have.
And the missus?
How much does she love
her mister?
More than anything
in the world.
How sweet...
and pathetic.
Wh--what?
Love is a bullet
to the brain...
or an arrow to the heart.
♪ Arrow 4x16 ♪
Broken Hearts
Original Air Date on March 23, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Please be seated.
First I'll hear the parties
on the question of bail.
Your honor,
the, uh, defendant wishes
to waive bail so that
the, uh, court can focus
its attention on our
motion to dismiss.
Your honor, the defendant
was apprehended
at the site of
a child abduction.
Because he
was being held captive
himself. Your honor,
these documents will confirm
my client's identity as
Kenneth Bender,
citizen of Markovia.
Your honor,
this is ridiculous.
The defendant's
name is Damien Darhk
According to whom? You?
Oliver Queen?
The media? Heh.
Your honor,
there's absolutely
no evidence whatsoever
to suggest that my client
is this Damien Darhk,
much less prove beyond
a reasonable doubt
that he committed
these acts
that Damien Darhk is
even accused of.
Your honor, we have
evidence,
and we will present it
at trial.
During which time what?
My client just rots
in jail?
I mean, fortunately,
he's no longer
in Markovia, right?
Because, you know,
in America, we...
We have preliminary
hearings to determine
whether the state can meet
its burden of proof.
Thank you, your honor.
Your honor--
You say you
have evidence, Ms. Lance?
Get ready to present it.
Mr. Darhk or Mr. Bender
or whatever
he's calling himself
is hereby remanded
to the custody
of the Department
of Corrections
to be held until disposition
of defendant's motion
to dismiss.
I worked out
a system to maximize
the efficiency of
the moving process.
The densest,
heaviest boxes are
put into the moving
truck first,
creating a solid
foundation
for the rest of
the boxes
and providing
maximum recovery time
during the most physical
moments of moving.
There's, um...
less chance for injury, too.
I hired a mover.
And I would never want
to step on the toes
of professionals,
but proper distribution
of the mass and density
of the boxes
inside the moving truck
could have
cost-saving effects for
the moving company
in the form of
improved gas mileage.
OK. Great.
So you're doing
great with the--
It's just amazing
how much progress
you've made in such
little time.
Paul must be just
a physical therapy
genius.
Yes, like a symphony
of the talents.
You know, with Curtis
and Paul, they're kind of
the perfect team.
You know, marrying tech--
Poor choice of words.
My bad. My specialty.
It's OK.
That's fine. I--
it's, you know,
it's not like, um,
I don't know what
it's like.
We were engaged, and now
we're not together.
That's what it's like.
Did you cancel
the venue? Please?
I'm--yes, I will
get around to
canceling the venue.
Great. Thank you.
And I will uninvite
the guests.
OK.
The movers
will swing by
whenever you want.
Just give them
a call.
I'll see you when
I see you.
So tonight, hmm?
Tonight?
Yeah. Tonight I, uh--
I mean, I guess we
didn't talk about it,
but I was a part of the team
before we were together.
I just assumed...
Oh, tonight. Like,
to--like to--
like every night.
Um...
Of course.
You are a part of
the team
forever and always.
Keep moving.
Stop here.
This is it.
Now that
you've found what
you're looking for,
you don't need us.
So we can just--
No. This isn't the end,
Mr. Queen.
It's the beginning.
Of what?
I grew up in a small
village in Africa.
a country whose named
has changed a dozen times
over the years.
One day, bandits came
to my village.
They wanted water
and gold and women.
Once they left with them,
the only thing remaining
of my village was ash.
My home and everyone I loved
was wiped from the earth.
And I was helpless
to stop it.
And I swore I would never
feel helpless again.
So killing all the people
you're holding hostage is
gonna help you not
feel helpless?
How does that make you
any different than
the people
who destroyed your
village?
Oh. It makes me
very different.
Let me show you.
How'd it go
out there tonight?
It was quiet.
Yeah. The City hasn't
had a quiet night
in 4 years.
Yeah. I can't
believe HIVE is silent
just because
Damien Darhk is in jail.
Not for long.
What are you
talking about?
The law's pesky need
for evidence.
The ghost who took
William also took
their cyanide
escape plans.
There's no one to testify
against Darhk.
What about my brother?
You mean the one
that was declared
legally dead
5 years ago? Oh...
should be fun
walking him into court.
Uh, what about us?
Yeah!
Damien kidnapped us
over the holiday.
- We're all witnesses.
- Actually that's good.
The fiancee to the City's
beloved mayoral candidate,
it makes
for a compelling story.
What's wrong?
Oliver and I aren't
engaged anymore, um,
or living together
or together together.
Felicity.
It's fine, which is
universal code
for "I don't want to
talk about it."
The pieces of
Darhk's idol. Yeah.
How you holding up?
Felicity tell you guys?
How are you
holding up?
Is this about
your son?
The fact that I lied
to her about him, yeah.
Yeah, well, you got
a kid, man,
that's a whole lot
to handle.
But don't worry.
She'll come around.
Give her time.
I mean, she wants
to stay on the team.
That's a good sign...
I think.
Hey, Lance
just called.
It's trouble.
HIVE?
Said it was an old friend.
Uh, you guys take five.
Hey. You OK?
You're a little--
little more grim than usual.
You said, "We know
who did this."
Look familiar?
Cupid!
She's supposed to be
in custody at ARGUS.
Yeah? Tell that to them.
What was there?
Left a note for us.
"Love is dead."
So is nobody else
gonna say it?
It's Cupid, stupid.
Well, she's changed
up her MO a little:
"Love is dead."
Oh! Maybe she's
not so insane after all.
Thought she was locked up
in some ARGUS sub-basement.
Yeah. Not anymore.
I just talked to Lyla.
Turns out Waller was
serious about prisoners
like Cupid working their
way off of Task Force X.
She's out.
Then we start
with her victims.
Did CSU ID them?
They're running
prints.
Like, seriously?
None of your crime tech guys
read gossip web sites?
Uh...heh heh.
Let's assume they don't.
This is Blaine, and
this is Shannon.
OK.
Really, guys? Come on.
It's the wedding
of the decade.
Why would Cupid
want to ice Star City's
most high profile couple?
Well, we figure
that out, we figure out
who her next targets
might be.
How do we know
there's gonna be a next target?
I don't think that
Carrie Cutter
has changed
that much.
We got to get to court.
I'm gonna stay here,
work up some leads
on Cupid.
It was
an Oliver Queen
campaign holiday party.
There was gunfire.
The security that we had
onsite was killed.
And then he walked in.
Let the record
reflect that
the witness is pointing
to the defendant.
And why did the defendant
walk into Oliver Queen's
campaign office?
He was the leader
of the gunmen.
He took myself,
Thea Queen,
and Felicity Smoak
hostage.
And while
you were held hostage--
Damien Darhk--
or whatever
he calls himself--
was there calling
the shots
the entire time.
Pass the witness.
This, uh, holiday party,
were you, uh...
were you there
as a guest?
No, sir.
I work security--
personal security
for Mr. Oliver Queen.
And I have been for
the past 3-plus years.
Even after Mr. Queen
lost his job
as CEO of
Queen Consolidated?
I mean...
how much does he pay you,
10 cents an hour?
Objection.
Relevance?
Sustained.
Move faster, Mr. Fitzmartin.
Of course,
your honor. All right.
Well, let's, uh,
talk about
your alleged co-captain,
Thea Queen.
Isn't it true
that 5 months ago,
you helped her buy $74,000
worth of cocaine?
And before
you answer that,
you should know that I
have a signed affidavit
from Ms. Queen's dealer
right here.
Which means
nothing
because it is
irrelevant.
Well, it goes
to credibility,
your honor.
Oliver Queen
publicly slandered
my client by
accusing him of
ordering a terrorist
drone strike.
Now, if--if Mr. Diggle can
work for Mr. Queen for free
to help Ms. Queen buy
illegal drugs, I mean,
is it really that much of
a stretch to believe that
he'd also perjure himself in
support of Mr. Queen's
campaign of character
assassination?
You watched me swear
an oath.
And then I saw you break it.
No further questions,
your honor.
I don't have
a law degree,
but I don't think
that went well.
It could have been worse.
If Fitzmartin kept pulling
on those threads,
then everything that we've
done for this city
could have been exposed.
It'd be worth it
to put Darhk away.
Except it
wouldn't put him away.
Vigilantes don't
make good witnesses?
No. But they
make excellent inmates.
Yeah.
OK. So where does
this leave us?
We can't just let
Darhk walk.
Well, unless
they come up with
a witness who Fitzmartin
can't tear apart,
then that's what's
gonna happen.
Then put me on the stand.
I don't have
a secret identity,
and I could testify
about Darhk
and his connection to HIVE.
And spend the rest of
your life in jail.
If it's a cell next to
Darhk, it'd be worth it.
No. We'll find
another way.
It's Felicity.
Ah.
Put her on speaker.
Felicity, we have
the whole team here.
What's up?
Good news is I got
Cupid's location.
Good.
Where is she?
That's the bad news.
Looks like she's kidnapped
another celebrity couple--
Allison Lee
and Robert Joyce.
"Allibert."
Can you track the GPS
on their phones?
When I said I had
their location,
how do you think
that I got it?
OK, Felicity,
what's next?
Where are we going?
They're on the move,
headed towards Pennytown.
Got it.
I'd suit up with
you, but--
No. What you're doing
here is more important.
Get Darhk.
Get Cupid.
Till death do us part.
Don't worry. You won't
have to wait that long.
Wedding crashers.
Hold on tight.
Thea, look out!
She's in the center.
Ugh. I'm OK.
Stay with Speedy.
Let them help you.
I got Cupid.
I'd say enjoy
the afterlife,
but we both know
that's just
eternal nothingness.
I was in love with
the Arrow,
but you're not him,
although I do like
the sleeveless.
Got her.
Guess you didn't
have her.
Really brings
a whole new meaning
to crazy ex-girlfriends.
And you didn't even get
to enjoy the fun parts.
Sorry.
Well, Cutter really fell
for Floyd Lawton last year.
Lucky guy.
She was heartbroken
when he was blown up.
No, Thea's right,
though. Cutter is...
pathological.
I mean, targeting happy couples?
Come on.
Well, it makes sense if you look at it
from her perspective.
Love betrayed her.
And now she wants to
go to war against it.
And--and that's
making sense?
Makes sense to her.
OK...she's not just
targeting regular couples.
Yeah.
She's targeting
celebrity couples.
Probably to bring
attention
to her anti-love
crusade.
Lance is getting
the word out.
He assigned
a protective detail.
I'm gonna run
forensics on this.
We're gonna hit
the streets,
see if we can get
a line on Cutter.
OK. You want
to talk about
the other
obvious problem?
Yeah, the, uh,
elephant in the room.
Felicity and I are fine.
Yeah, well, if you were listening to
her little asides,
you would know
that was not true.
John--heh heh--you were
the one who told me
to give her time.
OK. Do you want to get
back together with her?
I do.
Then tell her that.
Even if you fall
on your face, Oliver,
she needs to know
where you stand.
She needs to know
that you are willing
to say the words.
I am willing to say
the words.
That's good.
So what's stopping you?
Why did you
do that?!
Don't. Let him die.
Reiter, you're insane.
The difference
between insanity
and belief lies
only in the number
of believers.
This is the power of
a single life.
Above us, I have dozens
under my control.
Prisoners are
gathered topside.
The men are in position.
Tell them to shoot.
Hey! Come on! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Hey.
So how did the rest of
the day in court go?
If it went well,
I wouldn't be here
still doing this.
Listen, I was thinking,
what about
all the rest of the people
at the holiday party, right?
'Cause they all saw Darhk.
Yeah. That's probably
why they're all
too frightened
to testify.
Well, you could
subpoena them.
I did that this
afternoon.
One lied,
one in jail
because they refused
to testify,
and one actually
tried pleading
the fifth.
Well, I told you
there's one guy
willing to take the stand.
Dad, I went to my boss,
and I asked him
to give you immunity
from prosecution.
He said he'd prefer
to be reelected.
I don't care about immunity.
But I do.
Dad, I'm not gonna let
you incriminate yourself.
You--you wouldn't be
doing anything.
It'd be me,
and it'd be right.
I'm the one that got
into bed with Darhk, right?
I made those decisions.
And I should pay the
consequences for 'em, honey.
And, listen, it's the only
way to bring him down.
OK. OK.
If we do this, you
will also testify
that you acted under
duress,
that Damien
threatened my life.
Yeah. 'Cause that way,
I get to say on record
how much I love
my baby girl.
OK.
Felicity Scissorhands.
We struck out
trying to find
a line on Cutter.
What's this?
I couldn't exactly fit
the entire sleeve
into the gas chromatograph.
Speak of the devil.
The sleeve contains
fibers
from at least 60 different types
of white silk lace.
White lace, like in
wedding dresses?
That would be
ironic.
And also traces
of acid-free polypropylene.
What do they
use that for?
Long-term storage
of fabrics.
Well, maybe Cutter's
holed up in a spot
where they store
wedding dresses.
Colao Wedding Dress
Services is the only
long-term storage
facility in the City
that uses polypropylene.
28th and Hamilton.
That's 2 blocks from
where she posed
the first 2 victims.
The only movement I'm
tracking in that building is
you guys.
Stay alert.
Got something.
She does love her
shrines, doesn't she?
Now we know how
she's picking her targets.
The first 2 couples, they
both recently got married.
Carter abducted
the second couple
after their wedding.
Yeah. But Blaine
and Shannon--"Blannon"--
they had a secret wedding
48 hours
before they were killed.
Now we have
to figure out
what celebrity couple in the
City's getting married next.
I think I found one
we can rule out.
So by calling off
the engagement,
we took ourselves
out of Cupid's crosshairs.
I knew there had to be
at least one
silver lining.
Well, she keeps on targeting
high-profile weddings.
So we just got to stake out
whatever the next one is.
It's a big risk to run
with an innocent couple.
We're not gonna take
that risk
with an innocent couple.
Hey.
We need to get married.
How romantic.
But it's--Felicity, it--
This is the worst idea
you've ever had.
Actually,
it's not the worst.
Et Tu, John?
We lost our lead on Cutter,
Felicity, and this might
draw her out.
Oh, so she can kill me.
Pass. No, thank you.
OK. Now, John and I
will have your back.
Oh, I guess it's too bad
I already sent out
all those un-invitations.
Clearly not if you guys
spent any time
on the gossip sites.
OK, look, these bloggers
love nothing more
than a private
secret wedding.
I leak the news saying
you guys wanted
to keep it
under radar. Uh...
it becomes the top story
on their website.
It's catnip for Cupid.
OK, look, we have
to do this quickly, OK,
so Cupid doesn't change
her MO
and start killing more
innocent couples.
Can we do this tomorrow?
Tomorrow will work.
The venue still has
our deposit.
They'll be able
to move up the date.
I thought you said you
were gonna cancel that.
I did say that I was
gonna cancel,
and I am gonna cancel,
but I haven't canceled yet
because when I picked up...
when I pick up the phone
to do that,
it means it's over.
It is over.
Hey, Taiana,
wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Well, I think we
lost them.
Look, Reiter is not
gonna issue a kill order
if he doesn't have
that thing nearby.
You grabbing it,
you saved us.
If that's true,
then we should destroy
the damn thing.
No, wait--
Oliver Queen.
We took his radio?
I know you're still
down here, Mr. Queen.
You should have studied
those maps more closely.
The only way out of
these tunnels is
back the way you came,
which means going through me.
You can either return of
your own accord
or you can force me
to come find you.
But don't bother trying to
fight your way out of this.
After all, I'm the only one
of us who has men
and guns.
Well, last August,
Darhk asked me
for the vacation plans
for the chief of
the fire department.
Objection.
Darhk. Bender. Whatever
he wants to call himself.
I told him where
Chief Reynolds was staying.
The next day,
the place blows up.
Objection. Conjecture.
Something
you're free to challenge
on cross-examination.
Continue, Ms. Lance.
What else did you do
for the defendant?
He wanted
me to give him
access to the SCPD
computer network.
I did it.
He wanted me to give him
the departmental
patrol schedules.
I did that.
He wanted me to break in
to a federal server farm
to install a computer
virus. And I did that.
He wanted me to give
him information
on the City's leadership.
And I...I did that.
And 3 days later,
the City leadership
were all dead.
You did all of
these things
for the defendant?
The defendant and the
organization he works for.
He called it HIVE.
Objection. Your honor,
it's hearsay.
Statement against interest,
your honor.
Overruled.
Captain Lance, why would
you do these things?
At first, I didn't know
his intentions,
like with the fire chief.
But then when I confronted
Darhk about it, he told me
that if I didn't do
everything he asked--
everything he told me
to do--
he'd have you killed.
No more questions,
your honor.
Mr. Fitzmartin, your witness.
Captain Lance,
have you ever
personally witnessed
my client commit
any illegal act?
Well, I'm pretty sure
that threatening
the daughter of a police captain
isn't legal, counselor.
- Objection.
- Overruled.
You know, the fact of
the matter is,
I've seen your client in
his little hidey-hole
with his little men.
Ghosts he calls them.
And I've heard him say
repeatedly
how he wants to destroy
this city
and that if I didn't
help him do it,
then he'd kill my
daughter.
By saying all these
things,
I'm setting a match
to my career
and maybe my life.
So why would I be doing
that if everything I'm
saying isn't true?
In position.
There's no psychopaths here
other than paparazzi.
Tapped into
security cameras. All clear.
Everything OK?
Yes. Yeah.
You look perfect.
I'd like to assure you,
I won't breathe a word
of what goes on here
to the press.
Just thrilled to be part
of your day.
- Thank you.
- Can we get this over with?
Can't wait to be
married to this guy.
In that case,
I know you've written
your own vows.
Felicity...
The vows.
Yeah.
OK, um...
Oliver, you have many
qualities...
many astonishing
qualities.
And I, for one,
cannot wait to move on
to the next chapter.
All right.
Uh, Oliver?
Felicity...
before I met you,
I had a plan.
I had a way that I was
gonna be.
But then you walked
into my life.
Or, I--I...showed up
at your cubicle and...
you changed everything.
I was in darkness.
But with your kindness,
your generosity,
your compassion,
your intelligence,
your wit, and your trust...
you brought me into
the light.
You let me know...
that I deserved it.
You were that light.
And I don't know if I still
deserve that trust...
if I deserve you.
I probably don't.
But whatever has happened,
whatever will happen,
the way that you
make me feel is
the best part of my life.
You can ask me to say
that I don't love you...
that I will never lie
to you again.
You are my always.
And I just want the chance
to be yours.
Oliver.
Hello, lovers.
Run.
We have eyes on?
Copy that. I'm here.
Yeah, we got that.
Hold tight.
Your little speech,
it was only off
by a little.
You see, she isn't
the best thing
in your life.
Because that means
you love her.
And love means you're soft.
And soft
means death.
Here. Let me show you.
Oh. Sorry. I didn't
check your gift registry.
Was an explosion that
would bring down
this whole building
on your list?
Your engagement,
that horrible shooting,
your miracle recovery--
it was all just
a fairy tale.
Camelot in Star City.
Thank you.
But once Camelot dies,
everyone will know
my truth--
that love is a bullet
to the brain.
No.
No, it's not.
Kevlar under
the tux.
My bodyguard
insisted.
What was his plan
for C4?
That's a damn good question.
You know, you don't
have to do this.
I do.
The 2 words that start
every marriage: "I do."
True love.
People need to see.
They need to know
what a joke that is.
It's not.
I have loved
2 men in my life
with all my soul.
They're both dead now.
No matter what, love
always ends in death.
That's why it's in
the vows.
I'm just cutting out
the middleman.
Love is death.
It's not.
You saw all those
people outside, right?
They're out there
because love is real,
because
love is life itself.
And if I die tonight...
it'll be OK
because I was one
of those people
lucky enough to have
experienced it.
From the moment he
walked into my life,
everything changed.
I became a person that
I didn't even know
I was capable of
becoming.
I became the very best
version of myself.
That would never
have been possible
without our love.
Our love gives my life
meaning.
It gives
my life purpose.
And it...
brings us more joy
than you can ever take
away from us.
And it's worth
living for.
All of it.
You really know how
to make a girl
believe in love again.
You all right?
Yeah.
Thanks for giving
the rest of us hope.
You OK?
Uh, yeah.
About what you said
in there to Cutter,
maybe we could meet up
and talk about it tonight
or...
No, not tonight.
I think we're both
exhausted
from whatever
that was.
Tomorrow.
Hey, guys, Laurel
just texted.
I guess Judge Sakow
is holding court late.
And she's making
her decision.
Well, I should
probably change.
This outfit is
a bit of
a focus puller.
Not for nothing, Oliver,
but I heard what, uh,
Felicity said in there.
Nobody likes an "I told
you so," John.
I'm just saying,
she needs some time.
Watch it. It could
be a trap.
They just left it behind.
Why would they do that?
Drop the weapon.
Maybe you should
radio Reiter.
Why?
Now we have guns, too.
The standard of proof for
a preliminary hearing is
much less severe than one
for a trial.
Even so, the evidence
against the defendant
is exceedingly thin.
There is no forensic
or circumstantial evidence
that points
to the defendant's guilt.
But I found Quentin Lance's
testimony to be
particularly compelling.
His credibility is bolstered
by his status
as a police captain.
But the fact that he was
willing to incriminate
himself to see justice done
makes his testimony
especially believable.
On the strength of it,
I am denying
the defense's motion
to dismiss
and bounding the defendant
over for trial.
Mr. Darhk will be held
without bail
or possibility of release.
All right.
Next step, convicting
this son of a bitch.
Next step. Right.
Are we OK?
I wasn't exactly pulling
punches on the stand.
No, I'm glad you did.
Because of that,
Darhk's defense is
blown to shreds.
He's gonna spend
the rest of his life behind bars.
Hey, Quentin, you have
a minute?
Yeah.
Lieutenant Pike, if I
could just talk to you before--
It's all right, sweetheart.
We both know
this was coming. Frank?
You're being suspended
pending an IAB
investigation.
I'm gonna need your badge
and your weapon.
Yeah.
Sorry about
this, Quentin.
I'm sure your union rep
will make it clear
to IAB that you were
acting under duress.
Yeah, I'm good either way,
Frank. Truly.
It's a temporary
setback.
I'll represent you
in front of IAB.
You just focus on
nailing Darhk to a cross,
all right?
I'm proud of you, baby.
We have the results
of the high-profile
preliminary hearing against
purported Markovia...
Hi.
- Kenneth Bender...
- Hi.
also known
as Damien Darhk.
Darhk had previously
been implicated...
I thought you'd be
asleep by now.
Oh, I can't sleep.
What are you doing here?
I just came to pick up a few
things. You know.
In other news,
Star City's favorite couple,
Oliver Queen and Felicity Smoak,
had an unexpected crasher...
That's not
exactly how I pictured
our wedding day.
I don't know.
Being kidnapped by
psychotic criminals
has sort of been
the theme of our
relationship.
...at
the private ceremony at
the Hochman Hotel.
Armed with explo...
Um, I want you
to know that...
what I said today during
the ceremony...
well, I meant every
single word of it.
I love you...
with everything
in me.
But what I said
doesn't apply to us.
I can't be with you.
I can't marry you.
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can because
that's what both of us want.
You know, things
can be different.
I could be different.
And I am promising you,
I'm swearing to you,
there will be no more lies.
You know, no matter
how much you love me,
there's always gonna be
a part of you
that defaults to the man
who was on the island
alone...
who came back to
save the city alone.
And sooner than we both
think, you're going to
be stuck
in a situation
where you have to
make a decision that
requires you to hide
things from me again.
See, you can't know that.
I do know that,
and you know that.
That's this life.
I'm sorry.
You know, 5 months ago,
I convinced you
that we could have
it all,
we could come here
to this job
and have each other.
I was wrong.
And then I thought
that we could just
go back to the way
things were
before we left
for Ivy Town.
But, God, that was
as crazy as Cupid is.
So what does that mean?
It means that it is,
um, too hard
to be here with you
every night
and not be with you.
That's not fair
to either of us.
You told me how you
worked some tech magic
to return all the money
that Adam Hunt swindled
out of people. You...
you don't need me.
You'll be fine.
You don't give up.
You know, that's what
makes you a hero.
But there's
no fixing this.
We have to let
each other go.
I want you to keep
it for good this time,
please.
I don't want
to let you go.
I don't want to let
you go.
But I'm already
gone.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.