Previously on Arrow...
You kill because you like it.
That's not true, Anatoly.
Someday it's going to fall apart.
And when it does, you're not going to
like the man you see underneath.
- Don't have to do this.
- Yes, I do.
It helped me discover who I am.
That's what I'm going to
help you do, Oliver.
You don't kill because you have to.
So, why...
I wanted to!
And I liked it!
We're gonna get this son of a bitch
for whatever he did to you.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
I'm shutting everything down.
Oliver, what happened?
Yeah, and what did you mean
by "shutting this all down"?
Oliver, I really think that you should be
checked out by an actual doctor.
The only thing I need is
for all of you to go home.
Oliver, we're not going anywhere.
Not a suggestion, John.
Don't you think
you at least owe us an explanation?
The explanation is simple.
Chase is right.
Everyone that is down here, around me,
well, they either suffer or they die.
Oliver, I can't imagine
what you've just been put through,
but you have to know that Chase is wrong.
I don't think that he is and I can't...
Would you just go, please?
Can the two of you give us the room?
It's just you and me now, Oliver.
Now, you don't have to
talk to me if you don't want to,
but I don't think you should be alone.
I think I should.
John, I want you to leave.
RENE". He said all that?
I've never seen him so broken.
And I've seen him at his lowest.
Did he say what Chase did to him?
Nope. Don't wanna know!
I already have
more than enough nightmare fuel
from this job to last me a while. So...
Let's back up a second.
He said the team's over?
Like, we're supposed to just sit back
and let Chase run wild?
Nobody's sitting around, Rene.
Look, Oliver's in a bad place right now,
but he will get it together.
I don't have to remind any of you
how strong he is.
- What did Thea say?
- She agreed.
He just needs time to get his head right.
She said she'll contact him
once we update her.
I don't know,
this time it just seems different.
He will bounce back, Felicity. He will.
Until then,
we are this city's last line of defense.
'Cept, our gear is back at the bunker.
And Oliver reprogrammed
all the security protocols.
Lyla will loan us gear from A.R.G.U.S.
And what about Chase?
He's still out there.
We just have to remain alert.
We're not just the anti-Prometheus team.
There are a lot of people in this city
who need saving.
I'm on Chase.
You guys just focus on
protecting the city.
Feel free to use my apartment
as your new secret lair.
Where is she going?
No place good.
Well, City Council bought my story
about your spiritual retreat.
It turns out Councilwoman Pollard
is a big fan of all that stuff.
You know, the woo-woo zen stuff.
Look, I'm not asking
what he did to you, all right?
All I gotta know is
what we're gonna do to him.
I mean, nothing. It's over.
Well, how'd you figure that?
Chase doesn't give up easy.
He doesn't need to do anything.
He's already won.
Mr. Mayor, your 11:00 is here.
Thank you for your compassion in
granting me bereavement leave, Mr. Mayor.
Doris' death has been very difficult.
Yeah, well maybe you shouldn't have
killed her then.
I'd like to speak to the Mayor
in private, please.
It's not gonna happen.
Quentin, please, just...
What are you doing here?
You won. It's over.
What did I ever say
that gave you that impression?
What are you doing?
Proving a point. Soto speak.
You think I'm gonna stab
the district attorney
in the middle of City Hall?
You're an animal who enjoys murder.
There's no telling what you'll do.
And it's not like
your alter ego can kill me,
not since the SCPD
put me in protective custody
since the Green Arrow slaughtered my wife.
So, you kill me in broad daylight,
or you let me live
knowing that there's nothing you can do.
Disappointing.
You can keep that knife.
Idea of returning to Lian Yu
makes me weep like tiny baby,
but Oliver Queen, he plan vacation there!
It's not a vacation, Anatoly.
People are gonna wanna know
where I've been
for the past, nearly, five years.
Lian Yu is the simplest answer.
It's good to see you
thinking about the future.
Only wish I had more time to spend
with this Oliver Queen.
You have 48 hours.
I know just how to spend them.
In old days, Bratva used to work
on behalf of Russian people.
Then selfish leaders like Gregor
corrupted our cause.
So the new Pakhan wants to bring
the Bratva back to its roots.
And new Pakhan needs your help.
I fear I cannot rebuild brotherhood
without you, Oliver.
Like I said, you have 48 hours.
Hey, I finished that worm.
I would've been a lot faster
if I knew what kind of system I was
embedding a backdoor into but...
Your timing is perfect.
I just finished the compilation.
This is all that we found on your target
from all available video sources,
cell phones, traffic cams,
security footage...
Please promise me you're never gonna make
a Felicity version of this.
The world doesn't need to know
how often I'm at the wine shop.
I guess it's too much to hope that
Chase took off his mask on camera.
Actually he did.
Yeah, I figured he wouldn't. Wait, what?
Why is his face all pixelated?
We're assuming
the use of optic scrambling.
He's got tech that prevents
a camera from capturing his image?
Like those scarves that celebrities use
to frustrate paparazzi.
But here's the thing.
If he's using a piece of tech
- we can reverse-engineer it.
- We can reverse-engineer it.
If we can produce video
that Chase is Prometheus,
that's game over for him.
Let's get started.
He'!-
They told me you were back.
- I had to see you.
- Hey.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
This wasn't you, Oliver. It was him.
Well, I... I created him.
And I know that that might sound weird,
but, uh, this happened to you
because of me.
Don't let him do this to you.
Don't let that bastard inside your head.
Okay.
I gave the police a statement about him.
They didn't believe you because
he probably had an ironclad alibi, right?
Yes, but if you corroborate my statement...
I can't.
I know it would probably mean
outing yourself as the Green Arrow...
It has nothing to do with that.
It has to do with the fact that
Chase would have planned for that
just like he has planned
for everything else.
My only chance is, well, I have to
do something that he hasn't planned for.
Like what?
Listen, Susan, I know that
we never got a chance to resolve things.
I can't be with you.
My apologies if that's presumptuous.
Oliver...
This is not how...
This is not how I wanted
my life to touch yours.
I should've known better.
And for that I really, truly am sorry.
Thank you for being here
on such short notice.
I understand that after last time,
I have run out of favors,
but this is an impossible situation.
And you're my only option.
Obviously. Last time, you made very clear
you did not want Bratva in city.
Circumstances have changed.
I need you to kill Adrian Chase.
ANATOLY". Interesting.
I never thought
you would give up The Hood.
Well, you were the one who told me
it was silly to think that a...
A piece of cloth could contain
the monster inside of me forever.
You were right.
Such a burden, always being right.
Life has no secrets.
I should've listened to you back then.
Least now you see self clearly.
Man must know who he is
in order to be happy.
Do you think I deserve to be happy?
Why not? I am happy.
My old friend has
finally remembered his oath,
and is about to
make his brothers very rich.
You should be happy, too.
I just want to see
Adrian Chase in the ground.
You'll be pleased to know
I've got only the best men with me.
I'll get you Chase's schedule
and known locations.
There is only small matter
of my down payment.
There's no down payment, Anatoly.
I want Chase dead immediately.
After last time,
I need small gesture of goodwill.
So my men can see that you are serious.
It's how you Americans say,
"Let's make deal."
You said that your fee has two parts, yes?
I will make sure
that you acquire the first tonight.
You get the second
when you take Chase out.
See? I knew we could both be reasonable.
Let's toast.
Please tell me
you did not put away the vodka.
Adrian Chase, winter is here.
It's spring.
We're gonna talk about you not watching
Game of Thrones, but first, look at this.
The pixelation pattern was consistent
with that of an optics scrambler
that Kord Industries
is planning on bringing to market
- in the next six months.
- How does it work?
It interferes with the camera's
- digital conversion circuit.
- That's good!
That means we can use an algorithm
to remove the distortion
from the existing image.
Yes, but to do that, I would need
physical access to Chase's scrambler.
I'm sure he'd be happy to help.
Sounds like a super accommodating guy.
Great.
I've seen more firepower
in the stands at a Dogs game.
Lyla could only authorize hardware
that wouldn't be missed.
Hey, have you heard from Felicity?
It'd be nice for her to have
our backs when we hit the streets.
Radio silence since she left for Helix,
but without our comms,
I'm not sure she'd be much help.
We have these.
Uh...
We have a break-in
at the two medical research laboratories.
Let's move out.
Talk to me, Curtis.
Without the infrared
from our body cams,
we won't be able to pull heat signatures.
So we won't really know
how many hostiles we're up against.
Also, this mask is
really making my face itch.
Perimeter sweep is two
tangoes at the back entrance. No others.
I know we don't have
our tranq ammo,
but I need this done
as clean and bloodless as possible.
Not a problem.
I'm all for blood,
but look at the label on those crates.
Oplimid. That's a diabetes drug.
Back entrance is clear.
Spartan and Wild Dog moving in.
Hands up. Hands up. Hands up.
Hands up. Hands up.
He doesn't like repeating himself.
Sounds like Russian!
Look, this one's accent
has not improved.
Still sounds horrible.
Anatoly?
John Diggle.
My favorite American.
- We know this guy?
- What the hell are you doing
- in Star City?
- Isn't it obvious?
Anatoly, I can't let you
steal these drugs.
Is not matter of "let."
I have invitation to be here.
Invitation from who?
Oliver, you brought Anatoly Knyazev
to Star City?
Yes. I did.
And he just told me that his operation
was nearly compromised by my team.
I said that's impossible.
- The team no longer exists.
- The hell it doesn't!
When I told you to stand down, I meant it.
Anatoly is here for a reason.
To steal drugs.
I had to give him that
to get what I wanted.
He's here to kill Adrian Chase.
Oliver,
we don't hire criminals,
and pay them with diabetes drugs.
Chase has killed innocent people
in this whole sick game
he's been playing, trying to get to me.
Star City will not be safe
until he is in the ground.
And there is no price I will not pay
to see that happen.
- Even selling your soul?
- Better my soul than yours.
Or Felicity's or Curtis'
or anyone on the team.
So you got Anatoly to kill Chase
so we wouldn't have to.
I created Prometheus, John.
I created this whole thing.
Chase's death should be on my conscience.
Not yours.
What the hell did Chase do to you, man,
to convince you to think that
any of this is okay?
This is a mistake, Oliver.
A mistake that
you will not be able to come back from.
And I'm not gonna let you make it.
Well, I'm not gonna let you get hurt.
So here we are.
Felicity was right.
Prometheus trying to convince you that
you are responsible for everything bad
that's happened to people.
Oliver, I swear,
that's just a bunch of crap.
Tell that to Laurel.
Tell that to Tommy.
Tell that to my mother.
Tell that to Billy Malone.
I mean, you can tell it to Thea.
She's so damaged
that she had to leave town.
This is not post-traumatic stress, John.
This is a truth that I was
keeping myself from seeing
and I'm no longer doing that.
Anatoly and his men
will kill Adrian Chase.
That is the solution.
The team is done,
so I'm telling you,
I'm not asking you, I'm telling you
for the last time, stand down.
- I don't believe it.
- Really?
I mean, Oliver can't go after Chase
himself, so he finds guys who can.
He let them steal from a company
that was barely hanging on.
Oliver put hundreds of jobs on the line
and I know he knows that,
'cause I was in the same briefing.
Yeah, speaking of which,
why haven't you gone back into City Hall?
Because Lance banned him
until Chase is taken off the board.
Something to do with Rene threatening
to pop a cap in his ass.
What about breaking up the team?
Prometheus is in Oliver's head, Curtis,
like I've never seen before.
Hey, can we talk in private?
Um... Yeah.
Yeah.
He'!-
You and I need to
talk some sense into Oliver
before he does something
that he's gonna regret.
I'm not stopping you.
Well, Felicity, I know you're
full throttle with this Helix,
but it has to be the both of us.
We have to present a united front,
so we have the best chance
of getting through to him.
Well, maybe we shouldn't.
What do you mean?
The team has been after Chase for months,
and he's always been one step ahead of us.
If Oliver thinks that the Bratva is
our best chance at getting to him,
then maybe we should stay out of his way.
And when chemicals
from both medicines bind,
it creates powerful opioid.
It's more addictive than heroin.
It's just what the world needs.
Revenue is what Bratva needs.
It's gotten bad, Oliver.
I'm under much pressure.
This drug will help secure my position
as Pakhan.
So that's why you need the medicine,
to manufacture a street drug?
Shouldn't be here, John.
Should've known Curtis would
hack the locks, Oliver.
I didn't think I could be
more disappointed, I guess I was wrong.
I'll let you have room.
I'm not gonna keep having
the same conversation.
That's too bad 'cause I dedicated
five years of my life to your crusade.
So I'm the one that gets to say
if I need protecting. Not you.
I'm not gonna have your death
on my conscience.
Oliver, don't talk to me
about your conscience.
Not when you get back in bed
with the Bratva.
This isn't you, man.
The Oliver I know would never let
a group of dangerous criminals
crawl into his city,
let them steal medicine.
You don't know what kind of man I am.
What?
What the hell did Chase do to you, Oliver?
Whatever it was, he messed with your head
in a way I didn't think was possible.
Look at me, man. I can help you.
I'm your brother.
You don't want me as a brother.
What does that mean?
Chase showed me the truth about myself.
You signed on for a crusade
that turned out to be an outlet.
It was an excuse for me to murder people.
- Oliver, please.
- I put on a hood
and I created a persona because, John,
somewhere along the way,
something in me broke.
Something is sick inside of me.
The crusade, all of this,
the foundation of it, is a lie.
So I disbanded the team
because I won't sit by
and watch all of you
participate in my murder spree.
I am beyond redemption.
You and the team will be fine
if you stay away from me,
you stay away from this,
you stay away from Chase,
and you allow the Bratva to do their job.
Let my crusade die.
That kid won't last a month.
- He had tuberculosis?
- Mmm.
The disease comes from prison.
Super-resistant strain.
What? I mean, is it in any way treatable?
Yeah, with right medicine, yes,
but even Bratva cannot buy for them,
not in quantities needed.
All we can do is pay for funerals.
Anatoly, is this how we're planning on
spending my last two days in Russia?
I thought, what better way
to cap off your time here
than good old-fashioned heist?
If Diggle's the new Oliver, and I'm
obviously the new Felicity, don't hate,
which one of you guys is the new Diggle?
- I am.
Seriously? You've been here,
like, what, 10 minutes?
You don't even have a codename!
Fine. You're the new Digg.
The fact that she was not petty and...
I mean, that's extremely Digg-like.
- You see that, right? She's...
- Yeah, okay, you're the new Digg.
But as the only Rene Ramirez,
- I gotta ask...
- Oh, boy.
Shouldn't we be cool with
letting the Bratva kill Adrian Chase?
No, we shouldn't.
Look, guys,
if Oliver lets the Bratva kill Chase,
he's just going right back
into his old habits.
And he's willing to
make that sacrifice right now,
but, I think,
once Oliver's thinking clearly,
he's gonna regret this.
So we're just supposed to let Chase
live to kill another day?
No, we're gonna bring Chase to justice.
The right way.
This isn't about saving Chase,
it's about saving Oliver's soul.
Curtis, the hack you put on the DA's
office just pulled up Chase's schedule.
He's about to leave City Hall.
Trip to the safe house
SCPD's keeping Chase in
is the perfect time
for the Russians to do their thing.
Can't let the Bratva get a hold of Chase.
I can pull up his route remotely.
And I saw something on Felicity's computer
that might help us get Chase.
Good. Do that. Let's suit up.
"Suit up"? Wait, we don't have suits...
You meant figuratively. Suit up...
Suit up, like...
We're still in the lair, suit up, like,
but we're not in the lair.
But did you see what I'm saying?
Quite an escort.
Green Arrow could be anywhere.
Who do you think is under that hood?
The department has gotta have a theory.
Oh, my God!
Make sure that Kevlar stays on.
Go! Run!
Hey! Why interfere?
You want Chase dead, yes?
Yes, but not like this.
Mr. Holt.
How's that husband of yours?
Mr. Chase!
- I'm over here!
- Mr. Chase!
The hitters are retreating.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Rene and Diggle?
- Driving off Anatoly's men.
Did you get it?
I got it.
Good man.
It's clear the attack occurred
after details of the DA's schedule
were compromised.
A leak?
AGENT". Until we can confirm the source,
DA Chase will be transferred into
the Federal Witness Protection Program.
No Star City employee
will have access to his file.
I'm really not sure
all of this is necessary.
Adrian, please, your safety is of
paramount importance to this office.
Do it.
You actually tried something.
Consider me impressed.
This isn't over.
Chase is being transferred into
federal protection,
which means that
the Bratva can't get to him.
You're welcome.
Feel better?
No.
We're not done, Oliver.
You and me, we're never gonna be done.
Do you understand that?
Listen, man, you can tell me
that you're a serial killer,
that you're crazy or you're whatever
Chase has shoved into your head,
but I'm not believing any of that,
even if you do.
And that's because
I know the kind of man you are, Oliver.
The good, the bad, and the ugly.
I know.
And you don't need to punish yourself
or isolate yourself,
but what you need to do
is stop pushing me away
because I'm not going anywhere, Oliver!
Do you get that?
What do you want me to do, John?
I've told you what I am, who I am,
and even if you don't believe it, I do.
I do.
So I don't know where that leaves us.
It leaves us right back
at Langham, Oliver.
You remember that?
It killed my brother, Oliver,
and I was going to let myself
rot in prison for what I did.
But you told me to atone
for what I did as Spartan.
And if that's true for me,
it is 100 times truer for the Green Arrow.
You don't get to
just walk away from this, man.
The Hood is who you are.
You don't think you deserve it? Fine.
Work to become the man who does.
I don't know how.
You just ask for help.
You don't have to do this alone, Oliver.
I have an idea.
We hack WITSEC.
Can we find out
what town Chase is going into,
and then we get hired as waitresses
at the inevitably folksy diner,
we drug his coffee,
we steal his scrambler.
Mmm. You know how I know I'm exhausted?
That plan actually sounds plausible.
Free pie. For life.
- That's all I'm saying. Free pie.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Felicity.
- Yeah.
Do you know this guy?
Curtis?
- You told him about our operation?
- No.
I turn off the GPS on my phone.
How did you...
You son of a bitch. Those damn...
Tracking nanites, yup. Blueberries weren't
the only surprise in those pancakes.
I knew they were funky.
Um, can we talk in private?
- Uh, no.
- Fine.
Then you don't get to ask me
any questions about how I got this.
- Is that...
- Chase's optics scrambler? Sure is.
How did you know we were looking for it?
I might've taken a peek
at your IRC window.
I guess you can say
that I hacked the hackers. Wow!
- What?
- The pixelation algorithm, is encrypted,
I should've known it would be encrypted,
but it's encrypted.
Well, how long will it take you
to break the encryption?
If my math is right. 3.6, 10 to the 18th,
e to the six, seventy-five turf locks,
13 months.
Well, I know someone
who can break it faster.
Kord Industries.
I mean, they set the encryption,
they can break it.
I don't think that Kord
is gonna help us hack their stolen tech.
And that's why you'll have to break in.
Shouldn't be so hard
for Overwatch and Mr. Terrific,
who could pull off a heist at Kord.
You told them about our operation?
- I didn't. How did you...
- Come on, Felicity,
you really think we didn't know?
It took me eight minutes,
three for this guy.
These hackers are mean.
Well, deal with it.
We have to deal with this.
Thanks for meeting.
I am only here for you to explain
why team you disbanded
keeps interfering with business.
Because they don't give up,
and they convinced me not to.
Anatoly, I'm sorry, but you need to
tell your men to stand down.
Our deal is off.
No.
Excuse me?
You want Chase to keep breathing, fine,
but I'm not leaving Star City
until I get what I came for.
You know as well as I do,
once there is deal, it is forever.
I understand how the Bratva works. I...
lam asking you this as a friend.
Yes. And I am telling, as friend,
if you interfere with my operation,
no favor exists that can repair break
between you and I.
You either Bratva brother,
or you Bratva enemy.
We are in position.
I'll meet you by the side entrance.
The Bratva aren't backing down,
which means I have to stop them.
John has convinced me not to do it alone.
I wanted to shut all of this down
because I was afraid.
I was afraid that asking you to kill Chase
would corrupt you more than...
More than I already have.
To me, the...
The Bratva was the best option,
but John insists that as a team,
we can find another way
to bring Chase to justice.
You've put your faith in me
and I'm putting my faith in you now
because once...
Once we handle the Bratva, I'd...
I need your help to prove that
John is right and Chase is wrong.
Should be easy considering Prometheus
is all the way wrong, hoss.
I think what Rene is trying to say is that
it's not all on your shoulders.
We're here for you, Oliver.
Okay.
Suit up.
Alarms haven't been triggered all night.
No break-ins.
Yeah, except us.
Anatoly needs Revlextra
to manufacture his drug.
The Bratva will definitely be here.
Spartan's right.
Anatoly won't back off now.
They could be anywhere,
this place is huge.
Felicity and Curtis
picked a hell of a night to take off.
Okay, I'm in.
CCTV is compromised.
Got anything?
West wing is clear.
So's the East.
I was hoping
I wouldn't have to punch anybody.
All right, I just got a sentry.
They can't be far.
They're not.
Better get over here. Fast.
NO.
That worked.
You can't win.
Is that you behind mask?
What happened to hood?
It's over, Anatoly.
Leave the medicine and go.
I had feeling you would say this.
So I prepared insurance plan.
You have chosen
where you stand with Bratva.
Now you must make one more choice.
Save pills or save hostages?
Spartan, Wild Dog, get the hostages.
I'll handle the Bratva.
Kill them.
In Russia, you would have killed him.
And you would've stopped him.
Looks like we're not in Russia anymore.
You all right?
Curtis didn't leave us completely hanging.
Hand me your tablet.
You brought the scrambler here?
I wasn't gonna wait to see
if we could break the encryption.
Go ahead, Oliver.
You want to kill old life?
Start by killing me.
Very stupid. Now you have to run.
So do you.
- Did you get it?
- Oh, yeah.
That is what we needed.
Something that he couldn't plan for.
You.
Please let me be the one
to walk this into SCPD.
Knock yourself out.
Yeah, and then I'm gonna
throw it up on YouTube.
There won't be anywhere
that son of a bitch can run.
Does this mean that
we're officially back in business?
Aside from a few minor changes, yeah.
New lineup could use
a little more green, hoss.
I'm not quite there yet.
I'm thinking that
with this team behind me,
it'll be sooner rather than later.
How does it feel to be Robin Hood?
Hmm, you tell me.
You're the one with bow and arrow.
I know I said that
Russia's not good for you...
But you thought that this heist,
and helping these people
would convince me
to change my mind about leaving.
Da. Like I said, I need your help.
Russia is your home, Anatoly.
Let me go save mine.
You can do this without me.
I'm not worried about
what Bratva would become without you.
I worry about what I become.
But more important question,
how drunk can we get
before dropping you off at Lian Yu?
You have two minutes.
Then I'm calling the SCPD.
Oliver Queen, afraid to be alone
with Bratva gangster?
How far you have fallen.
Anatoly, you didn't bring me here
to insult me.
No. I give you friendly tip.
I go back to Russia tonight,
but leave Star City a little present.
My best men.
Your best men were arrested.
Already out on bail.
I hear they cannot wait to get revenge
on vigilantes that put them away.
This is between you and me, no one else.
"No one else"?
You betrayed every man in Bratva.
You betrayed Russian community.
You even work against own team!
I see this, I think,
I still trust him anyway.
What a fool I was.
No. I'm the fool.
Because I thought that our friendship,
everything we have been through together,
actually meant something to you.
The person that I knew
would never betray a friend,
would never threaten innocent people.
Over what?
A payday-
When I left Russia, I was convinced
that you could lead the Bratva,
that you could set them on a better path.
And now look at you.
You're no better than Gregor.
I told you.
I was worried about what I would become
without your help.
I did what I had to do
to keep Bratva together.
And to stay alive.
I became what I had to become.
You ask why I changed?
That is it.
This video has been authenticated
by three different experts.
It hasn't been doctored or altered
in any way. That is raw footage.
Chase is in the protective custody
of the U.S. Marshals.
Yeah. Well somebody better give 'em a call
and place that son of a bitch
under arrest.