Previously on Arrow...
No, Adrian!
The two of you are
working for Ricardo Diaz.
You're both fired
effective immediately.
Obviously, the Mayor terminated us
to impede the prosecution
of his activities
as the Green Arrow.
What Oliver Queen did
is an impeachable offense.
The way you lead alienates everyone
and everything around you. Look...
You put the team at risk by lying.
You leave a trail of bodies
every damn place that you go.
My trail of bodies
does not include my own brother.
Truth is, Oliver, you have
become a better man,
but with your focus split,
a worse leader.
If I'm gonna be the best version
of myself, it can't be with you.
You told Rebecca what's going on?
You kidding?
She'd have my nuts in a vise
if she knows I was on the take.
She doesn't get it.
It's a different city now.
It's a different world.
We better call back up.
- It might just be a power surge.
- It's not. Call back up now.
What the hell?
Come on out, you son of a bitch.
Where's Diaz?
Somewhere inside
surrounded by 100 cops.
You'll never get...
- He's here.
- That was predictable.
Lockdown mode, now. Protect Diaz.
Where's Diaz?
In there.
This is gonna be fun.
Allies are in short supply
for Mayor Queen as the city reacts
in the wake of the sudden
firing of Captain Kimberly Hill
and D.A. Samir Armand.
Though City Hall maintains
the firings had no relation
to the ongoing investigation
into the Mayor's reputed
vigilantism as the Green Arrow,
sources within the City Council say
that impeachment is highly possible.
You know, they can't
actually impeach you for firing
two people on Diaz's payroll.
They can if they claim
I did it to protect myself.
We need rock-solid proof
that they're working for Diaz.
That's why you have me.
But in the meantime,
I have something else.
I just have some more evidence on
how Diaz has corrupted the SCPD.
So, ever since Dinah and
company got fired,
I have been monitoring
the station's internal security feed.
Every night at 10:13,
this happens.
Whoop!
Forty-five minutes later,
the feed goes back online
like clockwork.
He's monitoring his minions-in-blue.
- He's gotta be.
- I agree.
If you're thinking
what I think you're thinking,
you need to stop
thinking it right now. It's bad.
I can't make a move
on Diaz unless I know where he is.
And you just told me where he is
every night at 10:13.
You can't storm the bad cop
castle by yourself, Oliver.
- It's suicide.
- If I get Diaz, this is all done.
The investigation,
the corruption, the impeachment...
All of it, I stop all of it.
You can't go there alone.
You will not come out.
You need help.
All of our help quit.
Well, maybe John
has changed his mind.
What are you talking about?
Hey, Oliver.
John?
- What do you need?
- Well, Felicity said that
she needed to update
the code on my chip.
She also said that
you would be at City Hall.
Well, I said he might be.
I didn't say he would be.
And, yeah, I parent-trapped you,
but it was a little naive
of you to think that I wouldn't
considering how well
you know me, you know.
Now that we are all together,
we can talk about what happened.
I'm pretty sure John has
said everything he needs to say.
I think you're absolutely right.
I did.
Guys!
This isn't about
what he said, or what he said,
or your egos. We have
bigger problems at hand here.
We need to stop Diaz.
And we have some pretty good intel.
Good intel tends to fall apart
in the hands of bad leadership,
don't you think?
Oliver, come on,
it doesn't have to be that way.
How would you like it to be?
Well, it doesn't change
the fact that neither of you
can take down Diaz alone.
I think there's more
than one way to catch Diaz.
I've been offered a job at A.R.G.U.S.
Are you gonna take it?
I'm thinking about it. Why?
Last time you needed something
from A.R.G.U.S., you had to steal it.
Oliver.
You keep that attitude, man,
you're gonna end up all alone.
I have listened to your advice
for the last six years.
I think I've earned a reprieve.
That is not how
I thought that would go.
Sure it was.
This is who he is, Felicity.
And no one knows that more than you.
Elected officials cannot fire
the very law enforcement
personnel investigating them.
To do so, is the definition
of obstruction of justice.
Captain Hill and D.A. Armand were
actively sabotaging the city
by allying themselves
with Ricardo Diaz.
I was not obstructing justice.
I was serving it.
From what I understand, Ricardo Diaz
is a second-rate drug dealer
who was released
from prison on a technicality.
I fail to see your point.
The idea that he could
compromise a police captain
and a District Attorney is laughable.
I assume that the Mayor
will get a chance
to address the City Council,
lay out the facts as he sees them?
Preliminary impeachment
proceedings begin this afternoon.
The Mayor will have a chance
to plead his case, of course.
For your sake, Mr. Mayor, and
for the sake of your administration,
I hope you have something
more concrete to offer the council
other than unsupported suspicions.
And I know we haven't
always gotten along,
but I do believe in due process.
I'll make sure the council
approaches this fairly.
I will see you and
the council this afternoon
with evidence.
You mind if I ask
what evidence exactly?
Felicity's working on it.
I guess that's
somewhat reassuring.
On the bright side, if I
get impeached, you get promoted.
I'm not much
of a politician, Oliver.
Well, with Diaz running the city
it's not really politics, is it?
Is that the only thing bothering you?
Diaz?
You've looked better.
John quit.
I'd say he quit the team, but
there's no team.
He seems to think
I'm to blame for that.
- Well, I don't see it that way.
- You're not there, Quentin.
Yeah, I know.
But I was there when
The Hood first showed up, remember?
And that guy bears
very little resemblance
to the guy I'm talking to now.
I mean, look at you, you're
the mayor, you're a family man.
You're out busting
your hump every night for this city.
I've seen how much
you've changed, Oliver.
So, why is all this happening?
Cayden James and Diaz,
they've done a number.
But things will get better.
You just gotta stay the course.
Where are you going?
Going to check in on Felicity,
see if she's making any progress.
And I promised William that
I'd take him to his science fair.
It's not the best timing.
I think schools plan it that way.
William, you outdid me.
For my science fair project,
all I did was hack Napster.
What's Napster?
Wow, I am getting
older by the minute.
I can't believe you cloned a cabbage.
When I was a girl,
cabbage grew in the ground.
Well, you're a long way
from home, Raisa.
That I know.
I'll put these in the car.
Thank you.
I just really hope it's better than
Sarah Epstein's solar hot dog cooker.
She's really been talking it up.
We're going to be late. Where's Dad?
- He'll be here...
- Hey.
Finally, let's go.
Yeah, I know. I just gotta talk
to Felicity for one second.
- But we're already late.
- Just a minute, I promise.
Council's convening.
I promised them
I would show them something.
Prepare to be happy.
Documentation of threats from Diaz
to Hill's family and
bank statements proving
that he paid for Armand's
son's cancer treatment.
That's it. That's good work.
Yeah, it's really good work.
It might be too good work.
Without the SCPD, the only
person that can really obtain
this type of evidence is...
Well, as far as
the council is concerned, is...
- You.
- Are you telling me that
the single piece
of evidence that will stop
this imminent impeachment
is also the evidence
that will directly connect me
to being the Green Arrow?
I mean, you can tell them that
you're married to a super-hacker.
- It's not funny.
- I know,
I tried to plant a fake trail,
it's just that I ran out of time...
You ran out of time,
because you're focusing
on making John and I reconcile
instead of doing your job.
Hey, I'm on your side here.
- Are you on my side?
- Yes, of course...
- Are you sure you're on my side?
- How can you say something like that?
What is wrong with you?
Dad, you said
you'll only be a minute.
I'm in the middle
of something, please.
- We're gonna be late.
- Well then, we're gonna be late!
Buddy, I'm really sorry.
- Get out.
- Felicity, it was an accident.
I will take care of William.
Get out.
What's wrong?
Looks like you half expected me to be
a member of the League of Assassins.
No, I thought I heard something.
- How's William?
- He won't come out of his room.
Look, I don't...
I have no idea what came over me,
what made me lose it
on him like that.
Everything's piling up.
Yeah, I know.
I think we should
take some space, Oliver.
I'm sorry, what?
How you lost it on William,
that is crossing a line.
I know that you
have a lot on your plate.
Diaz, John, then the impeachment,
but that is no excuse. It can't
be an excuse. He is your son.
And you just showed him
the man his father really is.
That is not the man that I married.
Hey.
You okay?
Thanks for coming.
Listen, I've... I know
I've said this already, but
you don't look good.
Felicity...
Felicity found proof that
Hill and Armand are in bed with Diaz.
That's great.
It's great.
Why you got a face
that says otherwise?
Council's gonna ask me
how I got that evidence.
And you don't exactly
wanna tell them it's your wife.
Just shine a big fat light
on the suspicion I'm the Green Arrow.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
My wife wants a separation.
I lost my temper in front of my son.
I scared him.
It was really bad.
Well, you know,
just apologize to the kid,
sleep on the couch
for tonight, and...
A separation just seems
a little extreme.
But, Quentin, with everything
that's been happening,
it feels like par for the course.
You're talking about John Diggle?
John, Curtis, Rene, Dinah...
Why haven't you quit?
The promise of a raise.
You said...
You said I've changed.
I appreciate what you said.
Why does everyone keep leaving me?
It's the thing about change, right?
You hope you're doing the right thing
by becoming a better person,
but you're also
becoming a different person.
Some people, they just...
I guess, like John,
they just react badly.
That's one possibility.
What's the other?
That I haven't really changed at all.
Come on, I don't buy that.
What you told me about John
and Curtis, all those guys,
they got their own issues.
They're just putting them on you.
And Felicity?
Felicity loves you, man.
That thing with her
and William,
it's gonna blow over.
Don't worry about that.
My advice,
you just gotta focus on what's
right in front of us now, okay?
I'm gonna reach out
to Samanda Watson.
Maybe she can help cover us on this.
Quentin, the woman
wants me in prison.
But she also wants justice, right?
Taking down a crime boss
who's overrun a city
seems to fit the bill in my eyes.
Yeah, call her.
Now, listen.
That council meeting's in an hour.
I gotta focus.
I gotta push this stuff
out of my head, but I'll be there.
See you back at City Hall.
Hello, Oliver.
Long time.
No, you...
You killed yourself.
Funny thing.
You never did go back for my body.
Guess you were
somewhat preoccupied, right?
Still
seems a little careless.
Come on, man.
You've seen people come back from
what seemed like certain death.
As I recall,
you once were stabbed
and fell off of a mountain,
yet, here you are.
Do it.
I didn't last time.
And then I killed
the mother of your son.
I'm not playing games this time.
This time, I'm coming
for you and Felicity and William.
Anyone and everyone
who's ever been close to you.
There's only one way
that you can stop me.
Now, wasn't that better?
You know,
you might just have to
start considering the possibility
that I'm just not killable, Oliver.
No, Adrian.
You're dead.
You're still on Lian Yu.
I'm hallucinating.
I knew you'd kill me.
Or try to.
I always was the one person
who saw you for the murderer you are.
What are you doing?
Oh.
You're running a blood test.
You think you've been
dosed with something.
You know,
there is another explanation,
a more likely one,
in my considered opinion.
You're finally going crazy.
It's completely understandable,
Ollie, you've lost every thing,
even the people I couldn't
manage to take from you.
I really like this Ricardo Diaz.
If he didn't exist, I'd have to
think him up myself.
He's going about
all this exactly right.
Don't hurt the people that you love,
just get them all to abandon you.
It's actually the easiest
thing in the world.
I told you this, Ollie,
I told you this, man.
Everything you touch dies.
What you're going through right now,
losing your team, your wife,
the impeachment, all of it,
it's happening just like
I told you it would.
And nothing in that
blood test is gonna change that.
Well?
Vertigo.
It was absorbed through my...
Kullens.
Friend of yours?
Apparently not.
Don't. Don't go talk to Quentin.
You're not in the state of mind
to be talking to him right now.
He might have you committed,
which would be a shame,
since by my count, he's the only
person still left in your corner.
Okay, Felicity,
William and I will be fine.
I just need to talk to them.
Maybe. But what about the rest?
It's tough to say
you're in a good place
when your oldest friend
leaves you high and dry.
John made his choice.
Deep down, you know he's right.
You've changed, sure.
Maybe you are a better Oliver Queen,
a happier Oliver Queen.
But it has sure made you
a worse hero.
You have a wife, a son,
you're the mayor,
all of which, yes, may be going away,
but still, it's a fair assumption
you're stretched too thin, buddy.
Maybe you've gotten so good
at being Oliver Queen,
that the Green Arrow's
mission is suffering.
You may be happier,
but the people that you love,
they're not.
Hey, what's Vertigo do?
Does it show you your worst fear?
You're not my worst fear, Adrian.
You're nowhere close.
Oh.
I know. Your worst fear is yourself.
Your worst enemy is yourself.
Guys like me, Ricardo Diaz,
Damien Darhk, Ra's al Ghul...
When it comes
to destroying you, Oliver,
we all come in second place.
You're the one enemy
you can't defeat.
Yes, Quentin.
Hearing's about to start,
where the hell are you?
Well, Kullens dosed me with Vertigo,
and I've been dealing with it.
Didn't you say that Diaz was
dealing Vertigo these days?
Well, Kullens is working
for Diaz apparently.
Now, listen.
Where are we with Agent Watson?
She's mulling it over.
She gotta mull faster.
All right, I'll give her
another call.
Listen, just get down here
as fast as you can. All right?
I'm on my way.
Ollie.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Ollie, are you okay?
I don't know.
You know, if you tell her the truth,
she'll just think
you're crazy, Oliver.
You'll break her heart
all over again, nobody wants that.
Hey. Hey, you can
tell me anything, you know that.
I know that.
I need to leave.
I thought the boat left at 6:00.
What?
The Gambit. The trip that you're
going on with your father.
I ran into Sara. She said
that you hadn't packed yet.
Do you want me to help you?
Look at how innocent she was,
how much she loved you.
You destroyed that.
- Ollie?
- Tell her about her future, man.
Tell her about what happens
when she becomes the Black Canary.
Ollie, please help me.
Please, I'm scared.
I don't wanna die.
This is gonna destroy my father.
He can't handle this.
She's got a point.
My question is,
why did you let her become
the Black Canary in the first place?
She's a lawyer!
What, after a couple
of self-defense classes,
and a few sparring sessions with you,
you think she's ready
to go handle thugs and killers?
It was a mistake.
Yeah, your mistake.
Which I had to pay for.
It was a mistake.
But I knew you.
And I knew that you'd
do it with or without me.
I thought this way
I could protect you.
How did that work out for you, Ollie?
Huh?
Yeah, "Ollie."
How'd that work out for you?
For me, not too good.
Mmm-mmm. I gave you an out.
I told you to stand down.
- Stay down!
- No way!
You know,
John came to see me in here.
Felicity, too.
But you were nowhere, hoss.
He's got a point, Oliver.
If your conscience
is so sparkly clean,
why didn't you check on Rene?
Rene made it clear...
Matter of fact,
all of you have made it clear
that you don't want
anything to do with me.
Always a comeback for everything.
That's enough.
It's not real.
Raisa?
It's not safe here for you.
A man came.
Hey, hey, hey.
Raisa, what man?
With a dragon tattoo.
He wants to hurt you.
I tried to stop him.
Well, the lady wouldn't
go down without a fight.
Your wife and kid aren't here.
They're at some science fair.
Come on, come on, come on.
You still think this isn't real?
Does that feel real enough for you?
Argh!
I always wonder
why nobody just does that.
Kill you straight.
Turns out it'd be a waste of time.
You're more dangerous as a martyr
than you are as Green Arrow.
But before that happens,
there's a lot left of you
that I wanna break.
Yeah, Quentin, hi. I'm gonna
need that hearing delayed.
I'll explain everything.
I'm on my way to City Hall.
You have failed this city.
And you know why.
Because I got away from you.
We were never
supposed to have partners.
There was never
supposed to be a John Diggle,
a Felicity Smoak,
a Team Arrow.
There was never
supposed to be a Green Arrow.
There was only the mission.
I lost sight of that.
You lost your city!
And now, you know what you have to do
to get it back.
It's been over an hour.
Where is the Mayor?
Well, why don't you ask Ricardo Diaz?
Apologies for being late.
Over an hour late.
And we certainly hope you've come
with something worthy of our time.
One minute.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Where are we with Watson?
We're on our own.
It's our only card.
Are you sure you wanna play it?
Mr. Mayor...
Okay, this flash drive
contains financial data
and correspondence
linking Captain Hill and D.A. Armand
with a known felon
named Ricardo Diaz.
Known by whom?
I've never heard of a Ricardo Diaz.
By design, he's kept
a very low profile.
How did you obtain
this purported evidence
against our former
police captain and district attorney?
The Green Arrow gave it to me.
Or perhaps, you gave it to yourself.
I'm not the Green Arrow.
Not according to the police captain
or D.A. that you fired.
And it also seems rather convenient
that you're not the Green Arrow,
but enjoy a close,
personal relationship with him.
That go down how you expected?
Are you aware we can impeach you
not just for obstruction of justice,
but for perjury
and vigilantism, as well?
Okay, I am so sorry, but something
very urgent has just come in,
and I need to speak
to the Mayor, please.
So, please...
Ten minutes tops.
Thank you.
Wait, what's happening.
Are Felicity and William all right?
Listen, the urgent thing was
just a line to buy us some time.
Felicity and William are fine.
Okay? It is you I'm worried about.
Have you still got that
Vertigo crap in your system?
Yeah.
Okay, listen, we need to retreat,
we need to regroup.
Okay? So I'm gonna go back in there
and I'm gonna tell them you've
got a family emergency.
You might not be wrong.
Okay, listen, you need to
go back to your secret lair,
get yourself well.
We'll figure out the next steps.
Sorry, Oliver.
Bad beat.
For what it's worth, I always thought
you were a halfway decent mayor.
Not a great track record when
it comes to hiring D.A.s, though.
This Vertigo is going to be
out of my system eventually.
Then you'll be gone.
Not possible.
I'm not here, remember?
I'm here.
I'm you.
Which is why
you're gonna listen to me
when I tell you what you have to do.
The only way to prove
that you're the hero
that you say you are and keep being
mayor is to take down Diaz, tonight.
No, he's got an army.
You mean all those cops at the SCPD?
I mean that walking
in there is a suicide mission.
That's the risk
a hero takes, isn't it, Oliver?
Diaz is there every night, 10:13 p.m.
Question is,
will you be there to meet him?
Thanks for helping me
put my project back together.
No problemo.
Second place too. Pretty good
even if that cheater
Sarah Epstein got the gold
for her solar hot dog cooker
that I swear I've seen on Amazon.
You know, when I was your age,
I could hit three science fairs a day
and now one...
One knocks me right out.
Where's Dad?
He's buying us expensive gifts
if he knows what's good for him.
Your purse is beeping.
William, go play video games.
I gotta do some work,
buddy, all right? Sorry.
I know what kind of work. Good luck.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
- Quentin.
- Felicity.
Tell me Oliver's with you.
He was.
I just sent him back to the bunker.
No, he's not on his way there.
I have a GPS on his bow
and it's on the move.
All right, slow
down, let me explain.
It has been a hell of an afternoon.
- What happened?
- Oliver was dosed with Vertigo.
Kullens did it.
That would explain
why he lost it on William.
He said you... You kicked him out?
No, I didn't. I would never...
He's on his way to the precinct.
And that's totally my fault. I told
him that Diaz would be there.
Quentin, this is a suicide
mission. You have to stop him.
- I'm on my way.
- Okay.
What's happening? Is Dad all right?
No, Dad is on drugs.
I mean, not that kind of drugs.
He's gonna be fine.
I just... I have to
go help him, okay?
I know, I was listening.
You're an angel.
Okay. I love you. You're an angel.
Hey.
Get out of here, Quentin.
What're you doing in that old thing?
Getting back to my original mission.
Okay, listen,
that's just the Vertigo talking.
You cannot go in there.
This ends tonight.
No, even if you weren't high,
this would be a bad idea.
You're outnumbered!
- I can handle it.
- Listen to me...
I said...
I can handle it.
Quentin? Quentin!
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, your husband packs a punch.
Diaz's men cannot find
the Deputy Mayor here.
Okay, you have to
get out of here, all right?
I have to go save my husband.
Don't, don't, don't.
Do not open that door.
On the other side of that door,
there's a bunch of
trigger-happy cops
just waiting for you.
It is a trap.
- You're not here.
- Yes, I am. It's me.
Okay? It's the real me.
Do not go through that door.
I have to.
- I have to stop Diaz.
- And you will.
But not like this, not tonight.
He's right on the other side
of that door.
So are a bunch of
angry cops just waiting for you.
You go through that door,
what happens to William?
William has you.
Well, what happens to me?
You left.
No, I didn't.
That was not me, Oliver.
The real me is standing right here.
And I'm not going anywhere.
I'm glue, baby.
Please.
Where are you?
The Vertigo is making its way
through your system, okay?
It's on its last gasp, so just...
Just listen. Listen to my voice.
No, no, no, don't listen to her.
Remember what you told yourself.
You were never
supposed to have partners.
I know it feels like
you've lost everything.
I don't know how to tell
if you're real.
That's the Vertigo, it's just
messing with your head.
Don't trust it.
Okay? Listen to your heart.
Come on.
Screw it.
Go after him.
- Come on.
- Just like old times.
Thanks for coming back for me.
- Okay, less thanking, more escaping!
- Right!
What's this?
It's an isotonic concoction
of my own making.
There are oranges
in there for vitamin C,
there's almonds
in there for Vitamin E,
there's avocado in there
for omega-3s, do not smell it.
Just drink it.
It's salty.
Yeah, that'd be
the fermented fish oils.
It's supposed to help
balance your serotonin levels.
I call it "Felicity's Party
Raver Hangover Supreme Cure."
Though that might be
an insensitive choice of words,
considering what you went through,
but trust me, it works like a charm,
not that I've used it much,
I mean, that was all in the past.
Trust me.
Drugs are bad.
Listen, that was gutsy as hell, you
going into the precinct like that.
Yeah, well, my man was in there.
Yeah, but whatever you said there
could have been caught
on security cameras.
No, Diaz had shut them down.
So, our identities are safe.
Irony sold separately.
Excuse me, I gotta take this.
It's the office.
I haven't seen that in a while.
Wanted to take it for a spin down
memory lane or something?
Something like that.
Vertigo gave me some
clarity.
- Sure you're not still high?
- Mmm-hmm.
John had a point.
I've spread myself pretty thin.
I'm not giving up on you,
I'm not giving up on William,
and if by some miracle
I'm not impeached,
I will keep being the mayor.
I believe deeply in the good
that I can do as the Green Arrow.
But I need to bring
the mission back to basics.
I need to bring it back
to where it started.
You mean alone?
Alone.
I'm sorry, guys, I hate to interrupt,
but we have to turn the TV on. News.
In a shocking fall from grace,
the Star City Council
has voted to impeach
Mayor Oliver Queen and
remove him from office.
We now go live to Councilman
Kullens' public statement.
Mr. Queen's affect
at today's inquiry
certainly placed his
fitness for office into question,
but fundamentally,
it was the unilateral firing
of Captain Hill and D.A. Armand
that ultimately sealed his fate.
Sorry, I just couldn't stand to
listen to him any longer.
Okay, listen,
I'm gonna call Jean Loring.
There's gotta be legal
options we can pursue.
No.
I don't want you wasting any more
time or political capital on me.
I don't give a crap
about political capital.
You should.
'Cause you're the mayor now.
Thank you so much, Raisa,
for coming on such short notice.
- I'm used to it.
- Thank you, Raisa.
Are you okay, Oliver?
I'll be just fine, thank you.
I know this question
might be questionable, but...
From what it sounded like earlier,
it's like you were firing Overwatch.
I'm not firing anyone.
It's just...
I need to go back
to doing things
like I did when I started.
And that means
doing it alone.
I need to stop Diaz.
And in order to do that, I need
to have a single-minded focus.
I've gotta separate these two worlds.
I just don't think
that's the best possible solution.
I respect your concern,
and I love you very much for it.
We will talk more about this, but
I need to chat with William.
Yeah.
Hey.
I didn't know if you'd be awake.
I can't sleep.
I got a news alert about the impairment.
It's impeachment.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I worry about you.
I'm really sorry about before.
I would never
purposefully try to
make you afraid, or...
Felicity said you were
on some sort of drug.
Accidentally.
I was dosed by someone who works
for the man I'm trying to stop.
Ricardo Diaz?
Can you stop him?
I think maybe I found a way.
Most important,
I need to know that
I'm not gonna lose you,
or Felicity ever.
You won't.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I heard about what happened.
I wanted to see how you were.
Clearly, I should have
brought a broom.
He's spiraling.
That Vertigo worked
even better than I was hoping.
I don't understand why you
don't just put a bullet in him.
Or 20.
'Cause it'd be a waste of time.
He's more dangerous as a martyr
than as the Green Arrow.
I'm gonna dismantle him
piece by piece.
Like with the impeachment?
The impeachment was
just the latest step.
And what's the next one?
We spread the word
that with Mayor Queen out,
Star City, it's open for business.