My name is Oliver queen.
For five years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will
fulfill my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
It's done.
And he won't be harmed?
Nor will he ever discover
your involvement.
You have my word.
You know Digs, when I confront
somebody on the list,
I tell them
they failed the city.
But tonight...
Tonight it was me
who failed.
Get that hose over
to the north face
or we're liable
to lose the whole block!
Danny!
Yes, Keith?
Getting a little smokey
out here, buddy.
Just clearing
the upper level.
Hey you, over here.
I can use some help.
I got a hot spot.
Hey! What--oh!
Ohh! What--
How you doin'?
Rehab going good?
Any news on Walter?
My contact at the Bureau
struck out.
Same with my guy
at Interpol.
They're both saying
the same thing.
Either my stepfather
doesn't want to be found
or someone doesn't want him
to be found.
It's been
six weeks, Oliver.
No contact
from the kidnappers,
no ransom demand,
no proof of life.
I hate to sound--
Dig...
We both know he's more
than likely dead.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
Even my contacts in the Bratva
can't dig up a lead.
I wasn't talking about Walter.
Back at fighting weight,
looks like.
And last I checked,
there were more than a few names
to cross off in this book.
Those people aren't
going anywhere.
With Walter missing,
my family needs me right now.
, tell them
to bring the plane.
My people will be
here shortly.
Do you not
think it convenient
you captured me
so easily?
Go!
What?
Run!
♪ Arrow 1x10 ♪
Burned8
Original Air Date on January 16, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
And, Judge Hinkle is ready
to grant them another continuance!
So I said, hell, no.
This trial starts
right now.
That a girl.
Thanks.
Dad.
What brings you by?
I need to talk to jo.
Is everything ok, Mr. Lance?
No.
What's happening?
Her brother Danny.
He was killed
on duty last night.
Jo, I'm so sorry.
No.
No, no!
I'm sorry.
No!
Jo, it's okay!
Shh.
Mom?
Hey.
I stopped by
the Big Belly Burger.
I thought maybe you, me
and Thea, have some take-out,
watch a DVD.
Thank you, sweetheart.
I'm not very hungry.
If you change your mind...
I've seen
the movie before.
Cut me some slack.
I've been gone for a while
and apparently I missed
the cinematic genius
that is Zac
Galafinak...is?
I mean, with mom,
when you and dad
disappeared,
she spent more and more
time at home.
Eventually stopped going
out altogether.
What snapped her
out of it that time?
Walter.
One morning,
he showed up
and, you know, when he gets all
British and stern-like.
"Moira, get dressed.
We're going out
for lunch."
And, I mean,
it worked.
Hmm.
You know,
I've been thinking.
Maybe Walter
wasn't abducted.
Maybe he's having
some mid-life crisis
and he's with some
stewardess in Bora Bora,
and he's too ashamed
to call home
and say that he's okay.
Just because
we haven't heard from him
doesn't mean he's...
he's gone, right?
Right.
So what strikes me
is that this Vigilante
was actually
making a difference.
In the four months
that he was active,
assaults were down,
muggings down.
The murder rate
dropped by 16%.
So in a very
quantifiable way,
this man in the hood
had been a positive
force in this city.
So where has he been
for the past six weeks?
Looks like
everyone's disappearing.
Hey.
What's this?
It's--it's nothing?
It's nothing?
"Reasons I deserve a drawer"--
Okay, we're going
to table this
for a less
tragedy-filled day.
Yeah, and besides,
I don't think
we're there yet.
I should probably get that.
All right.
I need your help.
Jo, come in.
I, um...
I don't think what happened
to Danny was an accident.
I think he might
have been murdered.
Jo, do you remember
when Sarah died?
I did all this research to try to
find an explanation
for why the boat
went down.
I needed to believe
that it wasn't just an accident.
That is not what
I am doing, Laurel.
I once handled a case
for a clerk
in the Coronor's Office.
He passed me a copy
of the incident report.
Said that Danny's turnout coat
was doused in turpentine.
But I checked,
and the plant owner
said that there wasn't
any in the factory.
A turnout's supposed
to withstand temperatures
in excess of 500 degrees.
But the coroner said
that the fire
did not exceed 250.
How did my brother
burn hotter than the fire
that supposedly killed him?
Laurel, a fireman died
fighting a fire.
I'm not sure I see the crime.
I did some digging.
Last week, another firefighter,
Leo Barnes, was killed in action,
same circumstances.
Traces of turpentine,
and ignition temperatures hotter
than the actual fire.
Do you think that you could
talk to the fire marshal?
You know, encourage him
to pursue this?
Well, the fire department
has its own investigative unit.
They don't answer to the police.
Sorry it takes so long
with the detectives.
CSU's been
really backed up.
Well, did you find anything?
The only prints
on it are yours,
the tech inside
is military grade.
I can't even trace
the manufacturer.
Forensics-wise,
it's a dead end.
Another case?
Vigilante.
The phone belongs to him.
Where'd you get it?
I--does he answer?
Well, like Kelton said,
it's a dead end.
Listen, kiddo, I feel
for Jo and her family
I really do, but, um,
there's a lot
I can do this end.
I got to go. I love you.
Hey. Let's go.
Hello?
I need your help.
I didn't trust
that you'd come.
No one's seen you
for a while.
Where have you been?
You said it was important.
My best friend's
brother.
He died two days ago
fighting a fire.
The police
and fire department
say that he died
in the line of duty.
But my friend,
she thinks he was murdered.
So you're asking
one killer to find another.
I heard what you said
to your father about me;
that I'm a killer.
That I have no remorse.
Do you?
Take a look
at the file.
If Danny de La Vega
was murdered,
then we have to bring
his killer to justice.
I'll look into it.
You need to rotate
your hips, Diggle.
That's where
the power comes from.
It's not just your arms, even if
they're the size of bowling balls.
Laurel reached out
to the Hood last night.
Really? Thought
the Vigilante
spooked her pretty
well last time.
She thinks somebody's
killing firemen.
It looks
all in the job.
Seems pretty thin.
Will you look into it?
Yeah.
I have a friend who has a friend
in the fire investigations department.
I'll reach out.
If you get any leads,
tip the police.
The police?
They just need something
to jump start them.
Well, isn't the whole idea
of being a vigilante,
is that you do
the police's job?
You know, Oliver,
you've been spending
a lot of time
around here lately.
I thought after six weeks,
you'd be anxious
to hood up.
Hell, I even prepared
the "you got to slow down" speech.
Let me see what's going on
upstairs in the club.
You know, I do realize
that it's difficult
for you to manage
my nightclub,
what with there not
being an actual nightclub here.
Yeah, I just took the liberty
of yelling at our contractor.
I told him if we didn't see
any real progress,
we were going to bring
someone else in to finish the job.
Good.
How's Laurel's friend?
The one whose brother
was a fireman?
She is hanging
in there, thanks.
I have something
I wanted to bring up.
I was thinking
that we could
throw a fundraiser
for the fire department.
Raise some money
for the families.
That's a great idea.
We could do it here.
We could keep
the overhead low,
make sure we maximize
the proceeds to the firemen.
Who are you?
Where's my friend Tommy Merlin?
The guy who once rented out
a pro football stadium
so that he could play
strip kickball with models.
That guy needed
a swift kick in his lazy ass.
Jo...
You really should
take some time off
and go be with your family.
You know, I seem to
recall when Sarah died,
you hit the books
pretty hard.
I am not exactly the best example
for healthy grieving.
Hey. Can I talk to you, please?
Where is it?
Where's what?
The phone.
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't have.
It's stolen evidence!
Yeah, you probably shouldn't have.
What are you--
I had to do something.
That man's a killer.
Then why did he
give you his phone?
Give me the phone.
He took it back.
You were with him?
When Sarah died, if someone
could have done something
to give you even just
a little bit of closure,
don't you wish
that they would have done it?
If it meant
breaking the law,
lying to the people
closest to them...No.
Surely there are contingencies
for these types of situations.
Bring someone over
from our London office, perhaps.
It's not solely a matter of the day
to day operations.
We have accountants
and the vice presidents to do that.
It's about perception.
Public confidence.
Ned, the company will be fine.
I don't mean
to be indelicate,
but this is
the second time
in five years
that the CEO
of Queen Consolidated
has vanished under mysterious
circumstances .
I don't need you
to remind me of that.
The last thing I want
to do is upset you.
Well, then you should consider
this visit doubly disappointing.
Good day.
Who was that?
Ned Foster.
The C.O.O. of the company.
He wants mom
to take Walter's place.
He says that the company's
stock price has been damaged
by Walter's absence,
and my stepping in
would help settle the board.
But I told him that I needed to be
at home, for my family.
Mom...
Thea and I are fine.
We can manage here
without you.
This sounds like something
everyone needs you to do.
Well, maybe I don't care
what everyone needs.
She's going to be
all right, Thea.
Mr. Queen, we're going to
have to get going
if you want to make
your dentist appointment.
Now, sir.
Eyewitnesses place
a '72 Ford pick up at the scene
of Danny de La Vega's fire.
Okay.
Stagg Chemical lit
up ten minutes ago.
I hacked into Stagg's video
security feeds.
Parked right on
the street running along the plant.
Same pick up.
I got your gear
in the car.
Oliver, by the time
I get someone on the phone
who will even listen to me,
at least one of those fireman
are going to be dead.
They need the man in the hood.
I have contact.
Two clicks southwest.
Portable one
to Deputy Chief Seven.
All clear of civilians.
Copy that. Bail out and wait
for second-in companies.
Who are you?!
Hello?
I have some information for you.
The killer drives
a 1970s Ford pick up.
There is a scar on his left wrist
from a severe burn
and a tattoo of a firefly.
Well, then you must
have gotten pretty close to him.
All the men
in Engine Company 15
had firefly tattoos.
Any one of them
could be the killer.
What should I do
with this information?
Whatever you would have
done before you met me.
Who was
on the phone?
Wrong number.
So Laurel's on her own
against a murderer
who burns people alive?
I can't right every
wrong in this city.
No, I get that, Oliver.
But maybe you're not back
to 100% like you thought.
Maybe I'm not.
What did that prove?
This is one sturdy desk.
And clearly, your problem
isn't physical.
I never said I had a problem!
You didn't have to, Oliver.
But this guy,
the other archer,
he got in your head,
he took something from you.
That's enough.
He took whatever's
in your heart
that lets you
jump off buildings
and take down
bad guys.
Thank you for the analysis.
You can avoid Laurel,
Oliver, avoid me,
avoid this,
as long as you want.
But until you're ready to take
a hold of the fear that's in you,
you might as well
let that archer kill you.
Text from Tommy.
I need to run an errand
for the benefit
at the firemen's station.
Maybe while you're at it,
you can let me know
if you still want to be a vigilante
or just
a nightclub owner.
Hey.
What are you
doing here?
I told Joanne
I'd clean out Danny's locker.
And you?
Tommy sent me over
to make sure
the guest list for the firemen's
gala was accurate.
Tommy's been working
very hard on that.
It's very generous
of you, Oliver.
It's truly not.
Speaking of Tommy,
he told me that you're being
very protective of your drawers.
This is not a fancy term
for your underwear.
Are you and I seriously
having this discussion?
Well, we're friends.
Yes.
Tommy asked
for a drawer.
And this is bad?
No.
It's just...
I'm an all or nothing
type of girl.
First it's a drawer,
then it's a closet,
half my rent,
it's half my life.
Am I really ready to do that
with Tommy?
You could take it slow.
I don't things slow,
remember?
I close my eyes
and I jump,
just like you.
I think that's why
we spooked each other.
Our feelings...
our fears, they control us,
it's not the other
way around.
You know?
Yeah.
I have to get inside.
There are eight firemen
in this picture.
I did some research.
You called yourselves
the fireflies.
Yeah, well, that station house
was shut down a few years back.
All the guys went
to different companies, so...
Four of these men
are now dead.
It's not all getting cats
out of trees, Ms. Lance.
But three of them died
within the last six weeks,
except for that man
right there.
Garfield Lynns.
He died two years ago
in the Nodell Tower tragedy.
Did you forget
something, Mr. Queen?
Just wanted to see if my friend
there needed some help.
What was
the Nodell Tower?
How do you not
remember that?
I was WiFi-free
for a few years.
It was 22 stories
of glass and steel.
Except it turned out
that the construction
company who built it
used substandard materials
to save themselves a few bucks.
It was nowhere near
the structural code.
Gas line blew.
There was a fire.
Yeah. Melted right through
the stanchions.
Whole damn thing came down.
Bad day.
34 civilians and six
of my fellow firemen died.
Do you need anything else,
Ms. Lance?
Other than reminding me of all
the friends I've lost and buried?
Hey!
What was that all about?
It was nothing, Oliver.
I have to go.
Hello?
Are you there?
I spoke to Danny's
old chief.
I didn't get anywhere.
What am I supposed to do now?
Nothing. It's my turn.
We have so many
of these old photos.
I really should
have them scanned in.
Well, that's an incredibly
ambitious plan.
Which will
have to wait.
Why?
Because we're going to go out.
To dinner
or to a movie
or shopping. Anything to get you
out of the house.
Ohh. No, Thea.
I'm just too tired.
Really, that's...
Pretty amazing,
considering you've
been in bed all day.
Please don't presume
to think that you know
what I'm going through.
I do know.
I lost dad, too.
I'm worried
about Walter, too.
But I don't get
to worry about him,
because I'm busy
worrying about you.
I never asked you to do that.
Right.
'Cause you don't ask me to do
anything anymore.
You don't ask me
to do my homework
or to be home
at a decent hour.
I mean, you basically
stopped being my parent.
Well, how's this--
don't talk to your mother
like that.
Maybe you should start
acting like my mother.
So I don't have
to act like yours.
I thought you were done
helping Laurel.
The first firefly to die, his name
was Garfield Lynns.
Well, being dead kind of rules him out
as a murder suspect, right?
Oliver...
I'm sorry I came at you so hard, man.
But I've been there.
I know what it's like
to stare death in the face
and...be the one who blinks.
That's not it.
I've...
I've been
close to death.
On the island...
More times than
I can remember,
and I never
feared it.
'Cause I had
nothing to lose.
But when that archer
almost killed me;
when I...
stared death in the face then,
I thought about
all the people
that I've let into my life since
I've been back.
My family,
Laurel, Tommy.
And that made me afraid.
Afraid of what would
happen to those people
if they lost me--again.
And for the first
time in so long,
I had something to lose.
Well, you got it
backwards, Oliver.
You think the people
you let in are taking your edge.
I think it gives you one.
Maybe a stronger one.
You can stare down death
with something
to live for or not.
Something to live for...
is better.
All the men in the unit had
an alibi for Danny's murder.
The guy that I fought
had a firefly tattoo
and his arm
was severely burned.
Okay. I don't see
where you're going with this.
The Nodell Tower fire.
Some of the bodies
were so badly burned,
they couldn't even be
IDed off dental records.
What if Garfield Lynns
didn't die,
but was just
presumed dead?
You know, ironically,
if we get any more
people in here,
we're going to violate
the fire code.
We're good on
drawer-gate, right?
All good.
Excuse me.
Can I borrow Laurel
for a second?
Absolutely.
Chief Raynes.
Hi. Mr. Queen,
this is spectacular.
Ahh.
The Starling City Firemen's
Relief Association
can't thank you enough.
You guys are
the real heroes.
Like at the Nodell Tower fire,
which I've been reading up on.
Oh, yeah?
Garfield Lynns
was the first man
to die in your unit.
Now, I read that
they recovered his coat
in the wreckage,
but they never
found his body?
You always interrogate
your club's guests, Mr. Queen?
Why?
Do you feel like
you're being interrogated?
You could see it
on your face at the fire station.
There's more to the Nodell Tower
fire than people know about, isn't there?
I've been doing this
a long time
and I've never seen
a fire like that.
It's like some monster out
of a science fiction movie.
I radioed for my men to get
the hell out of there.
But Lynns,
he wouldn't go.
Begged me to send
the unit back in.
But I wouldn't do it.
I couldn't.
God help me,
I left him to burn.
But I can't bring him back.
You don't have to.
He is back.
What the hell
you talkin' about?
Garfield Lynns killed Danny.
And the other men
on your unit.
There's no way he could have
survived that fire.
You'd be surprised the power
revenge can give you.
Thank you so much.
The people in the city
appreciate everything you--
You're insane. Gar did not
make it out of that building.
Just like you won't
make it out of this one.
Go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
This way!
Gar, what the hell
are you doing?
Run.
Go!
Laurel?!
Laurel? Laurel!
Where's Oliver?
He's still inside!
We can't leave him.
Tommy!
You know how long it takes
for your skin to melt?
I do.
From experience.
I told you to get out of there!
And I told you
that we could
save the building.
But you got scared.
You lost your nerve.
You...left me in there
to die.
How did you get out?
I was pulled
from the wreckage.
Listed as a John Doe
in the burn unit,
in a coma
for months.
When I woke up
and saw
what was left
of who I was...
I only had one thought.
To leave you as alone
as you left me.
Now it's your turn.
Go!
It's over.
I'm not afraid to die.
I know.
You're afraid to live.
Let me get you out of here.
Lynns.
Let me get you out.
Thanks.
But I'm already burned.
Eyewitnesses contend that numerous
lives would have been lost
if not for the timely
intervention of the Vigilante.
But these were not
the actions of a vigilante.
What's been described
are the actions of a hero.
What's got you all smiley?
Your new club's a briquette.
It was under
construction before.
Now it's more
under construction.
Good morning.
Sharp suit, Mom!
Not used to seeing you without
your bedroom wrapped around you.
Well, I could hardly
go to the office in my pajamas.
I'm taking Walter's position
at the office.
What changed your mind?
Not what. Who.
My daughter.
My family.
And I promise you,
Walter will
get back to us.
I will keep looking for
him and I will find him.
And I'll see you
for dinner.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Just feeling the whiplash.
She went from shut-in
to chairman pretty fast.
Sounds like you got
through to her.
Yeah, I guess.
It'll just be
for a few months.
My mom, she's
taking it so hard.
Whatever you have to do
to take care of your family.
Before I forget...
My brother's badge.
My mom was hoping
maybe you could find
a way to get it
to, you know...him.
As a thank you.
I don't care
what anyone has to say.
He really is
a guardian angel.
I'll find a way
to get it to him.
I'm going to miss you.
Yeah.
Hey.
You look after yourself,
all right?
I will.
Good.
So Joanna's taking
a leave of absence, huh?
She has to go be
with her family.
Yeah, well, family's important.
I already apologized.
It's my turn.
After what happened last night,
maybe it's a good thing
you got the Hood involved.
He didn't take the phone
off you, did he?
Maybe you should
hold on to this.
I mean, I may not like
the guy's methods,
but whoever this guy is,
he's got a habit of putting
himself between danger and you.
And that's not something
I can argue with.
Besides,
I shouldn't
have this thing anyway.
Kelton. We good?
I got a strong signal
from the crystal vhf transmitter
you hid in the speaker,
and it can't be backtraced.
Talk to me like
I'm a third grader, please.
Next time your daughter
calls the Vigilante,
we'll be able to listen
to every word.
I know you swore
to bring this guy down, Detective,
but using your own
daughter as bait,
that's stone cold.
Good thing the fire
didn't spread to down here.
It's one of the benefits
of concrete and steel construction.
Thank you.
What for?
You know what for!
So what's next?
More training?
No.
We go hunting.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==