Last season, on Arrow...
I convinced you that we can have it all.
I was wrong.
We have to let each other go.
I have a village, too. Run by
a government strongman named Kovar.
You'll go back to Russia,
and you can take on this Kovar.
What are you gonna do now, Oliver?
I know you wouldn't approve of what I did.
But you were always
better than me, Laurel.
That is what I loved most about you.
I thought about Laurel
and what she'd say.
I think she'd tell me to get out.
What are you gonna do?
Take some time
away from this team,
away from the city.
I, Oliver Queen, do solemnly swear
to faithfully
and impartially perform and discharge
the duties of the office of mayor.
- Your brother's late.
- "Late" is his "on time."
And he's not just my brother,
he's the Mayor.
Well, maybe someone should
remind him of that.
Is there something
I can help you with, Captain?
This evening is important, Miss Queen.
And it's supposed to be the kickoff
to the Anti-Crime Initiative.
And I don't think I need to tell you
how much this city...
City needs the A.C.l. Yes, I know
and so does he so he will be here.
He's just taking care
of a little business first.
Blonde or redhead?
Brunette actually.
I found the bomb.
No, no, no. That's not "a bomb,"
that's one, two, three, four bombs.
I'm in the brains.
It's gonna take a while to disarm.
- Do you think you can keep Machin busy?
- I don't think that'll be a problem.
Does this mean you're not gonna kill me?
What's a guy got to do
to get a little love?
I only tried blowing up the city.
I mean, half of it.
Sleep.
Tell SCPD I left a present for them.
Get away from that!
I'm disarming it.
It's handled. Overwatch?
Yeah. Oh, man,
that thing's just a really ugly piece
of modern art now.
Aw. You gonna make a new friend?
I thought I told you
to stay off the streets.
- It's my city, too.
- You wanna help?
Yeah.
Then make a donation
to the police department.
- And keep that elevated.
- Keep what elevated?
I don't want to see you out here again.
The Mayor will be making his official
statement on the Anti-Crime Initiative
at the ceremony honoring
the Black Canary, but...
But he can say a few words now.
The A.C.l. is an important step
towards lowering crime in the city,
but I'm not gonna consider it
without some major reform.
What type of reforms?
Uh, to start,
an investigation into allegations
of widespread corruption
within the police department.
Okay. Mayor Queen will elaborate
on all comments
at the ceremony honoring the Black Canary.
Thank you all very much.
You realized you just
accused the police department
of being corrupt
at the police department gala?
I answered a question.
Yeah, and you also just put blame
on the police department
instead of taking responsibility
for the city's crime.
- You know I'm taking responsibility.
- Yeah. As the other guy.
But as the Mayor, it looks like
you're sleepwalking, okay?
Showing up late again
is not helping that perception.
Being the Mayor gives me access
to actionable intel as "the other guy."
It's a means to an end.
Well, it didn't start off
like that, Ollie.
You wanted to become
and then became the Mayor
- to actually be Mayor.
- Right. And then reality set in.
Even if we weren't dealing with
a corrupt police department, and we are,
or an electorate that thinks
I got all my political knowledge
by binge-watching The West Wing,
I still wouldn't be able to focus
on being the Mayor, Speedy.
Because I'm flying solo
as "the other guy."
Okay, nice try.
Talk to the comptroller
about tax incentives.
- And Councilman Garcia about sanitation.
- Mmm-hmm.
I also put the applications
for Deputy Mayor on your desk.
I'm gonna go drink.
What I do care about is what
you promised me if I won tonight.
None of yours.
What?
Whose'?
What are you two doing here?
- It's late.
- That's what I told her,
but she's been complaining
that the secondary processor
keeps overclocking the GPU cache.
It must be nice to have someone
down here who speaks Felicity.
Well, I'm strictly repair and maintenance.
You guys are the vigilantes.
Yeah, well, it's getting to be
an awfully big club.
- What's this?
- A little dossier on Wild Dog.
- "Wild Dog?"
- Yeah, you know, 'cause of his shirt.
"Silly Dog" just didn't really
have the same ring to it.
I suggested the "Wild."
Right. And why do I need a dossier on him?
So, I was thinking,
instead of putting an arrow in him,
you might consider
bringing him into the fold.
He shot him? You shot him?
Okay, I know it's not the most enticing
of recruitment pitch plans.
But there are plenty of candidates
willing to compensate
for our ineffectual-slash-corrupt
police department.
Evelyn Sharp. Mr. Ski Goggles.
I'm still work-shopping that codename.
I'm not...
I'm not putting together a new team.
Okay, well, in case you haven't noticed,
we're a little short-handed.
Just for a little while.
John will come back.
- Thea will come back.
- And if they don't?
Then I will handle it.
Get some sleep. Both of you.
SCPD! We have you surrounded.
Guns on the floor, now!
What is this? These aren't our guys.
No, they're Los Halcones.
See, they tried to rob you tonight.
A shoot-out ensued.
You killed them. They killed you.
Drop the bodies,
empty the cash into the van.
Bravo! Cleverness and efficiency.
Very Robin Hood.
But I doubt that
you'll be providing the poor
with any of these ill-gotten gains.
Enlighten me.
- I'm new in town.
- Kill this prig.
Note! Any attempt to "kill this prig"
will result in your swift demise.
- Are you the one in charge?
- Go to hell.
Oh...
I'll take that as a "yes."
Okay, gang-
He said he was in charge.
Anybody else want to be in charge?
No takers? Then I guess
it's gonna have to be me.
Six DOA's. The dealer and his girlfriend,
two Los Halcones and one of our own.
And who's lucky Number Six?
Keating.
COD doesn't match the other vics,
who were all shot at close range,
- but Keating...
- Blunt force trauma.
And these, what?
Some sort of calling card?
M.O. matches a skel named Tobias Church.
According to his jacket, he and his crew
tore up Hub City and Blüdhaven.
- And now he's here.
- Question is, what was Keating doing here?
Nothing good.
He didn't call anything in.
You think he's one of the bent cops?
It doesn't matter. He's dead now.
Well, Lance was a royal pain in the ass,
but at least he kept
his department in line.
Well, you could always give him
his badge back. He's back in town.
Though word has it he took a few bumps
off the wagon on his way.
All right, all right, all right.
All right.
Knockin', that's not like you.
Give us a minute.
- How long you been back in town?
- Uh, couple of weeks.
- Where's Donna?
- She's in Heaven.
It's a casino in Vegas that
she's waitressing at these days. Not...
- So you two aren't, uh...
- Oh, come on, Oliver.
- Opposites attract, but not that much.
- Did you break up before...
Well, you know,
not that it's any of your business.
But you see, a drunk needs a reason
to stay sober.
Fresh out, my friend.
Well, Quentin...
You know what? I don't know if you're in
a position to be judging me anyway.
It's just me out there.
Sometimes, saving the city
takes priority over running it.
But that'll change
when the team gets back together.
I can devote more time
to actually being the Mayor.
That team could include you.
Would I cover up
this beautiful face with a mask?
That's not what I meant.
Is there anything else
I can help you with, Oliver?
I got a pretty full day ahead.
You know about the ceremony?
The city's gonna honor Laurel.
Yeah.
It's probably best I don't turn up
and embarrass her memory, then.
You killed my best fighter.
You cost me lots of money.
Your Russian's terrible.
Your accent's American.
So,
what are you doing so far from home?
Adam Hunt. Daniel Brickwell.
Frank Bertinelli.
If I were you...
I'd put that back in my bag.
Jason Brodeur. Leo Mueller...
I said, put it back.
You know what?
This book, it intrigues me.
It's the only reason
you are still breathing.
It was my father's.
I'm waiting to use it.
Waiting for what?
To be ready.
Well, I have some bad news for you.
You're going to be dead before you are.
You must be lost. City Hall is that way.
Wanted to see
if you had info on our new player.
And you wonder why your approval rating
is in the basement.
- I don't wonder.
- How'd you ditch your security detail?
I used to ditch John Diggle.
Yeah. Tobias Church.
AKA "Charon."
The ferryman of Hades. Left gold coins on
the eyes on one of his victims last night.
Well, well, well...
I didn't fail every course
that I took in college.
Warrants out for his arrest
on no less than 20 murders
and those are just the ones
that they can connect him to.
Mr. Church just became our top priority.
"Our" is not going
to be enough for this guy.
Okay. Felicity...
Church runs with a crew.
And yours is not coming back.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
It's called "not being in denial."
You really ought to give it a try.
Look, for the past five months,
you have been frozen in amber.
Waiting for things to go back
to the way things were, they're not.
You need to move forward.
Especially, with guys like this
coming into town.
Don't worry about him.
He's not gonna be staying very long.
Just find a way
for me to find him, please.
- Why isn't he at City Hall?
- That's a question I keep asking myself.
- What are you workin' on?
- If Oliver's asking,
- a location for our new baddie in town.
- And if he's not asking?
Got an address for this guy.
You mind checking him out for me?
I'm a happily married man, Felicity.
Just see what you can find out.
Like, if he's loco or anything.
We are callin' him the "Wild Dog."
Isn't that already settled?
- Please?
- No.
- Please.
- Okay. Fine.
Cities are like gen pop. First day in,
you find the biggest guy in the yard,
put him down. Hard. Sends a message.
"Screw not with me."
So here we all are.
Now who's the biggest guy in the yard?
It's highly unlikely that
he will just come out to play.
But it's like my younger brother
always said,
"Don't fish without bait."
Thank you all for coming.
With all that ails our city,
I think it's fair to ask
why we would spend time and money
to honor anyone.
Why we would commission a statue
and have a ceremony to unveil it.
Surely those resources
could be put to better ends.
But I for one think
there is no better end than a reminder
of what we are capable of
when we stand together united.
A reminder of those
who have made the ultimate sacrifice
protecting our home.
And a reminder that as long as
we keep their spirit in our hearts,
there will always be better days ahead.
And as she reminds us,
let us always remember her.
Ladies and gentlemen, Laurel Lance.
The Black Canary.
Whoa!
- Felicity.
- We saw it.
Why didn't Oliver fight back?
Sorry. Really dumb question.
- Yeah, well, can we track the van?
- No, they shut down traffic cameras.
And there're no satellites over the area.
We're blind.
Okay, well, if that SCPD van was legit,
then the police are gonna be no help.
Well, maybe this is a job for Speedy.
Can you suit up
and hit the streets for intel?
Can you maybe try to hack into
the police department
and see if there is any
internal chatter we can go on?
Gentlemen. And lady.
This is not personal.
I know it feels personal. But it is not.
You are all here as a means to an end.
I finally figured out a way
to make politicians useful.
You want the Green Arrow?
Ooh.
Your Honor.
Listen, the Green Arrow is not coming.
You're wasting your time.
Just for the fun of it, how is it that you
know so much about Mr. Arrow?
I have it on pretty good authority
that he's tied up right now.
- Are you his buddy?
- I have connections.
And I... Listen.
You let these people go,
and I'll make something happen.
Do we have a deal?
No, we most certainly do not.
I don't need your help, Mr. Mayor.
Do you think I would go to
all this trouble without a plan?
Yeah.
But that's because I think you're stupid.
Take Mr. Queen to a quieter place
and teach him some manners.
You almost shot my friend in the head.
Leave us.
My book!
Oliver Queen. My brother.
Anatoly. It is very good to see you.
What are you doin'?
Ahh!
I just dislocated thumbs. Useful if
getting tied to chair is to become habit.
- This is going to hurt little.
- Son of a bitch!
Yeah, with bit of practice
you can do yourself anytime.
Anatoly, can't you bring
a knife next time?
What is fun of that?
My old friend, I thought you dead!
Well, if you hadn't have shown up,
I probably would be.
It's good to see you, tovarisch.
What are you doing in Russia?
I'm here to kill Konstantin Kovar.
If this is true, I did you no favor
by saving your life just now.
We got a twenty
on Oliver's location.
- Felicity and Curtis?
- Neither.
Felicity says it's probably the work of
a "Tobias Church."
And look, he's done his homework too
'cause he knows the Green Arrow is workin'
with someone who's tapped into
the city's security cameras of...
Okay, so, he's trying to call
the Green Arrow out.
Yeah, except he doesn't know
he's already got him. Cute, huh?
All right, well, you...
You need to go do something.
Well, that was...
That was gonna be my line to you.
For the first time in a...
A long time, I'm really starting
to feel like myself again.
I'm not a killer,
I'm not a vigilante, lam...
I am a normal version of me.
And I think just after everything
that happened with Laurel...
I really needed to know
that life like this was even possible.
And now that I do,
I don't wanna give it up.
Yeah, yeah, I get
where you're coming from.
I do. I lost my job, I lost my...
I lost my daughter, I lost my girl,
and you know I just wanted to hit pause
on the world, you know?
- Yeah.
- But then I, uh...
You know, what?
I listened to Oliver's speech.
Well, you know, that's
when I realized that I, I can't do that.
I can't hit pause on it when I gotta
get on with my life, you know?
Even if that life
isn't what I want it to be.
I didn't vote for you.
That's okay. I ran unopposed.
"Mayor Handsome," they call you.
Not for long, though.
If you hit me again...
- I'm gonna kill you.
- You're delusional.
You're zipcuffed to that chair.
- Please, don't...
- I'm sorry. But nobody can know my secret.
- I thought you retired.
- Yeah, me too.
Speedy!
There are wires. They've been rigging
explosives to set up a kill cordon.
- A what?
- If we try to get down there
- we're gonna blow everything up.
- I can't just leave them there.
No!
We'll come back for them.
Felicity's already looking
for the power station blueprints.
Now, if we can get past
that kill cordon, we...
Then we can kill all of Church's men
instead of just those guys?
- Excuse me?
- I saw you break that guy's neck, Ollie.
You murdered him, okay. I thought
you weren't doing that anymore.
Maybe if I showed a little less restraint,
Laurel might still be alive.
Okay, you cannot keep hiding behind that.
And you know that's not
what she would have wanted.
You know, Thea, you told me
that the dead don't want anything.
Now, I could have killed Damien Darhk
before that night at Iron Heights.
I had multiple chances to do so.
And I didn't.
Because I thought
that taking the high road
was more important than saving lives.
And that is a mistake
that I will never ever make again.
I wouldn't call not killing people
a mistake, Ollie...
I would. Because when I did take
Darhk down for good,
I had to confront the fact
that Malcolm Merlyn was right.
Either I'm willing to do
whatever is necessary
or I shouldn't be out there at all.
Which is exactly why I can't be.
I won't ever again.
- Thea...
- No, no.
Ollie, lam sorry, but I wanna honor
Laurel just as much as you do.
Just not like this. And I don't care
what your reasons are,
putting killing back on the table
is a huge step backwards.
And I don't want anything to do with it.
- Sorry that you had to hear that.
- Hazard of the job. You okay?
I just... Seeing Thea in the suit, it made
me feel like everything was gonna
get back to normal.
Well, I'm running out of different ways
to tell you that it's not.
Hey. Look, being a vigilante
is not just putting on a mask
and thinking up a codename.
These people are amateurs, Felicity.
You really think that they're gonna
replace Dig or Thea or Laurel?
They couldn't do that if I wanted them to.
And I don't want them to.
They're already out there, Oliver.
Because of you.
- Inspired by you.
- After what happened with Laurel,
how can you ask me to put
more people in the crosshairs?
Lam not the one who is asking.
Or do you not remember the promise
that you made to Laurel before she died?
Laurel was thinking about the future.
You need to think about yours.
Right now, I need to think of ways
to stop Tobias Church.
- Oliver...
- So, you let me know
when you find a way around
the kill cordon.
Nothing ever simple with you,
Oliver Queen.
You survive Lian Yu, twice, you say.
And instead of going home,
you come to mine.
Well, I didn't know this was your town.
Or that you're a Bratva boss...
- Avtoritet. It's like a captain.
- Right.
- What business do you have with Kovar?
- It's a promise that I made.
What, that you'll kill him?
Or that you die trying?
'Cause second's much more likely.
Okay, Anatoly, you just need to tell me
if you can get me close to him.
Kovar has army. Government soldiers.
It's very dangerous.
You're sure you want to risk your life
for this promise?
- "The shark that does not swim, drowns."
- What does that mean?
I know real reason why you not go home.
You're not swimming.
This business with Kovar.
It's old promise. It's in past.
You need to move forward, my friend.
You need to move ahead. Move on.
All right. But the only way will kill you.
- Curtis?
- Okay.
This is the craziest
super-hero scavenger hunt
I have ever been on.
Not that I've ever been on any, but...
Wild Dog isn't a "super hero."
He's a vigilante.
You are really gonna have to explain
the distinction to me.
Either way, we'd have better luck
with an ad in the paper.
No one reads the classifieds anymore.
Why don't you just come on back,
and we'll figure out our next move.
You got it.
What do you want?
Hey, this is John. Leave a message.
Hey, John. Um...
I hope that everything's going well
over there.
Listen, no pressure, but give me
a call back when you get a chance. I...
I have a question and I figure
you'd probably have an answer.
Be well.
Lonely at the top, Mr. Mayor?
Actually, being the Mayor
isn't the job that's lonely.
- Thea?
- Thea's not coming back.
Neither is John.
There's a Russian proverb,
been thinking about it a lot recently.
"The shark that does not swim
"drowns."
You don't move forward, you die.
But listen, you will die if you try takin'
on this Tobias Church by yourself.
There's no more team, Quentin.
And I can't trust anyone
on the department.
Then don't. Just trust these guys.
Lieutenant Conahan.
I trained him back in the day.
The guy is so clean,
he doesn't even double park.
And he's vouched for each
of these officers.
- To do what?
- To help you
- whatever way we can.
- "We"?
Look, I don't know
any Russian proverbs, all right?
- But both of us have got to move on.
- Yeah.
Boy, I thought
that was gonna be a bigger fight.
That's what Laurel would've wanted.
After tonight,
I realize anything can happen,
which is why I need you to
make me a promise.
- Anything.
- Please...
Please don't let me be the last Canary.
That way, a part of me will always be
out there with you.
I promise.
There's nothin' out there.
Gonna grab a smoke.
We're in.
Copy that.
I'm gonna disarm the bombs. Fisher'll take
the others and get the councilmen.
All right, watch your back, all right?
I got you from here.
And where do they think "here" is,
- exactly?
- I forgot to mention that.
I am jealous.
I've been trying to get Oliver
to work with a team for weeks now.
- They're not a team.
- Well, you can look it up.
A team is, "a group of persons
associated with a joint action."
Duck.
Goose.
That's more like it.
Hey! Don't worry!
After I kill you,
I will let the hostages go. I promise.
Taking heavy fire.
- Fisher?
- I need backup.
Conahan, Fisher's catching heat.
Can you assist?
Negative.
We got a bigger problem.
Church has wired the conductor.
The conductor is in the center of... If it
goes, the whole building's gonna blow.
You have to get out of there.
Not without Church.
The whole power plant is gonna go up.
There's nothing I can do to stop it.
Get them out of here.
- I'll disarm the cordon.
- I got it.
Overwatch!
Hostages are safe.
You have maybe five seconds.
Hey. Keep her flying.
Good morning.
I had intended to state my position
on the Anti-Crime Initiative
during the city's tribute
to the Black Canary
but that speech was cut short.
In the intervening days,
I have refined my position.
Now, I have been reluctant
to embrace the A.C.l.
because of widespread corruption
within our police department.
But these four officers have shown me
and the entire city
that there are still good men
and women in the SCPD.
Today, I'm announcing the formation
of the Anti-Crime Unit.
These four officers will report
directly to me.
And by working together,
we will begin the process
of saving our city.
Wanna thank you all for comin' out.
Wanna thank you all
for deciding to hear my vision.
The Green Arrow
cannot be stopped. Unless...
Unless we all work together.
Under a singular command.
- And I suppose that leader'd be you?
- You need someone from the outside.
I know this because it took me less than
12 hours to get inside your organizations.
All of them.
What's that mean? "Get inside"?
It means that, Mr. Bertinelli.
What are you still doing here?
Thought you'd be out celebrating
after your big win.
Well, it wasn't exactly a win.
You went from being the Do-Nothing Mayor
to the Rockstar Mayor
in under 24 hours.
I would say that that qualifies.
- Church is still out there.
- I'm not worried about that.
What with your new unit of super-cops
and the new team of vigilantes
you're gonna be recruiting,
Church is gonna see
the inside of a cell in no time.
- I see what you did there.
- What did I do?
You talked about the new team
like it's a done deal.
Oh, that. Well, I just thought,
since you decided to
"keep swimming" as mayor you might do
the same as Green Arrow.
You might be right.
Lance told me about the Russian proverb,
by the way. Very poetic. Wait,
did you just say I might be right?
Are you okay?
- Been looking into your guy.
- Wild Dog?
- Says here, his name is Rene Ramirez.
- Yeah, but "Wild Dog" is much scarier.
- So by "looking into," does that mean...
- I'm thinking of recruiting him.
- Good.
- You better.
Because if you don't, I have no idea
what I went through this for.
- Oh, my God, what happened?
- I was looking for Mr. Dog,
and then I was jumped by two insanely
aggressive guys with knives.
Do you remember
what they looked like?
Yes, and I will tell you everything
on one condition.
You recruit me too.
Okay.
Kovar face many threats.
Many people want to kill him.
Only people who have power
to get past his army are Bratva.
So,
first you say that this is gonna kill me,
and now it looks like
you wanna initiate me.
Unless you are careful,
it will be one and same.
Okay, Anatoly.
So, I survive this.
Then I'm Bratva.
You survive this,
you can begin process of becoming Bratva.
Hey, buddy. How you doin'?
Well,
besides feeling like I've got the worst
case of déjà vu ever, not bad.
- How about you? You still the mayor?
- Yeah.
They haven't voted me out yet, so...
Yeah, well, give it a little bit of time
and they'll come to their senses.
I got your message. You all right?
I'm all right. I just, I...
I wanted to bounce something off of you.
And get your perspective.
Okay? On?
Felicity thinks that it's time
we put together a new team.
And you want to know if I think
that's a good idea?
I do.
I think it is.
Wasn't exactly the response
you were looking for, right?
No, no.
But I'm not surprised. Uh...
I need to make peace with the fact
that things aren't gonna go back
to the way they were.
- So, does that include you and Felicity?
- I don't know.
- Mmm. You're a magician.
- Tough day?
Mmm, just long.
Better now.
Hey, honey. Yeah, I'm headed home.
Yeah, it was a good day. It was real good.
Diapers and formula. You got it.
I'll be home in a bit.
How you doing? Help you with somethin'?
Green Arrow?
No. I'm not Green Arrow.