My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years I was stranded on
an island with only one goal--
to survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list of names
he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Stop looking into this.
It's not safe.
Accidents tend to befall people
who are too curious.
Felicity, I want you
to find out all you can
about that book.
I got these from applied sciences.
Look at the book again.
Where can I find the man
in this picture?
Aah!
Island dangerous, but you
not tell them where to find me.
I'm coming with you.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
Look, all I'm doing is looking
to get something going again.
Yeah, I know.
I know, but this time--
[creaking]
I have to call you back.
What?
Did you come back for
another pound of flesh?
You're gonna be
disappointed, pal.
Thanks to you, I'm--
[thwack thwack thwack]
Nice. Picking up the pace.
I could say the same thing
about you.
You crossed 3 names off
your father's list this week alone.
Yeah, well, some of these guys
are just giving it up now.
All I gotta do
is pay 'em a visit.
It seems the vigilante's reputation
is beginning to precede him.
Ah!
Whoo.
[Groans]
Another round?
No.
Gonna take my nephew
over to the mall
so he can let Santa know
what he wants for Christmas.
Oh. Christmas.
I didn't even realize.
That was because you've been
logging in so many hood hours
ever since that thing
with Helena.
I meant...
There were no holidays
on the island.
Every day was...
How do I stay alive?
To do that,
you had to forget things,
like Christmas.
My dad threw a party
every year,
and he would put
a Christmas tree in every room.
The whole mansion
smelled like...
It smelled like Christmas.
Maybe you can
give the list a rest
and just enjoy
the holidays with the family.
Besides, I hear St. Nick
has a list of his own.
I wager you're in
the "nice" column.
Go home, Oliver.
[Rocks falling]
You not, uh, hurt?
Where the hell you been?
I ran out of food and water
days ago.
Hey--hey,
where are you going?
You--
Uhh! Oh!
Stop!
Stop.
He's the one who tied me up
and had me tortured.
All 'cause he was looking
for you.
He would've killed me
if you didn't show up!
Then you kill him.
[Coughs]
Or he can take you home.
What?
He has a plane.
A way for you
off this island.
Hey. You look very pretty.
What's the occasion?
Mom and Walter are having
a dinner party
with some big
muckety-mucks.
Best night of my life.
Thea, why aren't there
any decorations up in the house?
What do you mean?
No wreaths, no trees.
Everyone has just been
really busy lately.
I'm sure they haven't
got around to it yet.
Does mom at least have some
of those boxes of candy canes?
Remember we used to race
to see who'd finish first?
Yeah. I always won.
No. You cheated.
Well, she went
sugar-free last year,
so I doubt you'll be seeing
any of those around.
The thing that people forget
is that Robin Hood
was a criminal.
And stealing from the rich
to give to the poor
is really the job
of the Democrats.
[Chuckling]
All joking aside,
Commissioner,
crime is down
for the first time in 5 years.
That's because of the changes
my department has implemented.
Or perhaps it's because
the vigilante's activities
have had a chilling effect
on the city's criminals.
What are your thoughts,
Oliver?
I think the vigilante
needs a better code name
than "The Hood"
or "The Hood Guy."
[Laughter]
I agree.
How about Green Arrow?
Lame.
[Cell phone rings]
Forgive me.
It's the office.
Excuse me.
I'm in the middle of a dinner party,
Ms. Smoak,
so I hope this is
of some importance.
I guess that depends
on how you define important.
See, most people would consider
finding a list of names
written in subsonic ultraviolet
invisible ink important.
But then I already
know that, now, don't I?
Did you know 7 of the names
on the list
are guys the vigilante's
had in his crosshairs?
That is, if bows
had crosshairs.
Which they don't.
Well, it is a rather
long list, Felicity,
so I would expect there
to be some overlap.
Like Doug Miller.
Head of Applied Sciences
at Queen Consolidated.
What of him?
Mr. Miller may end up
getting an arrow in his stocking,
because he's on the list.
So, important or not?
[Whispering]
I'm sorry.
Something's come up.
Is everything okay?
The vigilante has struck again.
He just put an arrow
in Adam Hunt.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Oops.
I really do need to take this call.
It's my contractor.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Well, the daughter came over,
used her key, found dad.
Hat trick to the chest.
The hood guy.
That's what I thought
at first.
But these black arrows
aren't consistent with his M.O.
And neither is the fact
that the Hood
took hunt for $40 million
a few months ago.
It doesn't make sense
to kill him now.
Something
doesn't add up.
We're dealing with
a copycat.
♪ Arrow 1x09 ♪
Year's End
Original Air Date on December 12, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Who would kill Adam Hunt
with an arrow?
I mean, other than you?
A setup, maybe.
You mean someone looking
to cover up killing Hunt
by making it look like
the work of the Hood?
Whoever he was, he's good.
The grouping on hunt's
chest was tight.
It's a compound bow,
most likely.
The guy is a...
The guy's
a legitimate archer.
So someone who would be
particular
about his choice of arrows.
We get an arrow,
we get a bead on where
he purchased them.
So what are you gonna do?
What anyone does
when they need help.
Call a cop.
Quentin Lance?
Yeah.
Sign here, please.
Thanks.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Lance.
[Voice altered]
I didn't kill Adam Hunt.
You...
You call me the Hood.
It's not a great nickname.
You told commissioner Nudocerdo
that you might be dealing with a copycat,
Another archer,
which makes me your best bet
to take him down.
But I need your help.
I need one of the arrows
from his murder.
Yeah, we're pretty good at pulling
down leads off evidence. Thanks.
Not like I am. I can do things
the police can't,
go places they won't.
Like I said,
I don't even know who--
If this archer doesn't stop
with Adam Hunt,
we both have a problem.
Think about it.
Then call me.
Number's programmed in.
[Door opens]
Doug. Thanks for coming.
Of course.
How is the construction
coming along
on the Applied Sciences
Center?
Over budget
and behind schedule.
Exactly as expected.
Is that what you wanted
to see me about?
No.
Adam Hunt. He was murdered
last night by the vigilante.
I read about that.
I've been concerned
by the idea
that the vigilante
might target an employee
or officer of this company.
Security red-flagged you.
Me? Why would this guy
go after me?
Well, that's a point I was
hoping you could shed some light on.
You got me.
From what I've read,
this vigilante only goes after
white-collar criminals.
Well, let's just hope
he doesn't decide to branch out.
I think there should be
a national holiday
for the guy that
invented French fries.
Or at least a statue
or something.
There is no Christmas party,
is there?
Thea, dad threw one of these
every year.
Do people think I just
wasn't gonna notice?
Hi, Thea.
Hi. Shane.
This is my brother
Oliver.
Nice to meet you, Thea's brother.
I bet the food on that island is better
than this stuff
they're serving here, huh?
You'd lose that bet.
We're heading down to the bay
to hang out if you want to come.
Thanks, but I'm spending
the afternoon with my brother.
Another time.
See ya.
How do you know
that Shane guy?
We rob banks and smoke
crack together.
That's funny, yeah. I have a feeling
I'm not gonna be a fan.
You don't even know him.
Let's change the subject.
Fine. You were gonna tell me
why we're not having
the annual Christmas party.
[Sighs]
When you and dad
disappeared,
by the time Christmas
rolled around,
none of us felt
much like celebrating,
so we kind of skipped
Christmas that year.
Every year.
And it's really fine,
so...
No. No, it's really not.
We're celebrating Christmas.
I went 5 years without it,
and then Thea tells me
that you guys didn't have it either
and I'm the reason.
So maybe now
I can be the reason
we have Christmas again.
I thought I would throw
the Queen Christmas party.
You?
I know that I haven't
been the son
or the stepson
or the brother
that all of you deserve.
Especially lately.
But this feels like
the right moment
to start making up
for lost time.
What do you say?
I say yes.
Yes! Okay. I will take
care of everything.
You don't have
to do anything.
Just show up,
look fantastic,
and bring some
Christmas cheer, okay?
Okay.
Fine.
You're a good man, Oliver.
You're a good man.
I can see it.
Well, beneath the privileged
upbringing and the wealthy veneer.
I saw it when my man
tortured you
and you wouldn't give up
your friend.
Not even a friend, really.
Someone you just met.
Shut up.
What do you know him?
Nothing, I suspect.
Do you even know
what this island really is?
It's a prison.
I mean this literally.
Until 8 years ago,
the Chinese military
operated this island
as a penitentiary
for criminals
deemed so dangerous,
they couldn't be safely
incarcerated on the mainland.
When the military
shut the program down,
my unit came in and disposed
of all the inmates.
With the exception of two.
Your friend was one of them.
Who was the other?
You met him.
He presided over
your interrogation.
He tortured me.
You had information
I needed.
What would you do
in my position?
to capture the man
who slaughtered
dozens of people?
Douglas Miller came to see me today,
quite concerned.
He said your husband
interrogated him,
and his questions suggested
a knowledge he shouldn't have
of the list.
Let me talk to him.
I think we're past the point
of conversation, Moira.
A month ago you came to me
and you told me
to stay away from
your family, and I did.
But your family isn't
staying away from me.
Which means something
must be done about it.
Don't you agree?
Yes, I do.
And I'll handle it.
I guess what I'm wondering is,
whether it's time for
our associate to handle it.
Hell, yeah,
I returned the money.
$70 million isn't worth getting
an arrow through the chest.
And you can tell him,
if he's got a problem
with that, he can--
[thwack thwack]
Commissioner,
this is Nelson Ravich.
The Hood hit him
earlier this week.
Ravich wired back the money he
embezzled less than 5 minutes later.
All right.
We tell the press
the Hood did this.
Hunt's murder
is a page 10 story, at best.
But Ravich makes this
a serial murder case.
We can't let the public
get wind of the idea
that there are two
of these nut jobs running around.
You want me to ignore
a serial killer.
Just catch one of these psychos.
I don't care which one.
That is a direct order
from your commanding officer.
Well, you can forget it, then.
Fine.
It's forgotten.
And you're off
this case, Sergeant,
effective immediately.
[Ringing]
Don't bother trying
to trace this back to me.
You'll never make it
through the encryption.
There's a heating vent
on the corner of O'Neil and Adams.
You'll find what
you're after there.
It'd be a mistake
to set a trap for me, Detective.
I'm trading away just about
everything I believe in here
'cause it's the only
way I've got to get this bastard.
You got till Christmas.
And then, copycat or not...
I'm coming after you.
So your friend Lance gave you
a Christmas present after all.
-Hmm.
Teflon-coated titanium blade
serrated to split the bone.
Shaft is some type
of specialized polymer,
which is stronger than
a typical carbon fiber.
This...this is
a custom job.
So Lance gave in after after the
other archer dropped another body.
Nelson Ravich.
Which is another name
you crossed off
your dad's list.
So is this guy trying to frame you
or call you out?
Either way,
I need to find him.
Oh.
Hey.
[Gasps] Don't you knock?
Felicity, this is
the I.T. department.
It's not the ladies room.
Right.
What can I do for you?
My buddy Steve
is really into archery.
Apparently
it's all the rage now.
I don't know why. It's looks
utterly ridiculous to me.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, it's Steve's
birthday next weekend,
and I wanted
to buy him some arrows.
The thing is, he gets these special
custom-made arrows,
and I have no idea
where he gets them.
I was hoping you could find out
where this came from.
- Careful.
- Yeah.
The shaft's composite
is patented.
And that patent is registered
to a company called Sagittarius.
That's Latin for the archer.
Really?
Could you find out
where and when
this was purchased?
According to Sagittarius
company records,
that particular arrow
was part of a bundle shipment.
200 units.
Sent...
to this address.
Felicity...
You're remarkable.
Thank you for remarking
on it.
And Merry Christmas.
I'm Jewish.
Happy Hanukkah.
The significant resources
of the Starling City police department
is clear that this vigilante's
cycle of violence has escalated.
I'm asking our citizens
to keep a close eye out
and to report
anything suspicious.
A tip line has been set up,
and a reward
will be offered
to anyone who aids
the authorities
in the capture
of this madman.
It isn't him,
is it?
We are all frustrated with the
crime plaguing our city.
The man in the hood
didn't kill those people.
You're the one who said
he was a monster.
He was
protecting me.
It's different.
...the apprehension
of this so-called "Hood"
that has been
terrorizing our city.
[Knock on door]
As police commissioner...
It's probably Joanna.
She said she was going
to come by with some files.
Merry Christmas, sir.
How are you?
Proficient with firearms.
- Dad.
- Yeah.
I told you I wanted to spend
the holidays with my dad.
Right. Because of Sara.
Because it makes
the holidays a tough time.
But when you are
with someone,
as I want
to be with you,
then there aren't
tough times.
There's just times.
Something
is holding you back.
The Queens are having
a last-minute Christmas party,
and I would like for you
to be my plus one.
I, um, was looking through
some old photographs
and...I found this.
Merry Christmas.
Bad enough you're
friends with this guy,
and now he's your...what?
I don't know
what he is.
But he's not wrong.
Something
is holding me back.
Right. Keep listening
to that something.
I try to stay out of your
personal life, Laurel, I really do,
but these guys--
Merlyn, Queen--
I mean, they're selfish.
They think they can treat people
any way they damn please.
It's you, me, and Sara.
What?
[Thunder]
[Door slams]
[Zapping]
[Music playing]
I see the halls
are decked.
You okay?
I'll manage.
Is everyone having
a good time?
You sure you want
to do this, man?
Maybe now is not the best time
for you to be Martha Stewart's elf.
My family needs
this party, Diggle.
Which means
that I need it.
Hey, dude.
Thea invited me.
I hope that's cool.
These are for your mom.
Smooth.
Good luck, kid.
Thank you for coming.
Oliver.
You guys look great.
Merry Christmas.
Let's get
a holiday photo.
I already sent out
our Christmas cards, Oliver.
Mom, let's get a picture
just for the 4 of us.
Of course.
Excuse me. Mrs. Queen?
These are for you.
Well, thank you.
I'll--I'll go put this
in water.
Is everything all right?
You and I
should talk alone.
Everything okay between
the two of you?
Yeah. I'm sure
it'll work itself out.
So glad that both of you
could make it.
Merry Christmas, man.
Merry Christmas.
Hi.
So how long do you guys
think it'll be
till this isn't so weird?
You know, the 3 of us.
It's not weird at all.
[All laugh]
You lied to me.
An odd accusation
coming from you.
When you came home,
you said you were through
investigating Robert's death.
Robert was my oldest friend.
Do you take me for a man
who wouldn't avenge
his hist friend's murder?
I thought I could
forget about it,
go back to the way
things were.
But you told me
too many lies, Moira.
You embezzled money
from the company.
Salvaged the Queen's Gambit.
Why, Moira?
What was it all for?
For leverage.
Against whom?
People who you made
very angry.
Well, then let me
help you fight them.
I can't fight them.
I am them.
I have tried so hard
to convince myself that I'm not.
And loving you...
You were my salvation.
Moira.
Whatever you've done,
and whoever these people are,
the time for lies is over.
You need to tell me
exactly what's going on.
Let's just get through
the party...
And I promise I will
tell you everything.
Hmm.
Tommy, do you mind
if I talk to Oliver for a minute?
Yeah, I'll go grab
us a couple drinks.
And drink them both.
[Chuckles]
I know it's probably not easy
for you to see Tommy and I together.
Ah, the invitation
said "plus one",
not minus Laurel.
[Chuckles]
I've been wanting
to move forward with him,
but something's
been holding me back.
I keep making these excuses;
that it's my dad,
it's my work,
when really...
it's you.
But for five years,
I was emotionally...
off, because you had died.
And the truth is,
the last person
that I expected
to make me feel again...
has.
I'm happy.
For both of you.
Thank you.
♪ A merry little Christmas
♪ now
[rock music playing]
Thea, it's Ollie.
Oliver!
Hit the road.
What are you doing?
Funny, I was going
to ask you the same thing,
because there's a party
going on downstairs
that I threw for you.
I told you,
I didn't want a party.
But you didn't care.
Because you came down
with the holiday blues.
I've been trying to get you
to open up for months.
All this party is doing
is bringing back memories
I've been trying
to forget.
Thea!
Why would you want to forget?
No matter how fancy
the party is you throw,
things will never be the way
they used to be in our family.
Ever again.
Oliver?
What is it now?
The other archer's
moved to the next level.
This just hit the news.
He's taken hostages.
Happy holidays,
Starling City.
For the past three months,
this city has been laid
siege by a vigilante.
But the police have been
unable to bring him to justice
because they lack the will to do
what justice demands.
[Sobbing]
I will kill one hostage...
every hour in the name
of this vigilante
until he surrenders himself
to my authority.
[Sobbing]
Police are on the scene, Oliver.
I think you should let them handle this.
Those people are there because of me.
I have to end this.
Oliver, this guy...
this guy,
he's very dangerous.
Diggle, there wasn't
anything on the island
that wasn't twice as dangerous
as this pretender,
and I survived there
for five years.
[Static]
Call your people.
Tell them to bring the plane.
There's no need,
Yao Fei.
My people
will be here shortly.
Do you not think it convenient
you captured me so easily?
Go!
What?
Run!
[All grunting]
Starling City
holds its breath
as the hostage crisis unfolds.
Police have attempted to enter
the abandoned structure in the Glades,
but found rigged explosives
preventing them from doing so.
At the moment,
there's been no sign
of the vigilante as his
one hour deadline nears.
[Police radio chatter]
[Sighs]
I count three thresholds,
each wired by Mercury
switches to Semtex charges.
Can you diffuse one
for HRC to use as a breach point?
Well, that's going
to take a while
and then he's going to know
which way we're coming in.
You got a better
idea, Sergeant,
now would be
a lovely time.
Where is he?
I don't know.
It's going to be okay.
Follow me.
Get up on the roof.
What about...
I'll handle him.
Move!
Hostages.
We've got five hostages
on the roof.
Repeat, five hostages
Thank you for coming.
After the warehouse,
I knew I'd have to do
something dramatic
to get your attention.
What do you want with me?
What any archer wants--
to see who's better.
First Hunt, then Ravich,
and now you.
I know about the list,
and the man who authored it
wants you dead.
They call you the Hood.
Let's see what
you look like without it.
[Both grunting]
[Coughing]
Dig. [Coughing]
Help--help.
Hey, relax.
Relax. Just relax.
You're safe.
You're in the hospital.
[Exhales]
What happened?
I back traced your signal.
I cleaned you up
and got you out of there.
You've got a pneumothorax,
three broken ribs
and a concussion,
but the doctor said
you're going to be fine.
Some people are here to see you.
What?
[Exhales]
Are you
all right?
Oh, God,
you look terrible.
Well, thank God you were
wearing your helmet.
I told them how you were
on a bike and a semi
pulled right in front of you.
What were you
even doing out?
You bailed on your party.
It seemed like
the right move.
I mean,
like you said,
it...wasn't
the best timing.
[Sighs]
Okay, but when
I was saying that,
that was me being a bitch.
Oh, the truth is, I don't think any
of us were at our best.
The real truth is,
you wanted to have
a party to bring us
closer together.
Well...
here we are.
[Chuckles] Ahh!
We're going to let you
get some rest, hmm?
So...
We never got
to the exchanging presents part.
[Chuckles]
I don't think
I deserve a present.
Look, I know
that I've been hard on you,
about being different
from the way you were.
But the truth is,
Ollie, I'm not
the same person
I was five years ago, either.
So maybe we can just
accept each other.
Not for who we were,
but for the--
for the people
we are now.
Yeah.
Ohh!
No cheating.
You're on.
Come here.
Aww.
Thank you, Felicity.
It was good of you to call,
but Oliver's
going to be fine.
He's already on the mend.
I'm stepping into
an elevator,
so I'll probably lose you.
I'll call you
straight back. Bye.
It's done.
And he won't be harmed?
Nor will he ever discover
your involvement.
You have my word.
Forgive me if I don't
find that comforting.
You were warned,
Moira.
I told you to get
Walter under control,
and you couldn't.
Steps had
to be taken.
That's what you said
to justify Robert's murder.
And you wonder why
I don't trust you.
Quite a bid of judgment
coming from the woman
who had her son
kidnapped and tortured.
To prove to you that Oliver
didn't know anything.
And what does it matter now?
What's done is done.
No, Moira.
It's just beginning.
In six months,
the organization's vision of what
this city should be
will be complete.
And you won't feel
a thing then, will you?
Thousands of innocent people
will be dead,
and you'll feel nothing.
That's not true.
I'll feel a sense
of accomplishment.
And you'll have
Walter back.
[Car door closes]
[Exhales]
[Oliver groaning]
You know, Dig,
when I confront
somebody on the list,
I tell them
that they failed
the city.
But tonight,
it was me who failed.
Oliver, five hostages
are home tonight with their families
enjoying the holidays.
Because of you.
This guy,
the other archer...
He'll get his.
And you'll give it to him.
We might have
a bigger problem.
The other archer told me
that somebody compiled the list.
I always assumed
it was my father.
But what if it wasn't?
What do you mean?
I think there's
someone else out there.
Someone who's
more of a danger
than the archer.
And I am going
to take him down.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==