My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day,
I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
You cost me something dear to me.
My son.
- We decided to go our own way.
- Good luck.
It's our new lair. Helix used
to operate out of here
but it's not like
they're using it anymore.
So we've got 'em fighting with
each other instead of fighting us.
Vincent's working with them, too.
Oliver saw him with
James and the rest.
You don't understand.
You lying son of a bitch.
You were the Green Arrow for my dad.
That's right, William.
I'm sorry you had to step in.
I'm sorry you had to lie to your son.
I don't want to lie to him,
but I can do it if it's temporary.
I may have solved the glitch
in my chip.
It worked?
Looks like we are not as undermanned
as we thought.
Yes.
I'm a city councilman.
I deserve some respect.
Weather
for the next couple of days,
looking for mostly cloudy skies...
Hey, didn't your shift end
at 6:00, Doc?
That's what I keep
asking myself, Gilbert.
Hey, man.
Six.
Joe and I are going to
watch the game tonight
if you want to join us, Frank.
No. I wish I could.
Today is going to be a long one.
All right, everybody. Stay calm.
Whoa, what was that? What's happening?
Back away from the walls.
Move back away from the walls.
No, no. We gotta get out of here.
No, no, don't.
Bull's-eye.
Indeed it was, young man.
- Try again, please.
- Okay.
Yes! Ha!
These things... You win again.
Well, you must be out of practice
since you quit being the Green Arrow.
That must be it. Yeah.
- Ready for your field trip, yeah?
- Yeah.
- The Coastal Biology center, right?
There's a prep sheet for the trip
and I tried one of the extra credits.
Hold on.
- Will you take a look at it?
- Yeah, of course.
I meant Felicity.
Sure you did. Yep.
I'm sorry. It's a math problem
about hyperbolic geometry
in marine organisms like coral.
I do know what coral is,
but that's okay.
This is a high-dimension math problem
most people don't get it
until they're in 12th-grade AP.
And it's perfect.
Well, congratulations.
Take your Flash backpack
and don't miss your bus. All right?
- Okay.
- Get out of here. Go learn something.
- I know what coral is.
- Hmm.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
I think we've reached
maximum-level domesticity.
Oh, God, I certainly hope not.
- What's up?
- Councilman Grovner is dead.
- What?
- So are six people in the hospital
and five more electrocuted
by an elevator.
- In an elevator?
- By an elevator.
What? That...
That doesn't make any sense.
- Yeah, Quentin.
- We got a problem.
- An elevator...
- Electrocuted five people.
- Yeah, how do you know?
- I just know.
Look, grab Thea and I'll meet you
at the SCPD, okay?
Oliver, one of the casualties,
it's Frank Pike.
Oh.
I will see you soon.
Frank Pike is dead.
Can you get yourself...
Can you go to the bunker?
Can you find out what's going on,
please? Thank you.
Hey, that chip's really working.
Yeah, I never felt better.
- That's great.
- Or stronger.
- Everything all right?
- No, not even close.
The city is under some sort
of electronic attack.
- Cayden James?
- You gotta figure.
I mean, cars, cranes,
life support systems,
even elevators are killing people
all over town.
Yeah, hacking electronics I always
thought was a bit of a bank shot
when you have a thermobaric bomb
and amplifier.
And control the port.
- Right.
- It's Oliver.
- Hey, I'm on with John.
- What do we know?
Accidents are happening all over
the city. The size of this attack...
Gotta think it's Cayden James,
but to what end?
Well, should I get William home
or should I be happy
that he's heading out of the city?
Oh, for sure the second one.
Now let's think about looping
in Dinah, Curtis and Rene.
We may have gone our separate ways,
but we have the same goals.
Do it. We need all the help
we can get.
Mr. Mayor.
Quentin, I am...
I'm sorry about Frank. He was
a good cop and he was a better man.
Yeah, yeah, he sure was.
But he wouldn't want us standing
around here grieving, right?
Listen, 911 is on overload. Now we've
got no one here to run the show.
Yes, we do.
Just when I thought I was out.
Can you catch me up
on the status here?
Yeah, well,
the status keeps changing,
but I can tell you what we know
so far.
Not bad for one week's worth of work.
I would rather have a team I can
trust than any kind of technology.
Word.
- It's Felicity.
- She isn't bugging us again, is she?
No. I'll do a sweep.
- Hey.
Cayden is attacking the city
with a series of coordinated hacks.
He just crashed a plane.
Yeah, I know.
He can hack anything
that is connected to the Internet,
which is practically everything
these days.
So, I was thinking that our teams,
our two separate teams,
could share information.
Yeah, uh, that's a good idea.
We'll share
any and all information
that can help.
Okay, thanks, Curtis. I'll send you
what I've got so far.
I hope that's all right, guys.
I know we looked at each other,
but we actually didn't verbalize.
Oh, we agreed, Curtis.
- Frank Pike is dead.
- What?
He was killed by one
of Cayden James' hacks.
Is Felicity doing this?
Wait, that...
That can't be.
You know what?
The last time I saw it doing this,
it was tracking Vigilante's visor.
I know, but he modified
his electronics
to block our signal. But...
This is real.
It's locking on to him.
Because your balls never malfunction?
Really? Not this time.
All right, but, I mean...
Could he have messed up?
Did he forget we could track him?
No way, he's too devious.
I think the son of a bitch
is trying to draw us out.
Trap us.
I say we trap him.
You all in?
One, two, three... Suit up.
Yeah, I don't think we should say
"Suit up" all together.
It'd be really cool
if we did, though.
I don't think
it would be really cool.
I mean,
let's just be different than OTA.
Let's be like NTA
and say it together.
But we are NTA and we're cooler
without having to say "Suit up."
Listen, this is kind of what Oliver...
- I'm just saying...
- I'm just saying we should try...
I'm sorry I'm late. There was
an airplane crash on State Street.
It's awful. Is this the Cayden James
you've been talking about?
Most likely. Look, Quentin
can bring you up to speed.
I've asked him to run things here
with your help.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
Listen, we're taking
SCPD systems offline.
We're setting up communication trees
so officers can talk in person.
Okay, cool.
It's just like the old days.
I'm not that old.
Look, I think it's a great idea.
We should take everything
in the city's government on analog,
and that way, we're out
of James' reach.
In the meantime, we need to do
everything that we can
to minimize panic.
Why don't we set up libraries, uh,
gyms and civic centers
with SCPD protection?
We can take them completely off-grid.
People can come, feel safe.
Safe zones are a good idea.
Now, I have to get back to City Hall.
With the death
of Councilman Grovner...
- No, go.
- Go, go, go.
We got it.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
I got nothing in the alleyway.
Same for the parking garage.
Zilch here. Back to base?
What was that?
You're comm's breaking up.
Yeah, I'm getting some interference
on my side, too.
Can you guys hear me?
No, they can't.
You're jamming us.
I'll be brief.
I'm on your side.
Cayden James is my target, too.
I'm undercover with his organization.
You think this "T" on my face
stands for "gullible"?
You know what I mean.
I tried telling Dinah last week,
but she didn't give me the chance.
Right now, James is killing
dozens of people.
By tonight, it'll be hundreds.
I need your help.
Why should I trust you?
Go to the subway tunnels where
the Red Line and the Gold Line cross.
An hour from now.
You might be able to save some lives.
Or I could lead my teammates
into a trap.
I could have trapped you here.
But I didn't.
Harold Grovner was
a dedicated civil servant.
Who always wanted what was best
for this city
and we will not forget that.
But with everything
that is happening,
we don't have the time
to mourn at the moment.
So, please, let's get back to work.
Becky, I need Councilmen Gattis,
McCaskell and Kullens,
in that order please.
Your 10:00 a.m. is here.
I don't have a 10:00 a.m.
on my schedule, and even if I did...
I think you'll find this one's
rather important.
Ben Gayle, pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Mayor.
Thanks for making the time.
Thank you, Becky.
I'll let you make the usual threats
in a minute.
But before we get to that, you should
know that my colleagues are expecting
to hear from me in six.
And if they don't, well,
you would be remiss in forgetting
the thermobaric explosive
that remains in my possession.
What do you want?
I've already told you.
Vengeance for my son.
I cared for him, protected him,
loved him,
just as you do this city.
But now,
your city's entire infrastructure
is under my control.
Buildings, institutions, even people,
all under my dominion.
These are innocent people.
And you can save them...
By wiring $10 million
into that offshore account
no later than 11:30 tonight.
And every night.
Until further notice.
That will bankrupt us.
Well, I certainly hope so.
Please don't imagine that I've gone
to these lengths for money.
No, this is for you.
So that you'll suffer.
I didn't kill your son.
Yes, you did. One year ago,
this very day,
right here in Star City.
You missed your intended target,
but your arrow found its way
into my boy.
Are you seeking vengeance?
If you want revenge,
why haven't you just outed me
as the Green Arrow?
If my understanding is correct,
that's already been done.
Star City will not negotiate
with a terrorist.
Oh, spare me the political claptrap,
Mr. Queen.
By tonight,
that will sound hollow even to you.
You okay?
I have tried every trick
to counter-hack what Cayden is doing,
and I am completely boxed out.
So I contacted Alena
to help me figure out why
and the answer is,
is that it's my fault.
Felicity, what are you talking about?
When we stopped Cayden and Laurel
from blowing up the Internet vault?
Uh-huh.
That was all a ruse.
Cayden just wanted us to think
that people were in trouble
so that I would break through
his firewall,
but instead of blocking him, I was
actually helping him plant a virus.
Now he has complete control
of the entire city.
The hackcident is killing
one person every 18 minutes
and I have no idea how to stop it.
I do.
Thanks to Cayden James,
who was kind enough
to pay me a visit at City Hall.
- What did he want?
- He wants $10 million a day.
That's not the actual part. He told
me the details of his son's death.
He was killed one year ago today.
Cayden thinks that he was
collateral damage from a fight
that I had in Star City.
It's not possible.
You were in Hub City
recruiting Dinah.
Yup.
If Cayden James is motivated
by revenge,
maybe we can get him to stand down.
Oh, I like that idea, because I have
no way of stopping him my way,
and I have no location for you
to find him your way.
Felicity, we need
incontrovertible proof.
Yeah, I know. I'm on it.
I can't believe
we didn't catch Vincent.
He had a 20-minute lead on us.
Where have you been?
Long story.
I need to check on something.
- Hey.
If we're still sharing intel, I need
you to check on something for me.
Yeah. Shoot.
The subway system specifically
where the Red and Gold Line meet.
I'm trying to stave off a disaster.
Yeah, the automatic track signals
just went offline. How did you know?
- Lucky guess.
- You want backup?
Felicity, I appreciate the intel, but
we're not working together anymore.
My team can handle it.
Handle what?
Cayden James is going to attack
the subway in less than an hour.
I'd say suit up but we already are,
so let's go.
You guys, take a look at this.
This is the city's
transportation system,
and these are all the accidents
that have happened so far.
A lot around the edges.
The train lines and the freeways.
He's laying siege to the city.
It's probably why he wanted the port.
It's exactly what he's doing.
He wants to block off
all the exit routes.
And stop all the reinforcements
from the outside.
Any roads he hasn't hit yet?
Yeah, there's one exit left under
the city and it's the tunnel.
William.
I saw your new mom on TV.
She's pretty hot.
She read you bedtime stories?
Well, at least she can read,
unlike your mom.
This field trip,
it's going to be fun.
- You sure you're good?
- Yup, never better.
I had Cisco put this together.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
We need to move.
Let's go save your son.
Careful
around these metal lines.
Sometimes they can be electrified.
I know that, T. I'm not six.
I didn't know that.
Hey, these tracks are set to cross.
The trains are going to collide.
That could be the switch, that lever.
Pull it.
It's stuck.
These switch boxes are locked though.
All right, stand back.
Here we go.
Okay. Well, Plan B...
Actually, there's no Plan B because
Cayden James has completely
overwritten everything
we can do here.
- Maybe Plan C would be...
- Guys.
We can literally
just start pulling things out
till we get the right circuit.
Guys!
Pull it all out. Pull it all out!
It's not working. Hurry!
- Hey, what's Plan D?
- There's no Plan D.
- What?
- Yes, there is.
All right. I'm going to go see
what's going on.
You kids stay put.
I'm bored, Clayton.
Read us a story.
We have to get out of here.
Everyone stay calm and follow me.
We have to get out of the back.
We can still make it out.
Okay, come on. Move it, move it.
You two help them out.
Hurry, hurry.
Tony. We need to get out of here.
- Come on, come on.
- I can't. I can't.
We need to go! Go.
I need you to go. Go.
William! William!
There's William's bus.
Go, I'll take care of everyone else.
Open the door. Open the door. Move!
Come on! Come on.
Get to the door. Move, move.
Go, go, go!
Come on, keep your head down.
Where's William, Clayton?
- He's stuck behind the sign.
- Go, go.
Come on.
William.
You okay?
- All right, it's okay, it's okay.
- Dad.
We got everyone out safely.
Unfortunately, that tunnel was
the last way out of the city.
So, this is your secret hideout?
Yeah.
You said you weren't
the Green Arrow anymore.
John did take over for me,
but he got injured.
- Guess he's not injured anymore?
- No, he's not.
We've lost the other members
of our team, William, and...
I can't have him out there
on his own right now
with everything that's going on.
- Listen, buddy. I promise...
- You've promised before.
I need to go meet your Aunt Thea.
Could you please hang here?
Damn, that was so fire.
Hey, man, New Team Arrow
is kicking ass.
You know what? I really have to say
that I think we should change
our name.
What do you guys think
about "The Outsiders"?
Ooh. Um... I think
it was a really awesome book.
You guys, talking to Felicity
actually was a good idea.
I mean, if she hadn't given us that
intel, those people would be dead.
About that. I got that information
from Vincent Sobel.
- I'm sorry, what?
- I didn't trust him at first either.
Okay, but I called Felicity
to confirm if his intel checked out,
and it did, clearly.
And that's why you were late
getting back here earlier,
you were talking to him?
So, you didn't bother telling us?
How very Oliver Queen of you.
I had to get all the information
first before I looped you guys in.
Then once I did
have all the information,
we had to stop a subway collision.
But we did, and now here I am,
telling you guys.
Telling us what?
Why would Vince help us?
He says he's a double agent working
to take down Cayden James
from the inside.
I mean, that does track,
and the guy used to be undercover.
Which makes him a professional liar.
He's had so many opportunities
to tell me he's a double agent.
Why hasn't he? He just somehow forgot
to mention it?
He says he tried to.
That is absolute crap.
Maybe. But if he
turns out to be legit,
he could offer a tactical advantage
that we can't turn down.
Well, I can, because I will
never work with him again, ever.
Well, obviously Curtis
and I disagree, so...
So nothing.
We all have to agree. Don't we?
Or are just screwing consensus now?
So, maybe you can get some
of your officers
and have them stand over there?
- Okay.
- Great, thank you.
Thought that will put a little extra
pep in your step.
You are my savior.
Me or the coffee?
- Why can't it just be both?
- Hey,
how are things going here?
Well, it's not good, no.
We got no customers at all.
Okay, there's so much happening
right now
that people are too scared
to even come to the safe zones.
Worse still, I got cops standing
around here doing nothing
when they could be out there
helping people.
I'd like to redeploy them.
No. If we get people here,
then we don't need to worry
about protecting them out there.
We have no idea where Cayden James
is going to attack next.
The best thing that we can do for
the city is to get people
to the safe zones.
Could you please call the press?
I have an idea.
Okay.
- Yes.
- You got something?
Bull's-eye.
Alena remembered that last May,
Cayden received a package
from Corto Maltese
and she thinks that in that package
was the evidence that made Cayden
think that Oliver killed Owen.
And how exactly is that a bull's-eye?
Because we know Oliver
didn't kill Owen.
So whatever was in that package,
that evidence...
That evidence had to have been
faked somehow.
- Bull's-eye. Boom.
- All right.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, it's just stupid.
Well, you don't do stupid, so?
I don't know. I was just hoping that
since the implant was working
so well, that maybe...
You'd be putting the hood back on?
- Yeah.
- I'm sure you will.
You know, once this whole Cayden
thing is dealt with.
Hope so.
Hope so for his sake.
Oh, man, he just found out that his
father has been lying to him
for a month.
I've been trying to work up the
courage to talk to him, but like...
Stepmom-in-training over here.
You'll do fine, Felicity.
Hey, Will, your dad's on TV.
Are we under
some kind of attack?
A hacker who goes by
the name Cayden James
has taken over the electronic
infrastructure of Star City.
In his hands anything, anything
that is connected to the Internet
can be used as a weapon.
Now sadly this had already led
to a number of casualties
including our police captain,
Frank Pike,
and Councilman Harold Grovner.
Mr. James has made his demands,
but make no mistake,
he is a terrorist
and Star City does not negotiate
with terrorists.
Period.
Instead, we are going to focus on
the safety
and well-being of our citizens.
In that spirit, the SCPD has set up
safe houses throughout the city.
These locations are entirely
analog and you will be safe there.
I promise you,
you will be safe there.
Mr. James, Star City has survived
far worse than you.
We will band together.
We will be united
and we will survive this.
- Thank you very much.
- So predictable.
Almost takes the fun out of it.
Time to proceed to the next phase.
Nice speech, and it worked.
Safe zones are filling up.
They are completely offline
and hackcident free.
And in other news.
Yeah, I might have a thing
on our other thing.
On Cayden James' son?
So Alena thinks that Cayden believes
that you killed his son
because of something that arrived in
a package from Corto Maltese in May.
Through a pretty close sequence
of hacks on the mail systems
of several different countries,
not that you need to know about it
but it was really intense
and really cool
and I did it, it was really hard.
You don't need to know about those.
In that package was a USB drive,
we actually have that USB drive's
serial number,
so Alena is just working on trying
to find the computer in Corto Maltese
that uploaded the information
onto that drive that Cayden received.
The information that made him think
that you killed his son.
You see how
I came full circle on that?
One hundred percent.
Awesome.
You should go talk to him.
I will.
- Dinah.
- Hey.
If you don't wanna work with him,
we won't.
We do it by consensus,
like we agreed.
Look, I acknowledge that Vince
is a complicated variable. Okay?
Well, let's break it down.
You know, pro/con style.
All right.
Pro, he's really good and he gets
deep into his assignments.
Con, on our last assignment
he got in too deep.
He can forget what side he's on.
Pro, he's in with Cayden James
and his crew.
and his last intel worked.
If you didn't know Vincent,
if you could remove
this history with him...
If, as a cop, he came to you
with some intel,
what would your gut tell you?
- Do we have new intel from him?
- No.
Then I'm not going
to answer that yet.
You know, there's, um,
a study I was reading
that was saying that actually talking
to a child is one of the most
effective parenting techniques.
- No kidding. Is that true?
- Yeah.
Well, I have learned several times
the hard way that
sometimes kids just
want to be left alone.
I know I have to talk to him.
I'm just trying to respect that.
Okay.
And I might
totally be projecting here...
Because my dad was a, you know,
super-villain, evil hacktivist but...
He did a lot of things
that I didn't like or approve of
and the way he chose
to live his life,
that's not the part that bugged me.
- Okay, what bugged you?
- The lie.
All I ever wanted was for him
to tell me the truth, you know.
And that's all William wants,
all he wants to know is the truth.
The good, the bad, the ugly,
he just wants to know the truth.
William knows the truth.
Well, he knew
the truth.
And he decided that
he didn't want me in situations
where he might lose me.
Okay, but here we are.
And everything that has
happened with John,
and everything that has
happened with the team,
and everything that is happening
right now with Cayden James.
Here we are.
And you know what I think?
I think William can handle it.
- I don't know.
- I do.
Because, you know,
genetics.
Aren't you ready yet?
We're moving out.
I'll be right there.
What's going on?
Vincent's using the link to my
T-Sphere to send a message.
Morse code.
Clever, what does it say?
"Attack.
"Oak Street,
"now."
I'm assuming that's a warning,
not a directive.
Oak Street is one of the safe zones
Oliver and Quentin set up.
What do you want to do?
Suit up.
Officers marching, guns out.
City under siege.
It's like Escape from Detroit.
I don't know whether to correct you
or to just embrace your attempt
at referencing one of my favorite
John Carpenter films.
- Huh?
- I think the point,
is that people are scared.
It's not good.
They should be scared.
It's why they need us.
When you say "us,"
do you mean just you,
and it's a passive dig at
our team, no pun intended?
Or do you mean all of us,
and you recognize our own team
as being independent...
Curtis, we got your message,
thanks for reaching out.
So what are we dealing with here?
We have it on good authority
this place is Cayden James' next target.
- How do you know?
- We know. That's all that matters.
Not to spoil the really awkward
team reunion, but you have incoming.
Oh, you have lots of incoming.
We need to move out. Right now.
Is Dad gonna be okay?
Yeah, he's gonna be fine.
Look, I know you're not all that
happy with your dad right now,
but this,
this is what he does best,
and nobody does it better.
But everybody makes mistakes,
things go wrong,
you can't plan for everything.
Yeah, you're right.
What your dad does, it's...
It's very dangerous.
And heroes don't always make it home.
I never forget that.
But, you know, I've loved your dad
from the first time he brought me
a bullet-riddled computer.
Remind me to tell you about that one.
That was a long time ago, which means
I've loved him for a long time,
which means I've worried about him
for a long time.
And he hasn't always been truthful.
He's lied, he's kept secrets,
he's not perfect.
This life, it's not ideal.
But he makes his sacrifices,
so we have to make ours.
I sometimes think to myself,
that that's what makes this love
deeper than other kinds of love.
I know it sounds cheesy but,
it does, because we can't
take things for granted.
We have to live with the fear
and the uncertainty
that everything
can be taken from us in an instant.
Traitor!
I'm taking you to hell with...
'Cause that's the price we pay
for choosing the people that we love.
Everything he does,
he does for a good reason.
Or what he thinks is a good reason.
So you can worry about your dad,
but you have to believe
that he's going to be okay.
Because that's the only way
that this works.
Okay?
Okay, now, watch.
Now, after he takes these two down,
he's gonna spin, disarm him, kick.
He's probably gonna use the arrow
right here. Oh!
You probably shouldn't have been
allowed to watch that,
that's definitely in Parenting 101.
Good work.
Doesn't change anything, hoss.
Come on.
At least, he's pretty...
Amazing, yeah.
Well, I was gonna say "badass."
- Badass.
- Yeah.
Well, for two teams
that do not trust each other,
you guys worked together pretty well.
Well, except for the fact
that they never shared with us
where they got their information.
What's happening?
Cayden's shutting down
all communications.
E-mail, TV, cell phones,
Internet traffic, everything.
We didn't meet his 11:30 deadline.
Please talk to Alena and tell her
that we are running out of time.
I already did, she is working
as fast as she can.
What are we gonna do?
I need to go talk to my son.
You saved Rene's life tonight.
Thank you.
I'm on your side, D.
I wasn't so sure before.
So, what now?
When I was growing up,
if something happened, my dad would
call a family meeting so that
we could all talk about it.
And I know we've both already
talked to you separately,
but we just thought
we'd all get together
and just sort of, talk it out.
Put it all in the open.
I'm terribly sorry
that I lied to you.
There is no excuse for it.
I'm new at this whole dad thing,
but that's not an excuse either...
I've been tryin' to work my way
through it, and I've hit more
bumps in the road
than I thought that I would.
As you know.
But no more secrets,
and no more lies.
And, William, if you need me
to stop being the Green Arrow,
I will.
Felicity showed me
what you did tonight.
I gotta say it was really cool.
The city needs you
and I get that now.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I mean, I was worried before
that I would become an orphan.
But it's different now.
I have Felicity.
I understand
why you have to go out there.
I'm gonna get to bed.
You sleep well, William, okay?
Thanks.
What you said was touching.
It was kind of awful, too.
That's the actual definition
of "bittersweet."
Okay, well, don't let it get to you.
Yeah, it's not...
- Oliver.
- It's not, it's...
If I've learned one thing about
parenting so far that I'm sure of,
you can't win 'em all.
It's Alena.
She went through all the computers
in Corto Maltese.
She didn't find anything, I'm sorry.
I've gotta get to City Hall.
What are you gonna do?
Wire the money.