Previously on Arrow...
Diaz has people everywhere.
He controls
Star City's government,
its infrastructure,
and its police force.
Diaz went after this
instead of going after Curtis.
What if these are all Diaz's books?
Everyone he has on his payroll.
We could liberate the city.
Your digital sniffer,
can it read the drive?
If you get me close enough, for sure.
Diaz's base of operations is too secure,
we can't move on it
without losing people.
You want my help,
I'm gonna need you to say the words.
I am the Green Arrow.
Sentries are not responding.
You know, somebody wanna tell me
why I gotta do everything
in this place myself...
Why don't you watch where...
You gotta be a special kind of stupid
to be coming back here alone.
I'm not alone.
Move, move, move!
- Clear!
- Where's Diaz?
Where is Diaz?
No sign of Diaz.
- What about Knyazev?
- Same.
Precinct reported he's not there either.
This isn't over yet.
Diaz clearly has
a third base of operations
we don't know about.
Yo, hoss, masks?
Mr. Queen and I
have come to an understanding.
Even if we didn't,
your identity is hardly a well-kept
secret, Mr. Ramirez.
So you're done trying to throw us
in jail?
Everyone has immunity
from prosecution, Rene.
The FBI recognizes that Diaz
is the clear and present danger.
Better late than never, I suppose.
That immunity deal
does include me, right?
'Cause I'd really like to not
spend my rest of my life in prison
if I can avoid it.
How did Diaz know
we were moving in on him tonight?
We rounded up the SCPD,
but Diaz still controls
dozens of city officials.
Diaz has a list of all of them.
He keeps it on his person.
Once we take Diaz, we won't need a list.
We need to interrogate
all the people we rounded up
and see if we can get one of them
to give up Diaz's location.
No, they won't give it up.
They're more afraid of him
than they are of us.
They also know, without corroboration,
Diaz, or this list of his,
we'll have to kick them in 48 hours.
Where's he going?
Probably to go talk to his guy
on the inside.
Anatoly.
Big night for you, Kapiushon.
How you turn FBI
from foe to friend? Hmm?
Same way you did me?
Where's Diaz?
Ah, he's been on the move ever since
he heard FBI coming to town.
When he settles, I want to know where.
Hmm, I'll try my best,
but he's not in very trusting mood
these days.
What?
Okay.
My sister, what you
Americans call high-maintenance.
You avoided the raid.
Yeah, I got hungry.
Therefore lucky.
Got dinner.
When I got back here,
FBI all over place like ants at picnic.
So
what is your next move?
You lost your army.
I made some new friends.
New friends?
The Longbow Hunters.
I thought those were a myth.
They're very real.
We're going somewhere
to mount our counterattack.
Be there in an hour.
Yeah, I love you, sweetie. Okay.
Bye-bye.
- Lyla?
- Yeah.
She, J.J., William and Zoe
are at the NORAD bunker.
But she would much rather be here.
We have enough backup.
A son needs his parents.
And yours doesn't?
I'm gonna see this through, Oliver.
I thought you might say that.
So I think you should dress the part.
I had a spare made up.
There's no rule saying there can't be
more than one Green Arrow.
I should have done this
from the beginning.
Oliver, our disagreement
was never about the uniform.
I know that.
I'd like to apologize for any part
that I played in it.
I really thought I wanted this mantle.
It means something.
You've made it mean something.
When our city looks at it,
it gives them hope, Oliver.
And it would be diminished
if there was more than one.
For everything along the way, thank you.
Hello. Excuse me.
Hello, everybody.
My name is Anatoly Knyazev.
And I'm here to turn myself in.
We also have costume parties in Russia.
- It's always great fun.
- What do you have, Anatoly?
Address for Diaz. He said to meet
him there in one hour.
But he's not going to be alone.
- He's bringing Longbow Hunters.
- The what now?
Three assassins that even
the League is afraid of.
Or they were because the last one
died out in the 1950s.
Or that's what they wanted
people to think.
We've got the FBI backing us.
Please tell me we're not afraid
of three guys.
- Hell no.
- Let's get ready to move.
I'll go tell Agent Watson.
Well, it's funny everything always
comes down to a signature
on a piece of paper.
Diaz's crimes are local,
which means the bureau needs
municipal authority
to operate in Star City.
Well, now you got it.
What is it?
Got a location on Diaz.
- This'll be over tonight.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, honey.
- Hey, Daddy.
So the relationship
between me and your daughter,
it took a turn.
I don't think she's, uh,
into me anymore.
- Listen to me...
- No!
You listen to me,
or Laurel dies a second time.
What do you want?
For the Mayor to get the FBI
out of my city.
Do it! Tonight!
Or Laurel's dead.
Go to hell.
What was that?
Nothing. You said you were ready
to move on Diaz tonight.
I'm ready to come down on him
like God's own righteous fury.
Do it.
I don't think your daddy
loves you anymore.
I think if you were the real Laurel,
he'd already be here.
- Go to hell.
- That's a witty response.
I was expecting better.
Do you know what the funny thing is?
You moved on me because of him.
You got yourself in this situation
because of him.
You could have skipped town,
but you came after me.
Were you afraid of what I was
gonna do to your daddy
when you were gone?
Huh?
Come on, baby, talk to me.
Talk to me!
We're on site.
The FBI has graciously given me control
of their Key Hole satellites,
which I gotta say
are a lot easier to operate
when they aren't being hacked.
All right, listen up.
Diaz may have lost his police force,
but we believe he still has
his personal security
and Quadrant muscle backing him up.
No warning shots. Let's move out.
If this is where Diaz
is planning on making his last stand,
I would have expected more guys
with guns.
Not seeing anything.
I'm getting a big thermal reading
from inside the northwest corner.
That's where we're headed. Stand by.
Son of a bitch.
- What is it?
- Laser trip wires.
Trip wires for what?
Triacetone triperoxide.
It's the thermal source.
Diaz was never here.
It's a trap.
Hang tight,
we're almost at your position.
Negative. If you go in there,
if anybody moves,
the whole place will go up.
If we can't move,
we can't get to the bombs.
- How we going to disarm them?
- I am working on that.
- Everyone else just get clear.
- We can't leave Rene.
No, there might be
more explosives rigged.
Just please get away from the building.
You heard her. Let's go.
Talk to me, blondie.
Tracing a radio signal
to the explosives.
In case Diaz gets impatient,
wants to set off bomb himself.
If I can piggyback off the signal,
I might be able
to fool the triggers into thinking
that you're not moving.
"Might"? You can't see this,
but there's enough explosives in here
to send us into orbit.
Pressure is not helping, Rene.
If the bombs can be triggered remotely,
Diaz can kill us anytime.
We're not making it out of here, are we?
Hey, peanut. It's Daddy.
No, everything's fine. I'm safe.
I just wanted to hear your voice
and tell you that I love you,
and I'm so proud of you.
You give my life meaning
every single day.
Yeah.
You're my everything, peanut.
And I need you to know that.
Daddy's gotta go. I love you.
I'll see you soon.
Okay. Bye.
Can we
get in through the roof?
Negative. Blowing the roof
will set off the TATP.
Stand by while I clone
the trigger frequency.
Hello.
So I'm curious.
How many did I get?
You betray me,
and I'm the son of a bitch?
The ones trapped in there
with those explosives,
they're gonna die in a blink.
But you, Anatoly...
I'm gonna make it last
for days with you.
He triggered the explosives,
but I'm bouncing the signal off
a bunch of satellites.
You have seven seconds.
Move!
Come on!
You okay?
Thought I'd check in on you.
I'm fine, hoss.
Agent Watson told me about
your call with Zoe.
I thought I was gonna die in that room.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Tell her how proud you are of her?
There's not enough words
to say how much.
I feel the same way about you, Rene.
When I first met you, I...
I didn't think you were much more
than a thug...
...in a ridiculous costume.
No prize yourself, hoss.
I judged you.
For far too long, I judged you,
and that was a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I think that you're a good man, Rene.
I think that you're the type of man
that this...
This city deserves.
I know it seems like I don't give
a crap about what anyone thinks,
but this means a lot.
Yeah.
Guys, we have another problem.
I told Diaz to go to hell because
you were about to move on him.
It was deception.
He learned I was helping you,
and he manipulated me.
It means
we're right back to square one,
not knowing where Diaz is.
But now we have a way to find out.
You tell Diaz you wanna see Laurel.
Proof of life.
We follow you to her, her to Diaz.
You go in there guns blazing,
my daughter takes the first bullet.
From what Oliver tells me,
she's not actually your daughter.
And she's a criminal
that made her own bed.
This isn't a hostage situation.
Our objective hasn't changed.
- Oliver, please...
- We can keep her safe.
How? The first thing he'll do
when he sees you coming is kill her.
I think this is a risk we need to take.
Yeah? Would you be taking that risk
if this was our Laurel?
Or is that the kind of risk
that got her killed
in the first damn place?
What the hell do you want?
To give you a second chance.
When you told me to go to hell,
you know, I figured that you figured
your buddies were about to take me down.
Well, it didn't work out that way.
So now we're back to where we started.
You kicking the FBI out of here
in exchange for Laurel's life.
I need to see her first, proof of life.
I'll send you the address.
Listen, you better come alone
'cause if something happens
that I don't like,
something's gonna happen to Laurel
that you don't like.
Anyone ever tell you it's rude
to sneak up on people?
Diaz?
- He's gonna kill her.
- I won't let that happen, Quentin.
What about Watson, huh?
She doesn't seem so important to her.
Just let me worry about Samanda Watson,
and let me try to keep Laurel safe.
I don't see how you can, Oliver.
You can start by trusting me.
Please.
I mean, I've earned it.
We've known each other
for a very long time, Quentin.
- A lifetime.
- Yeah.
We've come a long way, you and me.
It's been getting better since
the first time you arrested me.
You know, I've always been curious.
How did you beat
that lie detector anyway?
It just comes down
to keeping a regular heart rate.
I had a pacemaker that does that.
I didn't know you had a pacemaker.
I got it after that Mirakuru business
a few years back.
The old ticker couldn't
take that pounding.
Yeah.
Truth be told, I don't know
if it could take it now.
Yes, it can. Okay?
Because you're tough.
Laurel is tough too.
So trust me,
and this will all work out.
You're supposed to
bring Laurel.
I give the orders.
He's clean.
You're gonna give an order as Mayor
to get the FBI out of here.
And you're gonna do it
at a press conference.
Satellite track is clean.
Audio signal is five by five.
Everyone get ready to move.
Not going anywhere until
we know where he's keeping Laurel.
Not our objective.
You want me
to hold a press conference
before you even let me see my daughter?
Do you have a problem with that?
I'm not doing anything
until I see her alive.
What the hell is he doing?
The FBI is tracking me by satellite.
They're gonna move on you
unless we move right now.
Now, take me to my daughter.
Son of a bitch!
Get him in the car.
All units, move now! Go!
- Can your satellite track him?
- I've lost him.
Your friend
just blew this whole operation
and our best chance to get Diaz.
And his daughter's still gonna die.
When this is over, I'm bringing your
friend Quentin up for obstruction.
Our immunity arrangement
doesn't extend to him.
- He was trying to save Laurel.
- Well, I'm trying to save this city.
The city your friend's
supposed to be the mayor of.
I can't believe he'd so something
so reckless.
Or stupid. He knows
Diaz will kill him and Laurel.
- What the hell was he thinking?
- He wasn't. That's the problem.
Before Quentin went to see Diaz,
he went out of his way to tell me
that he had a pacemaker.
And he's never told us that before.
So why would he say something now?
- You can track a pacemaker?
- You know I can.
Quentin knew that Diaz's man
was gonna frisk him for a tracker,
just like he knew that
Diaz wasn't going to actually
bring Laurel to the meet.
So Quentin had Diaz bring him to her,
knowing that we could track him.
How long would it take you to find him?
Give me a high speed connection
and a few minutes.
You wanted to see her,
now you see her.
I'm a man of my word.
Great. Now, let her go.
I just promised proof of life.
We'll see how long that lasts.
Felicity has Quentin's location.
It's an abandoned chemical plant
on the border of Pennytown.
We're gonna move out in five minutes.
I'll be ready.
The FBI's only objective is Diaz.
They're gonna do their best
to keep Quentin safe,
but they don't care if Black Siren
is collateral damage.
Your point?
My point, Dinah, is that
it's up to us to keep her safe.
I know that you have
put your vendetta aside
for the sake of the mission.
And you wanna make sure
I keep it that way.
I wanna say thank you.
It takes a very big person to not
seek vengeance for someone they love.
If I haven't always been sensitive
to that,
I'm truly sorry.
I'm sorry I was so hard on you.
You know, the truth is,
I respect you more
than you could ever know.
You put together a team of heroes.
It's no small thing.
- I'm gonna go get ready.
- All right.
- Hey.
- What is going on?
What do you mean?
I mean, you've been giving
the "Oliver Farewell" tour
all round this place,
including giving John the hood.
You know, everyone's wondering,
what did you have to give Watson
to get her to give us immunity?
I'm just gonna go out on a limb here
and guess that it was giving up
being the Green Arrow.
- Sort of.
- You can't be serious.
What happened
to becoming your best self?
I don't know if I believe that anymore.
Oliver, this is who you are.
You can't let Watson
get in the middle of that.
She's not.
- It was my idea.
- What do you mean, it was your idea?
Uh, guys.
Uh...
Sorry to interrupt what looks like
a pretty serious marital moment,
but everyone's ready to go.
To be continued. Okay?
Showtime!
You're gonna get in front of the camera,
and you're gonna get the FBI
to leave Star City,
or your baby girl grows a third eye.
He's not gonna shoot me.
- You're willing to bet your life?
- Yes!
- Laurel.
- Yes, I am!
You got five seconds.
- Five.
- Don't let him take this city.
- Four.
- He's bluffing. He's lying!
Three! Two!
One!
No! Dad. Dad!
Stay with me. Stay with me, Dad.
Dad, stay with me. Look at me.
Look at me.
Stay with me.
Don't waste your tears.
Where I shot him,
it'll take a good chunk of time
for him to bleed out.
Laurel, you need to get your dad
to get on the phone
and get the feds to go back
to their swamp.
I'll show him some mercy.
Like the end of the movie
with the little dog.
What's it called?
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm not doing anything.
All right, we're gonna do this
another way
'cause I'm not gonna count.
Your daughter's brains
are gonna be splattered
on your face.
Don't shoot. Don't shoot!
Are you all right?
FBI!
- Quentin!
- I got him. Get Diaz.
No.
We gotta get him to a hospital.
- Come on.
- I got you.
I need a chopper.
Five minutes away. We're five...
I don't have five minutes.
I agree.
You wanna shoot me?
Do it.
Right here.
See, that's your problem.
That's always been your problem.
He needs
a doctor immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Enough.
This is my city!
You wanna stop me,
you're gonna have to kill me.
He's right, Oliver.
The movie with the dog.
- It's called Old Yeller.
- No!
- What did you do?
- I had to.
I had to end it.
You think that fall's gonna kill him?
A girl can only hope.
I had him!
We scoured every inch of the city
and trolled Starling Bay.
He can't have gotten far.
He was launched off a rooftop.
He shouldn't have been able to go
anywhere at all.
Diaz doesn't go down easy.
You seem pretty sanguine about it.
That wasn't a total loss.
Felicity reprogrammed this
with a digital sniffer.
I was able to get close enough to Diaz
to clone the drive that he wears
around his neck.
I got government officials,
city employees.
We can give you everyone on his payroll.
We can give you your city back.
But the fact that Diaz is in the wind,
it doesn't alter our agreement.
I know.
How is he?
He's septic. They're getting him
ready for surgery.
Rene is in there with him right now.
What about Diaz?
You're gonna be fine, hoss.
These docs are gonna fix you up.
Yeah.
- Do me a favor.
- Anything, hoss.
If this thing goes the wrong way,
and I don't make it,
don't call me "hoss" at my funeral.
You're gonna make it.
Yeah.
How's he doing?
Kind of macabre actually.
I'll give you guys a minute.
Mmm-hmm.
Hi.
What's the latest on Diaz?
Diaz... He got away.
How?
Doesn't matter. We'll get him.
We do have a list of everyone
he's been controlling.
FBI is rounding them up as we speak.
So we can take our city back.
Mmm-hmm.
- You did good, Oliver.
- Thank you.
It's not over yet.
It is for you.
Am I wrong?
I've been dealing with Samanda Watson
for months.
There's no way she was gonna help you
without strings attached.
But those strings,
Oliver, that's a hell of a sacrifice.
I had to look at the way
I've been doing things.
It's not working.
I lost my city.
I lost my team.
There's a penance for that.
It just seems a little drastic.
Coming from the guy who just took
a bullet for his daughter.
Quentin, I hope I took
the time to tell you,
uh,
you're a really good father.
So are you.
I had a good example.
Yeah, your dad was a good man.
I'm not talking about my dad.
I'm sorry, but we have to take him
to the OR now.
Well, um,
when you get out, everyone
will be here waiting for you.
Thanks, Oliver.
For everything.
Thank you for coming.
- How is he?
- In surgery.
The doctors, they're optimistic, but...
But I thought
you should probably be here.
Thank you.
This is probably really strange
for you, right?
A little.
Are you, um...
Are you like my Laurel?
Hardly at all.
How long is this gonna take?
How many times are you gonna ask that?
As many times as it takes to find out
how long it's gonna take.
Mr. Queen. It's time.
Time for what?
What is she talking about?
I'm sorry that I haven't
explained this to everyone.
There hasn't been any time.
There wasn't time to explain what?
- You're arresting us?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I thought you said we had immunity.
- You do.
- Thanks to him.
- Oh, my God.
It was the only way.
No, it's not the only way.
There are a million other ways.
The judge threw out his case.
You can't do this.
- I can. It's federal.
- Federal.
The Bureau is going to stay in Star City
until Diaz is brought in.
But only if Oliver agreed
to turn himself in.
What the hell is going on here?
Wait a minute. Just wait.
How's Quentin?
Mayor Lance seized during the procedure.
The surgeons worked to revive him.
They did everything they could.
But his brain was deprived of oxygen
for seven minutes.
He's gone.
I'm very sorry.
Unfortunately, this doesn't change
our arrangement.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm so sorry, Sara.
All of you please
take care of each other.
Ollie.
Transport's delayed.
We'll be transferring you
in a half-hour.
Okay, I talked to John.
We have a plan. We're gonna get you out.
- No, you can't.
- Yes, we can. We've done it before.
We got John out of...
We broke him out
of Langham Penitentiary.
Yes, we did.
They're transferring me
to a super-max, Felicity.
And even if I wanted to break out,
they would just arrest everyone,
including you.
I think that William deserves
at least one parent.
During your trial,
you said you didn't wanna go public
because you wanted a life
after the Green Arrow.
This is that life.
- You can...
- I wanted to stop Diaz.
And I wanted to save you
and William more.
Not everything went our way.
Quentin and...
That protective custody
that we talked about
for the two of you during my trial.
- No.
- Lyla's gonna handle everything.
I promise, just until Diaz
is off the board.
No, I refuse to believe
that this is the only option.
We won back the city.
We got it back.
I thought I lost it.
- You didn't do that alone.
- I know.
Diaz tried to kill everybody
close to me.
And I had to find a way
to protect everybody.
This was the way.
- Is William here?
- Yeah, he's outside.
He's...
He's scared. He's confused.
He's wondering how the woman
that he's known for less than a year
is suddenly his only parent.
Would you please go get him?
Yeah.
Buddy, how you doing?
I don't understand.
What's happening?
I'm gonna explain everything to you.
Mr. Queen,
why are you being arrested again?
I have voluntarily handed myself
over to the FBI.
- Can you comment any further?
- Yes, I can.
I am the Green Arrow.
I realize that I've denied
that claim with the same conviction
with which I'm speaking now.
I have let good people stand accused
of things that I have done.
Roy Harper is not the Green Arrow.
Tommy Merlyn is most certainly
not the Green Arrow.
These are two names
on a long list of people
who have given so much
and sacrificed everything
in the name of my crusade.
Some of them gave their lives
in the pursuit of one simple objective,
to save our city.
Star City still needs saving.
Last night, we dealt our enemy
a critical blow.
But there is still work to be done.
So I'm looking to the people
of this city.
I'm looking to my allies, to my friends,
to my partners,
and I'm asking them to continue,
to keep fighting.
I'm asking them to complete our mission,
to save our city.
I know you, Oliver Queen.
You're gonna die in here, sucker.
You're gonna...
Shut the hell up!