Previously on Arrow...
These are innocent people.
And you can save them...
By wiring 10 million dollars
into that account every night.
$70 million.
I'm going to make sure
Vince didn't die for nothing.
I'm going to kill
every last one of them.
Starting with Laurel.
Laurel!
There is a piece of my daughter
in you, somewhere.
And I'm gonna get it out,
whatever it takes.
Thank you for all you've done
to get justice for my boy.
The new police captain,
she's on my payroll.
Tell your boy I said hello.
Severed subclavian artery,
no defensive wounds.
How did this happen?
Sometime between transfer
and intake at Iron Heights,
an inmate caught James unaware.
By the time the guards intervened,
- it was too late.
- Motive?
The inmate was a headcase off his meds.
For all we know, he thought
he was killing his mother.
Well, the random murder
of Cayden James...
- It doesn't feel very random.
- It was bad timing,
and even worse luck, Mr. Mayor.
That's all.
All right.
Cayden James is my responsibility.
If a head has to roll for this,
make it mine.
That is not how I run things here.
Just...
Keep doing what you're doing.
Please, please! One at a time!
One at a time!
Thank you.
I understand that you're angry.
I am... I'm angry, too.
But we're not going to solve any
problems by yelling at one another.
Last I heard, Cayden James is dead,
but you still don't have
the money he stole.
You mean the money he was given.
We are still in the process
of recovering the money
that was extorted from the city.
We just need a little more time.
We are on the verge
of financial collapse.
Without an influx of cash, soon,
we all have to shut down.
Schools, sanitation,
emergency services, everything.
Fine. We will have those funds
back in 48 hours.
You have my word.
All of you have my word.
Thank you.
Okay...
Not that I don't love
your confidence and everything,
but should you really
be making promises like that?
The accountant is on his way back
from Corto Maltese
with the money that was deposited
into Cayden James' bank account
as we speak.
You could've just told them that,
got those folks off your back.
I'm not telling them anything concrete,
until that money is back
in the city's bank accounts.
My bigger concern right now
is finding Cayden's associates
before Dinah does,
because she is on the warpath.
- Yeah.
- Any luck with that?
John is working a few leads.
We should know more in a few hours.
Don't worry, they're not gonna
let anything happen to Laurel.
Oh, right.
The accountant's here.
Send him in.
All right, I'll take that as my cue.
I've got to head off to Planning.
Oh. Okay...
Welcome.
What are you doing here?
Well, he's carrying evidence.
I'm just making sure
it doesn't get up and walk away.
Good luck with that.
Wasn't planning
on seeing you today, Lieutenant.
Well, I wasn't planning on it either,
but we've got a problem.
Cayden James' Corto Maltese
bank account has been withdrawn.
What do you mean, "it's been withdrawn"?
It's empty. All 70 million.
Somebody took all the funds out
before we got access.
- Do we have any idea who?
- No. But I do have three guesses.
I put in a request
for the withdrawal log,
but it's a long shot.
If we don't have those funds
in 48 hours,
this city's government services
will shut down.
And I understand.
But banks in third-world countries
like Corto Maltese
aren't exactly known
for their transparency.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Mayor.
Something smells good.
Well, that smell is physics,
mathematics and chemistry hard at work.
Felicity is teaching me
about... "Thermodynamics"?
That's right.
- And we just really wanted cookies.
- Narc.
Don't you normally have tutoring
after school, bud?
We all got sent home.
Miss Joe said
it had to do with the budget.
Is it true they might have to
close the schools?
I'm working very hard
to make sure that doesn't happen.
There's actually something that I
needed to speak with Felicity about.
I'll keep working on the cookies.
Yeah, you definitely have
that "day from hell" look.
What's going on?
The money that Cayden
extorted from the city...
- Hmm.
- Someone emptied the account.
Yeah, well, that somebody is either
Anatoly, Diaz or Laurel.
Or another player
that we haven't seen yet.
We requested the withdrawal logs
from the bank.
It's Corto Maltese, taking too long.
You want me to help expedite it.
I need it to look like it's coming
through official channels.
Yeah, I know. It's not my first rodeo
with Corto Maltese.
Give me about an hour.
Hey, you don't think it's a coincidence?
Someone killing Cayden
right as the money goes missing?
Could be the same person that
framed you for Cayden's son's murder.
Could be.
The only thing
that I know for sure right now
is that if I don't get that money
in 48 hours,
this city is going to have my head.
Any luck finding Anatoly?
Just Bratva dudes
who don't know anything.
What about you guys?
Diaz's trail has gone colder
than my love life.
Same with Laurel.
If it's any consolation,
the other guys are striking out, too.
Ran into Digg chasing the same dead end.
I guess they're not sharing
their intel with us.
Not that we were sharing any with them.
Well, we can't trust them
to keep us looped in.
I mean, that's why I got put on
the Cayden James bank situation.
Any clue we get can lead us
to the scum who worked with them.
Scum singular or scum plural?
And yes, that is me bringing up
exactly what's going on
between you and Laurel.
Well, we're not
braiding each other's hair, Curtis.
I mean, but you are out for revenge,
and I don't feel too good about that.
Gotta go.
Looks like we got a lead
on the missing money.
You okay with this?
D hunting Laurel?
Let's just worry about the money first,
then we'll deal with Dinah.
You're not going to believe it.
The bank just sent over
the withdrawal log we requested,
plus security footage.
That is unbelievable.
What are we seeing?
The account was accessed by this woman.
She's listed in the withdrawal log
as "Siu Jerg Jai."
Took out the entire amount
in bearer bonds.
It's excellent work, Jay. Okay.
We'll take it from here. Thank you.
I'm guessing Felicity
had something to do with this.
Yeah, she did.
Thank you for inserting yourself
into this, by the way.
Yeah, sure. Well, you never would've
shared the information otherwise.
No, I wouldn't have.
Because I don't trust you
to do the right thing.
And what is that, politely ask Laurel
to give back the money?
Not kill her.
Dinah...
I understand that you're hurting.
I get it.
I also understand that
I don't have the most credibility
when it comes to telling people
not to commit murder.
But the city is on the verge
of economic collapse,
and we just found the key
to fixing that.
Laurel is never giving you that money.
- You don't know that.
- Yeah, I actually do.
Because I know that
when you look at her,
you see the Laurel that you lost.
And that's why
you'll never be able to do
what's necessary to get that money back.
And you will?
Understand something.
I will never let you cross that line.
If you're going to threaten me, Oliver,
you better be damn sure you can deliver.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
You'll pop your stitches.
How are you feeling?
Like I've been shot in the gut.
Where am I?
You're someplace nobody can find you.
I guess we now know
what happened to $70 million.
Right. If we find her, then we find it.
Quentin, I know that
we have been over this,
but just for accuracy, you were
the last person that saw her.
Yeah. Well, I...
You know, I didn't see her exactly.
- Right.
- Like I told you,
Dinah got off a shot just as Laurel
knocked us both out with her cry.
And, uh, yeah, when I came to,
Laurel was gone.
So, are we even sure that Dinah hit her?
No. She didn't leave a definitive
blood trail at the scene.
We can go back over it
with chemical analysis,
- see if we missed anything
- Yeah, yeah, we can do that.
Listen, actually there is
something I should tell you.
Um, while Cayden James
was holding the city hostage,
Laurel started following me.
All right? It was right after
James kidnapped me.
And so, uh, well, you know,
I caught up with her.
I tried to make a connection.
Well, I mean, after what we just
saw her do to Dinah's boyfriend...
Are we even sure that that worked?
Actually, it might have.
When we went through
her go-bag at the scene, there was...
There was a photo in there of you
and our Laurel.
I gave her that picture.
Anyway... My point
being, if she hasn't skipped town yet,
maybe she'll come try to find me,
make a connection, you know,
- say goodbye or something.
- I mean, it's a long shot, but...
I agree, but I also don't think
that we can afford to be picky, so...
I'll get home.
I'll make it easy for her to,
you know, get me alone.
If she shows up, just make sure
that you stall long enough
for John and I to get there.
Yeah, sure. Bye.
Well, do you need me
to go with you for backup?
No, no. You know, like I said
it's a long shot. Right?
So, your time is probably better
spent here at the office.
But thank you.
Okay, well, call if you need anything.
We've already been over this spot
a thousand times.
Yeah, which is exactly why
I brought my new toy.
Presenting...
Mr. Terrific's
Supersonic Spectrograph.
It uses Earth-2 sonic frequencies
emitted from Black Siren
and combines them with light imaging
to create a holographic replication
of her position
during that night's events.
- Is that...
- Laurel.
Is she crawling?
No. She was dragged.
Looks like she wasn't
putting up much of a fight.
- Your bullet must have tagged her, D.
- Good.
Now we just have to find her
before the others do something stupid.
Stupid how?
Oliver is not seeing clearly on this.
He's desperate to get that money.
He'll believe anything Laurel says.
Shouldn't we also
be desperate for that money?
- The city's hurting.
- I know.
But there are more effective ways
to find out
where she's keeping that money.
Sounds like
you're talking about torture.
And it sounds like
you wanna go soft on her.
Curtis, the only way
to get justice for Vince
and money for the city
is going to be messy.
Hey, guys, look at this.
Tire tracks.
If they're from whoever
dragged her off, could be something.
Let's make sure they didn't
leave anything else behind.
I picked this up at a noodle shop
my girls used to love.
I've never been to any noodle shop.
Well, hot and sour's
the best thing for healing
no matter what Earth you're from.
You know, I think I might have
a picture here of the three of us.
Would you stop?
I've already told you,
there's nothing inside of me
to change or going to change.
Um...
You know, you, uh...
You let me go.
Instead of killing me,
like James wanted.
You hesitated killing Vincent Sobel...
Before doing exactly that.
Yeah.
You've done
some pretty unspeakable things.
Do you ever stop to ask yourself why?
Huh?
Basically, you grew up without a father.
My guess, you spent your whole life
looking for one.
Zoom.
Adrian Chase.
Cayden James.
All those men are gone now.
Including Cayden James,
he was killed last night.
Well, it looks like I have an opening
for a new domineering father figure.
Feel free to send in your application.
You don't need anybody else telling
you what to do with your life.
Interesting.
Coming from someone
who has me locked up in a cabin
in the middle of nowhere.
You're welcome to leave anytime.
But, my, you know, my guess is that
it's been a long time
since you had a chance to decide
what you want your life to be.
So, I figured I'd give you
a little time and space
to do just that.
I've got my hopes for sure.
But you're the one
that has to want to change.
It's weird.
I actually really like
hot and sour soup.
Maybe we have more things in common
than I thought.
Would you tell me more
about your Laurel?
Well, the luminol's certainly
doing its work on this blood trail.
Yeah, so much blood, we shouldn't
need the luminol to see it.
Someone cleaned this place up.
Yeah, because Laurel
lost too much blood to do it herself.
What, so someone helped her get away?
No, someone took her.
I don't want to believe it, but I can.
We have to find her before
they do something irreversible.
If they haven't already.
- How has the print gotten us nowhere?
- We're not nowhere.
We've already ruled out
all the known vehicles
in the SCPD criminal database.
Which just leaves us with
millions of other unknown vehicles.
Otherwise, known as "nowhere."
Rene is right. This lead is exhausted.
What the hell?
Where is she?
We know you have Black Siren.
If she dies, you've destroyed the city!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We do not have Black Siren.
We'll figure that out for ourselves.
Since when is our word not enough?
Since you tried to kill her.
If she dies, that money is lost forever.
"Lost forever." Like Vincent Sobel.
Where was the Green Arrow
when he needed saving?
Your team walked into a trap.
If you came with us,
Vincent might still be alive.
Don't you dare say his name.
Thermal imaging is only showing
our six heat signatures inside.
I mean, if Laurel's here, she's...
She's not warm.
Are you hacking us?
Don't hack us, Felicity!
I'm not hacking. I wouldn't hack...
Yeah, technically I'm hacking you.
- Wouldn't be your first time.
- No, it wouldn't.
She's tracked all of you before.
Because we needed to know
if one of you broke our trust.
One of you did.
You have already
punished Rene for that mistake.
It's just too bad he doesn't
look like Laurel Lance, Oliver,
because if he did, you would
probably forgive him for murder.
Guys, we're not actually about to
fight about this, are we?
Like, physically fight?
Keep your team in line, Curtis,
and we won't have to find out.
Hold on! You guys barged
into another's team bunker!
Curtis, just listen for once.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, guys, no.
I do think Oliver wants to fight.
'Cause that's how
you always solve your problems.
That doesn't make you a hero.
It makes you a thug.
And it's a real shame,
because he's gonna feel
so betrayed when he figures it out.
You know who I'm talking about,
don't you, Hoss?
William.
Don't turn your back on me!
- Hey!
- Don't move.
- So, you're gonna shoot us, Digg?
- Do it.
So, this was your plan all along, huh?
To get the chance
to look through our bunker?
And you wonder why we can't trust you.
We don't have
to wonder anymore.
Laurel's not here. Let's go.
Just so you know...
We are gonna find her!
And when we do, you better
hope to God you're not there too.
You think you know somebody,
then they do a triple-worm
blue cobalt IP hack that you taught them
right into your soul.
God, I can't believe
we even ever worked with them.
You say "with,"
but what you really mean is "for."
They never treated us
like we were equals.
Perimeter alarm's reset.
Also, I borrowed
a piece of your tech, Curtis.
What did you do?
You didn't really think
I wanted Oliver to hit me.
Would you care to share
with the rest of the class?
I planted one of Curtis'
audio chips on Oliver.
So, if they get the drop on Laurel...
So will we.
Karma, bitch!
...the thought of being
against our guys, you know.
I hate to state
the oh, so depressingly obvious,
but since Dinah and company
don't have Laurel, we have nothing.
Nada, zilch, bupkis.
Not true. We have three former teammates
who hate us more now
than they did before.
Can't worry about them.
Guys, we're out of time here.
- Should I reach out to Lyla?
- I appreciate that, John,
but the last thing
that we need right now
is yet another group putting
Black Siren in their crosshairs.
Oh, square, meet one.
She didn't vanish
off the face of the Earth.
Are you sure? I mean, 'cause,
technically, she is from another Earth.
We're gonna find her.
Because we have to.
Quentin.
Thea, what are you doing here?
You followed me?
Yeah, well, I... I knew
you were lying about something.
But, I, I did not think it was this.
Okay, she's sleeping, please.
Okay, but why didn't
you tell me?
I thought we were in on this together.
I didn't wanna put you in a position
where you had to lie to Oliver, okay?
But listen, this is the right thing.
Okay...
I think I am getting through to her.
But you got to go
before she wakes up, please.
Okay, fine. But did you at least
find out where the money is?
Well, I'm building up to that.
Look, I know how important she
and this whole thing is to you.
I get it.
But the city is dying
without that money.
- We need to find it.
- Right, right, right.
And, you know, I'll ask her.
But she just can't feel like
she's being forced into something.
Okay, we are running out of time.
I got to call Ollie
and get him in on this.
Okay, I'm sorry,
but your brother's not exactly
known for his light touch, all right?
And you and I, we both know
that I'm the only person
with any chance
of getting through to her.
Well, that's so sweet
of you to think, Daddy.
But Thea's right.
You should probably call your BFF.
Thea, I'll be back to City Hall
as soon as I can be.
Ollie, I'm not in the office.
- Where are you?
- With Quentin.
- And Laurel.
- What?
Are you okay? Did she hurt you?
No, I'm fine. Don't worry.
She's too torn up to scream.
Quentin has been taking care of her
in a cabin.
It's really cool.
He's been hiding her up here.
Excuse me, it's a little
more complicated than that, okay?
No, Quentin, it's really not.
Okay, let's cut the crap.
I hear your city's on a clock.
Where's the money?
Don't worry, I'll tell you everything,
after you help me
get the hell out of this country.
No deal.
The offer's not getting
any better, Ollie.
And the only reason I'm even
considering handing over my nest egg
is because I need help getting away
from that nasty little
songbird friend of yours.
Fine.
Speedy, text me the address.
That was easier than expected.
Oliver's willing to burn Vince, but
he'll let that murdering bitch go.
You were right, D.
Oliver just took Laurel at her word.
The city's not getting
its money back that way.
It's up to us.
Can you track the bug?
You know I can.
Then let's suit up.
Six miles out. Head west.
Felicity, you might wanna make sure
your seat belt is on.
Yeah. It looks good.
- Why?
- We got a tail.
We're marked!
Oh!
- You think it's the others?
- Has to be.
How did they find us?
- Oh, my...
- What?
This.
Rene wanted me to hit him.
It doesn't matter now,
they're in our dust.
Can you keep them there?
You forgot what you hired me for
six years ago.
You know,
that was exhilarating.
It was Alanis Morissette-level ironic.
But exhilarating.
Hello, Ollie.
Where's the money?
Haven't we gone
through this already?
No money until
I am safely out of this country.
You are in no position to make demands.
I can think of 70 million different
reasons why you're wrong about that.
Okay.
Oliver, Oliver, please, please.
Listen, Dinah's just got her scared,
all right? And for good...
Good reason.
Laurel needs our protection.
Which is why
you should let me go with you.
I'll make sure you get
out of the country safely,
and then we can start your new life.
- Together.
- Quentin, that's insane.
Well, well, well...
That was quite the performance,
but now that I know that it was
only about the money, hard pass.
Actually, Thea had it right earlier.
I was more focused on getting
through to you than the money.
But I believe
that if you'd had someone
in your world to support you
when things got bad,
you wouldn't be a criminal.
This is our chance
to find out if I'm right.
If after a while you decide
that you don't want me there,
I'll leave.
Promise.
This time around,
everything's down to you.
Pack your sunblock.
I've always wanted to live
somewhere tropical.
Quentin.
The minute
that she is out of the country,
you get added to
the list of people she's killed.
I'm betting otherwise.
And you trust her enough
to risk yourself? To risk the city?
Tell me now.
I do.
Then so do I.
That's it. I am not sitting here
on the side of the road like trash
while they let that murderer go free!
Guys, we're gonna find them.
How? They tossed away our bug
like it was a bug.
I think I know a way.
But it's gonna hurt John.
You say that like it's a deal breaker.
That guy's the whole reason
I got shot, hoss.
Curtis, this is not the time
to be worrying about John's feelings.
No, I mean, really hurt John.
Physically.
Find them.
Whatever it takes.
Well, the union rep's deadline
is coming up soon.
Three-and-a-half hours
to be depressingly exact.
Don't worry. We'll be gone
and the money will be back
in the city coffers by then.
It better be.
Your new cover identities
are almost done.
You have a one-way ticket
on a private plane
to your father-daughter trip
of a lifetime.
Just keep that vengeful bird of yours
from finding me.
John? It's his arm.
The implant, it's been disabled.
Someone's hacking it remotely
to broadcast our location.
It's not "someone." It's Curtis.
They know where we are.
- Can you fix John?
- Rebooting the chip now.
It's gonna be a while
before you have full functionality.
You're going to be dealing with
your post-injury symptoms for a bit.
I'm aware.
- How long do we have?
- Based on the amount of time
that's passed since we last lost them
and now that they've attacked John,
not long.
I'm sorry, but with the other team
that angry, that close,
I can't protect Laurel by myself.
You don't have to.
Wait, are you gonna fight your old team?
This is insane.
Let's get ready to move.
You're gonna turn right in a mile,
dirt road.
You got us back on track, Mr. T.
I pity those fools now.
Do they know that
we know where they are?
Trust me, they know.
Here's the turn.
Listen...
Laurel is a meta.
Now, I know that people
protecting her were our friends,
but if you hold back, if any of us
hold back our punches here,
we are the ones who are gonna get hurt.
And Laurel and the city's money
will both be gone. Understood?
Sonic dampener arrow.
Never thought Dinah would be the one
we'd use that against...
Having second thoughts?
Best-case scenario, man.
Laurel avoids punishment
for what she's done.
We put a hurtin' on the people
who used to be our friends.
But we keep the city from dying.
But at what cost?
If the people going after her
didn't look like Curtis,
Dinah, and Rene,
would you even be asking this question?
No.
But I can't help but wonder,
would we be doing this
if the person they were after
didn't look like Laurel?
Listen, man, I would back any call
you make, Oliver.
Always have, always will.
But we should acknowledge the fact
that going after our former teammates
may be a line we can never uncross.
I agree.
But they crossed it first.
Take the other car
to the main road and don't turn back.
We'll stop the other team
from following.
You'll have the city's money
in two hours. I promise.
Thank you for fighting for me.
I'm not doing this for you.
But when it's over,
I don't wanna hear your name,
or see your face ever again.
Why not let me handle that?
You know, it's a shame you can't scream.
It almost makes this too easy.
Oh, sweetie,
I don't have to scream to kill you.
You are unbelievable.
I cannot believe you did that.
You could've seriously hurt John!
Just like you guys
are really gonna hurt the city
if you let her go!
Nothing's happened that can't be undone.
We're not saying it's a perfect
outcome, or even a good one,
but at least the city gets its money.
- That's not justice, hoss.
- That's enough.
We've debated this already.
We know where you stand.
- It's time to finish this right now!
- Dinah.
Not one more step.
Get to the car!
Rene!
You're wasting arrows.
Am I?
Hey, hey! Stop!
- Are you crazy?
- Yeah, I must be. Yeah.
- Run!
- All right. Go! Go, go, go!
Go help Curtis.
It's all right. We'll get there.
It'll be fine.
It's all right.
Laurel.
Laurel. Come on, we got to go.
We got to go.
- Come on.
- Quentin.
Quentin.
You stay behind me.
Dinah, you can't do this.
Get out of my way.
You can't do this. Please don't.
Dinah...
Last chance, Rene!
- Stay down!
- No way!
- Hey, is everyone okay?
- We'll live.
- Can you manage?
- Yeah.
We can cut him off. Let's go.
Is this what you felt like
right before you killed Vince?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
We are way, way past sorry.
Dinah!
If we lose her,
we lose the money,
but even if we had the money...
- You can't do this.
- Oh, God!
I have to, Curtis.
You know I have to.
I have to get justice for Vince.
Dinah, look around.
Look at what we're doing to each other.
Does this look like justice?
It's nobody's fault but theirs.
Then you sound just like Oliver.
We formed this team so we wouldn't
be like that. Like him.
Dinah, I don't wanna start today.
I will not be put
back in that cage!
- I'm sorry.
- We could still catch her.
No. You can't.
No more advantages.
I don't need them.
You still hurting?
Don't get soft now, Curtis.
We're just getting... Getting started.
Rene!
Quentin! You okay?
- What the hell's happening?
- We need to get to a hospital.
Now!
Any sign of Laurel?
That trail has gone cold.
I don't think that she'll be able
to get very far with her injuries.
What about yours?
Nothing Felicity can't fix.
You know, I still can't believe
Curtis did this.
I mean, messing with a chip in your
arm is totally crossing the line.
It's our company's prototype.
Obviously, injuring you
is way more of crossing of the line.
Way more.
Was not like
we didn't hurt them back.
Has anyone heard about Rene?
I mean, he...
He didn't look so good.
He was shot five months ago.
The wound reopened.
Well, we should go to the hospital.
We gotta make sure he's okay.
Unless anyone here has $70 million,
there won't be a hospital soon.
Well, listen, Laurel is gonna call,
all right? She's gonna call.
No, she's not.
I know how much we all wish
she was more like the Laurel
that we lost.
But she's not.
We should get ready
to talk to the press.
Quentin's right.
We should go and check on Rene.
Please tell him that I'm sorry.
- I screwed up, Thea.
- No, Quentin. You...
You just believed in your daughter,
okay? That's not screwing up.
And she is your daughter.
In the only way that really matters.
Yeah?
And what way is that?
In the eyes of her father.
Any update?
Yeah.
My bloodstream is about to
reach 90% coffee saturation.
You know, I said that joke
hoping that you would laugh, but...
Maybe now is not the best time
to be saying jokes, so I'll just...
No updates on Rene.
They've been working on him
for hours, huh?
Yeah.
But you know,
Rene is the definition of stubbornness.
No way is he gonna let Oliver
be the reason he goes down.
Yeah.
Dinah.
This whole Laurel thing...
It's not over.
The second Rene is in the clear,
we're gonna track her down,
and we are going to arrest her.
We will get justice for Vince.
Thank you for saying that.
If it wasn't for you,
I would have repaid Vince's death
with more violence.
That isn't justice.
I'm... I'm grateful to you,
you know,
just for pulling me back, so...
The speech worked
because I have faith in you, Dinah.
I also had my T-Spheres programmed
as a plan B.
City reps are all waiting,
and they don't know about the money
or lack thereof.
You don't need to be here, you know.
If you're facing the firing squad,
I'm standing by your side.
I don't know what to tell them.
- It's not your fault, Ollie.
- I'm the Mayor, Speedy.
I made a vow to protect Star City.
And I'm sorry, but I didn't.
I couldn't...
I swear that
I will make it up to them, but...
Just that, okay, Ollie?
You just tell them that.
I think we've waited long enough.
I need to...
I need to inform everyone
that the money
extorted from us
by the cyberterrorist, Cayden James,
has not been recovered.
And to be honest with you,
I don't know that it ever will be.
Now, I promised everyone that
I would find the funds
to keep the metro area running
without work stoppages, but...
I'm so very sorry. As Mayor, I...
I have failed this city.
Now I know that your faith in me
is likely shaken, but my faith...
My faith in the citizens of Star City...
Mayor's luck just keeps getting worse.
DA Armand.
You got a sec?
My case against Queen is built on sand.
It's only a matter of time before
Jean Loring figures that out.
And why are you telling me that?
I found something that could bury Queen.
But I'll need the full backstop.
All the SCPD's resources.
I can see why Mr. Diaz likes you.
The news isn't good.
Mr. Ramirez suffered
a traumatic hemothorax.
We were able to stop
the bleeding in his chest,
but the injury also caused
his lung to re-collapse.
Now, given the severity
of your friend's injuries,
I'm recommending
he be transferred to a facility
that can provide the care he needs.
Outside of Star City.
Mr. Ramirez is resting now.
You and your friends
will have to wait to see him.
What friends?
We thought Rene would be here.
Well, of course he's here.
You saw what Oliver did to him.
Yeah. Yeah. How's Rene doing?
You've lost the right
to ask that question.
- You two need to leave.
- No.
No, not until you tell us
if Rene is okay. This is...
Stop it.
Don't you guys get it?
We're not just done fighting you,
we're done with
the three of you, period.
No more cooperation,
no more communication, forever.
Let's go.
Fine.
I don't know what day it is.
I gotta go...
- Are you okay?
- I just escaped. I...
I was kidnapped two year...
Two years ago, I think. I...
I don't know, I...
Lady, what's your name?
Laurel.
Laurel Lance.