Previously on Arrow...
You're all this city has,
so stop being so hard on yourself.
That notebook belonged to my father.
I thought that it was my way
to save the city.
We all want to believe
in Oliver's crusade,
but I'm pissed that the guy
who only shares the important information
with his inner circle
used to be a serial killer.
For a long time, I blamed you
for my parents dying.
Knowing all this
doesn't make it any easier.
Nobody followed me.
They don't suspect a thing.
I brought what you asked for.
Addresses are on the back.
I took those last two myself.
What, that's it? We had a deal.
I get you the intel, I get to be there
when you take him down.
You think
you can make demands of me?
No.
No, of course not. I know he's your kill,
but I want to watch him die.
You haven't been listening.
I'm not going to kill him.
I'm gonna make him wish he was dead.
This is incredible, Speedy.
I can't believe you pulled it off,
especially after...
Oh, I thought we decided
not to talk about aliens anymore?
- Right.
- And besides, how can you be so surprised?
I'm Moira Queen's daughter,
and that means
throwing a killer Christmas party
is in my blood.
Mom and Dad would be very
proud of you, Speedy.
Me? Come on, you're the Mayor.
They'd be so happy, they wouldn't know
what to do with themselves.
Are you all right? Because,
what the Dominators showed us,
it was a little like losing them
all over again.
They didn't take anything away from me,
they gave me something.
They reminded me how lucky I am
to be a part of this family
and to have you as my brother.
How sweet.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- No, it's fine.
I know, I know, I already broke
the first rule of being a good date
by not arriving with you,
but I had a crushing deadline.
Glamorous life of a journalist, right?
The dress that you're wearing
makes up for it.
I...
You're his... His date?
Yeah.
Yeah, just... Just for this party.
Which, by the way,
is a definite improvement
over the previous Mayor's holiday bash.
Nicely done.
Thanks. It's really great to know
that this administration can do,
like, one thing right.
- Be nice, Thea.
- No,
I'm gonna go get a drink now,
talk to you later.
She's... I mean,
she's just being protective.
Mmm. To be fair,
I didn't make the best first impression.
Well, I of all people understand
that sometimes doing your job
means pissing people off.
It just means that you're doing it well.
I see you've reclaimed your optimism.
Oh, thanks to you.
Cheers.
- Is that your second champagne?
- Third.
Are you really that nervous
to finally introduce me to your friends?
I just want them to love you
as much as I I...
...like you.
These are my friends.
Guys, this is my Malone boyfriend.
This is Billy Malone,
my boy... Boyfriend
I'm Curtis, by the way,
the guy awkwardly standing in front of you
waiting to be introduced.
- And this is my husband, Paul.
- Curtis is my best friend at work.
Well, was, until I was fired
from my own company. Cheers.
I thought you guys were working
on a startup together?
The one he's been putting
all the late nights in on?
The very late nights at the startup, yes!
We, it's just...
The startup is so fun, I mean,
we barely call it work,
because it's just like...
Whoo-hoo!
So much fun.
Who needs a fancy party at City Hall
when all the most important people
are right here?
Oh, shucks, John,
you're gonna make us all blush.
Do you think it's a fire hazard
to light the menorah in here?
I think the only hazard's gonna be
if you mess with that table setting
before Lyla gets back with the turkey.
Oh.
- What do you think?
- Nice.
- Cute kid.
- Yeah, he gets it from his mom.
I figured.
Must be weird
finding out about Flashpoint.
Yeah, I'm still not sure
how I feel about that, man.
I should be used to all the unusual things
around here,
especially after last week, but,
I could never imagine a daughter.
Cool car!
Being a father's
the best thing in the world,
especially around the holidays.
Sounds like you know something
about kids, you got any?
Sorry, I'm late, but I come bearing gifts.
We had this tradition in my family
where we all open our presents
at the exact same time.
Since you guys are the only family I have,
I figured I'd try it with you.
Thanks.
Were you even listening to the rules?
I don't like rules, or listening.
This is dope, Evie!
Wow.
Thanks, Evelyn, it's very sweet.
You're welcome.
You know, the best part is,
this is gonna piss Oliver off
when we hang these up all over the place.
Happy Holidays, everyone.
Thank you so much for coming.
My favorite Christmas movie is Die Hard.
It's true. My second favorite
Christmas movie is It's a Wonderful Life.
And I was very lucky to be able to
rewatch that movie last week.
It reminded me how much work
I still have to do,
how much work all of us still have to do,
and it inspired me to recommit myself
to making our city, our home,
a better and safer place. Cheers.
Great speech.
Uh...
What she said.
Uh, Felicity, right?
Yeah, you must be the super-hot reporter.
Um, Thank you.
What I meant to say was, this is my,
this is my boyfriend, Billy.
It's nice to see you again, Mayor Queen.
Billy, please call me Oliver.
Hey, um, we're actually gonna head out.
- Everything all right?
- It will be.
L think.
So, you guys want to go on a double date
some time, or...
No. Cook
Paul! Paul, come on!
Tell me the truth. All those nights
you said you were with Felicity,
- what have you been doing?
- Nothing.
- Are you seeing someone?
- Baby, of course not!
- I don't believe you.
- Let me explain.
Curtis!
Get out of here, run!
- No!
Do what you want to me,
just leave him alone.
No!
Help! Somebody help us!
Please! Help!
- Hey.
- How you feeling?
Like someone threw a throwing star at me,
kicked me down a flight of steps,
and knocked me out.
The doctor said you're not
supposed to sit up.
Yeah, well, the doctor
doesn't know me that well.
Not sure I do anymore, either.
I can explain everything.
Great. Let's start with
where you learned to fight like that.
Fight like what? In case you
hadn't noticed, I lost. Badly.
You think I don't know who
that was, Curtis?
That was the Throwing Star Killer.
He's murdered people.
And yet somehow, you're still alive.
How is that even possible?
Oh, my God, Curtis, are you all right?
I'm great. Just a little banged up,
like I always am when I get into
street fights with muggers.
It wasn't a mugger,
it was a serial killer,
the Throwing Star Killer.
I thought you had the Anti-Crime Unit
taking care of this.
We do, Paul, and-and we're working
very hard to catch him. I promise.
Actually, your statement
could really help.
Detective Malone is just outside,
if you'd feel comfortable answering
a few questions?
It's all right, Paul.
Prometheus.
He attacked me, as well "me."
So he knows you're Mr. Terrific.
Yeah. Which means he probably knows...
He knows that I'm the Green Arrow.
If you remember anything else
that could help us, give me a call.
My cell's on there, too.
Thank you, Detective.
I can't believe that this is happening.
Can't you?
You think I haven't figured out
that the tall guy in the black mask
rolling with the Green Arrow is Curtis?
Promise me you didn't tell Paul.
No, but right now,
I'm more worried about you.
If Prometheus is targeting the people
working with the Green Arrow...
I'll be fine.
And I'll feel better if you're
staying at my place
at least until we track down Prometheus.
- We?
- It's my job, Felicity.
If there's a killer out there,
I'm gonna stop him,
especially if he's a threat
to someone I care about.
Billy. Billy!
Everything all right?
No. The doctor was speaking with Curtis,
he's gonna be fine,
but they found a drug in his system
called Dycloserol.
No, never heard of it.
But you have, what is it?
Well, it's gonna take some adjusting,
not trying to catch you
giving me the slip.
I grabbed some Big Belly on the way in,
hope you're hungry.
I lost my appetite. Come look at this.
TB outbreak in Lamb Valley?
Since when?
Since this guy got greedy.
That's one smug-looking
son of a bitch.
Justin Claybourne owns
Claybourne Pharmaceuticals
that recently acquired the rights
to this drug, Dycloserol,
which fights this particular strain of TB.
Let me guess,
as soon as the outbreak started,
he jacked up the prices.
Price went from $10 a pill
to $1,000 overnight.
The people of Lamb Valley,
they're working class,
low income, they can't afford this.
It's disgusting, but not illegal.
Claybourne is on the list.
I'm not worried about illegal.
Just because your father
wrote down his name?
My father explained this list.
These are terrible people.
How would you know that?
I thought he was dead.
I am gonna make sure that Claybourne
stops gouging people.
And what if he refuses to cooperate?
You ask that like he has a choice.
After what seems like a respite
from the serial murders weeks ago,
the Throwing Star Killer strikes again.
Another attack by the Throwing Star Killer
disrupted the annual holiday party
at City Hall.
Maybe we should change
the security codes on the bunker.
Yeah, we did that over an hour ago.
All the good that'll do.
Rene's right.
And you know
how much she hates saying that.
If Prometheus knows who Curtis is,
he knows who we all are.
Maybe Barry could do that
Flashpoint thing again?
Yeah, he does that,
Digg might end up with five kids.
Stuff makes my brain hurt.
How's Curtis?
He's gonna be fine.
Better, now that
the Dycloserol's out of his system.
Prometheus injected him with it
when he attacked him.
Dycloserol. Now, why does that
ring a bell?
Because four years ago,
The Hood took down Justin Claybourne,
the CEO of the pharmaceutical company
that manufactures it.
And by took him down, you mean killed.
- Right?
- Yeah.
After Claybourne's death,
his company went down,
he had no other family members
to leave it to.
Still, Prometheus using Dycloserol
four years after the fact
can't be a coincidence.
- It does send a message.
- What message?
I'm alive and I'm coming after you.
You think Prometheus is Justin Claybourne?
How's that possible?
Well, in our town, people who are dead
turn out to be secretly alive
almost every Wednesday.
Case in point, the old Claybourne
manufacturing plant
reports heavy usage of water and power
over the last few months.
Doesn't mean it's Claybourne.
Worth checking out. Suit up.
- We're in.
- Copy.
Ragman, are you in position?
If he's in there, he's not getting out.
Nobody makes a move
until I give the order.
Got it.
Hey, he said don't make a move.
Yeah, but he knows I never listen to him.
That could be something.
You keep moving, I'll check it out.
- Overwatch.
- Already on it.
Tracking the transmission
from the sensors now.
- That was fast.
- No, that was impossible.
He's letting me in.
No, you need to pull back, it's not safe.
Five years and he still doesn't listen.
Justin Claybourne,
you have failed this city.
Not as badly as you have, Mr. Queen.
Spartan, go upstairs,
Green Arrow needs your help.
Me and Artemis are on the stairwell,
we can get there faster.
You ready for a rematch with this bitch?
More than. Prometheus doesn't scare me.
I've been waiting four years for this.
Let him go, you son of a bitch.
What the...
Evelyn?
- Why?
- Because you're not a hero,
you're a fraud.
This city needs to be saved from you.
Where's Prometheus?
He's gone with Evelyn.
He took her?
He's working with her.
- Stuff from the plant.
- Can you put it over there?
- Where's Oliver?
- He's with Thea, helping her pack.
He wants her to stay here.
Lyla and J.J.
are at a A.R.G.U.S. safe house.
Give me the names and socials
of the people you care about,
I'll make sure they get to the safehouse.
Wait. What other secret information could
Evelyn have told Prometheus about us?
We've got to assume everything.
No one is safe.
This is on me. I should've done
a better job at vetting her.
This wasn't your fault.
Seriously. No one
could've seen this coming.
We don't have time
to play the blame game.
We have to find Claybourne.
We were hoping there was
something here that could help.
- Like ashes?
- Those look like crematorium ashes.
Question is, whose?
Right. Well, I got to go, so you guys need
to run a DNA test
on these ashes and bone fragments,
find out who this person was and why
Prometheus is keeping their remains.
You guys know how to run
a DNA sequencer, right?
No, of course you don't.
Look, who I'm talking to.
Just put some of the bone fragments
onto the slide,
put it in the slot, and the machine
will do the rest. Got it?
Uh, sure.
I'll be back.
Did you get all that?
You're the smart one, remember?
Hey. I thought you were gonna
let the Green Arrow handle this.
No, I'm pretty sure my exact words were,
"If there's a killer out there,
I'm gonna stop him."
Yeah, I was just hoping
that was boyfriend posturing.
I cross-referenced Curtis'
medical records with old SCPD case files.
Prometheus injected him with Dycloserol,
- which was manufactured at the Clay...
- Claybourne Pharmaceuticals
and their plant just came online.
Yeah, I know.
How did you know?
Because the Green Arrow hit it already.
And we already got everything
that there is to get there.
Why didn't you tell me?
Remember that part about me
not wanting you to work on this case?
Yeah, I'm a cop, Felicity, this is my job.
Yeah, and Prometheus' job is killing cops,
so you need to stay away.
Hey, if you're not gonna do it
for yourself,
can you do it for me?
I'm not letting this go.
Felicity, you know how I feel about you,
but I have to be true to who I am.
I can't believe it.
Evelyn was playing us this whole time?
RORY". Not the whole time.
Rene thinks she went dark
after we all found out about The Hood.
You know, I always thought she had
a sort of Children of the Corn vibe.
Anyway, I was just calling
to give you the heads-up.
Watch your back.
Will do. Thanks, Rory.
Hey, baby, what's going on?
Were you able to find me that ice cream?
- Who's Rory?
- Oh...
Oh, Rory. He's a friend of mine
from my Palmer Tech days.
He saw what happened on the news
and was just checking in on me.
You're the world's worst liar, Curtis.
It's one of the reasons I married you.
What're you talking about?
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
The late nights out, canceled dinners,
the inexplicable accidents.
I can't do this anymore.
You have to tell me what's going on.
How do I put this?
I work with the Green Arrow.
You? You work with the Green Arrow?
Yeah.
- Come on.
- It's not impossible.
You're helping the guy who is going around
putting arrows into people?
Well, yeah, but only bad people,
and only the ones who really
try to put up a fight.
Most guys, we just try to send to jail.
This is completely insane.
Yes, I know that,
but, you know, when you're out there
doing it, it's different.
It feels amazing.
Empowering.
Almost a little inspiring.
You lied to me.
- For months.
- To keep you safe.
To keep me safe? And what about you?
You've been hurt how many times
since you started this?
- Actually lost track.
- Which is why you need to stop.
- Stop what?
- This, being a vigilante.
I made a commitment.
You made one to me, too.
Last time I checked, our vows
didn't include me worrying every night
about whether or not you were gonna
make it home alive the next morning.
Paul...
You can be a vigilante,
or you can be married to me,
but you can't do both.
I can't do both.
Paul, wait...
Think in Flashpoint, I maybe dated her
back in high school?
It's an alternate timeline,
not an alternate reality.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means, and no offense,
but in a multiverse of possibilities,
there's no world where Thea Queen
goes outwith...
You know, someone like you.
What's that supposed to mean,
"someone like me"?
It means you're not my type.
- Any news?
- Nothing.
If Claybourne's out there,
he's not showing his face.
Well, maybe his dead friend
will give us some information.
- You get the sequencer working?
- I think?
Oh, good work!
You got the sequencer working.
Great. So whose ashes
was Claybourne keeping as a souvenir?
Claybourne's.
The ashes are his.
So if Claybourne isn't Prometheus, who is?
Thanks to the influx of cash
from our Dycloserol acquisition,
our R & D pipeline's fully funded
for the next two years.
These are exciting times, gentlemen,
and it's just the beginning.
Justin Claybourne,
you have failed this city.
I think you got the wrong guy, pal.
My company makes drugs that help people.
Not the people in Lamb Valley.
It's not my problem if some people
can't afford it.
It is now.
Your days of holding
this city's health hostage are over.
Do you understand me?
Okay, okay, yes!
You have until 11:00 p.m. tomorrow
to make this right.
And what happens if I don't?
I'll aim higher.
Jackpot
SCPD! Show yourself!
Cute baby.
Cute, yeah, but why would your boyfriend
send this to you?
That is what I'm trying to figure out.
That, and why men don't listen
when you specifically tell them
not to do something.
Why don't you guys listen?
Okay,
did you ask him why he sent it?
Yeah, texted him right back, no reply.
I'm kinda worried.
Billy says he found it at
the Claybourne manufacturing plant?
Yeah, according to the
GPS tag on his text.
Why would he send this photo?
What's the relevance?
It's what's I'm trying to figure out.
Right after I try to figure out
why men don't listen.
This is so strange. First human remains,
now baby pictures?
Prometheus, he's...
He's leaving a trail of breadcrumbs
for me to follow.
- Try facial recognition?
- Facial recog isn't exactly baby friendly.
Well, try it anyways,
it's kitchen sink time, and
we don't listen because we're stubborn.
Yeah, tell us something we don't know.
Take it Claybourne wasn't impressed
with your Robin Hood act.
No, he wasn't.
So I did some more digging.
Claybourne didn't just price gouge
with his drug, he created the epidemic.
He is connected to something called
the AK Desmond Group.
They are black marketeers
who specialize in creating bioweapons.
What do you think they've
been working on?
Weaponized tuberculosis.
He created the marketplace, Diggle,
and he didn't care
who died in the process.
And now you're gonna kill him.
How can you read what's in that folder
and have a problem with that?
Have you thought about the ramifications
of your actions?
Of actually crossing names off a list?
Of being judge, jury, and executioner?
Men like Claybourne buy judges,
they buy juries.
The law doesn't apply to them.
- I'm not saying you don't do some good!
- So what are you saying?
What I'm saying is that
maybe one day, your actions
might have some unintended consequences.
Got your 911.
911 might've been
understating things a bit.
Detective Malone's been abducted.
ACU thinks by Prometheus.
Why do they think that?
He went out to track down a lead,
didn't come back.
He's missed his last three call-ins,
GPS on his phone's been switched off.
Do you think he's dead?
I think that every cop
that's crossed paths with Prometheus is.
Whether or not Billy's alive,
and believe me, I hope that he is,
the ACU and the SCPD,
they need instructions.
Well, we've had a BOLO out for weeks.
I'm not talking about a Be-On-the-Lookout-
Order, I'm talking about a shoot-to-kill.
I don't know
how that'll sit with the public.
I do. They'll love it.
You know why? Because they are as sick
and tired as I am
of watching this psycho murder Star City's
finest and get away with it.
Our cops need to know
that they can fight back,
they don't have to take it easy
on this guy anymore.
Okay, do it, but you pull in
every cop that you can find,
you tell them holiday hours are revoked.
Yeah.
Talk to me.
Facial recognition did kick back
something on the baby photo.
Court records
related to Claybourne's divorce.
The baby is Claybourne's son.
You told me that Claybourne
didn't have any kids.
Not of the legitimate variety.
But the divorce petition
Claybourne's ex-wife filed says otherwise.
There's no record
of the kid's name in the files,
but due to the filing date,
he'd be about 30 today.
Just old enough to put on
a hood and a mask.
Old enough to want revenge on the man
who murdered his father.
Oliver, this isn't on you, man.
Yes, it is.
You warned me, John. You warned me that
there would be unintended consequences
and I didn't listen.
Prometheus surprised me
at the plant with a move,
a very specific, unique move.
It was taught to me by a woman
that I met in Russia.
You think you and Prometheus
had the same teacher?
I think what he's saying is,
Prometheus had over four years
to learn everything he does.
Right.
Felicity, Billy has gone missing.
Chase thinks that it's Prometheus.
We alerted the police.
We've ordered them to shoot
Prometheus on sight.
Now, we are gonna find Billy,
we are gonna bring him back to you,
I promise.
Let's call Rory and Rene,
we're gonna hit the streets.
If you learn anything, contact me.
Do not engage this enemy
under any circumstances.
I thought you weren't suiting up anymore.
Yeah, well, it's Felicity's boyfriend.
I figured, all hands.
Plus, John told me about Claybourne,
and four years ago.
Speedy, are you about to tell me,
after everything that's happened,
and everything that's happening,
this isn't my fault?
Do you remember when Tommy and I
went to the US Open?
And you tried to land that helicopter
on the grounds
'cause Tommy wanted to impress
Maria Sharapova and then
made Dad blow that huge acquisitions deal?
Because he had to bail me out, yeah.
Pretty sure that was the most disappointed
he's ever been in you.
I'm not seeing the relevance, Speedy.
My point is, Dad wouldn't be disappointed
in who you've become.
It's like you were saying
at that Christmas party,
Mom and Dad would be proud.
They might not be proud if they knew
that I created something like Prometheus.
There're two types of every legacy,
two versions of what we leave behind.
There's the good and then the bad.
You just really have a lousy habit
of focusing only on the bad.
Why are you not still in the hospital?
Rory called me,
told me what happened to Billy.
There's no way I'm sitting this out.
Wow, what did Paul have to say?
Actually, he made it pretty easy.
Give up the team or give up him.
Well, he clearly
doesn't know you very well.
What do you mean?
Well, you don't really respond well
to ultimatums.
He just doesn't get it.
I have to do this no matter what.
I have to be true to who I am.
- A singing telegram? Okay.
- Mmm-hmm.
My friend loves them and I thought
that I would surprise her.
- Her?
- Just a friend.
But I don't know
where her office buildings are.
She works at the AK Desmond Group...
AK Desmond Group. Hmm.
They're not on the Internet,
like, at all, that's really weird.
- Super weird.
- All right, well, lucky for you,
there is the Internet
And then there is the "lnternet."
And these magic fingers can pull things
out of it, even Google can't find.
Not that I believe in magic.
Or, that I have magic fingers. I just,
I'm really good at, I'm... I can...
Felicity? Please.
Right. Uh...
Mmm-hmm. 1852
West Maple, 30th Floor.
- Great.
- What? There you go. Just...
It's... I meant to put it there,
just leave it there. It's...
Thank you.
You can just...
Felicity.
I do believe in magic.
- 1852.
- What?
1852. I just remembered something
I should've thought of a long time ago.
Thought of what?
- I think I know where Prometheus is.
- I'll call the team.
No, I created this situation,
I am going to deal with it alone.
Detective Malone.
Kill that Robin Hood son of a bitch!
You going to tell me again
I failed this city?
You infected the people
in Lamb Valley to turn a profit.
You want to make this city great again?
This is how.
With business, money.
You are sentencing
innocent families, children, to death.
Nobody cares about those people.
They're a blight.
And I'm just thinning the herd.
So am l.
Did you hesitate at all
when you killed him?
Or was he just another name
you crossed off your list?
If you want revenge,
I'm right here.
This is about so much more than revenge.
I've studied you, Oliver Queen.
I know everything.
Who you love, who you trust,
who you've hurt.
Do you know how easy it was
to turn Evelyn against you?
How easy it will be to turn them all?
You're not a hero, you're a killer,
and I'm going to show them that.
I'm going to show them
how everything you touch dies.
Four years I've waited,
to make you answer for your sins.
I told you, Oliver,
everything you touch dies.
What happened out there, man?
Did you kill Prometheus?
Billy. Did you find Billy?
Oliver?
Prometheus staged Billy.
He duct-taped his mouth,
and he put a weapon in his hand,
and he put him in his suit.
Prometheus knew...
- No, Oliver, don't.
- That I was there to kill him.
- Don't!
- And he'd calculated every moment.
Where is he?
Where is Billy?
L killed Billy.
I'm so sorry, Felicity.
I didn't know it was Billy,
I couldn't have known
that it was him. I could...
I couldn't have known.
Oh, my God.
This was Prometheus.
This was all him.
He's trying to prove to me
that everyone, I...
I come into contact with,
everyone close to me dies.
And he's right, he...
I think that, uh...
I think that all of you
should get as far away from me
as you possibly can.
Oliver, we are exactly
where we're supposed to be.
Okay.
I know I picked the worst
possible night to come home late again,
but you have to believe me,
this was a seriously terrible day.
Which is not going to get any better.
I'm going to my brother's house.
Come on, baby, it's been less than
24 hours since your ultimatum.
That's the thing, I never wanted to be
the guy that makes ultimatums.
You know what's funny?
You were coming home every night, late,
banged up all to hell,
and I've never seen you happier.
I don't want to be the one
to take you away from that.
You don't have to be.
But I also can't live knowing that
every time I see you might be the last.
I love you too much.
Paul, please.
I'm sorry.
Paul, please. Please.
- Hey.
- Johnny, I need you to come
to the safe house.
Something's wrong with J.J.
Lyla?
Oliver.
What time is it?
I'm sorry. I didn't know
where else to go.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
Come on. Come in.
Can I get you a drink?
I could use a drink.
Why'?
I thought things were getting better.
So did I, but, um...
That feeling never seems to last.
Thank you.
And, why do you think that is?
I was reunited with someone
from my past recently.
I knew their father.
And they told me
that I ruin the lives of everyone
that I come into contact with.
Doesn't matter who they are.
Doesn't matter how much I love them.
If I'm in their life,
that life turns to ash.
I think that's ridiculous.
Everyone's life touches everyone else's.
Sometimes the result is good,
and sometimes it's bad,
but you are only focusing on the bad.
My sister
said something very similar to that.
Well, she's a smart woman.
Look, no matter what's going on
in your life, Oliver,
shutting people out
is the last thing you should do.
Let me show you.
Hi, Ollie.