My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years on a hellish island...
I have come home with only one goal:
To save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on Arrow:
Blood's trounced every
potential candidate we focus tested.
You want me to run against Blood?
- Child of Ra's Al Ghul awaits your return.
- Tell Ra's Al Ghul my family's off limits.
- It's time for you to come back home.
- I can't.
If they knew I was alive, Laurel and Mom...
they would never stop looking for me
and that could get them both killed.
Thea Queen telling me
enough is enough.
Now, that is rich.
Sara?
Welcome to Starling City
International Airport.
Please have your passports ready
and your customs forms filled out.
All passengers with departing flights
will need to show...
appropriate identification
and declaration papers.
International passengers
are required to have a passport...
and an airline boarding pass to travel.
Business or personal, Miss Raatko?
Personal.
All passengers
are required to pick up their luggage...
in the baggage claim area...
My computer froze.
Can you hold on a sec?
I'll be right back.
Down on the ground!
Get your hands on your head!
I said hands on your head, lady.
I will shoot you!
Welcome to Starling City...
A successful mayoral campaign isn't about
polling, it isn't about fundraising...
or hot-button issues,
it's about connecting with people.
That's why, right after we
announce tomorrow, Moira...
I want to get you in front of
as many cameras as possible.
- Morning shows, talk shows...
- Mark, I want to help rebuild the city...
- not pander to it.
- It's not pandering Mum, it's campaigning.
Let the people get to know
the real Moira Queen...
- and they are gonna fall in love with you.
- Speaking from experience...
this man knows
what he's talking about, Moira.
Mr. Steele, may I talk
to you about something?
I'm no longer your boss, Felicity.
So let's make it Walter from now on.
Okay. Walter. It's about Tempest.
Mrs. Queen's super sketchy offshore LLC
you asked me to look into last year.
I remember.
That's right.
So, the thing is, I left an
embedded account alert on it...
so we'd know
if anyone ever accessed it again.
A few days ago there was a wire transfer
made from Tempest...
to a numbered account
at Starling National Bank.
Probably the campaign
accountants shutting it down.
Or it could be something else.
That is the money Ms. Queen used
to do really bad things.
I mean, you guys got divorced
for pretty good reasons...
which is not my business.
I'll talk to Moira first thing.
Thank you for bringing it to my attention.
Of course.
Well, we're starting a campaign.
- Oliver, can I have a word?
- Yes.
I know that you and he are friends...
but you'll need to end
your support for Sebastian Blood.
- I will speak to Sebastian.
- Good.
Hello.
I'll be right there.
Oliver.
- Mrs. Lance.
- I came back as soon as I heard.
Thanks for coming.
Hey. How are you feeling?
- I've been better.
- Don't worry, baby.
We're going to get you
all the help you need.
There's a great rehab outside of Starling.
And they've got a bed waiting...
Dad, I already told you, I didn't OD.
I didn't take any pills last night.
I swear.
Laurel, the doctor wants to check your eye.
- What happened to her eye?
- Minor subconjunctival hemorrhaging.
Probably from hitting her head
when she lost consciousness.
After the exam, we can discharge her.
You feel better, okay?
Thank you.
We'll be outside. Let's go.
Dad...
What is it, sweetheart?
Before I passed out...
the strangest thing happened.
I saw Sara.
I know I was hallucinating...
but I saw her.
She was standing right over me.
I mean, I've dreamt
about her over the years...
but this was so much more real.
That's crazy, right?
Yeah, it's crazy.
She's been doing that
for like an hour.
You saw Laurel? Is she going to be okay?
You saved her life.
Thanks for calling me.
And I never did ask you...
how did you find me?
I wasn't going to lose you again.
- I should get going.
- Hey, so that's it?
You're back in town for 24 hours and now
you're just going to take off again?
The League of Assassins
is still after me, Ollie...
and staying in town
would put my whole family at risk.
I only came back because
Laurel's in trouble.
She's still in trouble, Sara.
Your entire family needs you.
And so do I.
Do me a favor? Dig up a copy of Laurel's
blood work from the hospital, please.
- Sure. What are we looking for?
- I just want to make sure of something.
It's for you.
- Hello, detective.
- Put my daughter on.
I know she's there.
Hilton, tell the lieutenant that
that the perp was
practically lawyering up when
I read him his Miranda.
If we don't get on top of this situation,
the lieutenant, he's not gonna...
- It smells amazing, Dad.
- Oh, yeah. Here, try one of these.
- Beautiful... No, I'm talking to Laurel.
- Quentin, hang up the phone...
...spend time with your family.
...time with my family. You heard that.
I gotta go. Bye buddy.
Sorry, ladies.
Our doer hired some dirtbag lawyer.
Says the dad whose daughter
just applied to law school.
That is not the kind of lawyer
that you're gonna be, young lady.
Because you, you're gonna
be a judge or you're
gonna be a professor
just like your mother.
Yeah, come over to academia.
The fun never ends.
Dinner is at a crucial point.
- Hiya!
- Hi!
- Hi there.
- Hi.
- Sara, what a surprise.
Please don't tell me you
got kicked out of college.
Oh, well, thank you for
the vote of confidence.
I had a three day weekend so I figured
I'd drive down, surprise everybody.
Well, you're just in time to eat.
Come here.
Get yourself another plate. Come on.
Here you go.
Hi, Dad.
I only have a minute.
One cup of tea is all I ask. Sit down.
I've missed you so much.
How's Laurel?
She saw you.
Right before she passed out.
She thought it was...
I don't know what, a hallucination.
- Good.
- No, baby, you don't understand.
Seeing you, it made her happy.
Dad, the League,
they're still hunting me.
So what, you're just gonna pop back
everytime one of us in trouble?
We can't live like this, Sara.
And you can't.
It's time we started
facing things together.
I've had better greetings.
I'm sorry, I just...
I didn't know what you were going to do.
To be honest, neither did I.
Yeah. We should talk.
Of course.
Do we need permission
from your boyfriend?
I am Nyssa.
Daughter of Ra's Al Ghul.
Heir to the Demon.
What are you doing here?
Sara swore her allegiance
to the League of Assassins.
It's time for her to return home.
That is not going to happen.
Nyssa, please,
would you give us a moment?
Take your time.
Goodbyes are never easy.
Is that why I didn't get one?
I can explain...
You don't have to.
But you're not leaving. I don't trust her.
Then trust me.
- Mrs. Queen?
- Hmm?
A Miss Smoak is here to see you.
- Who?
- Uh, me.
If you're looking for
Oliver, he's not here.
I know. I'm here to see you.
Really? What about?
Tempest.
I flagged a large wire transfer you made.
When I mentioned it to Walter,
he said he would talk to you about it.
I could tell on his face he wouldn't.
British people are really bad liars.
- Yes, they are.
- So I looked into it myself because...
full disclosure? I don't trust you.
You paid a substantial
sum of money to a Dr. Gill.
He was the the doctor who delivered Thea.
Which didn't make any sense to me.
So I went through a dozen different
theories until I remembered...
your testimony at trial.
You had an affair with Malcolm Merlyn.
One year before Thea was born.
Merlyn is Thea's father.
I can see why Walter and Oliver have
such a high appraisal of your capabilities.
So, what are you going to do
with this information...
Felicity?
I don't know. Confronting you in your
living room was as far as my plan went.
I thought you deserved
the chance to tell Oliver yourself.
He should hear it from you.
I'm not going to tell my son anything.
And neither are you.
If you won't keep
my secret for Oliver's sake...
you should keep it for your own.
I see the way you look at him.
You tell him this,
you will rip his world apart.
And a part of him will always blame you.
He'll hate me, for sure.
But he will hate you too.
We all have to keep secrets, Miss Smoak.
- You look different.
- I'm still me.
The Sara I know
wouldn't have betrayed us...
and fled Nanda Parbat
under the cover of darkness.
I didn't have a choice. The earthquake...
I needed to see my family.
Make sure they were safe.
And so they are.
Now come home.
I can't. I can't go back, Nyssa.
I don't have much of a soul left in me...
but what there is,
it can't take the killing anymore.
You swore an oath. My father
sent me here to make sure you honor it...
one way or another.
We both know the real reason
why you came here.
When I found you...
you were starving and alone,
simply waiting to die.
The League took you in...
nursed you back to health.
The only reason you're alive today
is because of me.
Hey, I wasn't with you
because you saved me...
I was with you because I loved you.
But not anymore.
Ra's listens to you
and you can ask him to release me.
My father has never
released anyone from the League.
He released Malcolm Merlyn.
An action he and the citizens
of this city dearly regret.
Do what you have to.
It's been two hours. And she should've
gotten in touch with me by now.
Felicity?
- Felicity!
- What?
- Sorry, what?
- Are you okay?
Uh, yeah. I'm fine.
- It's just... Things in here.
- The League's never going to let me go.
At least if I'm halfway around the world,
then I can keep my family safe.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Just got a copy of Laurel's blood work.
- She tested negative for drugs.
- Well then, why did she collapse?
Because they found traces
of snake venom in her blood.
- From a Tibetan Pit Viper.
- Wait, so Laurel didn't OD?
She was poisoned.
She was poisoned by Nyssa who
did it to draw you back here.
- And it worked.
- My family's in danger.
- Who are you texting?
- No one.
Did you meet a boy at school?
Cut it out. Boys at school are lame.
How's everything with you and Oliver?
Great.
We decided to start looking
at apartments together.
I know it's a big step,
but we're ready.
I think we'll live together for a year,
engaged for another and then...
- Mrs. Laurel Queen.
- Maybe one day.
This is kind of assuming
that he's ever ready to settle down.
What's that supposed to mean?
We both know at least
10 girls that he's slept with.
Can't you just be happy for me?
I mean if you met some amazing guy...
who wanted to spend the rest of his life
with you, I'd be so supportive...
I wasn't trying to be a bitch.
The title of your autobiography.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Dad, it's my fault. I'm so sorry.
This assassins group that you're
part of, they took your mother.
- Not exactly.
- Well, what exactly?
A woman, Nyssa, she's a
powerful figure in the League.
She poisoned Laurel,
she took Mom.
Well, to get you to
come back to the League.
To get me to come back to her.
Oh.
Nyssa, don't do this.
I tried to warn you but
you wouldn't listen.
I thought would be instructive
for you to know what
it feels like to suddenly
lose someone you love.
To have them ripped
from your life without warning.
- You do not want to hurt my mother.
- You're right. I don't.
You have one day.
Make the right choice.
- We have 24 hours.
- Detective, we'll find her.
Okay, Laurel's inside, she's
losing her mind. I gotta go.
Keep me updated.
Come on. You ought to buy a ticket
if you're gonna play like that.
Hey kiddo, how's the apartment hunt going?
Terribly.
I really wanted to find
the perfect place to
show Ollie when he gets
back from his boat trip.
Everything good was already taken
by the time I walked in the door.
Maybe it's a sign that
you're not supposed to move
in with that frat boy that
you call your boyfriend.
You and Mom were my age when
you moved into that place on Spring Street.
You weren't even engaged yet.
That's because your mother
kept turning down all my proposals.
- She did?
- You know your mother...
free spirit and all. "Why do
we need rings when we have love?"
You know I spent a year with that damn ring
burning a hole in my pocket?
Significant news day here in Starling.
Queen's Gambit sent a mayday
transmission late last night...
and has not been heard from since.
Among those missing are locals
Robert and Oliver Queen.
Do we have a lead on Dinah?
We researched the poison
Nyssa used on Laurel.
Lucky for us, Tibetan Pit Viper venom
is surprisingly difficult to transport.
It starts losing its potency the moment
it leave the fangs.
Another sentence
I never thought I'd actually say aloud.
- So it was bought locally.
- Not bought. Stolen.
- From where?
- The zoo.
A local break-in.
The perps didn't steal
anything so the cops chalked
it up to a bunch of kids
looking for a thrill.
I pulled up the zoo CCTV footage from the
night of the break-in. I got a plate.
Car is a rental. Address is in the Glades.
Sara. Call your father.
Sebastian, I am so sorry.
I have a bad habit of standing you up.
Look, I know you have to pull your support
from my campaign.
Blood is thicker than politics.
And it should be.
Thank you for understanding. And I really
hope that this doesn't affect our friendship.
- It's important to me.
- And to me.
Can I help you, alderman?
Oh, I had a meeting with your son.
I'm sure you can guess the topic.
I hope my decision to run against you
for mayor doesn't affect your relationship.
Out of respect for that relationship,
can I offer some advice?
- Please.
- Get out. Now.
The fact that you're advising me to get out
before I even announce my candidacy...
suggests that you're threatened.
I'm apprehensive
about destroying my friend's mother.
- I can take care of myself.
- Really?
During your trial, you portrayed yourself
as a fragile creature...
living under Malcolm Merlyn's thumb.
So which is it?
The woman strong enough to lead the city
or the one too weak-willed to save it?
The one who should not be underestimated.
- So, what exactly is the plan here?
- We wait.
The Arrow will lead him right to us.
You know, you never did tell me how you
joined up with the Arrow in the first place.
Where did you two even meet?
Vigilante club.
Same old Sara.
Well, not exactly the same.
I loved her, Dad.
Are you upset?
Honestly, Sara?
To think what you've been through
these past 6 years, pain, loneliness...
I'm just happy to hear you had someone
that cared for you.
What's the matter, they didn't teach you
about right crosses in assassins' school?
- Where is Nyssa?
- Tell me where my wife is.
- What the hell is he saying?
- He's praying.
No, don't...
Son of a bitch.
It's over, detective.
He's gone.
- How's Sara holding up?
- Not well.
And I need you to pick
up the trail on Nyssa.
Because Mrs. Lance is
running out of time.
I'm on it.
- Ah, Oliver. Felicity.
- Hi. Hi.
Well, I haven't been this nervous
since my wedding day.
- Both of them.
- Moira, it's time.
Oliver, you ready to
introduce your mother?
With pride.
Felicity? Felicity.
What is going on with you?
- And don't say... don't say nothing.
- Nothing...
The truth, please.
- You might have noticed that I talk a lot.
- It has not escaped my attention.
You might have also noticed
that I don't talk a lot about my family.
I have noticed that.
My mother is...
She's my mother.
And I don't really know what my father
is because he abandoned us.
I barely remember him.
But I do remember
how much it hurt when he left.
And just the thought of losing someone
that important to me again...
Hey.
You're not gonna lose me.
Whatever it is that's bothering you,
is it about your family?
No.
It's about yours.
Time's up.
Have you made your decision?
Let my mother go.
And I will return with you to Nanda Parbat.
You're doing the right thing, Sara.
For both of us.
Here you go, sweetie.
Chamomile, like you like.
Is there anything else I can get you?
My mother.
Although there's something
I gotta tell you.
It's about your sister.
What about her?
- Hello.
- Dad.
I found Mom. Meet me at the lower boatyards
in 30 minutes and come alone.
- Don't tell the Arrow.
- Copy that.
- I gotta go.
- What about Sara, Dad?
Look, I'll explain everything later,
all right? Just sit tight.
I say this with confidence
because the Moira Queen that I know...
is more than a successful CEO
and philanthropist.
She is a loving mother who has devoted
her life to raising two wonderful children.
Just to tell you how special she is,
I'd like to welcome her son...
CEO of Queen Consolidated,
Mr. Oliver Queen.
Ooh. Thank you. Ahem.
I'm here today to say a few words...
about Moira Queen.
I bet many of you think that you know her
because you...
read about her in the press...
or you saw her on TV,
but I can promise you...
you don't know my mother.
You don't know her like I do.
And you don't know what she's capable of...
when it comes to helping the people
of Starling City.
Ladies and gentlemen, my mother,
Moira Queen.
I know.
Thank you.
Thank you, Starling City.
Sara.
The snake venom. It's gone.
- She found Nyssa.
- She's going to poison her?
We need to stop her before she does.
Activate her tracer.
You put a tracer on her?
She has a bad habit
of disappearing on me.
I hate to sound cold,
but why do we care...
if Sara kills some bad-ass assassin
who wants to get her and her family?
Because, Diggle, if half of the stories that
I've heard about Ra's Al Ghul are true...
Sara kills his daughter...
we will all pay.
They're coming for you now.
Dinah. Move away from her. Move away.
It's all right. It's all right.
What's happening?
Sara.
It's me, Mom.
It's me.
My baby.
Oh, my baby.
I love you so much, Mom.
- I have to go.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Dad, get Mom out of here.
What?
No. No!
No!
You took the poison.
No.
No!
I can't go back.
I can't take the killing anymore.
It needs to end.
Sara.
Delta-Charlie 52 to Central, we need backup
at the lower boatyards.
Ambulance, paramedics.
If you want to be with your family so
badly, they can join you in eternity.
You get the hell away from my daughter.
Live or die.
It's up to you.
Nyssa. I can still save her.
Worry more about saving yourself.
Don't kill her. Please.
Sara.
Sara, you hold on.
Stay with me.
Come on, stay.
Not again.
No more killing.
Nyssa.
Please.
In the name of Ra's Al Ghul...
I release you.
Sara. Sweetheart, you okay?
- Are you okay? Oh.
- Yeah, yeah.
I can't believe it. Look at you.
Because Starling City is our city.
And starting today, we're
going to take it back.
I know we need to talk.
You need to listen.
For the past year,
I've stood by your side.
And I've fought...
because I wanted
to believe that you weren't this...
monster.
And I needed to believe
I still had a mother.
You do.
Oliver, I only lied about Thea
to protect her from Malcolm.
No, you lied because that's what you do.
And that is who you are, Mom.
Lies.
And now you've made me a liar out of me.
Because Thea can never find out
about Merlyn.
And she can never know
the truth about us.
Which is that as of right now,
we have no relationship.
I will keep up appearances
for Thea's sake...
publicly I will support your campaign.
But privately...
you and I are done.
Oliver.
Oliver!
I knew you were alive.
I just felt it in my bones.
I never stopped looking for you.
I know you have a lot of questions.
Nope.
How could you not have any questions?
Because I already know
all of the answers to them.
How could you still be alive?
Where have you been all this time?
Why didn't you call us?
And the answer to all of them...
is because it's Sara.
- Baby, don't to this.
- Dad, I swear, if you say one more word...
Laurel, look, I know you're angry.
And you have every right to be.
Please don't take this out on Dad.
If you need someone to blame, you blame me.
I do blame you, Sara.
Every single thing that's gone wrong
in our lives is your fault.
You got on that stupid boat
with my boyfriend.
You didn't call us
to tell us that you were still alive...
even though it would have probably
saved Mom and Dad's marriage.
And you brought some crazy assassin
into Starling City who nearly killed Mom...
and who poisoned me.
You.
You stole my whole life
away from me.
- Now, get out.
- Laurel.
Get out.
- I'm sorry.
- I said get out!
Now what?
Please, come in.
Tell me Oliver's okay.
Tell me everything's okay.
I wish I could.
Moira, I'm so sorry about Robert.
About Oliver.
I really am.
Is... em...
I need to tell you both something.
What is it?
Robert and Oliver
weren't the only ones lost.
Along with the crew...
a friend invited along
by Oliver at the last minute.
Tommy?
No.
Sara.
Your Sara.
I'm so sorry, Quentin.
The dockmaster saw her
sneak on board.
With Moira Queen's
impressive speech earlier today...
some pundits are suggesting
her candidacy may not be so farfetched.
While Blood's campaign
has yet to issue a public response...
to Mrs. Queen's announcement...
I warned you not to underestimate
Moira Queen.
What do you want me to do?
Thank you. Thank you, Starling City!
Nothing.
I'll take care of it.
You've been crying.
I was happy to know I still could.
Are you okay?
Laurel wasn't as thrilled
to see me as you thought.
Give her time.
I gave her six years.
What exactly are you taking out
on that dummy?
My mother...
She's not who I thought she was.
I guess it's going around.
So, what now?
I don't know.
I don't either.
I know one thing.
What's that?
I'm home.