Bianca!
Bianca Bertinelli?
Who the hell are you?
Your life's in danger.
I'm gonna need you to come with me now.
My night's just
getting started. Bye.
Get off. Get off!
Help!
Seeking his third
straight term, Mayor Ramirez
has declared Star City
the safest city in the country.
In other news, the vigilante
museum has received
a generous seven-figure donation
from Victor
and Maria Bertinelli.
Hey. What are you doing?
Babe! You scared me.
I'm just the guy who you share your bed
with most nights.
Hm? Remember me?
How could I forget?
Your snoring always reminds me.
I don't snore.
Look, I know you
hate to be anything less than perfect,
but you do, like
old man style.
Ha ha. Right.
I got up early to finish writing
my speech.
Wait. Is there something
special happening today?
Funny.
A gift for the graduate.
Wait what's happening?
Mia Queen,
I love you more than anything
in the whole world.
Will you marry me?
Please say yes.
- Yes, of course.
- Yeah?
Of course.
I love you so much.
♪ Sunny... ♪
Excuse me.
I'm looking for the owner.
Over there.
♪ Ohh oh, sunny ♪
♪ You smiled at me ♪
♪ And really
eased the pain ♪
♪ Oh, the dark days are done ♪
♪ Now the bright days are here ♪
♪ My sunny one ♪
♪ Shines so sincere ♪
♪ Ohh oh oh ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
Dinah, this is where
you've been living?
Well, it's right
above the bar,
and it has got
a hell of a view.
Black Canary and the captain of SCPD
now owns a bar.
Also, when'd you
learn to sing?
We didn't have much time
for karaoke back in 2020, did we?
So how did you
find me? Sara?
She said that she found you here
a couple months ago
and that you didn't want
to come back with her.
The day after Oliver's
funeral in 2020,
I woke up here.
I had no idea how or why.
When I got here, I found out that
I don't even exist.
I'm sorry. How is that
even possible?
I don't know, but there is no trace
of Dinah Drake or the Black Canary.
And what,
you're just fine with that?
I guess I came
to realize that
not having an identity
can either be sad
or it can be oddly
freeing.
I can let go of
the people I lost,
mistakes that I made.
I'm not gonna lie,
your zen is kind of creeping me out.
Thank you.
You know, there has been
no real crime in Star City
in 20 years, Laurel.
And zen's not that
hard to come by.
Well, I hate
to break it to you,
but Star City
isn't safe anymore.
Bianca Bertinelli's
been abducted.
Helena's daughter.
The socialite. Why...
why would anybody want to hurt her?
Money, revenge, something
to do with Helena.
Who the hell knows?
D, I need you to help me find her.
You really came all
the way to the future
to rescue a kidnapped
socialite?
- What am I looking at?
- Star City 2041.
This is a year from now.
It's not possible.
The city's safe.
Doesn't stay that way.
Because Bianca Bertinelli
gets kidnapped?
No. Because she dies.
Three days from now,
her body is found in the bay,
her killer never caught.
The city falls apart.
Everything that Oliver
sacrificed his life for.
I thought this part of
my life was done, Laurel.
Then don't do it for you.
Do it for Oliver.
Okay.
For Oliver.
Good.
Now there's one more person we need
who's well-connected.
- And who is that?
- I'll inform you on the way.
You do have something
nicer to wear, right?
♪ Lookin' over you ♪
♪ Is something I do ♪
♪ Finally had to look... ♪
Ms. Queen,
when is the wedding date?
What are you going to do
now that you've graduated?
Not sure yet
on both counts.
What would
your dad think about your life choices?
My father saved Star City
so that we can enjoy it,
and he also never
graduated college,
so I think he'd be
pretty impressed.
- Ms. Queen?
- Ms. Queen...
It was my mom's.
JJ knew I'd want
the family ring.
He's honestly the most
thoughtful guy in the world.
Can I just say what
an amazing man of honor
I'm gonna make
at your wedding?
William!
Zoe, hi!
I hope you don't
mind me crashing.
Never.
So good to see you.
Where's Keven?
No. I thought he
was the one.
Yeah. Well, apparently
only having one partner was his problem.
But it's fine.
This is your day.
And speaking of, tomorrow
there's gonna be an office for you
at Smoak Tech.
How many times do I
have to tell you,
tech is not
really my passion?
What is your
passion exactly?
I don't know.
Because you can't
be a socialite forever.
Hmm, she technically can.
No. No, I'm sorry. She is
way too smart for that.
Okay, can I just enjoy
tonight
before I have to start
adulting?
Fine. But I need a drink.
I just want to thank you
all for coming tonight.
You are my life.
I particularly want to thank JJ
for always having my back.
I love you so much.
And William.
I could not imagine
life without you.
Thank you for always tolerating
your little sister,
even when I did draw all over
your walls when I was five.
- To the class of 2040.
- 2040!
Whoo!
Sorry, is it all right
for me to be here?
I'm sure it's okay.
Hey.
I thought you were
still in rehab, Connor.
What's the matter, trust fund?
You don't want me
at your fancy little party?
As long as you don't
punch anyone or set anything on fire,
we'll be okay.
Can we just try to get along
for one night, please?
- Be right back.
- Okay.
Hey, Trev, have you
seen Bianca?
She was supposed to be
here an hour ago.
No, I'm not
her keeper anymore.
Okay, I thought you
guys were still cool.
No, we are, but even when
we were together,
she never told me
where she was.
But you were the last
to see her, weren't you?
Excuse me?
Your number was
the last one she texted.
Uh, who the hell
are you?
Wait. I-is something wrong
with Bianca?
I don't know. You tell us.
Ah...
You can't just crash my party
and harass my guests.
Do you know who I am?
A lot more than you do.
We were friends
of your parents.
Then how come I've
never seen either of you before?
Long story and less than
zero time to explain.
Your friend Bianca,
she's in trouble.
And we need your help
to find her.
Yeah. I'm calling security.
No, I'm sorry to take
you out of your bubble,
but we really need you.
I know
how to protect myself.
- You made sure of that.
- I sure did.
The four of you are
the heroes that the city needs.
We are staring
at our father alive!
Dad. So what's next?
Mar Novu has
seen my fate.
- Dad...
- I don't survive Crisis.
Mia.
- Back off.
- Um, I'm sorry. You fainted.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Sorry. Uh, sorry. I... I guess
I had too much to drink
without eating or something.
Maybe you should lie down,
party animal.
I think I need some air.
- Hey, Mia, listen...
- Ooh. No.
What the hell did
you do to me?
I would love to know that
myself.
There's this guy,
J'onn J'onzz.
He's a Martian or something.
He's why we remember everything
that happened before the Crisis.
Cisco was able to replicate
the Martian's powers
using tech.
So a friend of
Supergirl's has a power
a friend of the Flash
can replicate.
Yeah.
That's what I said.
I want to say that
you guys are crazy
and that none of this
is possible,
but I know you're right.
I remember everything,
you two fighting
alongside my dad,
Zoe dying, my...
my fiancé killing her.
I remember
my father dying.
Why would you do
this to me?
Look, there'll be time
for emotions later.
I woke you up because
your friend Bianca was kidnapped.
But there hasn't been any
crime in Star City in 20 years.
What is that, like
the city's motto now?
You don't know Bianca,
all right?
She's flaky. She's probably on a beach
somewhere having a ball.
I saw her, and she
was taken.
How are you even
hesitating?
Aren't you supposed
to be the Green Arrow?
Not anymore.
Mia, I understand
that you are torn
between two worlds
right now,
but we need your help.
Look, I don't even know
if I can do this anymore, okay?
I haven't trained. I don't...
See?
Just like riding a bike.
Is Bianca actually
in trouble?
Yes. And if we don't
find her, she's going to die.
Fine. I will help you.
But this is
a one-time thing.
Okay, I'm not interested
in joining
your Canary club, all right?
I have a life now,
I am happy,
and I would like to
keep it that way.
Whatever.
Where was Bianca
when she was taken?
Partying at Club V.
Nothing Bianca loved more
than a good party.
Oh, to be in my
20s again.
Ick. Hard pass.
I was married at 21.
Seriously?
Who are you?
Bianca.
She was adopted.
Any chance that
created tension?
Helena was a great mom
before she disappeared.
She lives with her
great-aunt and uncle now.
Back in the old Star City,
the Bertinellis were
one of the biggest
crime families around.
Well, that sounds
like enough reason
to violate some
privacy laws.
It's time for you
to pay that family
a little visit.
I'm sorry Bianca missed your party.
You know how she is.
Free spirit.
Totally. Actually,
I wanted to speak
with you about that.
I think Bianca might be
in some kind of trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Mia's in position.
D, you're up.
- You ready?
- Never not.
I think Bianca might
have been taken.
That's ridiculous.
You know how safe it is here.
I haven't been able
to contact her in days.
Her social media is quiet, it's...
she's not even
posting those videos
she's always
addicted to making.
I wouldn't worry
about it.
In a couple days,
we're gonna find out
she's been, uh,
what partying
off the coast of
Corto Maltese or something.
Dinah, what's your progress?
Three more rooms to go.
You're about to have company,
one of the help,
I'm guessing.
Mia, we need a distraction.
Wouldn't it be better
to be safe than sorry?
I mean, maybe since
we're here,
if we call the police...
oh, my God! I'm so sorry.
Logan, get Remy!
Remy?
Remy, we've got
an emergency.
Do us a favor.
Stop worrying about Bianca.
She's fine.
Okay, I will.
I'm clear.
Please tell me
you got those eyes and ears placed.
All of them.
We can see and hear everything
that goes down in that house.
Good. I'll meet you
at the bar.
I want to talk to Bianca's
friends, see what they know.
- You want company?
- Ha.
And have to explain who you two
are again? No, thanks.
You know, I could get used to all
this free alcohol.
So that means you will not be paying
your tab downstairs.
I thought it was a friends drink for
free kind of place.
They say anything
interesting yet?
A couple stock tips,
where to vacation,
nothing that helps.
Oh, man. This is
one hell of a view.
I can see why you
hide out here.
Subtle. I am not hiding.
I told you, the world
doesn't remember who I am.
Don't you
remember you?
I really don't expect
you to understand.
Try me.
I mean, isn't this
what friends do?
They sit around and drink,
talk about their problems.
Okay, well, when I first
ended up here,
I spent a lot of time
asking myself why.
It took a while, but I think
I finally understand the answer.
This is the universe's
way of telling me
I'm not supposed
to be a hero.
Why? Because you didn't
get a gold star?
Because in this version of the future,
the one where I'm not a hero,
everyone is
better off.
Mia's happ...
Mia was happy
until we dragged
her into this.
Zoe's alive because
she's not a Canary.
And all of a sudden,
what, you're gun shy?
Zoe didn't die because
she was a Canary.
She died because she was
a hero, because you
inspired her and a bunch of
other women just like her
to fight for something
greater than themselves,
myself included.
What, are you guys
on a break or something?
It's called surveillance.
How did it go
with Bianca's friends?
Let me guess.
"Oh, Bianca was just being Bianca.
And, oh, my gosh, what
shoes am I gonna wear?"
They didn't know anything.
And, by the way,
three of them went to Harvard.
That's awesome.
Oh.
Logan Bertinelli
just got chatty. Hang on.
He's worried about something,
"taking precautions,"
specifically moving "it"
out of the city.
What are the odds
"it" is Bianca?
Logan's an ass, but he
wouldn't kidnap his cousin.
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Let's suit up.
You earned it.
I'm not wearing that.
- Why? It's yours.
- It's my father's.
She doesn't have to wear it
if she doesn't want to, Laurel.
Fine.
♪ I know you think it's all for fun ♪
♪ I'll be the one to run, run, run ♪
♪ I don't need love,
I got my gun ♪
♪ Don't need love ♪
♪ I've got my gun ♪
♪ I don't need love ♪
♪ Ha ha, I don't need love ♪
♪ I've got my ♪
W-what the hell are you
guys waiting for?
Secure our friggin' position.
You go get Bianca, and
we'll take care of Logan and his friends.
- What?
- You'll be fine.
♪ I don't need love, I've got my gun ♪
♪ Ha ha, I don't need love ♪
♪ I've got my ♪
Bianca's not here.
Looks like some kind of
chemical or drug.
I... I give up, okay?
Run!
Well, that could've gone
better.
You've got some nerve
leaving me alone out there.
What if I hadn't remembered
how to fight?
But you did.
You're welcome.
I could've died.
Okay, that's a little dramatic.
We were there the whole time.
D, some help, please?
It was pretty
risky, Laurel.
How about less talking
about your hurt feelings
and more talking about
the fact that your fiancé
just became
suspect number one?
There is no way
this is JJ.
The guy who attacked us
in the Deathstroke mask?
You do know who
Deathstroke is, right?
It could've been anyone
under that mask.
It does seem like
a pretty big coincidence,
especially given who JJ
was before.
I mean, he used to lead them.
Yeah, and I used to be
a cage fighter.
That is not who I am
anymore,
and that is clearly
not who JJ is.
Are you really that naive?
Are you really
that judgmental?
You don't even have
the slightest bit of doubt
that JJ is the one who is
behind that mask?
No.
Prove it.
Mia Queen.
These are my plus-two.
See? A much better idea
than punching our way in.
- Hm.
- A lot less fun, though.
Mia, you sure
you're up for this?
I'm here, aren't I?
JJ's office is in back.
Dinah, you take
cameras.
Mia, go distract
your fiancé.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. It's
the strangest thing.
I have all these
memories of my old life,
but I have
my new ones, too.
I just really don't
want it to be him.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Oh, yeah. I was
starting to worry.
You left in a hurry
earlier.
Yeah, I wasn't
feeling well.
"Actually, I just remembered
"you were a dangerous
murderer,
probably
a kidnapper, too."
Hey, be nice, Laurel.
- I need a drink.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
There's only
one guard at the door.
This should be easy.
Where are we on cameras?
Almost there.
In the meantime,
why don't we go back to
talking about Mia's love life?
Let's not.
You know I dated
your dad, right?
Well, a version of him anyway.
- Gross.
- Thank you.
My Oliver also went down on the Gambit,
also cheated with my sister.
Please
stop talking.
People are who they are, Mia,
no matter what timeline,
universe, or earth,
and that's not your fault.
Was that supposed to be
some kind of pep talk?
Cameras are down.
That's my cue.
This area
is restricted.
Oh, I'm just gonna
step out and get some air.
Trust me, I am not
an art thief.
Well, you're welcome
to step outside.
Okay, let's not cause
a scene here, Laurel.
- I'll do it.
- Fine.
No offense, Mia,
but if I couldn't
get in there,
do you really think
that you're gonna be able to just...
Oh, you were saying?
I'm in.
Now what do I need to do?
Just put the device
anywhere near the computer.
It'll transfer the data
from your search.
It's working.
Run a search for
the Bertinellis.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Uh, something's wrong.
Mia, you need to get
out of there now.
Hey, step away
from the computer.
Mia, what are you
doing in here?
Where is she?
I'll take it
from here.
What is going on
with you?
You break into
my office,
and you hack
my computer?
I know you have Bianca.
That's what this
is about?
You think that I
kidnapped her?
Do you know how
crazy that sounds?
You're calling me
crazy now. Wow.
Because you are
being crazy.
Okay, if you have
nothing to hide,
then show me what's
in these files.
Our honeymoon.
You said that you always
wanted to visit Fiji.
I was hoping I
could surprise you.
Namaste.
Can I call you
crazy now?
- Bianca? What the hell?
- Namaste.
I have to get
back to the party.
Okay. Let me explain.
J...
Bianca looks pretty
happy to be kidnapped, don't you think?
Turn off your
socialite brain and use your gut.
Don't you think that video's
a little convenient?
I think whoever
posted that is trying
to keep people from
looking for Bianca.
We should analyze it,
you know,
see what clues we can
get in finding her.
Okay, I just accused my
fiancé for nothing.
Oh, he'll get over it.
Or you'll move on to someone who wasn't
a homicidal maniac in another life.
Win-win.
Oh, frak you.
Okay, that's enough.
I think we just need to calm down...
No. I am not the one
who cares more
about my relationship
problems
than my friend
who might die.
Do you not see how
selfish you're being?
Me? You're the one
who's using my friend
to drag me and Dinah back
into this superhero crap
just because you can't handle
the fact that Star City's fine
and doesn't need you to
be the Black Canary anymore.
And here I thought making
you remember your old life
would open your eyes to how
pointless and stupid
your new one is.
My "stupid and pointless"
life is the one that
my father sacrificed
himself to give me.
Don't you dare
trivialize that.
Okay, I think
all Laurel was trying to say
is that Bianca is out there,
and she's in danger.
Bianca is fine.
You had no right
to make me remember.
All that did is bring back
the suffering and the loss,
because that's
all being a hero is.
I would've met you at
your place.
I needed the drive.
I hope that I didn't screw up
your event too badly.
I wish it was just
the event that you'd screwed up.
JJ, I'm sorry.
You accused me of
kidnapping our friend.
How in the world do you think
I could do something like that?
You were keeping
things from me.
I guess I just jumped
to conclusions.
Jumping to conclusions is...
is I'm cheating on you,
not that I'm a kidnapper.
And for the record,
I'm neither.
I know that.
Can we please just go
back to a time
before I accused you
of being a criminal?
I get it now.
This never had anything
to do with Bianca.
What are you talking
about?
You have never really
had to commit to anything in your life.
That's why you brush off
your brother's job offers.
And it's why you hesitated
saying yes to our proposal.
It's why you're pushing me
away right now.
You don't want to
marry me.
That is not true.
Then how come ever since
the party...
ever since I proposed
to you, i-it's like
you're seeing someone else
when you're looking at me?
When I look at you,
I see the rest of my life.
I can't marry someone
who doesn't feel the same.
- John, please.
- No. I... no.
I think it's best
we take some space.
We're running
out of time.
Please tell me you're close to finding
something on that video.
Our hunch was right.
There's evidence
the image was altered.
I'm running a decryption program,
but it's gonna take a bit.
Since when did you learn to do all
this Felicity stuff?
I was a police captain,
Laurel. I have tricks.
Like knowing when someone's
not telling me everything,
for example.
Like you.
What?
You've been pushing Mia
real hard, which is weird,
because normally, you keep a fairly
healthy snark-filled distance
from caring too much
about anything.
This is personal.
Look, I wasted
a lot of time
pretending to
be something I wasn't
because it was easier, and
I don't want Mia making the same mistake.
You...
You know, part of empathy isn't only
understanding other people's pain.
It's also sharing your own.
You know how hard it is to be a hero.
I mean, hell, I'm struggling
with it right now.
Imagine what she's
going through.
The last time Mia put on
that Green Arrow suit
was the day Oliver died.
The program's finished.
Oh, boy.
Whoever did this
wanted people to think
she was safe on vacation.
They didn't know they were
giving us a lead.
Well, thank God for morons.
I gotta figure
out where this is.
But for the record,
I think you're right.
If there is evil back
in Star City,
the Green Arrow
should be here, too.
Oh, God. Are you crying?
What the hell
are you doing here?
I guess it's that
feelings thing or whatever.
Look, I'm sorry.
JJ broke up with me,
if you even care.
I do care.
You're strong
enough to get through this.
You're strong enough to
get through anything. I've seen you do it.
Is that why you
woke me up?
Mia, I spent so much of my life
choosing the easy path.
And for me, that meant
becoming Black Siren
and destroying things
and...
killing people.
It's not a good look.
Not exactly
what I'm doing here.
Okay, but can you honestly
tell me that you were happy with your life
before I woke you up? Truly?
I spent my whole life
looking at these
pictures of my dad,
all of the amazing
things he did for the city,
what a hero he was,
wondering how I could
possibly live up to that
you know, in... in anything
I chose to do.
And...
and so I chose to do
nothing.
He would probably be
so disappointed in me.
I doubt that.
Your father, he wanted
you to be happy.
And he... he gave you
all this,
but I also think he wanted
you to have a choice.
I am not gonna
sugarcoat it for you.
Being a hero kind of sucks.
And it never gets
any easier
because it is the hardest thing
that you can do.
Then why do it?
For me, it gave me a purpose.
And that's why I woke you up,
so that you could have
the chance to realize your own.
Mia, this is your city,
and you're the Green Arrow.
Hey. How'd it go?
Ask her.
I'm glad you
decided to join.
Bianca's my friend. Any
luck finding her location?
Not yet. But she's in
a greenhouse of some sort.
Only problem is there
are hundreds in the city.
It's gonna take time.
That's not
a greenhouse.
The design's biophilic.
It's meant to power the
building photosynthetically.
What are you,
a botanist now?
I took a couple classes
in design theory
and sustainable concepts.
Socialites can have
brains, too.
Great.
Well, use your fancy brain
and narrow it
down for us?
Uh, there's about 12 buildings
in the city that fit the bill.
But only one of them
is currently unoccupied...
a complex downtown.
Let's go save my friend.
You sure you're
ready for this?
One way to find out.
Thermal imaging
places Bianca on the top floor.
There's 2 bodies beside her.
I'm guessing they're guards.
How much more company
can we expect?
It depends on how
fast we move.
That's comforting.
Oh, and another
piece of good news.
The whole place
is laced with meta-dampeners.
- So no Canary Cries.
- Perfect. Ready?
I so wish I got that
on my live stories.
We have to go now.
Why leave now, huh?
The fun is just
getting started.
Trevor.
You know my name.
I'm flattered.
Cool masks.
Yeah, very, uh, 2020.
Actually, I... I have...
I have one of my own.
So this is what you've been spending
Daddy's money on?
You know,
Bianca never told me that she had
such, uh,
colorful friends.
Oh, I get it.
She broke up with you,
and now your feelings are hurt.
- Aw.
Is that why
you're doing this?
Oh, don't flatter
yourself.
You're a pawn
with a fancy
family name.
That's the only reason
you're important.
Yeah, I see why
you dumped him.
- Enough talking.
- Great.
So I guess that means
you're waving the white flag.
The three of you
against all of us.
- I'll take those odds.
- So will we.
♪ Tick, boom ♪
♪ Mi nah really
care weh mi bump into ♪
♪ Bulldozer, make room ♪
♪ Write that pon fi mi tomb ♪
♪ Televise this dress ♪
♪ It's an Alaïa,
show some respect ♪
♪ Sitting, no armrest ♪
♪ Get in, I'm what's next ♪
♪ Incoming text
from the vets ♪
♪ No hate here, I'm blessed ♪
♪ Mild-mannered, no stress ♪
♪ I never let a broke
ho get shi vexed ♪
♪ Too wake to walk
with the rest ♪
♪ Abstract, fearless ♪
♪ Mi say what's pon my chest ♪
♪ Di gyal dem try,
but dem dare not test ♪
♪ Tick, boom, mi nah really
care weh mi bump into ♪
- There's too many of them.
- We have to get out of here.
Stay close.
♪ Bulldozer, make room ♪
♪ Write that pon fi mi tomb ♪
♪ Tick, boom ♪
♪ Bulldozer, make room ♪
♪ Write that pon fi mi tomb ♪
Now what?
We're too high.
How are you
still alive?
Death by tantrum?
You're gonna have to do better than that.
Don't come any closer.
You see, all the, uh,
greenery in this building is linked
to the same system...
all state-of-the-art
and all very, very...
explosive.
If he drops that lighter,
this whole place is gonna go up.
Trevor, don't do this.
You can't stop
what's coming.
She won't let you.
And who the hell is she?
We have to jump.
I thought you were
trying to save me, not kill me.
Trust me.
Welcome back.
Oh, my God.
Who are you bitches?
Any word
on how Bianca's doing?
She is back to her old self,
posting live videos.
So I'm not very good at
this, uh, feelings stuff.
I wanted to thank you,
both of you.
And now you can go back
to your glamorous life
of singing to drunk
hipsters in your bar.
Oh, thank you for that.
But, uh, actually, I was
thinking of going part-time.
You know, Trevor's not just
a jealous ex-lover trying to get even.
Somebody pushed him
to do this,
and we still haven't
figured out who or why.
Trevor's tattoo
looked familiar.
We start there.
We?
Star City needs
the Green Arrow.
But what about JJ,
and what about your life?
I'm not giving that up,
but I'm also gonna protect
my father's legacy.
Mia, living a double life
is really hard.
Well, somebody once
told me that
being a hero is
the hardest thing you can do.
It's also
the right thing.
Well, that person
sounds really smart.
I mean, she has
her moments.
But putting on
that suit again wasn't easy.
But it reminded me
that it's not all bad.
There are some really,
really good parts, too.
Well, uh, before we get
back to saving the world,
I say we should have
a celebratory drink.
And after what we did
tonight,
I say we deserve
the good stuff.
Cheers. To the Green Arrow.
To the Canaries.
To the future,
whatever it holds.
Well, I'm glad you didn't
change the locks on me yet.
Mia...
Look, before you kick me out,
just please let me say I'm sorry.
You were right. I... I have been acting
weird since the graduation party.
- So then I did spook you.
- No.
This has nothing to do
with you proposing.
Look, graduating
got into my head.
I'm trying to figure out what I want to do
with the rest of my life,
what kind of person
I want to be. I...
I want to help you with that.
And that is why I
love you so much.
You're a good
person, JJ.
I couldn't imagine spending my life
with anyone else.
You know, it's been a while
since I had a roommate.
I'll get my own place,
I promise.
Your own place?
That sounds pretty permanent.
The city's under threat,
and I'm not gonna leave until it's over.
You know, while you're here,
we could turn this place
into a base of operations
for the Canaries.
Canaries, as in more
than just us?
Tonight made me remember
who I really am, Laurel.
I may have been erased,
but I'm not gone.
I need to figure out
how I got here.
And while I do that, I can help a whole
new generation of women.
So basically,
what you're saying is
that I was right.
Don't gloat.
But please do explain why
you didn't tell me
the whole story about what Bianca's death
would have meant for the city.
Sara said
when the city falls...
someone's at
the center of it... Mia.
But Bianca was dead
in the future,
and Mia wasn't
the Green Arrow.
We should be
in the clear, right?
I hope so.
I can't believe it's
been 20 years
since he sacrificed
himself to save the city.
Who's that?
Oh, just the Star,
the Globe, the Gazette,
Byline, channel 52.
They all want to know
if I'm the Green Arrow.
Course they do.
Isn't it a little
misogynistic
that they're not calling
you as well?
I mean, come on, guys.
It's 2040.
Oh, my God.
You brought the pet rock.
Excuse me.
Are you referring to the Hozen?
This is the closest thing
we have to a family heirloom,
passed down from Dad
to Aunt Thea to Mom and to me.
Show some respect,
please.
May I see it?
- Yes, you may.
- Thank you.
What the hell?
Oh.
William!
Hey, babe. I didn't think
you'd be back so soon.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I need you to remember.
I have vision.
We can fix this...
together.
JJ!
You were wrong
about me.
It was never a mask.
Greg, move your head!