Previously on "Arrow"...
- I need your help, Roy.
- You really think
an energy weapon's
gonna stop this Monitor guy?
We got the plutonium
with an assist from Roy.
You're working
with the Monitor.
Mar Novu is trying to save worlds,
not destroy them.
I didn't want to
believe it.
The only way to win
is to accept the inevitable.
Where the hell are we?
We're on Lian Yu.
The name of the island
they found me on is Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin
for "purgatory."
Now I understand why.
The memories, the pain,
I've never escaped them.
They're always with me,
a reminder of what I had
to endure
with only one thought,
one goal...
survive.
To save the multiverse,
I must become something else.
To do that, I have to return
to where my journey began...
purgatory.
So this is the famous
Lian Yu.
I did not
want a return ticket to this place.
The three of you were supposed
to be safe and sound in Star City.
How'd you get here?
A bunch of guys
in tac gear came
and stormed the bunker.
A.R.G.U.S. agents.
Sounds just as fun
as tranq darts.
I'm sorry about that.
I needed you here,
and I didn't have time
to convince you.
What the hell's
going on, Lyla?
Mar Novu needs us
to build a weapon,
and it has to be done
on this island.
I'm not doing
anything for that guy.
No, we have to.
Since when do
we take orders from the enemy?
We were wrong
about Novu, John.
He's not our enemy.
Since when?
He dropped me in an alternate reality
in order to teach me the lesson that
to fix the multiverse
we need to work
with him.
This is crazy.
I know it's hard
to hear, Johnny,
but it's the truth.
John...
Um...
how do we build
the weapon?
The materials we need
are already here
in the crates outside.
Dr. Wong has been
experimenting
with the dwarf star particles
since leaving Hong Kong.
He's designed schematics
for the build.
Schematics?
Why does that make me think
that this Dr. Wong guy
won't actually build this thing?
We're counting on you
for that.
- Say again?
- The device is powered
by plutonium.
Dinah, Roy, and Rene
are on their way here
with samples
from Star City.
So my mission
was part of this?
All of our missions
are a part of this.
With all due respect,
what am I doing
back on Lian Yu?
In the past few days,
the island has seen
a rash
of energy spikes.
Is that your reason
for it being green?
Because the last time
that I was here,
Adrian Chase blew it up.
Yes. Harnessing
that energy is the key,
and we need to do it
right away because
we have no idea how long
the energy spikes will last.
Okay. Wait. So we build this
magic weapon for the space god
and we stop Crisis?
There is no stopping Crisis.
Well, then what's
the weapon for?
I don't know,
but Novu said this
is how we survive it,
and I believe him.
If we can't stop Crisis...
Sorry.
What is he
talking about?
Oh, my God.
Would the group mind
if I had a moment with my kids?
Of course.
There's no easy way
to say this.
Mar Novu has seen my fate.
I don't survive Crisis.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that he told me
what would happen to me
the day that he walked in
and asked for my help.
And when exactly
were you planning on telling us?
I've been fighting my fate
because of the two of you,
and I can't fight it,
I can't change it.
So you're just giving up?
I am attempting to
save the multiverse,
and I'm trying to keep
the two of you safe.
We gotta build the weapon,
and finish this mission,
and that's the way
that it has to be.
Well, then I guess
we better get to it.
Lyla, what happened to
no more secrets between us?
I'm sorry I couldn't
tell you.
So you thought tranqing me
and bringing me here
of all places was somehow
a better explanation?
Mar Novu made it clear
that silence was
a requirement
of the mission.
We couldn't risk interfering
with the journeys
of the other players.
As in Oliver's journey
ending in a death sentence?
What did Novu ask you
to do, Lyla?
He didn't give me
details.
He just told me that
when the time comes
I would know
what to do.
You're just fine
with that? Why?
Faith.
You remember that IED
that took out my unit in Afghanistan?
I remember that.
Of course I do.
You were
the only survivor.
Took you years to stop
having nightmares about that blast.
Mar Novu when he
first came to me,
he told me he
rescued me that day
because I have
a greater purpose.
- And you believed him?
- A grown man in costume
prophesizing
the apocalypse?
I thought it was
a joke,
but then he came
to me again,
and he showed me... us,
our future
just wiped away,
gone as if it never existed.
So you made a deal
with him?
We would work together
to find heroes
strong enough
to face this Crisis.
He told me it was the only way
I could protect our family.
Lyla, you may have accepted that this
was the only way to move forward,
but I have not.
I won't.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised
the Black Canary knows how to fly.
Flying's easy.
Landing's the hard part.
Kidding.
There it is...
purgatory.
Looks a little less
bombed out than I remember.
Wow. After everything
I've heard about this place,
I didn't imagine
it to be so...
Terrifying?
Beautiful.
Makes sense you'd think so
since apparently
you're moving here.
Maybe not.
This time around,
you are part of a team.
Island team,
do you copy?
We are five miles south
and inbound for landing. Over.
We copy. Island team
will meet you
at the airstrip
to unload. Over.
No wind to speak of.
Looks like we're in
for a relatively
smooth landing.
Hang on. Hang on.
What the hell is that?
Something's wrong.
Hey. Is everything
all right up there?
We're picking up...
something's incoming.
Did she say, "incoming"?
Dinah, are you there?
Can you read me?
Oh, my God.
Brace for
emergency landing.
Hold on!
They're not gonna
make it.
- We need to find the crash site.
- I'm working as fast as I can.
I can't get in contact
with Roy, Rene, or Dinah.
Something keeps
blocking my signal.
Not something, someone.
Whoever shot down that plane.
You should have
told us we weren't alone.
I thought we were.
I had A.R.G.U.S. sweep
the entire island.
Okay. I just
got the coordinates,
but the plutonium landed
in a different spot.
There's a tracker
in the case,
but it's nowhere
near Rene, Dinah, or Roy.
The people
are the priority.
Well, obviously, but we still need
the plutonium to build the weapon.
All right.
John, let's split up.
I'll run point
on the rescue.
Connor, you're with me.
I'm coming, too.
I called them here.
This is on me.
Whatever
the three of you do, just be careful.
We don't know who these people are
or what they want.
Copy that.
And I guess that
means, what, the three of us,
we are on
nuclear weapon duty?
I'm staying here.
Are you okay
with that?
Someone needs to
protect William.
Gee. Thanks.
It's fair.
Thank you.
William synced this map
to the plutonium's location.
Gonna get us
close to the case,
but the coordinates
won't be exact,
so we're gonna have to
sweep the area.
Well, the sooner
we find it, the better
because I am not
a fan of this island.
Yeah? Well, it has
that effect on people.
You know, I, uh...
I never expected
to be on a mission
with you like this, you know.
I'm glad you're here.
No offense, but shouldn't
this Kodak moment
be with you
and someone else?
- What?
- You and Mia.
Oh. Trying to
give her a little space.
Sure you're not trying
to avoid a difficult conversation?
I'm pretty sure she doesn't
want to talk to me, Laurel.
Oliver, don't be
an idiot, okay?
All that girl wants
to do is live up to her father.
Fine. All this father
wants is to complete this mission
so that my kids actually have
a world to live in.
- We are almost there. Come on.
- Oliver.
Piece of advice.
Don't leave this island
with more regrets
than you already have
buried here.
Oh. Building this weapon with
2019 tech may actually kill me.
I miss the future.
What's this?
Those are very volatile
dwarf star particles
that could level
an entire city or island.
All right. What can I do
to help, huh?
Well, do you know how to calculate
the volume of a sphere?
4/3 pi times
radius cubed.
I was raised
by Felicity, too, remember?
Right. Well, do you know what
the Pauli exclusion principle
of quantum physics is?
Didn't pay
that much attention.
Well, then that pretty much
takes you out of the running
of helping me
in any meaningful way.
Damn. I'm gonna need
a wire stripper.
These are the most
complicated coding
and design sequences
I have ever seen,
and I'm including 2040
when I say, "ever."
It's not like you
to hide out in the bunker
and miss out
on all the action.
Still mad at Dad?
It's his life.
He can do whatever
he wants with it, right?
Always has.
You're being a bit
harsh, don't you think?
And you are being a bit chill,
don't you think?
I was right all along.
Yeah. He has always
been a hero first
and a dad second.
We never should have
trusted him.
- Mia.
- I'm getting your wire stripper.
I'm sorry our
first meeting had to be this.
I envisioned getting to know
my future son over a meal,
not en route
to a plane crash.
This... this feels about
right for our family.
Most of our milestones
got interrupted
by some sort of international
emergency or another.
Yeah. I guess your dad and I
weren't really there
for you and JJ.
You were there
when it counted.
Besides, I was
beyond proud to be the son
of the two superspies
that co-founded Knightwatch.
You never mentioned that.
I think maybe
I wasn't supposed to.
Time travel rules
and all.
Have to assume that
the timelines are different now
unless you remember
your mother being in league
with a evil deity.
Mar Novu is not evil.
Our friends' plane got
shot out of the sky, Lyla.
How do you know that
wasn't part of his cosmic plan?
And don't say faith.
Because I'm fresh out.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey.
You guys okay?
I think so.
We have no idea
where Roy is.
Okay. You are
definitely not okay.
We cannot let this
get infected.
You guys keep searching.
I'll take Rene back
- and get him fixed up.
- Okay. Go, go, go.
- We need to find Roy.
- Where? Where?
This way.
Laurel, I found it!
Laurel!
- Let her go.
- I'm afraid he can't do that.
Hello, Oliver.
Fyers.
- You're dead.
- What?
Seems I've been given
a new lease on life,
though this time I'll
be sure to finish the job.
Drop your weapon.
Drop... your weapon!
Friends of yours?
Edward Fyers
and Billy Wintergreen.
They were on the island
when I first got here,
and they're both dead.
So now we're fighting ghosts?
How is that even possible?
- Get this to William.
- Where are you going?
I have to go
after Fyers.
Or you come with me,
and we finish
this weapon
and get the hell
off this nightmare island.
Fyers is my mess.
He's a mercenary
that I fought and I killed.
He clearly wants revenge,
and ma... makes him
my responsibility.
All right. I'll be
back as soon as I can.
Yao Fei?
- Are you real?
- As real as the men you hunt.
Why'd you try to shoot me?
Like the first time.
To keep you from danger.
No one can keep me from danger,
okay, not even you.
Because you are
fated to die?
There are forces at play
that want you to not succeed.
Fyers and his men know
about the weapon,
and they want to use
it for themselves.
All right. Well, who else
has, um, returned?
Only those who were
with you from the beginning,
but you must not let the evil
that tempted you at the start
distract you
at the end.
He's coming after more than my mission,
Yao Fei, you understand?
I'm not gonna
let that happen.
Last time you tried
to do alone did not end well.
I'm not that person
anymore.
I will hope.
- Roy!
Roy!
There!
I can't...
I can't move!
Roy, we're gonna
get you out of here.
His arm is pinned.
- Can you feel anything?
- No, no.
We got a problem.
Fuel.
- Okay.
- We got to get him out of here
before this
whole thing blows.
Let's get this off
of him, okay?
- Yeah.
- One, two, three, lift!
How bad is it?
Tell me!
Your arm
is crushed.
If you can't feel it,
then that means pretty badly.
If we can't move
what is pinning you,
then we need to start
thinking about other contingencies.
What are we
talking about here?
We don't have
much time.
The best way to get
Roy out
might be amputation.
- What?
- Can you do that?
I have a med kit
in my pack back there.
It'll have what I need.
If we can just move
this off of him, okay,
we have a chance
at saving his arm.
I mean, the odds
aren't very good.
We owe it to him
to keep trying!
So let's move this
thing, all right?
Let's go!
- Dinah.
- I'm gonna check it out.
Yeah. All right. Look.
Let's try to find a lever
to help get this
off of him, okay?
Roy, just hang tight.
We'll be right back.
Oh, good.
You're not dead.
Or maybe I spoke
too soon.
Rene is injured
but okay.
Roy's in a bad spot.
Well, we're all gonna be
there with him
if... if we don't
keep moving.
Sounds like you found the guys
who shot down our plane.
Oliver's old island enemies.
They've been dead
for the last 12 years.
Of course they have.
Where is Oliver?
He went after them,
made me the radioactive
material mule.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3!
It's got to be
caught on something,
- a root system or something.
- All right. Then we dig him out.
- We dig him out.
- We have to hurry.
Guys, we're about
to have company
- and not the good kind.
- We can hold them off!
The fuel's about to spark, John.
We don't have time.
We can trench
it, Dinah!
- Dad, we are out of options!
- We are not out of options!
- I don't accept that!
- We don't have a choice!
We always have
a choice, Connor.
Then I'll make it.
Do it.
Just cut me free.
No. No, Roy.
John, it's better
my arm than our lives.
Get the kit.
Laurel and I will
distract them.
Here. You apply
the tourniquet.
I'll get ready.
Just hold on, okay?
Just hold on.
Okay.
- This will be over fast.
- Am I gonna feel it?
Probably.
I'm with you, Roy.
I'm with you, okay?
You ready?
Do it!
Hyah!
Fyers' camp is just up ahead.
We should not
be back here.
You don't have to
help, Yao Fei.
I help for Shado.
I'm sorry
I couldn't save her.
You know the bond now
between a father and child.
I do. It's exactly why
I have to put Fyers down.
Should be right
up here.
They're gone.
Okay. That doesn't
make any sense.
He should be here.
Fyers knew
you'd come here.
Well, now he's free and clear
to attack my friends and my family.
We need to get
out of here.
How?
Use your bow?
It's pinned.
All right. Well, we will
have to cut our way out.
The net is made
of braided steel.
- That blade won't cut.
- It'll cut.
- Ohh!
- Gotchu, gotchu, easy. Shh.
What the hell happened?
His arm got pinned
underneath the landing gear.
We had to amputate.
I'm sure you did
what you needed to do.
- Roy?
- William.
Not sure it's really
a good time for a meet and greet.
Is Oliver back yet?
We thought
he was with you.
No. He went after
the bad guys on his own.
- Why would you let him do that?
- Seriously?
Okay. We have to
go after him.
No. No. William
has to finish the weapon.
I don't care
about your weapon!
Oliver knows this island
better than anyone, Mia. He'll be fine.
Plus it's smarter
for us to stick together.
No. We are not leaving
him out there.
Mia!
Fine. I'll go on my own!
- This is a bad idea.
- Then don't come with me.
You heard Laurel.
We should stick together.
- It's smarter tactically.
- Are you really gonna lecture me
on tactics right now?
Well... no, but...
Dig is right.
I mean, Dad and this island,
they go way back,
and he knows every
inch of this place.
You going out there
could make things worse.
I'll take my chances.
Get out of my way.
William.
Look. It is okay for you
to be afraid of losing him
especially after the way
that you left things.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
This is exactly what
happened with Felicity.
You were angry with her,
but you still wanted to save her.
I'm not just gonna
sit here and do nothing, okay?
I will not leave him
alone out there. I...
I will not... let him die.
I let myself believe for just...
just a minute that
I could actually have my dad.
Look. When I was a kid,
I spent a lot of time pushing him away
because I never thought
that I could lose him,
and then he disappeared.
Yeah. Now we might
lose him again.
How are you so
calm about this?
I'm not,
but when I was little,
Felicity had me down
in that bunker
watching Dad
out in the field,
and I saw that he could
cheat death more than anyone,
but if this really is the end,
I don't want to waste the time
that I have left with him being angry.
Do you?
I was wrong.
You haven't changed.
Still that impatient
boy I found.
You realize that
insulting me is not gonna
make this go
any faster, right?
Breathe. Remember
in everything, breathe.
I'm trying to cut my way out of a net,
Yao Fei, not shoot an arrow.
We wouldn't be
in this net if you had breathed.
You know what Fyers
is capable of, right?
I need to get back
to my family,
and I'm running
out of time.
You could be
with your family,
but you chose here
instead.
I chose to protect them.
You avoid them
because you're fated to die.
I've been fighting
that fate for a long time.
I've accepted it.
That hasn't made things
any easier.
What am I supposed to say
to my kids?
What I could not
to Shado.
You say good-bye.
I don't think
that I can.
My kids have spent
basically
their entire lives
without me.
And they're about to
have to do it all over again.
You think you
have failed.
The first thing that you
taught me... shengcun, survive.
Well, I can't do
that anymore.
Shengcun is more
than body.
It is spirit,
what lives on,
like I did in Shado,
like she does in you.
That is survive.
How do I do that?
You live now
with your children
with the time
you have left.
I need to get out
of this net first.
Always have patience.
Like I said,
patience.
Just came by to check on you.
How you feeling?
I... I've been better.
I'm so sorry, Roy.
I should have found
another way to get you out.
This wasn't your fault.
Yeah. Well, that's
where you're wrong.
I mean, you wouldn't even
be in this situation
if I hadn't come to
find you in Hub City.
Roy... I can't protect
the people I care about.
You know I worked with you
and Oliver for a really long time,
and if I've learned anything,
it's that this team
has each other's backs
no matter the cost.
Things just didn't exactly
go as planned.
That's an understatement.
No, but I would
rather be here.
I would rather be here
with you
and with the team
than back in Hub City,
living a life all alone.
Heroes make
sacrifices, John,
and for better
or for worse,
this just had to be mine.
John... we got
a problem.
Fyers and his men
have surrounded the camp.
We can expect an attack
any minute.
How long before
the weapon is ready?
I'm done building it.
Once the plutonium finishes
transferring the energy,
I can turn it on.
- How long will that take?
- I'm not sure.
Can we take this
to a safer part of the island
- and finish it there?
- No, no. It has to be here.
I've tapped into the center of
the island's energy.
- We can't move.
- And it has to be tonight.
We don't know when
the next energy spike will be,
and we can't afford to wait.
We need to
buy William more time.
Dad, you're okay.
Yeah. An old friend
steered me back.
I'm sorry that
I took off.
I should have been here
with the two of you.
You're here now.
How are we
supposed to beat an army of ghosts?
Power up the device.
The sphere's absorbing
the energy of the island,
and if that's what brought these dead
people back to life in the first place...
Activating the device
will destroy them.
We're talking
about plutonium here.
That's nasty stuff.
It can take out
this entire island,
us included!
If this is our best chance
of surviving the Crisis,
then we need to
take the risk.
Lyla's right.
She's right.
This is it.
This is our best shot.
Suit up.
You are as foolish
as ever, Queen.
Surrender!
I suppose that means
you're not here to surrender to me.
I'm the one who
killed you, Fyers.
I'm very pleased
to return the favor,
a task you've made
much easier by coming alone.
I'm not alone.
Now that the plutonium
has transferred the energy,
all I have to do is
power it on,
and voila!
It doesn't look on.
- Why isn't it working?
- I have no idea.
It doesn't matter
how many people you have.
The outcome
is the same.
Kill them!
William, we're running
out of time.
Okay. I think
I have something.
There was a double helix
genetic sequence
in Dr. Wong's formula.
I thought it was an error, but now
I think the device can only be powered on
using a specific DNA code.
Oliver. Oliver,
we need you back here
to activate the device.
Oliver,
you got to go!
Yao Fei, if this works...
We will part again,
but the dead are never really gone.
I've got your six.
They're not gonna be
able to hold them off much longer.
- We need to hurry.
- The sphere is touch-activated.
It'll turn on the moment you
pick it up and...
I don't know what
happens after that.
Okay.
Wow. That was anticlimactic.
- What the hell?
- What? What is it?
Dad's DNA doesn't match
the algorithm's specified sequence.
- Does that mean we can't turn it on?
- Sequence match.
You can't...
but she can.
What are you talking about?
The DNA sequence isn't Dad's.
It's yours.
Is it me,
or is this not going well?
We gotta buy
them some time.
God, I hate this island!
Might as well go out
with a bang.
I thought this weapon was
supposed to help us survive Crisis.
That's what Novu
told me.
Does this mean
you're the weapon?
Johnny...
I understand why
you have to do this.
Lyla, are you all right?
I have to go.
Hey, guys.
I just, uh...
I just connected
with A.R.G.U.S.,
and Lyla organized
a rescue boat
before everything
happened.
Should be here
any minute, so...
so we're all
going home.
Did Mom... did she know
what was gonna happen to her?
No. No. She was
just as surprised as the rest of us.
Novu just loves
surprises, doesn't he?
Whatever Mar Novu
has planned for Lyla,
she can handle it.
How much time
do we have
before the Crisis?
Not long.
Should, um, probably
finish packing
before the boat
arrives.
Agreed. No more
island vacations.
Uh, hey, guys.
Listen. I just wanted to...
I wanted to thank
both of you
for just being there for me
no matter what.
Why does this sound
like a good-bye speech?
Pass. Do not accept.
This ain't over
till it's over, Oliver.
All right.
Come on.
Hey.
I don't really know
what to say.
I'm really happy
that you're back with the team, and...
I'm really sorry.
I'll be okay.
Plus Dig's gonna
set me up with
one of those fancy
A.R.G.U.S. doctors, so...
Uh, the boat's
almost ready.
Uh, we good down here?
Yeah. We should go.
Oh. Uh, almost forgot.
This is what led me here
in the future
to you and, uh,
to the team.
Thought you might
like it back.
I don't need it.
Plus I think it should
stay in the family.
You know, when Felicity
gave this to me,
she told me it was
a symbol of reconnection.
- She was right.
- She normally is.
No. You keep it.
William, what you
were able to do,
you're a hero.
Well, I had
a pretty good example.
It means a lot to me
that I've had a chance to...
to see the type of man
you've become.
I hope you'll forgive me
for lots of things
eventually.
Dad, I already have.
I mean, I know for you
I only left a year ago.
For me, it's been
20 years,
and back then
when I was a kid,
I didn't understand
what it meant
to fight for something
bigger than yourself,
but now I do.
I'm really proud of you, Dad.
Not as proud
as I am of you.
- I'm gonna hug you now.
- You better.
Okay.
Thinking about
where Lyla went?
Can't think
about anything else.
I know this is a sacrifice
she has to make
for the multiverse.
I feel like I'm always
asking you favors.
Anything you need,
Oliver, always.
I need those kids
back in 2040
somehow, some way before
whatever's gonna happen happens.
Yeah. I was thinking
about the same thing.
I'll make sure they
get home safe.
One more thing.
When this is over,
track down Felicity and...
just tell her that
I don't want...
Mia and William
kept separated.
I think that they deserve
to grow up with each other.
I'll tell her.
Yeah.
You know, Oliver,
I once told you a long time ago
that uh, a soldier never lets
a brother go into battle alone.
I think that's why it was so hard
for me to accept the idea that...
you weren't gonna
make it out of this.
I felt like I'd be
failing you.
You could never
fail me, John.
I'm gonna stick
by your side
for as long
as I can,
but I know you
have to do this alone.
Every mission
has an end.
I wish this one didn't.
I couldn't have done
any of this,
any of it
without you.
You've always been
my rock.
Don't mean the best man
you've ever known?
I also mean that.
Hey, let's get out of here, man.
Don't want to keep
the boat waiting.
I'll be right behind you.
One more thing
I got to do.
Hey.
Um, William said I might
find you here.
Figured you'd be
the first one on the boat.
You okay?
My whole life I heard nothing
but stories about you.
You know, this legendary
Green Arrow and his team.
I should have been
proud of you
because you were
a hero, and...
all I could see
is that that is
the reason that
you weren't with me,
and it's... it's kind of
hard to let that go.
I never meant to cause
you any pain.
Your mom and me just
wanted to protect you.
I know.
I, uh... I understand
that now.
For a very long time,
I have hated this place.
Just, I'd think about all the people
that it took from me.
It would just... it would just
make me so angry.
But you're not now?
I'm still a little bit angry.
This island taught me
to survive.
It turned me
into someone else,
somebody better than
the person I was before.
So despite my feelings...
there are no stories
about the Green Arrow to tell
if I don't make my way
to Lian Yu,
and I'm also not standing
at this moment
looking at my daughter.
Thank you for letting me
be a part of your story
even if it was only
for a little while.
Mia, something tells me
you're gonna create your own stories.
So what now?
We need to get back home
and just be prepared
for whatever's
coming next.
Okay.
Dad.
- Lyla?
- Not anymore.
I'm now a harbinger
of things to come.
- And that's...
- Yes.
The Crisis has begun.
For so many years,
I've traveled across worlds,
across the multiverse
to do one thing...
kill you,
and now here,
you save my life.
Submit and
begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.
Greg, move your head!