My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal,
to save my city.
Now others have joined
my crusade.
To them, I'm Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else,
I am something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
[Gasping]
Don't waste
your breath.
Your concern should be
for your home
and what has become
of it in your absence.
Together, we are gonna
take over the Glades.
All city servicemen,
especially the police, evacuate.
We won't abandon
an entire district.
If I even see
a hint of a blue,
your city yes men,
they will be buried.
The mayor's gonna cave
and cede control of the Glades.
So it's up to us
to stop Brick.
It's not just Oliver's
mission anymore.
It is ours.
Ahem.
Tatsu: Are you trying
to kill yourself?
I have to get back.
You have to rest.
I suppose you planned
to leave without telling me.
Well, I knew that
you wouldn't approve.
You saved my life.
Thank you.
Maseo saved it.
I merely treated you,
and you are going to
undo all that work
if you try to leave now.
I can't stay here
any longer.
My sister, my city.
Will mourn your
passing I'm sure.
If you are so concerned,
just come with me.
You can make sure that
I drink my penicillin tea.
Like Maseo, I've disappeared
from the world.
I have no desire
to return.
Oh. Tatsu.
Be well, Oliver.
[Wind blowing]
The Glades have been
without police presence
for a week now.
Daniel Brickwell
threatened every member
of local government.
What else was Mayor Castle
supposed to do?
This is worse than
negotiating with terrorists.
This--
[whistling]
Tax time.
Brick wants his cut.
Now give me all the cash
in your register...
or I'll make your head
look like that TV.
I have another idea.
Looks like we got ourselves
a real live superhero here.
You that red streak
I've been hearing about on TV?
Wrong city.
Either way, I bet
Brick will pay us
a finder's fee.
Make the call.
Laurel: Guns down!
Grant must be
some teacher.
Laurel: Diner
at 10th clear.
Diner's taken care of.
Why are these people
calling 911?
Don't they know the police
have pulled out of the Glades?
Because they're
desperate and scared.
Multiple reports of looting
at Western and Oxnard.
Got it.
On our way.
Sara?
Woman: Someone's dying here.
What are we supposed to do?
You can't just ignore--
[ringing and vibrating]
It's Lance.
Good. Maybe
the cavalry's coming.
Captain Lance?
You guys have
been busy.
Just trying to keep
things together.
Doesn't really feel
like it's been working.
- How can I help?
- Can you?
I mean, I thought
the mayor was
pretty specific about Blues staying
out of the Glades.
It doesn't mean
I can't help out
the hood squad
off the books.
We call ourselves
Team Arrow.
Well, actually,
that's just me, but--
I just got everything
we have on Brick
from evidence lockup.
Ok. I'll send Arsenal over once
the next brushfire's put out.
Arsenal? What, are you
guys just pulling names
out of a hat now?
Felicity, you might
want to wrap it up.
We just got two more
calls that came in.
Talk soon, Captain.
Man on radio: Then there
was this red-hooded guy
and a blond woman
all in black.
[Swords clanging]
Change in pattern.
"Disrupt and revise"
just like you said.
Hesitation is death.
I didn't hesitate.
I just--
I just didn't
kill you.
And when the fight
is real?
I'm not a killer.
Then you're gonna die.
The League of Assassins
are called that for a reason.
Mercy is not part
of their code.
I didn't sign up
for any of this,
the assassins league
and no mercy.
All I asked for you
to do was to teach me
how to defend myself,
to never let someone
hurt me again.
And now you face people
who want to kill you.
To prevent that,
you must kill
them first.
It may not be
what you signed up for,
but make no mistake--
it's what you face right now.
Thea, I know it's
difficult.
I wasn't always
a killer.
The first time,
I have never been
more frightened
or remorseful.
Then why did you
do it?
Because the man I killed
murdered my wife.
Hey. That's fine.
Put the prospectus
on my desk.
We'll get into it
tomorrow.
I need to get at least
3 hours' sleep,
so good night.
Young Tommy: No, no, don't!
No, don't!
Tommy.
Hey, Tommy buddy.
Ohh. Come here.
You're just having
a nightmare. Oh!
- Dad?
- Yeah.
I'm here now.
Don't worry.
I won't let anything
bad ever happen to you.
Promise?
Promise.
I will always be
here for you.
Hey. What--ohh!
What--wow!
Heh heh.
Heh heh!
Where's your mom?
I don't know.
Ingrid put me to sleep.
[Doorbell rings]
Is that mommy?
Probably, so you
better go to sleep.
Otherwise, you're gonna
get me in trouble!
Ha ha ha!
Captain Lance.
Harper.
I'm not sure
what you--
Look. I've seen you
wearing a red hoodie,
I've seen you shooting
arrows at people.
You think I don't
recognize you
with a little extra
leather and lace?
Well, I guess I won't
be needing this anymore.
No. You'll be
needing this. Here you go.
What's this?
Everything on Brickwell
we could salvage from evidence storage.
May be something in there to help
you guys figure out
where he's holed up
in the Glades.
Thanks. We'll get
Felicity right on this.
Any word on our
green-hooded friend?
Still unavailable.
And Sara? I mean, I hear
the Canary come up
every so often
on the 911 calls.
I'll let her know
you were looking for her.
No.
You just watch
her back, ok?
Always.
Roy: If I don't suture
this, it's gonna scar, Laurel.
I'll just add it
to my ever-growing collection.
My father give us anything
to use to locate Brick?
I don't see how.
Some of this stuff
goes back decades.
There is plenty of
evidence against Brick,
but there's nothing
the police can make stick.
So this is what Brick has
reduced us to--
grasping for straws.
[Radio chatter]
I don't know how you guys have done
this for so long.
We had Oliver.
John: What are
you doing?
Grasping at straws
I'm pretty sure,
but maybe there's
something in Brick's M.O.
That would suggest
a couple doors for us to kick down.
I mean, for you
to kick down.
[Beep]
What was that?
Cross-reference with
alderman Ford's murder
and the evidence
your father gave us.
The same gun was used
in a 20-year-old shooting.
The same gun?
Either that's
arrogance or stupidity.
In this case,
definitely stupidity.
The victim
from 20 years ago--
Rebecca Merlyn.
Daniel Brickwell killed
Malcolm Merlyn's wife.
♪ Arrow 3x12 ♪
Uprising
Original Air Date on February 4, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[Coughing]
If you want to tell me
"I told you so,"
how about you say it
in person?
Just couldn't stay away
from me, could you?
[Coughs]
What changed
your mind?
I've been
to enough funerals.
So help me.
That isn't what
I have been doing?
The man who Maseo
serves,
when he finds out
that I'm alive,
he is gonna come
for me and my sister.
Ra's al Ghul.
Yes.
Maseo spoke of him
while you were
recuperating.
He fights with swords,
and he's good.
I seem to remember you
being pretty good
with a blade yourself.
Mastery of swords is more
than mastery of technique.
To defeat this man,
you must think like him,
be like him.
You must fight
in the ways he does.
Your only hope
for such a teacher was Maseo.
Only the student
has hope
of defeating
the master.
Sorry I'm late.
What's going on?
Is it the League?
No. This is personal.
Personal how?
I told you I killed the person
who killed my Rebecca.
I recently learned
I didn't.
I killed the wrong man.
The guilty party
is still alive.
Everything I thought
I believed in
for the last 21 years
is false.
My wife's death
remains unavenged.
So let's go
to the police
or Laurel Lance, ok?
She's a friend,
and she'll listen.
I swore that I would
always protect her from harm,
but I couldn't.
For years, I believed
that justice had been done.
The Undertaking
was for her.
I truly believed
I could change the Glades
and prevent what happened
to my family
from happening
to anyone else.
It's all been a lie,
but now I have the chance
to set it right.
I don't understand.
I know because you're
not a killer,
but I am.
Your dad told me
that your mom's an angel now.
I don't want her
to be an angel, Ollie.
I want her to go back
to being my mom.
Ahem.
I'm so very sorry
for your loss.
I have a friend
in the police department.
He says that they have
a person of interest in Rebecca's--
in the case.
They don't have
enough evidence yet
to convict him,
but if it were me,
I'd want to know.
So Brick killed
Malcolm's wife.
What does that have to do
with anything?
Felicity: It is just
another reason for them
to share bunk beds
in hell,
not that I generally
believe in hell,
but for them,
I will make an exception.
John: Maybe we should
get Merlyn to solve
our Brick problem
for us.
That's pretty dark.
Laurel, if you don't think
things are dark,
you haven't been
paying attention.
Even if we did sic
Merlyn on Brick,
which I am not
advocating,
he would have just
as much trouble
finding Brick
as we've had.
Brick's men have
been busy.
They're cutting down
cell towers
and disconnecting
traffic cams
and staying out
of satellite line of sight,
like basically every way I know
how to find somebody.
Roy: Well, if
the cell towers were down,
the how was Brick's
crew communicating?
At the diner, his men,
they were--
They were using walkies.
Do you think that
you could--
I don't know--use
those signals to locate Brick?
You haven't been
down here that much.
If they're communicating
via radio,
they'll be on the FRS,
somewhere between
462 and 467 megahertz.
If I send out
a frequency burst,
I should be able
to triangulate their location.
I did not understand
one word that you just said,
but Oliver was
certainly lucky to have you.
[Beep]
114 Grandview Plaza.
Felicity, that's
the Glades precinct.
Well, it's not like
the police are using it.
Great. We can add irony
to the list of charges against Brick.
Let's gear up.
So why don't you explain
it to me, boys?
We cleared the register
from that diner on 10th.
No. The part where
you had the red one
stood in front
of your shotgun
and somehow he's still
not dead.
Now you know
the deal, boys.
You take me down first,
you walk out alive.
Ok. I've cut
the power.
There's a ventilation shaft
40 feet north
of your current position.
It should drop you off
in the east wing.
There are only
two sentries there now.
Roy: Got it!
If you see anyone,
kill them!
You want to get me?
Roy, are you there?
Laurel, can you
hear me?
This is what we do
when we get you in our sights!
Modulated voice:
Daniel Brickwell.
What the hell are
you supposed to be?
We need to talk.
Somebody please tell me
how this is happening again.
Daniel Brickwell.
It seems we have
a common interest.
You know that Brickwell
killed your wife.
Her name was Rebecca.
Since my death,
maintaining my usual
network of associates
has become--heh--
shall we say, problematic,
but the fact that you
were able to locate Mr. Brickwell
despite the fact that
he has gone to ground
demonstrates
your group's capacity.
You followed us.
We led you right to him.
And I saved your
lives in the bargain.
So why not continue
our association?
You want us
to team up with you?
I guess the question
before you is
whether your scorn
for me outweighs your need
to see Mr. Brickwell
dealt with.
You mean killed.
You have
your options.
Weigh them.
Cheers, guys!
Ha ha ha!
[Sighs]
You stole my idea.
I was gonna lean here
and wish my problems away.
That obvious, huh?
So what are your
problems?
They're not problems
exactly.
More like
weighing options.
What about you?
Brick's tax collectors
giving you trouble?
No. It's Malcolm,
but it's probably
the last thing you
want to think about right now.
You'd be surprised.
He found out who
murdered his wife.
He's fixated
on finding the guy
and killing him.
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but isn't killing people
exactly what
Malcolm Merlyn does?
Yes, but he also
protects people.
During the siege,
he was the only one
who made me
a top priority.
He saved my life.
I didn't know.
Despite everything
Malcolm was or is,
it means something that
he was there
when I needed him
the most.
Even after everything
he's done,
he cares about people.
Even all the terrifying
things he's done
it was because he thought that
he was helping the Glades.
So what's on your mind?
Anything I can
help you with?
Believe it or not,
you already have.
Felicity: How can you even
be arguing for this right now?
Because I am actually
paying attention.
Brick has the Glades
under siege.
He has the police
running scared,
he has us outnumbered
and outgunned,
and I am not saying
let's give Malcolm
a glass case of his own.
All I am saying is
let's use him.
The same way that
he wants to use us.
To point him like
a loaded gun
at Brick.
Exactly.
Well, A, I'm not
ok with that,
and, B, even if I was,
there has to be
a better way to go
about doing it
than to get in bed
with Malcolm Merlyn.
Roy: There isn't.
Oliver is gone,
and there's only so much
the 4 of us can do.
I just found this out,
but the night
of the siege,
Malcolm saved
Thea's life.
He didn't have
an ulterior motive,
he didn't have
an agenda.
He just wanted to protect
what he cared about.
He cares about this city.
He just went about it
in a completely unimaginable way.
So just like Thea
did the night of the siege,
we need him.
I can't think
of a world or a universe
or a plain of existence
where Oliver would agree
to any of this.
Well, Oliver isn't
here anymore,
so we need to stop
pretending like he is.
We need to make decisions
of our own.
I genuinely have
no idea how else
we're supposed
to stop Brick.
And I genuinely don't know
how we live with ourselves
if we go about
doing it this way!
So how does
this work?
Do we vote?
Has the jury
reached a verdict?
It has.
Guilty.
I guess that means
no then.
You were expecting
something different, Merlyn?
That you'd have some
measure of common sense? Yes.
You really thought
we'd throw in with you?
After what you did
to Thea, to Sara,
to Oliver?
To save your
precious city, yes.
Well, that's the thing.
Once we let the ends
justify the means,
that's just
the first step.
Towards what?
Becoming you.
[Music playing]
Excuse me, excuse me.
Um...
I think I'm lost.
I suggest you run
real fast
before I swipe that
nice watch of yours.
Do you enjoy
robbing people?
I mean, it can't be
for the money.
You can't steal enough
wallets and watches to live on.
What the hell is
wrong with you, man?
Wait.
I just want to
understand.
I want to know what
drives a man to do what you do,
to ruin
other men's lives.
Want my watch?
Here. Take it
because you've already taken
everything from me.
You're not gonna
shoot me.
I bet you've never even
held a gun before.
Ohh!
[Coughs]
Go back to your
rich neighborhood.
Is it safe?
Safer than a boat.
Your medicine.
Apply twice a day.
Ok.
Tatsu.
Why don't you
come with me?
So I can watch you die at the hand
of Maseo's master?
I do not intend
to die.
There are many forms
of death.
To defeat a man like
this Ra's al Ghul,
you must be willing
not just to die
but to live knowing
what you had to sacrifice
in order to beat him.
And what will that be?
I don't know.
That is what you will
have to discover,
but it will be whatever
you hold most precious.
Thea: Going out?
How did you get
in here?
I had
a good teacher.
If you've come to tell me
what a horrible person I am,
I'm afraid you'll have to
wait in a very long line.
Actually, I'm here
to do the opposite.
Told Roy about that night at
the train station,
how you saved my life.
You're my daughter.
You protected me,
risked your life for me
just like my mother did.
Thea, I know you want to believe
there's more to me than a killer,
but the fact is,
there's not.
That man died
with his wife.
[Knocking]
What happened
to your face?
Is it all there?
Yeah. 50,000
in hundreds.
You went after
Kendrick Weller.
Hey. What--
what did you do?
You killed him,
and now you're running?
We can--we can
cover this up.
I can't stay here.
I can't pretend to be
something that I'm not.
Your son needs you,
Malcolm.
Not like this.
Killing him did nothing.
It didn't bring her back.
It didn't cleanse
this anger.
I've heard about a place
where anger can be forged
into something else.
Daddy?
Tommy, hey.
What are you doing up?
Look. Go back to sleep.
I miss mommy.
Tommy, I have to go away
for a little while.
You can't leave.
You said you'd always
be there.
I know, but you have
to be strong now.
I'm going somewhere
where I can learn
how to make sure
that no one
will ever hurt us again.
Come here.
Laurel: How'd
Merlyn take it?
I think he just felt
inconvenienced.
We made the right
choice, right,
by refusing
Merlyn's help?
I don't know if we
made the right choice, Laurel,
but we definitely
did the right thing.
Roy: And how many people
are gonna die tonight because of it?
We made
a decision, Roy.
I know, and I know
that I was outvoted,
but that doesn't change the fact
that we're outmanned.
What if it doesn't?
Roy's right.
We need the support
out there,
but Merlyn--he's not
the only person in town.
Who else is there?
The town.
Dispatcher: Emergency services
are currently unavailable.
Hi.
You've been busy.
Ted, I was--
I said you weren't ready.
Guess you weren't
listening,
or are you gonna tell me
that masked blond
that I seen on the news
isn't you?
It's complicated.
I couldn't wait.
I didn't come here
to argue with you.
What did you
come here for?
That a Monte Cristo?
Those will kill you a lot quicker
than being
in this neighborhood.
Abercrombie!
Where the hell
have you been?
I saw Sara
last night.
Why didn't you tell
me she was back?
We need to talk
about that after.
After what?
Felicity: Feels like recess and
we're about to fight the school bully.
Looks quiet.
For now.
You ready?
It's ok to say
you're scared.
Ok. I'm scared.
Is what we're
doing crazy?
I've learned it's
better to ask that question
when I'm not wearing
a mask.
There's never been
an armed occupation in history
that wasn't
overthrown by force.
An all-out assault
on Brick.
That's the only way
to end this.
Then let's end this
one way
or the other.
Let's go.
Ha ha ha!
My two favorite
trick-or-treaters.
Well, look at that.
Didn't anybody tell you
Halloween was 3 months ago?
Daniel Brickwell...
You have failed
this city.
And you seem to have
failed in your maths.
Can't you see there's
a lot more of us
than there is of you?
Sin: Guess again,
Brick-head.
Is this little parade
supposed to mean something?
I'll tell you
what it means.
It means the population
of the Glades
is gonna plummet
severely.
Get them!
[Shouting]
And which costume
are you supposed to be?
Wildcat.
Is that all you got?
I've learned you can
survive a bullet
but not one that's
put through you head.
You're gonna be fine.
Really?
How many more
of you masks are there?
It's ok.
It's good thing you fight
better than you lie.
Oliver?
This is for Rebecca.
What?
You don't even know
her name, do you?
Is this the weapon
you used to murder my wife?
Everybody I dropped
was with that piece.
She was a good person,
decent, kind.
She ran the clinic
right here in the Glades.
Brunette? Ha ha ha!
Yeah. Now I remember.
She was my first,
my initiation
into the Orchid Bay
Butchers.
Heh heh heh.
You murdered her because
you wanted into a gang?
No.
Because she was weak!
Because she was crying,
begging me not to kill her,
but you won't get
that from me,
so come on!
Finish it!
Oliver: Don't do it!
You are too late.
Drop the gun.
No more death.
That's easy for you
to say.
You just returned
from the grave.
Killing him won't
balance the scales.
When you have killed
503 people,
including your own son,
you tend not to worry
about scales,
and don't tell me
it won't stop the pain
and it won't
bring her back
because you don't
understand!
If I had taken care
of him back then,
it could all be different.
The League,
the Undertaking,
Tommy...
Every choice I have made
since my wife died.
Then you make
a different choice now for Thea.
Thea will never
forgive me.
Start giving her
reasons to.
Listen to me.
I'm telling you.
My guys say he's
out of commission.
We can go back in.
[Cell phone vibrates]
I got to call you back.
There's something
I got to go see.
Oliver: I've been gone,
and I'm sorry,
sorry for what the city
has had to endure
in my absence,
but you did endure it,
and the evidence
of that struggle
is lying at my feet.
You did not fail
this city,
and I promise
I will not fail you
by leaving it again.
I want every block
turned upside down,
inside out till each
of Brick's dirtbags
are lying on comfy cots
in Iron Heights, all right?
Hey. Thanks, Captain.
You should see
a doctor.
No health insurance,
but thanks for bringing
the cops back.
Words I never thought
I'd say.
Cindy, right?
Sin. Yeah. I'm friends
with your daughter Sara.
Yeah, yeah. I thought you
looked familiar.
Haven't seen you
in a while.
Well, I haven't seen
Sara in a while.
Well, then you missed some major
ass-kicking tonight.
That woman running around
in black leather tonight,
that wasn't Sara.
Well, sure it was.
Who else would it be?
Well, I don't know.
That's why I'm talking to you.
What do mean?
I've spoken to her.
Well, then you should
know that wasn't your daughter.
[Footsteps]
You ok?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
I just wanted
to see you.
I was worried.
But are you ok?
I am, in fact.
I didn't do it.
For me?
For me
but because of you.
Oliver: Is my room
still available?
Oh! Where have
you been?
I've been so
worried about you.
I was in Bludhaven.
Ran into an old friend
of mine,
things got--ahem--
interesting,
and I actually spent
the past few weeks in jail.
I thought you
grew out of that.
So did I.
- Ollie--
- It's ok.
Good to see you
again, Oliver.
Yeah.
I think I'm hallucinating,
but thank you
for being cool
with this.
I-I'm gonna make
some tea
and try to keep
things zen.
Heh.
Thank you for not making this
difficult for her.
I wasn't always
like this, you know?
Before Rebecca died,
I was a good father.
I remember.
Killing changes you.
It takes away
a piece of your soul,
and you can never
get it back again.
Oliver, I know I wasn't
there for Tommy,
but I see Thea as
my chance for redemption.
You turned my sister
into a killer,
and then you put her
in the crosshairs
of one of the most
dangerous men on the planet.
You won't believe me,
but I did so
with a heavy heart
and expecting a different outcome.
Ra's is going to
come for me,
and he will learn
the truth about Sara eventually.
And then he will
come for Thea and me.
That's why I have to
kill him.
You couldn't before.
This time, I will have
you to train me.
Only the student
has hope of defeating the master.
[Grunting]
I am Nyssa,
heir to the demon.
I'm not here
to fight you.
There's no other
reason to be here.
Why shouldn't I
kill you.
Al Sa-Her.
What does that mean?
The Magician.
Sorry that I didn't
come by sooner.
I just wanted to
check in on Thea.
It's ok.
I'm ok.
Merlyn told us
you were killed.
I was close.
I'm sorry that I didn't
reach out sooner.
I wasn't exactly
in a...cell service area.
You kept
the city together...
saved the Glades.
Well done.
It's gift
from Malcolm Merlyn.
He went looking
for you.
It's Ra's al Ghul's,
right?
Yep.
So what are we
gonna do about him?
I mean, if he finds
out about Thea--
Merlyn and I are
working on that.
Sorry?
For a second there,
it sounded like you said, "Merlyn."
I need to know how
to defeat Ra's.
Merlyn has
the knowledge.
Merlyn is a monster.
You're in this situation,
Thea is in this situation
because of him.
- Felicity--
- No. Just a few hours ago,
I stood right here,
and I swore
that there was no way
that you would ever agree
to work with
Malcolm Merlyn, not ever.
I guess I was wrong
about everything.
I need some air.
I'm glad you're
not dead.
Felicity.
"I need some air"
really means
"I don't want to talk
right now."
I'm sorry.
For what?
Maybe you could be
a little more specific.
For letting us believe
you were dead
for weeks
or for abandoning
every principle you claim to have
by getting into bed
with Malcolm Merlyn.
Uh-uh.
That's not why
you're upset.
While you were gone
for almost a month,
I allowed myself
to fantasize,
to dream that maybe,
just maybe
Merlyn was wrong,
that you were alive
and that you would
come back
and that when you did
you would be different,
that almost dying
would give you
a new perspective
on life,
that you would just
do things differently.
Things between us,
you mean.
Before you left,
the last thing
you said to me...
was that you loved me.
Now you're back,
and the first thing
you tell me
is that you are working
with the man
who turned your sister,
a woman you're supposed to love,
into a killer,
who killed a woman
you used to love.
I don't want to be
a woman that you love.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man