Oliver: My name
is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I'm Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am...something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
If you want to go out
there, I can't stop you.
But I don't have
to help you.
[Grunts]
Who the hell are you?
I'm the justice
you can't run from.
It's Danny Brickwell.
His street name's Brick.
You are all part
of my crew now.
Together, we are going
to take over the Glades.
[Groaning and gasping]
Oliver.
I asked her to come here...
So she could
bring you back to life.
This is a duel...
Oliver,
with one of the most
dangerous men
that has ever walked
the earth.
I wouldn't be doing it
if I didn't think
I could win.
I don't worry that
you can beat him.
I am terrified
you won't kill him.
That's not who
you are anymore.
And I'm afraid
that Ra's is going
to use your humanity
against you.
You're right.
- I'll stay.
- Really?
Are you sure?
I'm sure of one thing--
I love you.
[Shrieks]
[Gasping]
[Groaning]
[Grunting]
Drink this.
More herbs?
Penicillin.
For the infection.
[Groans]
You saved my life.
The snow
and cold helped.
And your will
to live.
You should be dead.
Did you know Maseo
would bring me here?
He was the one who told me
to meet you at this cabin.
I didn't realize
that the...two of you
were still in contact.
We are not.
[Door opens]
[Grunts]
Maseo...
You're in no
condition to stand.
Then help me.
[Groaning]
I'm glad you stayed.
Then you'll be
disappointed.
When the storm passes,
I'll return to Nanda Parbat.
Maseo...
If Ra's finds out
that you saved me,
betrayed him...
He's going
to kill you.
Don't waste your breath
for worries on me.
Your concern should be
for your home,
and what has become
of it in your absence.
[Door opens, closes]
Man: You picked the wrong alley.
See, this one
cuts off here at Carlisle.
You pick the next one,
and you're free and clear
to Reimer Avenue.
Now, you want to do this
the hard way...
Or the harder way?
Woman: Hey!
Run.
[Grunting]
I heard rumors about a mask
who protects girls around here.
[Grunting]
I guess you ain't her.
This is Brick's town now.
[Sirens approaching]
I think we should talk.
Roy: This is going
to hurt a little.
Just one more.
Sorry,
I warned you it was
going to hurt.
You said a little.
Yeah, well.
Dig taught us how to suture.
I guess Felicity got the hang of it
quicker than I did.
- Where is Felicity?
- Let's talk about you.
What the hell do you think
you were doing out there?
Same thing as you.
I've had training
from Oliver
and years
on the streets.
You have a law degree.
Look...
[Scoffs] I get it.
This?
This isn't how
you deal with grief, Laurel.
This is how
you get yourself killed.
[Door opens]
Laurel, what the hell?
[Scoffs] I'm fine.
You are certifiable if you think
you can wear your sister's mask.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
But Oliver, the Arrow...
He's gone now.
And like it or not, the Canary sends
the same message.
- They fear her.
- No, Laurel.
They fear your sister.
Yeah.
She's not here anymore.
♪ Arrow 3x11 ♪
Midnight City
Original Air Date on January 28, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey.
What are you doing
here so early?
The meeting's
not for another three hours.
Yeah, well,
I convinced Mayor Castle
it might be a good idea
to move it up.
What, with a murderous killer
running amuck in the city.
Isn't that what
the police are for?
Well, she wanted to speak
to city leaders.
And I'll help
in whatever way I can.
And by help, you mean money
and counsel,
not a suit
powered by...
Dwarf star alloy
that fires lasers at people?
Well, they aren't lasers.
That would be ridiculous.
They're compressed
hard light beams.
And they don't actually
fire, because I can't
get anyone,
specifically you,
to help me fix
the Nanite chip.
Well, I already told you, Ray,
I am not interested
in helping you with
your suicide mission.
There is nothing that you can say
or do that is going to change my mind.
Are you ready to go?
Hey. What are you
doing here?
Oh, with that Brick
guy running around the Glades,
I figured I shouldn't leave my gear.
any place he might find it.
What are you
doing here?
This neighborhood
isn't exactly
a safe place to be
hanging out right now.
Well, I'm not hanging out,
I'm just doing my job.
Are we cool?
It just seems like
you've been avoiding me,
you know,
ever since we had
that moment.
Moment? You have a very high opinion
on your kissing skills.
Judging from how
you responded,
I think you've got a pretty high opinion
of them, too.
Unless you need
a reminder.
No, not right now.
[Chuckles]
But, um, I'll see you later?
- What are you doing here?
- I went by your apartment
to see how
your packing is going,
only to discover
that it's not.
[Sighs] I can't leave.
Not without knowing
where Oliver is.
I thought it made it clear
that leaving was not optional.
No, actually, you didn't
make anything clear.
You just ordered me
to uproot my life
and didn't even give me
a reason why.
All you need to know is that
we're in danger,
and every day
we remain in Starling,
the danger grows greater.
Now get in the car, Thea.
No.
Not until
you tell me the truth.
You're not ready
for the truth.
Then I guess I'm not ready
to leave Starling City.
[Starts engine]
Yeah, I know, yeah.
Ok, I'm on it.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- You're not late.
Castle's still hashing things out
with her people.
Um, you heard
from your sister?
No. Why?
Well, she's, uh,
back in town.
A girl came into the precinct
a few hours ago.
Claimed a blonde in a mask
and a black leather jacket saved her life.
All right, thank you, everyone,
for coming, please take your seats.
As you know,
over the last week,
a criminal organization
headed by Danny Brickwell
has been on a crime
spree unlike anything since Al Capone.
Which begs the question--
why aren't you arresting him?
We sent in an ESU team
to do just that.
Most of those men are in
the hospital now.
Now we got no clue
where he's holed up.
Maybe if we had more men,
but that means more money.
[Door opens]
Ah, I've got a few bucks.
Sorry. In fact,
Palmer Technology
has just made a large
donation to the SCPD,
but it'll take time for that personal
equipment to do any good.
We need to consider
calling in the National Guard.
[Gunshots, all yelling]
[Gunshots]
Always wanted
to meet the mayor.
Bring her
and the aldermen.
[Gunshot]
Kill the rest.
Laurel!
See? That's why I need
a technosuit.
Is Mayor Castle
secure?
Yeah.
But what about the aldermen?
[Sighs]
Brick's got 'em.
Your penicillin tea
tastes like penicillin.
[Coughs]
[Door closes]
[Wind blowing]
We can't let him
go back to the League.
It's not our choice.
Maybe we could
have changed Maseo's mind,
but not his.
Not Sarab's.
Sarab is just a name
that Ra's al Ghul calls him.
He's still your husband.
Thank you.
Maseo blames himself
for what happened.
Yeah. It wasn't his fault.
The line between
grief and guilt
is a thin one.
Sometimes, death
is preferable
to the agony of life.
[Dance music playing,
indistinct chatter]
Tracker's in there.
Looks like
a VIP area.
Probably where
they're holding Tatsu.
There's a lot of muscle
in front of that door.
This club
is a Triad front.
It will be
heavily guarded.
But will you do anything
to get her back?
Yes, I would.
I told you it would be
heavily guarded.
You're late.
- That's funny.
- I wasn't talking to you.
I was addressing
your partner.
What's?
Did you bring the item?
What is she
talking about?!
I want to see my wife.
I said I want
to see my wife.
Once I know she's alive,
then you can have
the Alpha.
Sorry, Oliver.
Maseo!
What are you doing?
Hey.
How's your heart?
Ah, still beating. You ok?
Listen, I couldn't help
but notice that nobody in a green hood
showed up to save the day.
That's because
he's gone.
What do you mean, gone?
It means
we're on our own.
But that doesn't
make sense, what,
the Arrow's gone,
but Sara's back?
Wait, Sara's back?
What are you
talking about?
Yeah, she's been taking out
Brick's men solo.
I've been getting reports
down at the precinct.
Blonde, mask, Bo-staff.
You didn't know?
I've sort of been living under
a rock these days.
Hmm.
Ask him to give me a call.
Yeah.
Will do.
[Sirens in distance]
[Door opens]
Jim Huffman.
34, eight arrests,
no convictions.
Grand Theft Auto,
B&E, drugs.
You did pretty well
flying solo.
What made you decide
to start working for Brick?
I'm not telling you
anything.
Are you sure about that?
I still have another heel.
[Scoffs]
Kidding.
You don't want to talk
about Brick, that's fine.
Then let's talk
about something else.
Why would you murder
Julio Salazar?
Salazar?
Head of Los Halcones?
I had nothing to do
with him getting popped.
Well, that's not
what your file says.
See?
[Scoffs] What kind
of game is this?
You just
wrote that down!
You're making
this stuff up!
Actually,
I can charge you
with whatever crime
that I want.
Of course, then they'd have
to keep you in custody
until the trial.
Good news--
Belle Reve, it's a lot more
comfortable than Iron Heights.
Belle Reve's where
the Los Halcones are locked up.
They think
I offed Salazar.
I won't last two
seconds in there!
Tell me where I can find Danny Brickwell
and you won't have to.
They'll kill me.
[Drops pen on table]
Charges filed by Dinah Laurel
Lance, assistant district att--
Hey, stop. Stop!
I'll tell you where
you can find Brick.
If you're looking
for Thea,
she's not here.
I know.
I came to see you.
[Chuckles]
Following me, Mr. Harper?
You need
to stay away from her.
I don't know why you want her
to leave Starling City,
but I'm not letting her go
anywhere with you.
Well, thank you
for that.
I was in need
of some humor.
I wasn't joking.
You are poison.
You put her
in Ra's al Ghul's gunsights.
You had her kill Sara.
Thea knows nothing
about Sara.
And she never will.
That's where you're wrong.
I know her.
She'll get to the truth no matter
how well you think you're hiding it.
And when she does find out
that you've been lying to her,
you're going
to lose her forever.
Trust me;
I know from experience.
[Chuckles]
This is a family
matter, Mr. Harper.
And you are not family.
- Sit.
- Ok.
[Exhales]
Are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Armed gunmen
attacking you.
That had to have brought back
a few bad memories.
Yeah.
When it started,
all I could think about was
the night Anna died.
But when that gunman
charged us,
all I could think about was
saving you.
[Chuckles]
[Groans]
Ah.
You were right.
Hmm?
I've been going
about this all wrong.
When I started
the Atom project,
it was all about
avenging Anna.
But what it has become about
is...protecting
the people I care for.
You mean the city?
No.
I mean you.
You sure you still want
to use that thing?
We have plenty of
other weapons here.
- It was Sara's.
- Roy!
I thought we were on the same
page with this.
That was before Brick
kidnapped three aldermen.
Laurel said she knows
where they are.
We put their location through Felicity's
surveillance program
but Brick keeps moving them.
We can still track them,
take them out en route,
but the window's closing.
Fine. Laurel,
monitor us from here.
- Talk me and Roy in.
- No.
That's not how this
is going to work.
Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
Laurel, you're not
your sister!
You think I don't know that?
You lost a brother.
If there's anyone
who I thought would understand,
it would be you.
Stay close to her.
We should have got the mayor.
That was a loss.
Let's go.
Laurel...
Laurel, Laurel, watch your six!
Lucky for you, I don't
like hitting women.
Go, go, go!
[Tires squealing]
Bad choice!
This one's on you.
[Gunshot]
[Siren in distance]
Danny Brickwell
is still at large tonight
after abducting three
aldermen from city hall
earlier this evening.
Though he's managed to
evade SCPD thus far--
- Dad.
-... cell phone video shows two vigilantes...
- Hey. You ok?
- Yeah.
...associated
with the Arrow,
the Red Arrow and the woman
in black, in pursuit.
Reports now trickling in
suggest a confrontation...
Your sister
did her best.
Channel 52's running cell phone
footage of her
and the Arrow's partner,
the guy in the red hood.
Did Sara talk to you?
What? No.
Uh, she hasn't, not yet.
You know, she must
know we're seeing this stuff.
Woman: Madame Mayor,
there's a call for you on line one.
- Take a message.
- It's Danny Brickwell.
Mr. Brickwell.
How is your evening
going, madame Mayor?
Mine's not going too well.
Because your city's
"vigilante problem"
became mine earlier tonight.
And it's forced my hand--
Look, if you have demands to make,
just get on with it.
No demands,
just Shakespeare.
"Julius Caesar,"
Act Five, Scene Two.
"They stand
and would have parley."
The war stops and together
they converse.
I would have
parley with you.
That isn't what we're doing
right now.
In person, Brockton
Point, one hour.
I don't negotiate
with terrorists.
And I certainly
don't do it in person.
You are already going
to one funeral, madame Mayor.
If you want to make it a hat trick,
well, that's your prerogative.
Me? I'll be at
Brockton Point.
[Door slams]
If you came to see
how packing is going,
it's not.
No.
I came to apologize.
I don't want
to lose you, Thea.
But at the same time,
sharing the truth with you
is sometimes difficult for me.
Well, maybe you'll
get better with practice.
Who are we running from?
His name
is Ra's al Ghul.
And why does
he want to kill you?
Ra's has a particular
code of honor
he feels I've violated.
And he's marked me
and my family for death.
I fell in with Ra's
because I was consumed
by the death of my wife.
And I was marked for death
because of the Undertaking
that killed my son.
You're all
I have left, Thea.
Keeping you safe
is all that matters.
Please let me.
Alderman Richard Ford
was in his second term at city hall.
He leaves behind a wife
and two children.
The city asks the family's privacy
be respected during this trying time.
[Knock on door]
Laurel...
I'm sorry. I can come back.
No, it's ok. Is...
Is everything ok?
I came to ask you
the same thing...
Canary.
I guess you came
here to talk some sense into me.
Seems like you could use some.
Not sure you're going
to have to bother.
Brick, he...
He killed someone tonight.
In front of me.
I thought that being--
being Sara would
make it hurt less.
But instead, it just...
it caused more pain.
Not just for me.
[Clears throat]
So you don't have to worry.
[Sniffles, sighs]
I'm not going to be putting on
that mask again.
I'm not strong enough
to fight for Sara.
Maybe you're not supposed to.
Maybe it's not about Sara,
or Oliver, or anyone else
that we care about,
who we lost. Maybe
what we've been doing
we've been doing it because
there are people we care about
that are still...alive.
Maybe we're doing it for them.
I thought you quit.
Mayor: He's confident.
Meeting out here
in the open where
any police sniper
could take him out.
Yeah, well, that's
'cause he's got men
that could take the hostages out,
check mate.
Madame Mayor.
All this for me?
I'm impressed.
What are you doing
here, Palmer?
Just want to make yourself
look important?
Good luck with that.
Star City. [Laughs]
Seems more like
Brick City to me.
Night is young.
Tough talk.
Too bad all you got
is money to back it up.
But you can't fix this
with money, Palmer.
I don't know.
I got a lot of money.
Mayor: Say what
you came here to say.
We can all end
this farce.
Ok.
I've still got
two of your men.
If you want them back,
it's simple.
Get out of the Glades.
The city servicemen,
especially the police--
evacuate.
You're out of your mind!
And you've got until
midnight tomorrow.
If I even see
a hint of a blue,
your city yes-men,
they will be buried.
We won't abandon
an entire district.
They did in L.A. in
'92, didn't they?
Besides, you don't want
every news station
in the country showing
graphic footage
of the murders
of the aldermen, do you?
You have 23 hours,
59 minutes.
I suggest you move
your sweet ass!
[Engine starts]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Captain Lance?
Quentin: Brick wants every cop
out of the Glades
or he's going to
kill his hostages.
We need help,
we need it now.
Look, I know you said
the Arrow is gone.
Are you sure
about that?
Yes, I am.
But I think I know
where to find the Canary.
The storm has passed.
Maseo...
You don't have to leave.
You can still have a life.
Why do you assume I want one?
Because I know you
and this isn't who you are.
I love you.
No matter who you think
you've become.
Maseo?
They found you.
[Door opens]
[Speaking Arabic]
Sarab.
What are you doing here?
Ra's al Ghul wants
Oliver Queen's remains.
I found no body,
only tracks.
Which led here.
Queen is still alive.
But there is no one here.
I was just about to go.
[Floor creaking]
Brothers...
We should go.
Traitor!
She's the mother of my son. You do
not get to judge me.
Too late.
This concludes
our business.
Only...if the serum
is genuine.
It's genuine.
Then you should have
no problem with me testing it.
[Beep]
It's a fake.
Kill them all.
[All grunting]
Go, go, go!
That alderman died
because of the decision
that I made.
And there was no Mirakuru
to blame this time.
Don't take that
on yourself, man.
That was Brick.
What's that?
[Sighs]
Sometimes, me and Oliver
will come down here after,
you know, tough nights.
He would pour this,
look up and say...
"Prochnost."
What does that mean?
I have no earthly idea.
To Oliver.
We can't do this
without Oliver, can we?
Felicity was right.
Actually, I was wrong,
and I'm not wrong a lot.
I talked to my father.
He said the mayor is going to cave
and cede control over the Glades.
They're going to evacuate
the police force.
So it's up to us
to stop Brick.
"Us?" What, are you and Laurel
a team now?
I was wrong when
I said Oliver's mission was over,
because it's not
just Oliver's mission
anymore, it is ours.
It's our home
that is under attack.
For all we know,
Oliver could be dead
and Sara
certainly is.
But there are people that are
still alive.
People who need us.
Ok.
First we have to find out where
those aldermen are.
- It's a bad idea.
- So you've said...
repeatedly.
But it's my decision,
so do as I tell you
and give the order!
You give it. You want
to pull my men out the Glades,
fine, that's your funeral.
But I don't want any part of it.
Excuse me.
[Cell phone rings]
Hello?
Hi, Daddy.
Sara.
Sara, where you been?
I've been worried sick
about you.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Are you ok?
Well, yeah, I mean,
I've been better.
I'm sure you have been, too.
Listen, why didn't you
call me sooner, honey?
It's complicated.
How is she doing this?
I fed recordings
of Sara's voice
through a symbolic
algorithm.
Daddy, I'm sorry
that I've been away,
but I don't want you
to worry about me.
I'm fine.
And I'm here to help.
Ok.
What do you need from me?
I need you to tell me everything
you know about the hostages.
No matter how
seemingly insignificant.
Well, I don't know
how knowing their favorite color's
going to help
find them, honey.
There has to be something.
Some sort of Intel
that you couldn't move on
because of the mayor's orders.
I wish.
The clock's running down
on these guys, too.
I just found out one of them's got
a heart condition.
If his pacemaker
isn't recharged soon,
we're going to lose
another alderman.
Daddy, that
actually helps.
But, I have to go now.
Wait, just listen to me.
Be careful out there, ok?
Because I don't know what I'd do
if anything happened to you.
I'll be careful.
I love you, sweetheart.
I love you,
too, daddy.
One of the aldermen
has a pacemaker.
If it's remote programmable...
It'll have a GPS.
It's going to take me a few minutes
to log on to the pacemaker.
Gear up.
This one breakthrough,
is all we need, is one--
Psst.
Yeah. One second.
Sorry to interrupt.
What's going on?
Oh. I need the keys
to your helicopter.
How would you
even fly it?
I got that covered.
Can you please just
give me the keys now? I...
Promise, promise,
I will not crash it.
I've got to be honest;
I'd feel a little
more confident
in your aeronautic
abilities if you knew,
for instance, that helicopters don't
actually have keys.
They don't have keys?
No.
Is it on the roof?
Yeah, it's
on the roof.
Thank you!
I'm going to hold you
to the no crash promise.
You do realize it's been
five years since
I've flown one
of these things, right?
It's like riding
a bicycle, I hope.
Do you have
Brick's location?
According to the last signal
from the pacemaker,
Brick has the aldermen
in a warehouse at 16th and Kent.
Not for long,
he doesn't.
Man on walkie talkie: We got a chopper
outside. Take a look.
Roger that.
Checking it now.
I guess we're even now.
Follow the hallway
20 yards.
Turn left.
Aldermen!
Come on!
Don't worry!
We're going to get
you out of here.
Let's go.
Go. Go!
Dig, I'm going to need you
to find me a way out of here.
Copy that.
I still don't like
hitting women.
But I could make
an exception for you.
Black Canary:
So come and get me.
You're getting warmer.
I will keep
this city safe.
By killing anyone
that doesn't do what you say?
Something like that.
Warmer...
We're not going to let you--
[Groaning]
Well, it's--it's done.
Bodies will not be found.
Ok, Maseo, I get you wanting
to go back before,
but that was before.
When Ra's finds out that
you betrayed the League...
Maseo!
Why the hell
did you do that?!
I didn't. You did.
In a successful
attempt to escape.
Or you could just come back
to Starling City with me.
[Speaking Japanese]
[Clears throat] Can I talk to you
for a minute?
If you're going
to bluff with a fake virus sample,
let me in on it.
- I wasn't bluffing.
- What does that mean?
That--that the Alpha we
stole from the military was a fake?
That Amanda Waller knew
I would try something like this.
She must have switched out
the vial before I took it.
Maseo! You were
willing to risk
letting hundreds,
maybe thousands
of people die?
For my wife...yes.
There's nothing
I wouldn't do for my family.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
Dad?
[Chuckles]
Both aldermen are back
with their families.
Nice job.
For all the good it did.
What does that mean?
Mayor Castle caved.
She's pulling SCPD
out of the Glades.
But why? Brick doesn't have
the aldermen anymore.
No, but what he does have
is the home address
of every city council member
and their family,
and the means to hurt them.
Played that card
15 minutes ago.
Hey, sweetie, sweetheart, hey,
how about we, uh, cry over
each other's shoulders?
Over dinner,
at the Chinese place you love.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
What's going on
with you, sweetheart?
Why are you trying
to avoid me?
I'll explain
everything.
Just...not tonight.
You ok?
I'm fine, daddy.
I'm fine.
Are you ready to leave?
No.
I'm not leaving.
Is this supposed to make up
for me missing your adolescence,
this routine of listening
and then disobeying me?
Just hear me out.
You told me that
we were in danger.
You even told me
who was after us.
But what
you didn't tell me
is why.
Yes, I did.
Because Ra's al Ghul
wants us dead.
That's pretty much the case
anywhere we go.
So why run?
Why not stay
and fight?
Seven months ago,
I asked you
to teach me.
To teach me how
to not be afraid
and how to not
get hurt.
So why are you
asking me to be afraid now?
I am not asking you.
I am telling you.
You should be very afraid.
Well, I'm not. 'Cause my father
taught me not to be.
You taught me how
to stand my ground
and how to not give
an inch in a battle.
I'm not afraid
of this man
and you shouldn't
be, either.
He should be
afraid of us.
Then we'll stay.
Your helicopter
is back on the roof.
I didn't crash it.
Turns out...
It actually had keys.
And this.
The reason you couldn't
get the Nanite chip to function
is because what you
actually need...
is a quantum
processor.
The design is elegant.
Hmm.
Thought you weren't going to help me
on my suicide mission.
Well, that's the thing.
With my help,
you might not end up dead.
Hey.
I thought you knew
about this whole neighborhood
turning into a scene
from "The Purge."
We didn't even
open tonight.
I forgot my music files here
and I've got another gig.
Cheating on me with
another club manager.
Well, I heard a rumor
you were leaving town.
Happy to say that
those rumors are false.
That's good news.
For both of us.
Don't get so ahead
of yourself.
My hard drive's up there.
Take your time.
[Speaking Arabic]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man