My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day,
I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I am someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Traitor! I'm taking you
to hell with...
I'm sorry you didn't
get to know your father.
I guess you're stuck knowing me.
What I saw in her
is what I see here.
It sounds crazy, but if there is just
some way to get through to her...
- We have a massively huge problem.
- What is it?
The nano-thermite,
when combined with the explosive
creates a thermobaric weapon.
Cayden James could do it.
And he'd probably detonate
in a populated area.
Maximize casualties.
Your city's entire infrastructure
is under my control.
Buildings, institutions, even people,
all under my dominion.
These are innocent people.
And you can save them...
By wiring 10 million dollars
into that offshore account
no later than 11:30 tonight.
And every night.
Wire the money.
All right, we're all set here.
Captain Hilton, thank you for
stepping up to lead the department.
I wish it was under
better circumstances.
After tonight, they will be.
All right, take me
through the details.
We know Cayden James is monitoring
traffic in and out of the city.
Airports, highways, ports.
But the shoreline
might be the blind spot.
Specifically, right here,
there's no satellite flyover
for about 10 minutes.
That's our window.
SWAT has the perimeter,
so no one's getting in or out
without us knowing it.
Good. When do we make contact?
Should be any minute.
Mr. Mayor, I'm Alex Scott, A.R.G.U.S.
- Good to meet you.
- We're good to move?
Yes.
All clear on shore. Exit. Exit.
- What's wrong?
- No, just some weird feedback.
Are your comms line of sight?
No, we're patched in.
You gotta get those things...
We gotta get the other divers
out of the water.
$70 million.
At this point,
we've got maybe another day or two.
What about the federal government?
I mean, don't they have plans
for this kind of stuff?
A.R.G.U.S. was our best shot,
and Cayden James was ready for it.
I think that we are on our own.
So does that mean I go forward
with the emergency bomb shelters?
Yeah. We need a contingency.
It won't save everyone.
But it's a start.
How is William holding up?
Doing as well as can be expected.
He's holed up
at an A.R.G.U.S. safe house
with Raisa and a PlayStation 4.
You look like
you could use some rest.
I'll get some if you will.
Like brother like sister, I guess.
Hey, don't worry, okay?
Cayden James is not the first guy
to try to take our city hostage.
We will figure it out.
Cayden James' hold on Star City
has reached eight days
and counting now,
with all routes in and out
of the city under James' control.
Though Mayor Queen
has urged for calm,
tensions are running high
as the threat of the thermobaric bomb
continues to loom.
With supplies running low
and desperation growing,
many are left wondering how long will
the city last before it implodes?
That's a damn good question.
You're late.
Sorry.
SCPD's been dealing with the fallout
from last night's debacle.
I didn't know
about the A.R.G.U.S. team
until after Cayden killed 'em.
You believe me, right?
Cayden James likes to play things
close to the vest.
Even with the people he's supposedly
in league with.
Which makes finding the location
of the thermobaric bomb
very difficult.
You believe me, right?
About not knowing
about the A.R.G.U.S. divers?
I already told you, I do.
I guess what I'm asking is,
do you trust me?
Does that answer your question?
- Sorry I'm late.
- Don't be sorry.
Just don't be late.
Vincent Sobel, meet Dinah Drake.
- "Tina Boland" is my cover name.
- Tina Boland.
You got quite the rep.
No idea you were a cop.
That's the idea, isn't it?
Vince has spent the last eight months
in Sean Sonus' operation.
And he is smart.
He makes sure that no one person ever
sees enough of the whole picture.
Sounds like you could use
an extra set of hands.
And eyes, and ears.
I gotta tell you,
Sonus isn't just smart,
he is unpredictable.
This could go south, fast.
When do we start?
Didn't know we were having
a clubhouse meeting.
Only boys allowed today or what?
Ms. Lance is en route.
And this is less a meeting
than it is a wake for Mr. Sheck.
He bought the farm a week ago.
I didn't think we were
sentimental like that.
It's not sentimental. Surprised.
Oliver would not kill a man this way.
None of his team would.
The place wasn't lacking for cops.
One of them probably took him out.
What's really behind
this sudden paranoia?
Mr. Queen was obviously able
to get word outside the cordon
we placed around the city.
To A.R.G.U.S., you mean.
He seems more than capable.
Agreed. But it was unexpected.
As was Mr. Sheck's demise.
I don't like surprises.
And I like even less the feeling
that I can't trust my comrades.
It sounds like it's just me
you don't trust.
If I didn't, you wouldn't be
drawing breath right now, Mr. Sobel.
Oh...
Oh, I love your face, but that is
just not a good face.
What's up?
Just spent the past two hours
trying to convince the city council
that we will get out
from underneath Cayden James' thumb.
Not sure even I believe that,
at this point.
Hey.
You know what I'm looking forward to
once we put Cayden James away?
What's that?
- Our honeymoon.
- Hmm.
We are going on a honeymoon, right?
- Aruba.
Ooh.
Mmm-hmm. Any news here?
We split the city in half
with the other team.
Divide-and-conquer is not getting us
any closer to finding Cayden James.
Our sector has been quiet
for a few hours.
"Has been" being
the operative phrase.
Okay, facial recognition
picked up Vigilante,
despite his mask having no face.
Cayden James' people don't ordinarily
walk around like that.
We might have caught a break.
Let's text John the location.
I'm headed your way.
Going somewhere?
Where's Cayden James?
You're making a mistake.
You've got three seconds.
- Oliver, listen.
- One!
- I'm trying to stop Cayden.
- Two!
I can't blow my cover.
Three.
Hold your fire.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- He's a friendly.
- What?
He's here for a meet, with us.
He's undercover
with James' group.
We were gonna tell you guys.
Eventually.
I can't believe that you had time
to secretly put all this together
and continue starting our start-up.
Well, being single does wonders
for your time management.
Okay, on your next date you are
not allowed to lead with that.
How do you know you can trust him?
He saved my life last week.
Killed one of James' men to do it.
And he's in love with Dinah.
Look, just stating the facts.
Vince is working on locating
the thermobaric bomb.
We take that out of play
and we got the situation handled.
What kind of progress are you making
locating the bomb?
Not much.
Cayden keeps the bomb
on the move constantly.
He's become especially paranoid
since I killed one of his men.
Your stunt with A.R.G.U.S. last night
didn't help matters.
So why don't you just take us
to where Cayden
and his men are hiding?
'Cause the second you show up,
he'll detonate the bomb.
The amplifier he has,
he'll take out the city.
He's right.
And until we find out where
that bomb is, we've got no moves.
Okay, well, then we just...
We find out where the bomb is.
Last year we used a sniffer device
to pull information from
Prometheus' mother's house.
You wanna use the same device
for Cayden James?
That's exactly
what I wanna do.
We can gather all his
ones and zeroes.
There's gotta be a scrap of data
left in there somewhere.
Then we have someone to plant
Felicity's toy for us.
Yeah.
There's just one small problem.
- Just one?
- Well, two, actually.
The sniffer needs to be manually
implanted into Cayden's server...
No, no. There's no way he can do that
without Cayden noticing, Felicity.
Especially now
that he's circling the wagons.
I knew what I signed up for.
I didn't expect this to be easy.
What else?
Okay, Cayden's server
is deep within the building,
so while our comms will be working,
transmitting a data-pull that large,
it requires line of sight.
Which means you'll
have to install the sniffer,
then wait for it to download
the content to Cayden James' server.
Making sure Cayden doesn't see you or
the sniffer. That'd be bad, very bad.
And then get it outside
so you can transmit the files.
Yeah, that sounds
like more than two problems.
Sounds like a good way
of getting yourself killed.
Then it's a good thing I heal fast.
Vince.
May I speak with you, please?
Ms. Queen, I'm telling you,
there is nothing liquid.
And we have no way
of borrowing capital.
Jake, that's just
not gonna work for us,
so I need you to try
to find more money.
I might be able to pull
a few hundred thousand but...
That's not gonna be enough money
for Cayden James,
so I just... I need you to try
and find some more.
Sorry, sometimes he just needs to be
pushed a little bit.
Quentin, what's up?
She's been following me.
- Laurel?
- Yeah.
It started a couple of days ago.
Okay, have you talked to her?
Not quite.
Every time I turn around,
she disappears.
What do you think it means?
I think maybe we made
some kind of connection.
She wants to reach out,
but she's afraid.
- Does that sound crazy?
- No.
Not after everything
we've seen lately, no.
So what do we do?
If it seems like she's trying
to reach out to you, then...
I don't know, maybe we
just gotta find a way
for you to reach out to her.
What's on your mind?
Dinah, Curtis
and Rene trust you.
I'm not there yet.
I want you to try to imagine
how little I give a damn.
You've taken a shot at me.
Matter of fact,
you've taken a shot
at nearly everybody in that room,
so I will be convinced
that you're not playing us,
the way that you claim
to be playing Cayden James.
I don't have to convince you.
Because you're not stopping me
from doing this.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
Because you know saving this city
means doing whatever's necessary.
And you know that means using me.
Did Oliver push you to do this?
He didn't have to, D.
It's the right play.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
I'm not so sure.
Something just doesn't feel right.
You know, the same way it did for you
when everything went bad with Sonus.
That was my call, D.
Don't you wear that guilt.
I don't wanna lose you again.
I'm so happy to hear that.
And you won't.
Aces and queens.
Got me.
And you are in the black, barely.
Thanks.
Yeah, this cash inflow coming
from San Francisco is huge,
but it wasn't very efficient.
You know, if I knew more I might be
able to maximize revenue stream.
Sorry. I know I'm not supposed
to ask specifics.
Just... We need a little more of it,
that's all I'm saying.
I'll take that under advisement.
All right.
Well, I'm going to go home
for the night.
Good night, boys.
I'll walk with you.
Can't let a lady walk home alone, hmm?
That was subtle.
What, you didn't have a neon sign?
It's fine, no one noticed.
So what did his book say?
He's got a boatload
of money floating around
neither of us have eyes on.
And seriously, Vince,
Sonus should not see us together.
They all think I'm just trying
to get in your pants.
Hmm.
Well, if only wishing made it so.
Nice.
Love what you guys haven't done
with the place.
Let's get this over with.
We turned your room into a home gym,
because...
'Cause this extremely
awkward situation
needs to be masked with humor.
I think what she means to say is,
welcome back.
We have the inside man,
you have the tech.
It's the only reason
we're back, hoss.
- Is Vince on site?
- Should be, as of five minutes ago.
That is, if everything
goes according to plan.
You sound like it might not.
Vince said he doesn't have access
to the server room,
so if anyone spots him in there,
he's gonna have
a lot of explaining to do.
We've got eyes.
- Can I talk to him?
- Yeah.
Hey, Vince.
You get any kind of
bad feeling here at all, you abort.
You hear me?
Don't worry, I'll see you soon.
He's at the server.
The door to
the server room is locked.
You guys have a solve for this?
Try 0-6-1-4-1-9-9-8.
- "Try"?
- It's his son's birthday.
- If you're wrong, he's dead.
- I'm not gonna be wrong.
Okay, Vince, you're in the red
zone, just let the sniffer do its thing.
Eighty terabytes of data.
You guys can get comfortable.
This is gonna take a minute.
Mr. Sobel?
Frack.
I think we need to talk.
All of my people
have specific domains.
I don't believe
that IT is one of yours,
which means you would not have
a proper pass code to enter.
How much data's been copied?
20%.
No, but Mr. Sheck did.
He was a little more loose-lipped
then you'd like.
Rest in peace.
Still, it doesn't explain
what exactly you're doing in here.
- We gotta pull him out.
- Dinah, not yet.
- Oliver!
- Okay, wait.
Vince, if you wanna stay alive,
repeat exactly what I say.
- "You think just..."
- ...because I can handle a gun,
doesn't mean I know
the difference between
a transpolymer hybrid
and a fiber-optic cable.
I'm just impressed.
I wanted to know how you maximize
the data through-put.
Sorry.
I should have asked first.
Perhaps.
I may have underestimated you.
It seems that you have more skill
than I gave you credit for.
I keep telling people
I'm more than just a pretty face.
Keep him talking, we're at 80%.
Funny thing is,
I underestimated you, too.
Is that right?
When you recruited me to help you
take this city from Oliver Queen,
I didn't think you'd have
the resolve to do
what was necessary
to make him fear you.
I was wrong.
Does that mean
that you also fear me, Mr. Sobel?
I'd be a fool not to.
Such flattery.
Are we done here?
Yeah, we're good.
Take the sniffer and leave.
After you.
It appears that Mr. Knyazev
has returned from the ports.
Join us in five.
Absolutely.
You were amazing.
Yeah, we'll engrave your Oscar
when you're out of the building.
Heading out now.
That's our final offer.
Oh, please, your final offer
is never really final, Sean.
You got a vice under there?
You want me to just
gently put my nuts in it for you?
So, are we gonna celebrate or what?
I think she's gonna drop
half the product
and leave us with our asses
hanging out, like she did last time.
I'll make good on my end.
You don't need to worry about me.
I'd take a look
at your own house first.
What the hell are you talking about?
The Darbinyans rooted out
a mole last month.
An OCB operative.
A few fingernails later,
he got very chatty.
According to him,
you have a cop on your payroll.
Hold up. Mr. James wants to see you.
Did I teach you that move?
I taught you that move.
All right. Transmitting now.
It's coming through.
Man, this is the mother lode.
We're gonna need Alena on this
to help us process.
Now get your ass back to Helix.
On my way.
We need to call Singh.
Roll this thing up right now.
We don't even have Sonus yet.
We've got enough.
If the Alvarez buy falls through,
we have got nothing.
Vince, we need Sonus in the room.
- We need money changing hands.
- I know.
But what we don't know
is which one of us is made.
No, baby.
If Sonus knew anything at all,
one of us would already be dead.
We've been working
at this for months.
And we're close.
You know, we're so close.
We can't pull the pin on this now.
All right.
We'll play it your way.
Mr. Sobel.
Sorry. I got a text
from my girlfriend.
She's at the hospital.
Thinks it's appendicitis.
Well, I'm sure the doctors
are doing everything they can.
I need you here
for a rather important assignment.
Yeah? What's that?
Rooting out a traitor.
Cayden sure has a lot of junk
in his server
for someone who's as type-A
as you say he is.
Well, brilliant people are often
slobs. Or so I tell myself.
- And my dates.
- Show-off.
- I can't even get a date.
- Anything yet?
Well, if by "anything," you mean
the location of the bomb...
- No, not yet.
- Okay.
How much longer is this gonna take?
Yeah. How much longer
do I got to be here?
'Cause I'm starting to get PTSD.
- Maybe an hour.
- Hopefully less.
I'm gonna head back to Helix.
I should've heard from Vince by now.
I'll go with you.
Sorry, boys.
Guess I'm just lucky.
More like pretty woman
make smart men dumb.
Speak for yourself, Declan.
Hey, Tina,
can I borrow you for a sec?
Yeah. What's up?
I got the Alvarez buy coming up.
I wanted your expertise
on the numbers.
Yeah, sure.
You want me to dive in now?
You can start on page 12.
I noticed something
a little concerning.
Looks like your luck is up.
You were always the enigma,
Mr. Sobel.
The vigilante willing
to ally himself with criminals
to take out other vigilantes.
I must confess,
I never totally bought into it.
Given your background
as an undercover operative,
I would have been a fool to.
I don't strike you as a fool, do I?
No.
You are coming off
a little crazy, though.
I've done good work for you.
I got no love for Oliver Queen.
You know that.
I don't know anything for certain.
That's what this is for.
I must admit, that is fascinating.
You can torture me all you want.
You'll keep getting the same answer.
I didn't do anything.
I admire your tenacity.
But even a man
who's difficult to kill
cannot withstand torture,
at least, not forever.
Hmm.
In my country, we do things a little,
how do you say... Dirtier?
We'll give the two of you
some privacy.
Okey-dokey.
Where shall we begin?
Okay, Thea, I'm inside.
Are you sure she's still following?
She's right
behind you. Keep moving.
All right.
Laurel? Wait, wait, wait.
Don't go. Please.
This was a mistake.
If you really thought that,
you wouldn't have spent
the past few nights following me.
- I think you wanna talk.
- There's nothing to talk about.
Then don't.
Just listen.
And watch.
You see her?
This is Laurel.
This is my Laurel.
She was incredible.
When I look into your eyes,
I see the girl I raised.
I see the same warmth,
kindness and love.
And I see a hero.
You just need to see it, too.
Please.
This isn't me.
This isn't... This isn't me!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You know, I know it sounds crazy,
but I think I just saw
my daughter in her eyes.
I saw her.
Vince didn't make it back to Helix.
- Did he reach out to any of you?
- No.
- Boom!
- Goes the dynamite.
Maybe not the best choice of words
considering the circumstances.
Oh, if by circumstances
you mean locating
Cayden's bomb then yes, we just did.
- Where?
- Warehouse District, 10th and Valley.
What exactly
are we walking ourselves into here?
We have no idea.
It's a surveillance dead zone,
we can't really see a thing.
- No surprise there.
- The place is massive.
Then we need everybody.
Agreed?
- What's that?
- That's Vince.
He just activated his comms.
The pain stops
once I have my answers.
Vince!
Oh, my God. We need to help him.
Hey, look, like Vince said,
James is constantly moving the bomb.
This might be our only chance.
- He is being tortured!
- And he can handle it.
With his healing abilities they can't
do anything to hurt him permanently.
As far as we know,
this could be a trap.
Once the bomb is rendered safe,
we go back in, we get Vince.
He has already been made.
By the time we get there,
that bomb is gonna be long gone!
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do!
Look, we all got him into this.
We should all be getting him out!
Fine.
- I'll do it myself.
- Dinah.
Vince would not want you
to do it this way!
Don't you dare!
You know damn well
if it was Felicity out there,
if it was Lyla,
this wouldn't even be up for debate.
Vince is my family.
But I'm not letting him die.
Not again.
Dinah?
You're not talking me
out of this, Curtis.
We know.
That's why we're coming with you.
You're our family, too.
We'll save Vince.
You guys save the city.
We're not gonna be able to cover
the bomb's location
with half the manpower.
Looks like you're gonna
have to figure out a way, hoss.
- How much further?
- About 100 yards or so, give or take.
That might as well be
a mile away at this rate.
- Not if you draw their fire!
- Follow the T-Sphere. Go!
Looks like your little buddies
finally found us.
Took longer than expected.
Good for us. Bad for him.
No sign of the bomb. You?
Nothing.
This place is too big to search.
We're gonna run out of time!
I've got movement. East corridor.
Hello...
No need for me
to explain choice here, yes?
- I thought you were an honorable man!
- I am.
Why else I give you choice?
Find bomb, or save...
Go. I'll take care of them.
Vince?
Thank God.
Smart work
activating your comms.
I didn't.
Hang on.
Vince.
I'll get you free.
Oh, I highly doubt that.
Your ability to withstand
extreme punishment is impressive.
But we all have our limits.
Let's find Mr. Sobel's.
Don't make me doubt your loyalty,
too, Ms. Lance.
No... No... Please.
Don't...
Hey, Tina.
You're not lookin' too good.
But I got something here
that might put a smile on your face.
Look who we got here.
My God.
Vinny.
I am begging you. Please!
Oh, my God.
Hey!
Baby.
Baby, wake up.
No, baby, please.
Baby, please wake up.
- Wake up.
- He's gone, D.
No.
Oh, my God.
No, baby, not again. No. No.
Baby, no.
She hasn't moved or said a word
in over an hour.
After my wife was murdered,
it took me days.
What do we do?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
You're definitely not fine.
How can we help you, Dinah?
You already have...
By having my back.
Did they get the bomb?
Tell me.
Felicity called.
There was nothing they could do.
Vince died for nothing.
Sorry.
We needed more numbers.
We didn't have it.
- Any word from the other team?
- I wish it was better news.
Vince?
He didn't make it.
How is Dinah?
As good as she can be.
It was a choice between
an entire city or one man.
He made the right call.
I know it feels like
this was all for nothing,
but it's not entirely true.
Alena found something.
I've been working on my data haul
from Cayden's servers.
Mmm-hmm. What'd you find?
Evidence he received
while in Corto Maltese.
Video of his son's murder.
It's Cayden's son, Owen Post.
Guess we know
why he hates you so much.
This is fabricated.
It didn't happen.
This could not have been you.
You were in Hub City.
Yeah, but Owen Post
was still murdered,
supposedly by the Green Arrow.
Wouldn't the SCPD be all over this?
The FBI?
Records on the case were wiped clean.
Right. So, Cayden wanted me
all to himself
and didn't want anyone
to get in the way.
How do we prove that this is fake?
Well, we're working on that,
but there is something
super-interesting about this.
The digital alteration of this
is consistent with that of the bogus
surveillance photo of you
in the Green Arrow suit.
We thought
Cayden James leaked that image.
Whoever doctored this
leaked that photo.
To make James think
you killed his son.
Whoever planned this,
knew exactly how Cayden would react.
Which means that person
has to be close to Cayden.
If that's true,
Vince wasn't the only traitor
that Cayden has to worry about.
Hey.
You know what?
Laurel, she needs to see this. Right?
'Cause the video worked,
it got through to her a little bit,
but this is gonna...
What is it? You all right?
I think we might've been wrong
about Laurel.
What are you talking about?
Felicity just called.
Dinah's former partner,
her boyfriend...
Right.
- He's dead.
- Oh...
And Laurel killed him.
I know how badly
you want to believe in this,
and believe in her and then...
Seriously, Quentin, I really do, too.
I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't be here.
Dinah, please give me
a chance to explain.
You lost that right when you decided
to leave Vince on his own to die.
I'm truly sorry about
what happened to Vince.
Because I know what he meant to you.
But this was his call.
And he knew what he signed up for.
Wow, you are really bad at apologies.
I'm not here to apologize.
Of course you're not.
I'm here to explain that...
This wasn't all for nothing.
Felicity's been going through
the data that Vince pulled out.
And for the first time...
Dinah, for the first time...
- We have some viable options.
- "Viable options"?
You know, I used to tell Vince
his way of seeking justice
wasn't "viable."
I convinced him to change.
Just how you convinced me.
But you know what, Oliver?
Vince was right.
The only way to bring justice
to this city is with a bullet.
No. Dinah...
I need you to listen to me.
I'm going to make sure
Vince didn't die for nothing.
I'm going to kill
every last one of them.
Starting with Laurel.