My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I am someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Susan Williams.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
Unfortunately, Mayor Queen
doesn't seem to have the first clue
of what's going on
within his own administration.
You give me one month with no attacks.
- Let me show you what I can do.
- One month.
- What's this?
- My personal cell.
- Why would I need that?
- I think you can figure it out.
- What are you doing in Russia?
- I'm here to kill Konstantin Kovar.
Tell me if you can get me close to him.
All right. But the only way will kill you.
I have no family. I have no home.
I have no name.
You got much worse coming.
He calls himself Prometheus,
and he's gonna end you.
You want the Green Arrow.
I can give you his name.
It's Oliver Queen.
What's the status on Church's cell phone?
It's holding still
at Aparo and Puckett.
This is one well-traveled phone
considering its owner was killed
on the other side of town last week.
Prometheus is trying to bait me.
Yeah. That's the general point
I was trying to convey.
And also that this is probably a trap.
You should've let me
call in the rest of the team.
- No.
- Why?
Because it's probably a trap.
We've got this, Overwatch.
Who is this?
It's a lot of trouble to go to
for a prank.
"And so it begins"?
Who knew Prometheus was
a Babylon 5 fan-boy?
Don't judge until you've seen it.
- So what begins, that's the question?
- That's a good point.
It would seem like he's already started,
considering he's dropped two bodies.
I get killing Conahan, he led the ACU team
to help the Green Arrow
rescue the city councilmen.
- But why take out Church?
- According to Detective Malone
it's because Church got in between
Prometheus and his real target.
- The Green Arrow.
- Yes.
So Church goes after you,
Prometheus goes after Church, and shunk!
What? That was my
throwing star sound effect.
- Why? What does yours sound like?
- I just don 't understand,
a person that leaves a trail of dead cops
just to kill a guy who's after you
because he wants to kill you himself.
Well, I'll say it again.
It's serious enough to warrant telling
the rest of the recruits.
Who? Curtis and three people
we barely know?
One of which gave up your identity
to Church,
who we can only pray didn't share
that information with Prometheus.
Well, for the record,
Rene didn't "give up" Oliver's identity.
Okay? He was tortured.
That's exactly
why we have to keep them out of this.
I don't wanna put the recruits
in harm's way
until we know exactly what it is
we're dealing with.
Okay, once your wire is attached... Good.
Now take the other one
and attach to battery
and the other one to the igniter.
I failed chemistry in high school.
- Twice.
- Then learn like I did, in,
- how you say, school of hard knock?
- I don't see the point of this.
I'm here in Russia
to take out Konstantin Kovar.
Not to learn how to make a bomb.
You must be like sponge, Oliver.
Making bomb, working with electronics,
welding metal.
Bratva spend off hours
learning many trade.
Fine.
Attach one into igniter,
other one to battery terminal.
Careful, do not touch circuit board.
Oops.
Get back!
It's okay, Oliver.
First time I try, I nearly lose finger.
What the hell was that?
Declaration of war against Bratva.
- By who?
- Your friend.
Kovar.
I'm proud of our new zoning ordinance.
Along with the work
that's being done by the ACU.
Our citizens need to feel safe,
but they also need homes and jobs.
Thank you for joining us.
I, uh, overslept.
- What're you gonna do? Dock my pay?
- No, no, it's just...
It's not the first time
it's happened this week.
Is there something you wanna tell me?
If that's code for
"are you still drinking"
then my answer hasn't changed
since the last 50 times you asked me.
What the hell's he doing talking with her?
It was his idea.
She rakes him over the coals
about making me deputy mayor,
- and now he gives her an interview?
- I think we're done.
For all accounts, she's actually
going pretty easy on him.
Great.
- Thanks for taking the time.
- Thank you for giving me a chance
to explain my side of the issues.
Well, I said I'd give you a month
without any negative headlines.
Clock's ticking.
And it's ticking on the other thing, too.
Right, um, the...
Tick-tock, Mr. Mayor.
Ready?
You were not actually flirting
with that woman.
She can literally ruin your career.
I haven't done anything yet.
- Wow.
- I hate that he just said "yet."
Okay, come on.
There's something I wanna show you.
- What is this?
- This is a music and arts festival.
Seattle's been hosting one for decades.
I mean, they are great for publicity,
and tourism, tax revenue...
Except, revenue is what you're gonna need
to pull that off and we don't have revenue
- to pull that off.
- Yes, we do, because
the mayor's chief of staff
is a former nightclub owner.
And all the right people
still owe me the right favors, so...
I mean, I may not be able to get
all of these bands there,
but enough to draw a crowd.
Well, Speedy, this is, this is good work.
Well, I... I still need a venue.
Let's put together a list, I'll make
whatever calls you need me to make.
Okay.
Actually, I might have an "in"
at the Rockets Arena.
Deputy Mayor Lance.
Hold off on giving me keys to the city.
I just know a guy.
I'm just trying to do
whatever I can to help.
Thank you.
Please... Please...
Take whatever you want! Just don't...
I have two children.
Could we get the room for a minute?
Neat trick. Must come in handy when
you lock yourself out of your place.
I'm Adrian Chase. I'm the new D.A.
I thought crime scenes
were below a D.A.'s pay grade.
I'm not that kind of D.A.
What's your excuse for being here?
Radio call mentioned the murder weapon.
Like Church and Lieutenant Conahan.
What do you have on the victim?
Gay Eked.
Divorced mother of two.
And before you ask,
her ex has an airtight alibi
and Mrs. Eked's criminality
is limited to three parking tickets.
What do you know that I don't?
The killer calls himself Prometheus.
And why would this Prometheus
target an average housewife?
Another body just dropped.
Another throwing star murder.
Peter Meld, 38, cab driver.
He was killed
while filling his taxi up with gas.
Oliver's headed to the crime scene now.
Okay. Any connection
between Meld and Gay Eked?
Just the same M.O.,
killed by a throwing star.
Hmm.
You know, Felicity, it sure would be nice
to get our hands on one.
Yeah.
What?
- Why're you looking at me like that?
- I'm not the one dating
- a detective.
- Oh. No. Well, Billy doesn't know
that I work with the Green Arrow.
I'm not crazy about overlapping
my work and personal lives.
And even if I was, what am I
supposed to do, steal it off his desk?
Felicity, you're one of the
smartest people I know.
I'm sure you'll think of something.
Four bodies so far. Let's do
whatever we can to make sure
- it doesn't become number five.
- Ah, that sounds like an argument
in favor of looping in the recruits.
When there's a reason to, we will.
This is the reason, we should do it now.
- What'd you find?
- Nothing but the victim's blood.
No fibers, no shards, no prints.
So how the hell
are we supposed to find this guy?
Apparently, we're not.
Oh. You do not look happy.
Is it because I'm not bearing Americanos?
- No, it's not the coffee, it's a case.
- The throwing star killings?
Kind of hard to miss.
Although apparently this guy didn't.
Oh. That was unexpectedly morbid. Coffee?
Which actually brings me to why I'm here,
not the coffee, the morbidness.
I was friends with one of the victims
in your case.
Well, more like, acquaintances.
You know. Friend of a friend of a friend.
Is this the, uh, same "friend"
whose housekeeper got their towel stolen?
It wasn't a towel, it was a rag, and no.
- Totally different friend.
- Wow.
Another friend involved
in a random crime in the city.
Ooh.
You must run in
a pretty rough crowd.
You have no idea.
I'd have a better one
if you'd just cut the crap
and tell me whatever it is
you're not telling me.
What? There's no deception here.
I actually was, kind of, sort of,
friends with a victim,
- Gay Eked.
- "Kind of, sort of"?
Pike wants us in his office.
- We'll talk later.
- Uh...
Okay. So, we've got
a problem with your girlfriend.
- Who?
- Susan Williams.
Detective William Malone, who is believed
to be in charge of the investigation,
- could not be reached for comment.
- This is a disaster.
Nor has SCPD issued a statement
on the matter.
But it is believed that this
"Throwing Star Killer" is responsible
for a total of four deaths so far,
including that of reputed crime lord
- Tobias Church.
- "Throwing Star Killer"?
You have to admit it has a certain flair.
I don't need
to be the one to tell you
that having a city-wide panic
is, like, the worst thing
- that can happen before this festival.
- No, Thea.
You don't have to tell me that.
Anatoly? Why didn't you tell me
that Kovar was making a move
against the Bratva?
You know he's the reason
that I'm here in the first place.
I told you, Kovar has army.
Who did you think his enemy was?
You told me I could get at Kovar
by joining the Bratva.
It looks like
you are going to get your chance.
Well, Pakhan is going to be here
any moment. He'll explain everything.
Tidy yourself up, show him your respect.
Ah. The puppy speaks.
The infamous Oliver Queen. What?
Did you think that we would
not learn of your past?
That we would allow rich American
into this organization
without special circumstances?
- I've earned my place here.
- So I hear.
So why don't you tell me
what the hell is going on!
Oliver, respect.
It's okay, Anatoly. Hmm.
I appreciate his eagerness.
Kovar decided to expand his territory.
A casino. What happened here tonight
is warning for us to stay away.
- But we're not going to do that.
- So what are we gonna do?
Kovar needs money to expand.
Investors. Like, say a rich American.
- Come on.
- Uh-huh.
You can get meeting with his people.
When you do, you're gonna get inside
and you're going to blow
his new casino up.
And you thought making bomb
was waste of time.
What do you say, Oliver?
Ready to play
a rich American playboy again?
Your new girlfriend certainly knows
how to whip a city into a frenzy.
- Excuse me.
- Thea might've mentioned something about
- you dating Susan Williams.
- I'm not dating Susan Williams.
Did the person that you're dating
actually give you that?
No.
- I might've stolen it off his desk.
- Are you kidding...
I generally don't kid about something that
could get me 10 years at Iron Heights.
- Well, I hope it was worth it.
- Yeah, so far, not so much.
And here I was just so happy Curtis got
our gas chromatograph working again.
I'm hoping to have better luck with this.
I've plugged the four victims
into an algorithm that ViCAP uses
to track serial killers. The computer can
tease out connections between the victims
- that the FBI generally doesn't make.
- Well, that's smart.
And I cross-referenced in our own database
along with SCPD's to hopefully
get better results.
- What is that?
- News alert.
Reports are just coming in that someone
spotted the Throwing Star Killer
at an outdoor shopping mall,
inciting widespread panic
that is threatening to spill into nearby
streets and homes.
Well, I hope your new girlfriend
is happy with herself.
Let's call the team
and have them meet me there.
- All of them?
- All of them.
They deserve to know
that this has escalated.
And stop calling Susan Williams
my girlfriend.
Yes, sir.
Who the hell are those guys?
They're just shooting into the dark.
GREEN ARROW". It's because they're scared.
Prometheus probably
isn't even here.
Our job here is to keep the peace.
Me, Spartan and Ragman
will handle the shooters.
Everyone else get people to safety.
Why's Ragman get to have all the fun?
Because I said so.
I'll never get tired of this part.
Oh, no! Make it stop. Please.
You're safe with us, okay? Come with me.
You saved us. Thank you.
It's okay.
That's it. Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Slow down. Slow down. Slow down.
Hey, man, you all right?
I got you. Let's get out of here.
You're safe. Come on.
There's no threat here. Go home.
He's up there! Get behind me!
The killer isn't here. You're safe. Go.
Move. Move. Now. Now! Go. Go!
Put your weapon down!
I've got a right to protect myself.
- Hey, that's my property!
- Not anymore.
The Throwing Star Killer isn't here.
All you are doing is causing panic.
Go home. Now.
This is the SCPD.
Please return to your homes.
Well, if Prometheus wanted to
push the public into a frenzy,
mission accomplished.
Well, I'm guessing
we're not gonna like his encore either.
I will stop helping.
We need to canvass the city.
Felicity can coordinate.
We need to help the SCPD maintain order.
- Hold up a sec.
- More, like, back up. Way up.
Yeah, tonight's the first we're hearing
of a serial killer operating in the city.
He calls himself Prometheus.
He's the one who killed Tobias Church.
Did you know about this?
He knew about this.
Why didn't we know about this?
You know about him now.
So let's get to work.
These throwing star killings
are some kind of message
that Prometheus is sending to Oliver.
He's calling him out.
Sounds like, and I'm guessing,
you and blondie have known
about this a while.
- Yeah, that's not insulting at all.
- Evelyn, this isn't about feelings
or ego. We had to vet the situation.
He means the A-Team had to make
sure the B-Team was worthy enough
of being kept in the loop.
All right,
the only team here is Team Arrow.
I actually agree with you guys.
But the whole city is going
- nutso crazy right now so...
- She's right.
- There's plenty of time for this later.
- Except for Curtis.
I need your brain
on this victimology algorithm.
- Sir.
- Victimology algorithm.
This is just like Zodiac.
And I'm Jake Gyllenhaal.
- Wait, wouldn't you be...
- Don't take this from me.
Ollie, where are you?
This place is going through
five kinds of hell right now.
What do we have?
You guys, uh, think you wanna
clear the room for us?
Seriously, bro?
Felicity and Curtis found
something, we wanna know what it is.
Yeah, we're a team. Or at least we were.
- Fine. What do we have?
- At first, not much of anything.
No links between home addresses,
personal histories, favorite colors, nada.
So the victimology algorithm moved on
to crazy Zodiac Killer kind of stuff.
Such as looking for anagrams.
In case Prometheus was sending a message
in the names of the victims
he's been choosing.
- Is he?
- Kind of.
The first four victims, Tobias Church,
Sam Conahan, Peter Meld, Gay Eked.
Victims three and four
were not random.
We think Prometheus is using those names
as anagrams to spell out other names.
Adam Hunt. Ted Gaynor.
Palmer Cokes. Sachi Beech.
Those names supposed to
mean anything to us?
They do to him.
Care to enlighten?
Those names are on the list.
What the hell is the list?
Let me get this straight,
you got a "to kill" list?
- And I'm the out of control one?
- I haven't used that list,
I haven't looked at it in four years.
Wait. Four years, I thought
there was some other guy in the hood?
No, that was Oliver. "The Hood,"
"The Arrow," "Green Arrow," all him.
That notebook belonged to my father.
And when I was first starting out,
I thought that it was my way
to save the city.
Well, I think we now know the message
Prometheus is trying to send.
You do? 'Cause, I don't. Do you guys?
He's saying you're the serial killer.
Harsh.
- But feeling pretty accurate.
- I was trying to help this city.
Prometheus isn't.
You convinced me to not get revenge
on Ruvé Darhk
for my parents because killing would
tarnish the Black Canary's legacy.
How are you anything
other than a hypocrite?
First, it would've tarnished her legacy.
Second, you knew that I was a killer
when you came on board.
Not a serial killer.
I know some of these names.
You've got bankers in here.
Lawyers. A city councilman.
You need to anagram the names on the list
against Star City's population.
Because that should point us
towards Prometheus' next targets.
I know it's not much to look at now,
but with your investment,
we can make it a premier
destination in the area.
No, look, as long as you have craps
in here. Right? I am awesome at craps.
You gotta fill this place with girls.
- Tons of girls.
- I'm sure you will be very pleased.
All of your requests will be accommodated.
I'm convinced, but my associate
Would like to see the blueprints just
to make sure you're all buttoned up, yeah?
Here you are.
I can have copies sent to your hotel.
But first...
Yes.
- You want to see the money.
- Not to be rude, but, yes.
That's fine. That's fine.
Show the man the money.
This will do just fine, Mr. Queen.
If you don't mind my asking,
why you have not returned home?
Supposedly you're a big deal.
All right. We wanna set the charges
there and there.
For maximum damage. What?
You play, what's American term,
"douche" very well.
Let's get this over with.
What?
Quentin?
Are you home?
- What're you doing...
- God!
What're you doing? What are you...
What, are you trying
to kill me or something?
Where the hell have you been?
The whole city is in crisis.
Well, yeah, my stomach's been
on a tear since lunch. l...
It must have been some fish.
It was the fish. It was the damn fish.
Yeah. Probably didn't wash down
well with all the whiskey.
When did you relapse?
You didn't... You...
You've been drinking the whole time.
You lied to me.
Well, I'm a drunk, Thea.
That's what we do.
- Yeah, okay. I'm taking you to a meeting.
- Hmm.
You can't help a man
who doesn't wanna be helped.
Watch me.
Lam not giving up on you.
And I'm not letting you give up
on yourself.
I don't think that
his deputy mayor
being seen at an A.A. meeting
is exactly what your brother needs
right now.
The second "A"
stands for "anonymous," right?
What the hell is this thing?
Oh, um, thanks. What is this?
Regan family schnapps recipe.
It's strong and a little sweet.
Just like you. I thought we could use some
considering the circumstances.
- Would you care for some?
- Um, Rory, she's 17.
So? My dad was giving me this stuff
when I was 11.
And what a fine weirdo
you turned out to be. Mmm.
Mmm.
Look, if this little meeting is
because we learned Oliver's a killer,
I've got news for you, it's not news.
Look, killing Damien Darhk,
and Church's guys is one thing.
But having a secret kill list...
Yeah, that he never even told us about.
It's something completely different.
Well, what's not different
is him not telling us stuff.
Haven't you noticed when it comes to
information sharing,
there seems to be two different teams?
It's only gotten worse
since Diggle's been back.
Make up your mind, guys, are you pissed
because Oliver killed people
or that he doesn't tell us everything?
How about both?
How about I'm pissed that the guy
who only shares the important information
with his inner circle
used to be a serial killer?
Which again, he didn't tell us about.
Look,
we all want to believe
in Oliver's crusade.
But how are we
supposed to follow him into a battle
when his first instinct
is to hide the truth from us?
First it's "I used to be a serial killer."
What's tomorrow's revelation going to be?
I don't know how to operate
with that in the back of my mind.
Wow, haven't seen you do that
in quite some time.
I wanted
to take my mind off things.
Yeah. I don't think they make
enough tennis balls for that.
Where's Felicity
with the list of potential targets?
She's working on it. It's a big city.
Yeah.
Something tells me,
that's not the only thing weighing on you.
- How are the recruits?
- Taking a little time out.
I expected them to be upset
with me and that's fine. But...
John, they seemed horrified.
No, I wouldn't call it that.
Just a bit surprised.
Look on the bright side,
it does show how far you've come.
I haven't seen that guy in a long time.
And the way the kids reacted...
I think it proves how much you've changed.
Except I haven't.
I killed Damien Darhk,
and I haven't stopped since.
Yeah, well, don't forget
who you're talking to, man.
I know, first hand,
what it's like to be a murderer.
I know the difference
between a good kill
and one made out of pure rage.
You killed Damien Darhk, Oliver,
because you had to.
You took down Church's men,
The list was something different.
You were targeting lawyers, stockbrokers.
You were killing as a first resort,
not a last.
And now Prometheus is just
dredging all that up again.
I wanna move forward.
I'm trying to move forward. But I...
- I feel stuck.
- I think you're being hard on yourself.
Which is a bit annoying because
that's usually mine and Felicity's job.
But, Oliver, in that official capacity,
I think you are moving forward.
I think you're evolving.
I think you're growing.
What makes you so sure?
Because that guy with the list
wouldn't have even thought
to ask the question.
I need a cleanup on Aisle 12.
And, also,
I got a list of potential victims.
I know you're all upset with me.
So, thank you for showing up despite that.
Well, we were afraid you would kill us
if we didn't.
- Too soon? Okay.
- I was able to cross-reference the list
with the city census,
nailing it down to six potential targets.
How do we know who he'll hit?
We don't. In order to cover
that much ground,
we have to split up
and each take one potential target.
We run surveillance. Whoever spots
Prometheus first, call it in.
Then we all converge.
Cool.
- Is everything okay?
- No. It's not.
For a long time, I blamed you
for my parents dying.
That you were responsible
for leaving them to suffocate
in one of Damien Darhk's
testing chambers.
- I know.
- It took a lot
for me to come work with you.
Knowing all this,
it doesn't make it any easier.
Evelyn, are you sure
you should be out there tonight?
Yes, lam.
Because I'm doing this,
protecting people, for me.
Not for you.
- I've got eyes on Target Number Four.
- Copy that.
You know, it seems we have a minute alone,
- is there anything you want to talk about?
- No.
Are you sure? 'Cause I'm kind of an expert
when it comes to finding out
ugly things about Oliver's past.
Actually, I'm the...
I'm the leading expert.
- Overwatch?
- Yeah?
I really don't want to talk about it.
Oh, my God.
Get back!
- The hell?
- Get out of here! Go call 911!
Stay away from him!
- Go.
- We've got a problem.
Artemis seems to have
disconnected her coms.
She in trouble?
I don't know, but I'm worried
she wouldn't tell us if she was.
Do you have her 20?
When Wild Dog was kidnapped,
I put trackers in all their suits.
I'm sending you the information now.
- She's moving.
- She's on a subway that's moving.
Train's a few blocks from here.
I'll go check on her.
You tell everyone else to hold
their position.
Hey... Hey... Come on, man.
Come on, please!
- You okay?
- Yeah. What the hell was that?
Stop the train.
He'!-
- You all right?
- I wasn't going to be.
Prometheus?
- Gone.
Whatever he's planning,
it wasn't to engage me tonight.
Hey, we got a problem.
- We got a big problem.
- What?
I don't have time to disarm that.
We're getting off the train. Come on.
You're joking, right? 'Cause now's a
really bad time to be trying out jokes.
Trust me.
Good as new.
What's gonna happen to the train guy?
This morning, Mayor Queen is gonna
put him and Prometheus' five other targets
into witness protection
until this is over.
Won't Prometheus just
find another way to go after you?
Probably.
But when he does, we will deal with it.
And, I promise, you will find out
right when I do.
I was a jerk.
And I'm sorry.
No, Evelyn, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for your parents.
I'm sorry that I'm not the man
you thought I was.
But John reminded me, as he does,
that I'm trying to be that man.
And I might actually be getting there.
Slowly.
In the meantime,
I would really appreciate your patience.
Sounds reasonable to me.
When I was a boy
my mother told me
a story about her grandfather.
She said he grew a turnip so large
that he could not pull it up by himself.
So he asked his wife to help,
but together they could not do it.
So they asked my uncle,
my aunts, everybody to pitch in, but...
Yet they could not pull the turnip
out of the ground.
And so I said,
"Mama, Mama,
"did he ever pull the turnip
out of the ground?"
And she said, "Yes.
"But only...
"Only after they called everybody
in the village."
Every man, woman and child.
Every farmer, every Vagabond.
Every animal even.
The dogs and the cats.
And finally, together,
they wrestled it free.
Does your story have a point?
Yes.
That without unity
one cannot accomplish anything in life.
As I got older, I realized it also meant
something else.
That scum
will never amount to anything
without help.
That the Solntsevskaya Bratva
can pull at the turnip all they want.
But they will never, ever,
ever
set it free.
Oh.
Yes, that and, uh...
To become a damn farmer.
Hello,
Oliver Queen.
My name is Konstantin Kovar.
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
Hey.
Oh, so, to what latest crime or criminal
do I owe the pleasure of this visit?
I thoroughly deserve that.
Is there somewhere private we can go chat?
Step into my office.
Oh, yes, the interrogation room.
How appropriate.
Felicity, I was just giving you
a hard time.
I figure whenever you're ready to tell me
whatever's going on with you,
you'll tell me.
I'm gonna tell you now.
I have this friend.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Who I just watched for the umpteenth
time not tell the people
he's closest to what is going on with him.
I don't want to be like that.
I don't want you to be like that.
So, what is it, are you,
like, a serial killer?
Or something? The Throwing Star Killer?
A true crime groupie?
I've got a million scenarios running
through my mind. Like, you're...
I work for the Green Arrow.
That wasn't one of 'em.
It's why I keep odd hours and
why I disappear at random times.
And it's why I keep asking you
for favors,
and in case you haven't noticed,
it's why I stole evidence off your desk.
You know, I looked everywhere for that.
It goes without saying that me
being like a criminal
probably isn't good for our relationship.
But you're not like a criminal, Felicity.
You are one.
But it's for a good cause.
Seriously? Are you not, like, mad?
Or hurt? Or feeling a lack of trust?
I'd be a jerk if I did.
Felicity,
you're helping save this city.
Wow, that went a lot better
than I expected.
I just got so many questions.
Do you know where he lives?
Is his face all scarred or something?
- Is that why he wears a hood?
- Billy, Billy, Billy.
Shut up.
Yes, ma'am.
- Thanks for putting this together, Speedy.
- I can't take all the credit.
- Lance did come up with the venue.
- Shouldn't he be here?
Oh... Yeah. He came down with that flu
that everyone's been catching,
- so he just decided to sit this one out.
- Oh. Hey!
Well, if it isn't my favorite chief
of staff. How are you doing?
Still not interested.
Ooh. It's cool, man.
Nobody saw you get completely shot down.
You know, 'cause we did see you get...
- Everything looks really nice, Mr. Mayor.
- Thank you, Curtis.
Yeah, I can't remember the last time
I saw a concert. Or danced.
- Or smiled apparently.
- Okay.
Come on, Rory. Just follow our lead.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Can I talk to you privately?
Yeah. Give us a second please, guys.
- What's going on?
- You remember the throwing star
that I stole from my boyfriend. From...
My... From Malone? You remember the...
You remember this?
You said it didn't turn anything up.
- Pretty sure I used the word "yet."
- Okay. So, now?
The alloy is very specific,
with trace quantities
containing dozens of different
genetic markers.
And I was able to nail
the forensic evidence down
- to coming within the past four years.
- What're you trying to tell me?
This is gonna sound crazy,
but so is Prometheus.
I think that Prometheus has gotten
his hands on the various arrows
you've used over the past four years,
melted them down
and fashioned weapons out of them.
But if that's true,
that would mean that...
That would mean that Prometheus
has access to SCPD lockup.
Oliver, I think we have a real lead
on who Prometheus is.
He's a member of the SCPD.