Previously, on "Arrow"
and "Flash"...
Thanks, mister.
Yeah.
Barry said that
you need our help.
Somebody very
dangerous is after you.
Give her to me and I'll
make your death fast.
The man you're looking for
is Vandal Savage.
An immortal.
Chay-Ara,
it's me, Khufu.
We're drawn to each
other in each life,
and after we die,
we reincarnate.
Do you know who
Vandal Savage is?
In every lifetime,
he hunts us down.
We think he's trying
to locate the Staff of Horus.
I'm never going to become
who I really am unless I let go.
No!
Chay-Ara.
Price Khufu, my son.
What have you come
to offer?
Father, we bring
this tribute
to the protector to all
we see and know, Horus.
Praise be upon him.
It is a fine
offering, Khufu.
At least worthy
of a God.
And yet,
priestess Chay-Ara
does not seem to agree.
Your offering is
lovely, my prince.
If not a bit naive.
Naive?
To think that Horus
would be appeased by...
trifles.
The portents of his
dissatisfaction
grow with each
passing day.
The celestial rocks used to fall
once a generation;
now they strike
with each phase of the moon.
I thought it was your job
to keep Horus in a good mood...
Priestess.
Priestess Chay-Ara
only speaks out of concern for all.
Otherwise, she would
remain a bit more...
Polite.
We have warned you time
and again of the sky rocks
and the threat
they pose to the court
of Ramses the Wise.
Dark times are coming, my pharaoh.
Prayers and trifles will
not be enough to stop it.
Priestess.
You spoke with quite
the tongue in there.
Did I overact?
No. I love your tongue.
You ok?
Yeah, I'm fine,
I just have a headache.
Are you sure?
Usually that's a sign
of your memories
returning.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I can't remember
anything yet.
A bunch of superheroes
in a farmhouse?
I feel like I've seen that
in a movie before.
We need
a secure location.
What's wrong
with S.T.A.R. Labs?
Well, I mean, absolutely nothing
if you forget about
the revolving door
you guys installed
so the bad guys can come and go
as they please.
Remind me again
what happened to your old lair,
or the one before that.
Well, lair number
one was compromised by the police,
and...
I will stop helping.
Savage only let
Barry and I live
because he felt Kendra start to
emerge as Hawkgirl and went after her.
He can sense
her and Carter's presence.
We don't need to make it easier on him
by staying in the city limits.
Bet you wish you were
staying at your mother's place now.
We need to find a way
to neutralize
Savage's advantage.
Barry, you're late.
Sorry. It turns out, it's not easy
finding the ass end of nowhere.
Yeah, for real.
The roaming charges alone
are going to bankrupt me.
We're discussing
how to take away
Savage's newfound power.
And his magic stick thing.
Yeah, Staff of Horus.
Well, it's protected
by some kind of energy field.
I couldn't lay
a finger on it.
Maybe you wear
mittens next time.
What if we made some sort
of insulated gauntlets...
Oh, yeah, yeah, the magnetic shielding
could disrupt the--
The staff's magnetic polarity.
Well, while
the geek squad works--
Heard that, honey.
While they work to get
the staff away from Savage,
we need to know everything
there is to know about him.
Well, I googled
reincarnated nut jobs
and came up
with nothing.
Kendra and I would
be the reincarnated nut jobs.
Savage is
merely immortal.
Merely?
Welcome to the new normal.
Anyone who's been around for 4,000 years
should leave a trail.
I'll check with A.R.G.U.S., see if they
have anything on him.
Laurel and I can check police reports
and stuff like that.
Good. We need
to find a way to utilize
your new ability.
My ability?
It might give us
an advantage.
Yeah, whatever you do,
don't let him train you.
I'm sorry,
but when it rains,
I can still feel where he shot me
with those arrows.
I'll handle her training, then.
Yeah.
Oliver.
Uh, I need to run
something down.
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
And what exactly
are you running down?
Don't worry,
it's nothing dangerous.
Well, are you ok?
Well, we're up against an
immortal mad man
armed with
a magical staff,
so I do have a few
things on my mind.
Yeah, but you were
acting fine with everything
while we were home,
and now that we're here
in Central City,
you've just been not...you.
Well, maybe it's too
bright and sunny for me here.
There is something
going on,
and I am going
to tell you all about it.
I would just like the chance to know
what I'm dealing with first.
Ok.
Hey!
You must be going
through a lot right now.
Yeah. You know,
we should talk.
Never in the history of romance have
those words ever meant anything good.
I just mean we
should probably talk
about everything
that's happened--
that's happening.
You know what,
I'm going to suggest
something radical here
and say let's not talk.
Look, you've got a lot
on your plate right now.
And I just don't want to be that piece
of very nutritious broccoli
that you scrape off the plate
to give to the dog.
My point being,
I don't think you can afford
to be distracted
right now.
Let's go.
Yes.
Let's.
Sorry, buddy,
this is private.
Private?
Yep.
I'm just going to go do some
push-ups over there.
Open it.
Why? What's inside?
Something we have to track down
in each of our incarnations.
Sometimes I find it;
Sometimes you find me
and we go look
for it together.
4,000 years, 206 lives.
We've seen about every
combination there is.
I don't think
I'm really--
Ready for this.
You say that
in every lifetime.
Look, as you emerge,
as your memories come back to you,
so will other things.
Skills, languages,
pieces of your private life.
Katalavaíneis?
Déchomai.
There you go.
This is nuts.
It's ok.
I'll help you through it.
Yeah, well, the last
time you helped me,
I got pushed
off a building.
Yes, and after that,
you, uh, you soared,
if I remember
correctly.
And that is
because anger, fear,
adrenaline--those
are the things
that bring out
the warrior within.
Well, according to Savage,
I'm a priestess.
The clergy
were warriors.
Warrior priests,
and that is the side that you
need to remember.
And if I can't?
Well, then, we'll both
probably die.
Again.
It's your turn.
All right,
let's not be late.
You all set?
There you go.
Oliver?
Hi!
Uh, hold on one second.
What are you doing here?
So sorry to just
drop by unannounced.
I came to town
the other day,
and I saw you
with your son.
William.
William?
That's a nice name.
Oliver, what are you
doing at my house?
I saw you
and William together,
and it's difficult
not to wonder,
because he is,
what, nine?
And you know, we had a thing
10 years ago...
Ok, let me stop you right there.
All right.
William isn't yours.
I told you I lost
our baby, Oliver,
and I met William's father two months
after moving to Central City.
So...
Mom, we're going
to miss the game.
Sorry, I have to go.
No, go.
Ok.
Oh, here you are.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Wish William good luck for me,
all right?
I will.
Now's not a good
time, Malcolm.
I've arranged a meeting
with Vandal Savage.
You, me,
and the speedster.
What? Wait, why--
Because negotiation
is the only way out
of this situation,
Oliver.
Savage is going
to decimate Central City
to get what he wants.
If your child were here,
you would understand.
Suit up. I've already
spoke with fleet feet,
he's on his way.
Thank you for coming.
I know this is more
than a little crazy.
Yeah, well, your friend
with the creepy ring asked so nicely.
Please tell me we're
not going to negotiate with terrorists.
Or, you know, 4,000
year old bad guys.
Just think of this more
as a fact-finding mission.
Maybe Savage slips up
and gives us something
that we can use
to our advantage.
Thea said you were
being a little more humorous lately.
I'm sorry, how do
you know so much
about Savage,
anyway?
I don't know anything
about him,
Mr. Allen. No one does.
That is why
I'm afraid of him.
That's not the only reason
to be afraid of me.
I assure you.
♪ Arrow 4x08 ♪
Legends of Yesterday
Original Air Date on December 2, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Thank you for joining me.
What do you want?
What all living
things want--
not to die.
I thought that wasn't a problem
for you.
Only if I take the lifeforce
from Prince Khufu
and Priestess Chay-Ara.
Kendra and Carter.
The three of us are locked
in a vicious circle
played out over
thousands of years.
None of your concern.
We've made it
our concern.
Robin of Locksley.
I taught him how
to use a bow.
He taught me how
to not feel pain.
I'm the enemy
you can't defeat.
The only way for you and yours
to live through this
is to render onto me
what is mine.
Turn over Prince Khufu
and Princess Chay-Ara
within 24 hours,
or I will lay waste
to this city,
killing everyone
that you hold dear.
And after that, I will
travel to your home,
and do the same thing there.
All right,
I'm just curious--
did you rehearse
that speech
in a mirror
this morning,
or this all
just off the cuff?
Why would you
risk the lives
of your friends and family
for two strangers?
206 times I have killed him.
What hubris possesses you
that makes you think that you can
prevent me from doing so again?
Not hubris.
Hope.
I came to this meeting
out of curiosity.
It is now sated.
Bring Khufu and Chay-Ara to
Jurgens Industrial in twenty-four hours
or I will see you
dead and buried
under the bodies
of your loved ones.
We're not giving up
Kendra and Carter.
That's not
your decision to make.
This is a cycle
that has played out
for the last 4,000 years.
Savage may be immortal,
but he isn't a God.
No, but he's
the next best thing.
Oliver!
What?!
You better be certain
that your stubbornness
does not get
my daughter killed.
Because if that happens,
I will come for you.
And in a way that will
make you beg
for the likes
of Vandal Savage.
24 hours.
Until what?
Until we are supposed
to hand you and Carter
over to Savage, or--
Savage lays waste
to Central City.
Yeah.
We've been through this before.
1887, the Huang he floods,
Savage killed nearly
two million people
to get to us.
And he did.
We weren't helping you then.
We are now.
We have 24 hours to come up
with a workable plan.
No, this is insane.
My life isn't worth millions
of people's lives.
Kendra.
I'll talk to her.
Yeah.
Hey, I got this.
I said,
I'll talk to her.
Hey, here's an idea--
why don't we just toss him
over to Vandal Savage?
Where were you?
Hey.
You missed the whole,
save the city
or turn my girlfriend over t
an immortal psychopath briefing.
Yeah, sorry.
Um, dude, last night, I, um,
I ghosted.
No.
Yeah, I think
I'm going--
Don't say it.
I think I'm going
to time jump.
I just told you
not to say it!
I'm sorry. I don't know what else
I'm supposed to do.
The first rule of time travel is you
don't talk about time travel!
Because by having this conversation,
we're screwing history!
Look, I know that time travel
has consequences.
I mean, the last
time you vibed--
Well, I'm not vibing
anything right now.
Okay, um, all right,
look, don't panic.
A., you don't know that you
time jumped for a bad reason.
It could have been
a good one, right?
B., now that you know
you time jumped,
you might not
do it, right?
So knowing the future might
change the present,
which might
change the future.
What?
My head hurts.
Chay-Ara--sorry, Kendra--
you shouldn't run off.
We don't know is Savage is--
Do we ever
kill ourselves?
Excuse me?
In our prior lives.
Savage has to kill us in order
to live forever.
Do we ever kill ourselves in order
to deny him that?
You know,
in our past lives,
I'm typically the one
that makes the plans,
and I'm starting
to think
this is probably why.
Everyone in there
is willing to die to protect us.
You don't think
that's a little bit insane?
No.
I think it's noble.
I think it's what makes
them all heroes.
Yeah, well, heroes or not,
I'm not letting anyone
die for me.
Then don't.
Be the person,
the woman,
the warrior you were
meant to be.
The one you always
have been.
Come at me.
What?
Hit me.
Or...try to.
Yeah, well, as much
as I'd like to do that,
I'm really not
in the mood right now.
Oh, really? Well,
I'll just tell Savage
to come back
when you are.
Ow!
Again.
Ahh! Ahh!
Good.
Do you feel that?
The rage?
That's the key,
Kendra.
It's the only way
of finding
the warrior within.
Hey.
Sorry
to interrupt...
The weirdness.
Um, John,
Laurel,
and Thea are back,
and they've
got something.
Where are
Oliver and Barry?
Oliver's back in secret-keeping
mode, apparently.
Barry, I don't know.
Caitlin and Cisco
are working
on the anti-staff gauntlets.
What do you guys have?
Beta Max. Aww, what,
did you guys get this off of eBay?
Lyla hooked us up.
Yeah, well, it's going
to take a while to play
since we live
in a digital world now.
The tape came from
a conspiracy theory group
that's interested
in Savage.
Pentagon had a file
on Savage back in '86,
but it's all been
heavily redacted.
Got it.
Is this on?
I hope so.
My name is
Dr. Aldus Boardman.
I'm a professor at
St. Roch University.
The date is
April 8th, 1975.
I don't think anyone
else knows this,
and those that do,
don't believe.
He's a myth.
An urban legend.
He has been compared
to Machiavelli and Nostradamus.
He's gone by many names,
but I know him as Vandal Savage,
and he will be
the death of the world.
But I believe there is a way
to stop him.
Savage is an immortal,
Egyptian priest.
His long life
is a result
of an unearthly
calamity.
I believe that any object
associated with this calamity
should be able to undo its effects
and kill him.
And I suspect that our
precious, fragile world
may one day depend
upon us doing so.
Well, that's the understatement
of the year.
Or, you know,
the last 4,000 years.
Do you have any idea
what he meant by these objects?
This calamity?
No, I--I don't
recall a calamity.
The staff.
Staff of Horus?
Yes.
I think the staff
belonged to Savage
back in
ancient Egypt.
You remember?
It's a hunch.
And if Professor Boardman's
guess is right,
that staff has
helped me kill Savage.
Ok, someone needs to inform
Oliver and Barry.
Ok, here you go.
I gene sequenced
the hair strand with the blood
sample you gave me.
Still not sure what it has
to do with Damian Darhk,
but the Y chromosomes match.
Are you ok?
Thanks for this,
it's a big help.
Yeah, well--
Barry.
Yeah?
Don't tell anyone about this.
All right, I'd like to know
what's going on here.
Felicity...
Yes, I tracked you down.
I find people for a living.
Actually, I don't get paid, but--
what was that?
What was what?
You just super-speeded
something into your pocket.
Oh, um, no, nothing.
Um, well,
actually, it's, um,
it's something Oliver wanted me
to track down.
It's, uh, it's about
Damian Darhk--
I want to see it.
Why?
Because you don't
want me to see it.
I'm sorry, Oliver
specifically asked me--
Show me.
Ok...
I don't know what
the big deal is.
It's just a DNA test.
No, it's not.
Honey, why don't you
finish that inside?
Mom, the Flash hasn't
saved the city yet.
Now, honey.
Can we talk?
Look, I don't know
what you're trying
to accomplish here, Oliver.
I know, Samantha.
I know that William
is my son.
Ok...
Why didn't you
tell me?
Ok, just keep
your voice down.
Your mother told me not to.
What?!
She offered me
a million dollars
to tell you that I miscarried.
My mother was
a complicated person,
but she would
never do that.
Wait here.
Here.
I never cashed it.
I didn't need
her money to know
I didn't want her anywhere
near my child.
Or me anywhere near him.
So what, he can be
just like his dad?
Punching out paparazzi
and getting young girls knocked up?
Samantha, I'm not
that person anymore.
I know, I know.
You're--you're running for mayor,
your mother was killed.
Your friend Tommy,
you're a different person now.
But can you
really tell me
that your life
is any less crazy?
Can you honestly
say that William isn't better off
with your world
kept away from his?
No, you're right,
I'm being selfish.
But I want an opportunity
to get to know my son,
and I think that a young boy
deserves the opportunity
to get to know
his father.
He's happy.
He's--he's
well-adjusted.
I don't want to run the risk of him
getting sucked into your orbit.
That can't happen.
Which means...
That he can't know
that you're his father.
And nobody else can.
I don't care
if that sounds harsh.
I'm his mother, and I
will do whatever--
whatever I feel I have
to do to protect him.
Samantha, there is
someone in my life now.
Please, don't make me
keep this from her.
Oliver, you will
if you want
a relationship
with my son.
These are
my conditions.
You've already asked
the world of me,
I'm just asking for
the same in return.
Everyone's
waiting for you.
Sorry, just something
I had to take care of.
So I guess you're off
the secret-keeping wagon.
That's not it.
Then what is it?
I think Damian Darhk has someone
operating in Central City.
So I sent Barry
to run down a lead.
This kind of lead?
He didn't know
what he was giving me.
But I run enough tests
on your blood
to recognize your
DNA sequence anywhere.
Felicity,
you don't...
You had to run
a paternity test, didn't you?
Look, Felicity...
Stop.
I cannot hear another lie.
It's more complicated
than that.
God, Oliver,
you are the only person
on this planet
who considers
the truth complicated.
Just to be clear, I don't care that
you have a child.
I can't believe that
you have a child
that you didn't
tell me about.
I care that you
lied to me just now.
You know that my whole world
just exploded?
And I think that
I'm entitled to a...
A minute to process that
by myself.
You somehow managed
to go to CCPD
and track down Barry.
You didn't keep it to yourself;
you kept it from me.
When were you planning on telling me?
I don't know.
If you loved me,
if you trusted me,
telling me this
wouldn't be such a burden--
it would be
a relief.
But you don't
trust me.
You never will.
And how can I be with someone who
doesn't trust me?
Felicity...
Are you guys ok?
Oliver?
What happened?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Uh, are you sure?
I mean, you don't seem fine.
You seem out of it.
Is everyone inside?
Yeah.
Coming up on
Savage's deadline.
Where's Felicity?
Are the gauntlets
working?
They have to be,
we're out of time.
I think they'll work.
That staff's going to go
from "can't touch this"
to "invisible touch."
Savage doesn't know
Kendra has access to her full abilities,
which makes you
our Ace in the hole.
We're going to put you up
against Savage;
you attack with
the element of surprise.
I will lay down
the cover fire.
Barry, you speed in, and--
Snatch the staff, I got it.
Where
do you need us?
This me, Barry, Kendra
and Carter. We've got it.
Ollie!
No, we're not risking
any more lives tonight
than we have to.
Suit up.
You brought them.
And dressed
for the occasion,
I see.
We're only doing this
because two lives
aren't worth two cities.
Well, in that case, you are wiser than
I gave you credit for.
It's been
a lifetime.
Still wearing those
ridiculous
outfits, I see.
You don't need
to be here for this.
The culling has
a tendency to be...
Unsightly.
Your new friends
betrayed you.
Just do what
you're going to do.
It's wonderful to see you again,
my love.
I will never be your love.
I know.
That always
makes this...
Easier.
Chay-Ara...
Parting is such
sweet sorrow.
Now, Kendra!
Carter!
Ahhh!
I've got it!
The gauntlets
aren't working!
You got to let go, Barry!
No, I'm not
leaving you.
You're fast enough
to get away, go!
Ollie, no.
Run, Barry. Run.
Thank you for coming.
I know this is more
than a little crazy.
I came to this meeting
out of curiosity.
It is now sated.
Bring Khufu and Chay-Ara
to Jurgens Industrial
in 24 hours,
or I will see you
dead and buried under the bodies
of your loved ones.
Barry, you all right?
We need to brief
the team.
Come up with some type of
counter attack.
It's not going to work.
What?
Oof, nothing.
All right, never mind,
I shouldn't have said anything.
Barry, what's going on?
Ok, look,
this isn't going
to make any sense to you,
but I--all right,
so I traveled back in time
from when we tried
to take out Savage.
I mean, later,
when we tried
to take him down in the future,
and it doesn't work.
You're right, that doesn't
make sense to me.
My world is
stranger than yours.
Well, maybe we use that
to our advantage.
You say that whatever do against
Savage doesn't work?
Then we come up
with a new plan.
No. No, no, no.
Ok, look, you can't.
You--when I mess with time,
it just,
it doesn't end well.
But what you're telling me is
that it already doesn't end well.
Barry, people in our line of work,
we don't get second chances.
We need
to take this one.
All right,
I hope you're right.
All right, let's start with
what went wrong.
You did. When we
go up against Savage,
your head's not in the game.
You're not yourself.
Why not?
Oliver...
Barry!
Why not?
Ok, are you planning
on giving me
a hair sample
to run forensics on
in the near future?
Yeah...
Well, I did.
And you were pretty shaken
after the fact.
And then Felicity
found out,
and you guys
had a pretty big fight,
and it sounded like it was over
between you two.
What was the fight about?
I'm pretty sure
you're someone's father, Oliver.
So when we go up
against Savage,
you're not focused.
And then, Kendra can't
access her powers,
and then the tech
they're developing
to counteract Savage's staff
does not work,
and...
Everyone dies,
Oliver.
This time they won't.
This time we do
things differently.
How are they coming?
For my first pair of anti-Gandalf
magic staff gloves,
pretty good, I think.
Just double
and triple check, ok?
I'm a little worried
about them not working.
Based on what?
Call it a gut instinct.
Also, I need you
to talk to Kendra.
Oh, I get it. You shoot arrows,
you give love tips,
it's like you're Cupid
or something.
What Carter is doing
with her isn't working.
We need her power
to fight Savage,
and we need her
to be able to use it reliably.
Carter's a jerk.
But he's supposed to be with her,
'cause destiny says
they're supposed to be together,
and he's supposed
to be her soul mate,
so I'm not even sure
what I can say--
We need to do something,
Cisco. We need to reach her.
Egyptian reincarnation
is not in my wheelhouse.
What Kendra
is going through
is about accepting
who she really is.
Who better to
help her do that
than a guy who is clearly
in love with her?
I don't know if we're at
the L-bomb stage yet.
I'll talk to her.
You don't think that's
a little bit insane?
No, I think
it's noble.
I think it's what makes them
all heroes.
Yeah, that's nice.
I'm going to talk to Kendra
for a minute, He-Man.
Talk, man. Thanks.
We should talk.
I thought you were the one that said
we should wait till this was all over.
Oh, this isn't
that talk.
This is the "trying
to help you sprout wings" talk.
Yeah, well,
according to Carter,
I'm a warrior priestess,
and rage is the key
to rediscovering myself.
Yeah, I'm not surprised
Mr. Agro thinks that,
but I think he's got this whole
thing twisted.
Instead of focusing on the warrior,
focus on the priestess,
and the nurturer,
the good-hearted
person inside of you.
How do you know I was
so good hearted 4,000 years ago?
Because I know you,
Kendra.
Some things
don't change.
I think you're
resisting what
Carter's trying to teach you
because it means
remembering who you
were, and that is somebody else.
Somebody who loves him.
Ever since I emerged,
I've been remembering
our first life,
in Egypt. But I've
been telling Carter
I can't remember
anything, because--
because I don't want to accept that
I'm some reincarnated
Egyptian warrior priestess.
Ok. Yeah, that's
pretty heavy.
But it's also
pretty amazing.
I've been through this,
you know I have.
And what you're going through right
now, this is a gift.
It's a miracle that most people
don't even get to experience.
Yeah, well, it feels
like a nightmare.
Yeah, but that--
that is a choice.
You can choose the other thing
to remember who you are,
or who you were.
Close your eyes.
Just close your eyes.
Let yourself.
Let yourself remember.
Hey, hey, hey, wait.
Stay a little
longer.
I can't.
Hath-Set and I need
to make another offering to Horus.
The augers have said
more sky rocks will be falling soon.
Well, I hear
he covets you.
How fortunate I know
the man who can handle him.
Prince Khufu.
What a surprise
to find you here.
In Chay-Ara's bed chamber.
Surely you must know
that the clergy
is forbidden to lie
with royalty.
Get out.
The penalty for such
a transgression
is death.
I said, get out.
I'm not afraid
of your father.
Soon the sky rocks will
decimate this kingdom
and end his rule.
But first...
I shall know Chay-Ara
as you have known her.
Ahh!
Oh!
It'll be all right.
Look behind you.
Ohh!
The sky rocks have
come to do their work.
And my hate will be
everlasting.
My enmity will never die.
And I'll follow you
from this life to the next,
and to the next
and to the next.
Horus...
Your children need you now.
They need your protection.
Shroud us in your wings.
I will wait...
for eternity.
Come back to me.
No!
What?
What happened?
I think I know
how to beat Vandal Savage.
Oliver, you were right.
I don't know how you knew,
but you were right--
the gauntlets won't work,
they're missing a critical element.
How do you know?
Because I remembered.
I remember how
Savage killed us the first time,
back in Egypt.
I've never been able
to remember our first death.
Well, these sky
rocks--meteors--
they fell and they completely destroyed
the royal palace.
During the Middle Kingdom,
Egypt experienced a high
level of meteor activity.
I know stuff.
Which is one of the many reasons
we love you so much,
but also doesn't
seem to help us stop Savage.
It's the calamity Professor Boardman
was referencing.
The meteors,
they had a glow about them.
And Savage's staff had two gemstones
with the exact same glow.
Yeah, the gemstones
might be made up
of the same element
as the meteorite.
The Egyptians would use
meteorite in their craftsmanship.
And the minerals
glow in proximity to each other.
Like Sankara Stones.
Oh, wait,
the Indiana Jones reference
is the only thing
I understood.
Two pieces of the same
meteorite, like an nth metal...
that is the key
to counter-acting the staff.
Believe it or not, this isn't actually
the craziest thing I've heard today.
There's a sample of the meteorite
from the Middle Kingdom
at the Keystone City Museum of
Natural... History.
Hopefully I got
the right one.
I could synthesize
the compatible isotope
out of this and coat
the gauntlets with it.
Ok. Do it.
Savage doesn't know
that Kendra has gained
access to all of her abilities.
It makes you
our Ace in the hole.
Where do you
need us?
Suit up.
Ollie...
Everyone's in position.
All right.
Are you sure about this?
About changing
the future?
Barry, what can happen here
that is worse than
what already did?
If I knew that,
I wouldn't be so worried.
Let's do it.
It's wonderful to see
you again, my love.
I will never be your love.
I know.
That always makes
this easier.
Chay-Ara...
Parting is such
sweet sorrow.
Ahh!
Now, Kendra!
Get clear!
The gauntlets are working.
No, no, no, Oliver,
get yourself to safety!
We're not leaving each other!
Did we do it?
Is he gone?
Yeah, it looks like.
I knew you
could do it.
I'm having
the strangest deja vu.
You're not the only one.
So how do you feel
now that Savage
is pushing daisies?
Does this mean you guys
are the immortal ones now
and he's the one
who gets reincarnated?
'Cause that would suck.
I just sprouted
wings a few days ago,
and I'm just trying
to wrap my head around that.
He does raise
a good point, though.
Savage is gone
for good now, right?
I don't know.
We never
defeated him before.
But we're free.
Ugh, get a room.
You finally have the rest of your lives
in front of you.
Have you thought about
what you're going to do?
Carter says in
our past lives,
we used
to help people.
And after everything
you guys have done for me,
I think I should
give that a try.
You make it sound like
this try is happening somewhere else?
In our prior incarnation,
we used to live in St. Roch,
and we really liked it there.
Could Cisco and I
have a moment?
Of course.
Here we go.
Cisco...
I'm really sorry.
You know what,
it's fine. It's cool.
It's actually kind of
a classic story--
boy meets girl,
boy gets girl,
girl sprouts wings and flies away
with her reincarnated soul mate.
The only part I don't get is you
don't even really seem to like him.
It's kind of
a complicated relationship.
Hmm.
Like most 4,000 year
old relationships are, I guess.
A week ago,
I was a barista
and I really
didn't have a plan
for what I was going
to do with my life.
And now you do?
Well, at least
I know I want to find out.
Ok.
I made you something.
To remember me by,
I guess.
I made it out
of the nth medal
Barry got
from the meteorite.
It's got a micro GPS
chip embedded in it.
So if you're ever
in trouble,
I'll come find you.
What was that for?
For being you.
Thank you, Cisco.
Well, you did it,
Barry.
Everyone's alive.
Our guardian angel.
That's what you told me I could be
when I told you about my powers.
Meant it then
and I know it now.
Hey, Oliver, um,
we need to have a difficult
conversation, I think.
About my son?
God, it feels
weird to say that.
Less about your son
and more about
whether or not you're going
to tell Felicity about him.
I don't think that's any
of your business.
You know what, yeah, you're right,
it's not really my business,
except I told you, when I mess with time,
time messes back.
And we've already changed
how things turned out with Savage,
and I'm worried
about temporal backlash.
Wait, you think that the timeline
cares about what I tell my girlfriend?
What are you going to tell her?
Well, you're right
when you say that
the rules keep changing
and that the lives
that we lead,
they make us feel...
powerless.
And it makes me
wonder if...
if William wouldn't
be better off
with my world kept
separate from his.
Look, Oliver, take it from someone who
didn't get to grow up with his father--
I think the best thing
for William
is for you to be
a part of his life.
Thanks, Barry.
Yeah.
I'm not really
a hugger.
Yeah, tell me something
I don't know.
But the thing is,
I am fast enough
to just hug you
without you knowing,
so you might as well let me.
Yeah. Thanks.
Wasn't so bad, right?
These are my
conditions, Oliver.
You've already asked
me for the world;
I am just asking for
the same in return.
Ok.
I won't tell anyone.
Even Felicity.
Felicity, that's a nice name.
She is
a nice person.
She's the best.
William is in his room.
You're just a friend
of mommy's, ok?
Hey, William.
Hello.
You like the Flash?
Can I tell you
a secret?
I've actually
met the Flash.
What's he like? Is he cool?
Yeah, he's cool.
He's--he's one
of the best guys that I know.
I'm Oliver.
I'm a friend
of your mom's.
We've known each
other a long time.
Want to play action figures?
Sure, sure.
William, I'd
love to come by
every once
in a while
and say hello.
Would that be
all right with you?
It's Captain Cold.
He's a bad guy.
Yes, he is.
The Flash is going to have to be very
fast to catch him.
He will. He's
the fastest man alive.
Oh!
Gotcha.
Oh, what a mess.
Well, we have to clean
this place up.
Unless you're ready
to tell me what
you said you'd tell me.
Felicity, um...
Oliver...
We have a life together.
Right? We're a team.
Ow.
If something
is bothering you
and I don't
know about it,
I can't help you fix it.
I can't be
a good teammate.
I love you,
and that makes me
want to be the best teammate ever.
Not in a Lance Armstrong
performance enhancing drugs kind of way.
More like...More positive
sports analogy I would use
if I knew anything about sports.
What had you acting so strange
when we got to Central City?
It doesn't matter,
it's over.
And I am back
in Star City,
with you.
Come here.
Your hate will be
everlasting.
Your enmity will never die.
It will follow them
from this life
into the next,
and the next...
And the next.
You owe me one, buddy.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.