Previously on "Arrow"...
This place looks exactly
like it did when I was 13.
We had planned
to come back here with both of you.
Yeah. That didn't
really work out.
Because I died.
Have you come to doubt
your commitment to this mission?
It might help
if I actually knew why.
The recovery
of your universe
will require
a single task.
You must betray
Oliver Queen.
If saving it means
going back
to the person
that I used to be,
then what the hell
is the point?
I'm sorry.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo! Count it and the foul.
Ohh.
Comets, who have
stormed all the way back
to tie it up
in the fourth quarter.
No way.
It tastes the same.
I'm telling you these
Big Belly Burgers are just better.
I think he's right.
This is pre-Gwespin
Foods merger.
Dad, what are you
still doing here?
How did we
get here?
What do you mean?
Uh, I was on a roof
with John and Laurel,
and we were tranqed.
Yeah. By Lyla.
Look, Dad said it was all
just a big misunderstanding.
Ahem. What did we do with
Burov's plan for the weapon?
You said we didn't
need it anymore.
Why? The Monitor's
still out there.
He's still a threat.
Dad, are you okay?
You... you look like
you don't remember any of this.
I...
I need to talk to John.
That should
be easy.
He's waiting for you at that
fancy fundraiser.
What fundraiser?
The one you're
very late for.
I mean, you do remember
you're Oliver Queen, right?
Hey, Queen,
what's the difference
between a cop
and the Green Arrow?
Cop doesn't need
to play dress-up to do his job.
Ha. Yeah, sure thing. Ohh!
- I'm so sorry, Mr. Queen.
- It's fine, it's fine.
There you
are, man.
Party started
an hour ago, Oliver.
Do you remember
getting tranqed last night?
Yeah. Um, Lyla
feels awful about that.
By the way,
that wasn't last night.
- That was two days ago.
- What? No.
No, no. That...
John, that is the last thing
that I remember
before waking up
in my apartment
earlier tonight.
You okay, man?
No. This is... this...
is this the...
this is the Monitor.
- Oliver.
- Your wife is working
with the Monitor, John.
What...
I thought we
already settled this.
I have been working with
the Monitor but as a double agent,
which I told you
on the roof.
I don't... I don't
remember that.
I'm not remembering
anything.
Oliver, look. Just maybe
you should go home, man,
get a little sleep, okay,
just some rest.
Oliver, there you are.
Mayor's looking for you. Come on.
What?
- What happened there?
- Oh.
Can't give a speech
with a stained shirt.
Give a s... what speech?
I'm giving a speech?
Very funny.
Your joint remarks with the mayor.
Rene, um, serious question.
When did Palmer Tech
get rebuilt?
You really need to drop
this amnesia routine quick.
This fundraiser is
our only chance to take
the SCPD Vigilante
Pilot Program global.
The mayor needs you
to be on point.
- He's waiting for you.
- He who?
Isn't... isn't
Pollard the mayor?
In her dreams maybe.
What's the matter, Oliver?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
So listen. I was
thinking about making
a few changes
to the speech,
so I figured I should
run it by you first.
This is not possible.
This is...
What? Don't tell me
you're scared
of a little last-minute
memorization, Oliver.
It's been a while
since I've seen you.
Couple of days maybe.
You're looking at me like it's been years.
No. You're right.
A couple days.
Right. So listen.
I was thinking
about adding a line
about, you know,
me telling you it was
a bad idea to unmask,
but, you know, maybe
a joke about how
you'd rather take it
to supermax
than take my advice.
Heh. You know?
What do you think?
You know that I went
to Slabside?
Uh... yeah.
What's that,
your way of saying
I should have come visit more often?
Quentin, right before
I turned myself in...
Diaz shot you, right?
Oh. Yeah.
That son of a bitch
almost killed me.
Almost died in the O.R.
You don't remember?
I remember it differently.
Well, the doctors
called it a miracle.
I was without oxygen
for so long,
I should have been
six feet under.
Felt like I escaped
my fate or something.
Hey. There's
something you need to see.
So... there's a hostage
situation at the SCPD.
The leader's demanding
to meet with the mayor.
No. You can't
go down there.
We'll call in
a special-ops team.
I'm the mayor. Nobody
does my dirty work for me.
Give my apologies
to the guests.
I'm... I'm gonna come
with you.
Okay, but you might want
to bring a change of clothes
because something tells me
we're gonna need the green guy.
Get the feds on the line.
Tell them I need backup
- here now, right now.
- Yes, ma'am.
What's
the situation, Captain?
Armed mercs stormed
my precinct,
took a dozen
of my guys hostage.
How did they get
by your men?
It's a long story that
I don't have time to tell.
The only demand was to
speak to the mayor.
All right. Well, I'll
go talk to them.
I appreciate that,
but there is no way
I'm sending you in there.
Listen. I wore the blues
a long time
before I wore
this monkey suit, okay?
- I can hold my own.
- I know, sir.
It's not the point.
She's right.
It's too risky.
Says the man who risks
his life every day for this city?
Give me a vest.
I'll go in there,
I'll distract
the son of a bitch,
and in the meantime,
you sneak around the back
and do your thing, okay?
The longer
this drags on,
the worse it gets.
Let me do this.
I'll have his back.
I want you on comms
the whole time.
Sure.
All units,
be advised
Mayor Lance is entering
the building.
I repeat Mayor Lance is
entering the building.
This is Mayor
Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed.
I'm coming in.
- That's far enough.
- All right.
Just... just take
it easy, okay?
Take it easy.
I'm in position. Keep him talking.
You asked for me.
Here I am.
What do you want to
talk about with me?
You're the Mayor.
You're a guy
who can make things
happen.
Why don't you let a few
of these guys go while we talk?
So I can get stormed
by the cops?
No, thanks.
I'm not stupid.
But it would show that
you don't want anybody to get hurt
because if anybody gets hurt,
you're in real trouble.
Actually, I think
you're already in trouble.
I'm the one holding the gun.
Not for long.
Put it down.
Agh. Err.
This... is... over.
This isn't over
until you stop it, Oliver.
That's the only
way out.
What are you
talking about?
- No!
- Quentin!
Ahh!
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo! Count it and the foul.
That's an 8-0 run
by the Comets,
who have stormed
all the way back
to tie it up
in the fourth quarter.
88 apiece. What a comeback
for the Comets,
and there's a timeout...
No way.
It tastes the same.
I'm telling you
this Big Belly Burger's just better.
I think
he's right.
This is pre-Gwespin
Foods merger.
Ooh, Dad. What are you
still doing here?
I'm late
for a fundraiser.
Yeah. Really late.
You want a burger?
Those things never have good food.
Did something happen
at the SCPD headquarters?
Like what?
Never mind.
Hey, Queen.
What's the difference
between a cop
and the Green Arrow?
Cop doesn't need
to play dress-up to do his job.
- Ooh! Nice reflexes, Mr. Queen.
- Thank you.
There you are. You know
the party started an hour ago, right?
I need to speak
with you.
Uh, this is gonna
sound crazy.
Um... I have been
here before. So have you.
What are you
talking about?
About the Monitor dropping
me into some sort of
alternate reality
t-time loop or something,
where everything is different,
where Lance is still alive.
Oliver, Lance has
always been alive.
No, he hasn't.
You just don't remember
because the Monitor has done
something to people's memories,
but I... I think I know
the way out of this,
but I... I need to stop
a bomb at the SCPD.
Oliver, will you just
calm down, man?
If there was a bomb,
we would know about it.
Lyla would know
about it.
Lyla's a part of this.
Part of what?
Oliver seems to
think that he's caught
in some sort
of time loop.
If we're traveling
back in time,
I'd like to revisit
my 20s.
I... I need to speak
with Quentin.
The mayor's waiting
for me.
Yeah. How'd you know?
Mr. Mayor.
Oh. Hey, Oliver.
Listen.
I, uh... I made a few last-minute
changes to the speech, so...
- We need to talk.
- Sure. Let's.
Uh, yeah. I wanted to run
these changes by you anyway.
You want to add
a joke about Slabside,
about how I would
rather spend time
in a supermax
than take your advice.
You steal a copy
of my speech or something?
We've had this
exact conversation already.
What are you
talking about?
Fully aware of how
this is going to sound.
Quentin, I am trapped
in some sort of... time loop,
where the same events
just keep repeating themselves.
- Like "Groundhog Day."
- Sure,
except this one ends
in a lot of people dead,
including the two of us.
Okay. How can I help?
Do you actually
believe me?
Oliver, I've seen
one daughter die
and come back
to life twice.
I've seen another
come from some other Earth.
I've seen a guy in red run
so fast he can reverse time.
This is not exactly
outside the norm, is it?
Also, I'm done learning my lesson
about doubting you
because that always
bites me in the ass. Heh.
What happens now?
Very shortly, we are
gonna learn that
there is a hostage situation
at the SCPD.
They're going to insist
that they talk to you and only you.
And how does it
go south?
There's a hidden
explosive device
that I didn't know about
the first time through,
and judging from the blast,
it's underneath the building.
- Eh. So you find it.
- Yeah.
You keep us from going boom.
- What then?
- I break out of the loop.
Great.
Here you are.
There's something you need to see.
Get the feds
on the line.
- Tell them I need backup now.
- Yes, ma'am.
What's the situation,
Captain?
Armed mercs stormed
the precinct,
took a dozen
of my guys hostage.
They have a bomb.
We already did a sweep
of the entire building.
It's not in the building.
It's underneath it.
How could you
possibly know that?
I trust him.
Instinct thing.
So what do you
want to do?
This is
Mayor Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed.
I'm coming in.
Stop right there.
Oh. It's you.
Would you relax?
We are both here
for the same thing.
Hey. How did you know
to come down here?
I may have learned
about the existence
of this place as a part
of a former career.
How did you know
about the bomb?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Well, actually, since you're
not going to remember anyway,
there is a crazy space god
who has me trapped in a time loop.
Yeah? Me, too.
- It's my second time through.
- Same.
- I wake up in the bunker.
- I wake up in my apartment,
so clearly,
the Monitor is doing this.
- You mean punishing us?
- Yeah.
We are the two people
who have royally pissed him off the most.
In Russia,
I disobeyed him,
and you... you tried to
destroy him.
At least we're in it
together now.
I think disarming that
is the way out of here.
How long do you think
until this thing goes boom?
Oh. Your guess is
as good as mine.
Quentin's upstairs
buying us some time.
- Quentin... he's here?
- Yeah.
I think we just activated
some kind of failsafe.
Look. We need more
time on the next loop, Laurel.
It would probably help
if we found each other faster next time.
There's a party
at the Palmer Tech building.
- Meet me there.
- Are we talking formal wear or...
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo!
No way.
It's the same.
I'm telling you.
This Big Belly Burger is just better.
Guess you realized
you're late.
Something like that.
Hey, Queen.
What's the difference
between a cop
and the Green Arrow?
Cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Sorry.
Mr. Mayor?
Hey, Oliver. Listen. I made a few
last-minute changes to the speech.
And you figured you should
run them by me first.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, baby girl.
I didn't think you
were gonna make it.
Me either.
You okay, honey?
I'm just really
happy to see you.
Oh. I'm happy
to see you, too.
Though I got to say
I'm glad you left
the black lipstick
at home tonight.
You know that I'm
Earth-2 Laurel.
Who else would
you be?
Look. I'm really sorry
to interrupt,
but you and I
need to go.
You're coming with us.
We need your help.
What do you mean
there's a bomb?
I know how to stop it,
but you have to trust me.
I'm gonna need
a vest.
Not this time,
Quentin.
This is
Mayor Quentin Lance.
You wanted to talk.
Let's talk.
The detonator operates
on an oscillating frequency.
If we can find the right one,
we should be able to disrupt it.
Vincent, listen to me.
I know you don't
really want to do this.
And I know that
if you don't get in here
these men are
gonna die.
I have an idea.
We did it.
Okay. Fine. You did it.
We stopped the bomb.
What the hell are we still doing here?
I don't... I...
we must have
missed something.
No!
No! No!
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo!
Lovely to have you
here this evening.
Thanks for coming out.
All right. Quentin's death
is the reset point,
which means that
saving him must
be the key.
What kind of sick game
is the Monitor playing?
I don't know.
We need to find out
who is behind this
hostage situation.
If it's just about killing Quentin,
then why plant a bomb?
It seems like a lot
of extra work.
Maybe whoever is
behind this wants
their involvement
kept a secret.
Do you really think
there's a larger conspiracy here?
Those were
mercenaries, Laurel,
which means that
somebody had to hire them.
Great, and I'm sure they're
gonna be really easy to find, too.
Any idea
where to start?
Let's get Quentin
out of here.
Why don't you take
him to the bunker?
What about you?
I'm gonna go take
a look at that bomb.
Laurel, I didn't think
you'd make it tonight.
I am really not
in the mood for small talk
with the Monitor's
bestie.
- Excuse me.
- It turns out tranq darts,
they don't
feel so good.
I told you that was
a big misunderstanding.
Well, understand this.
The second I get out
of this sadistic
"Edge of Tomorrow" reboot,
I am going to make sure
to tell everyone
exactly what kind
of traitor you really are.
Laurel, I truly have
no idea what you're talking about,
but whatever it is
you're feeling toward me,
that's on you.
Thank you for
the advice, Dr. Phil,
and now here's
some for you.
The next time you decide to
double-cross someone,
don't pick a woman
who specializes in revenge.
You're threatening me.
Yes. Yes, I am,
but don't worry.
You won't remember
anyway,
and by the way, I pull off
the short hair way better than you do.
What are you
doing here?
Well, word came down that
the Green Arrow called in a bomb threat,
so I thought to myself,
"How did he know about that,
and why didn't
he call me?"
Because the Monitor
has me trapped in a time loop.
Already told you that.
Okay. Definitely not
the answer I was expecting,
but if the Monitor's involved,
anything is possible.
Any idea
how to break out?
I have to save
Quentin's life.
I thought that this
was the key to it,
but I'm not finding
anything.
Well, has to be something.
No case is unsolvable.
This might be impossible.
Well, you'll
figure it out.
I do wish I was
as sure as you are.
You want to know what
makes me so sure?
- Huh?
- You.
You, Oliver.
You always figure it out.
You never stop fighting.
You never give up.
You always keep at it.
Why should this be
any different?
Whatever version
this is of you,
you still give
the best advice.
- Yeah. I'm flattered.
- Well, A.R.G.U.S. has
some more sophisticated
analytical equipment.
Any chance you can
get me in there?
Yeah. I bet I can make
a few calls.
So you're telling me we're in
some kind of a alternate reality
based on the plot
of a Bill Murray movie?
Well, I was gonna go with
a Tom Cruise flick but basically.
Also just really glad
that you believe me.
Well, it's not the craziest thing
you ever told me.
I mean, I'm just
glad this Monitor guy
just kept me
as mayor, you know?
What is it?
What's that look?
It... it's just that, uh,
in my world
or in the real world, uh,
you're not mayor anymore.
Really?
Pollard.
She always had it in for me.
There something else?
Laurel. Sweetheart,
I always know when you're
hiding something
from me.
Please tell me.
What is it?
It... it's a year
and a half ago
when Diaz...
when he shot you
in... in the real reality
or whatever,
you... you didn't
exactly, um...
I didn't recover.
No. No. You died
to save me.
Best way I could
have gone.
What?! I'm sorry.
I basically just
told you you're a ghost,
and you're completely okay with that?
It doesn't... it doesn't faze you?
You're completely calm?
I always felt like
I cheated death with that one.
Guess that's
because I didn't.
Fate's just tricky
like that.
- It's Oliver.
- Yeah?
He figure out who
wants me dead?
Not yet, but he did
figure out the location
of the mercs' hideout.
Okay. So we better go.
How'd you find
this place?
Uh, we analyzed
the bomb
and traced the chemical signature
back to this building.
Interesting.
- What?
- Your mouth
but Felicity's words.
It still doesn't tell us
who hired these bozos.
Maybe this will help.
Bomb!
Uh, w-what the hell
are you doing?
Helping you. You're missing
the point, Oliver.
- What?
- You can't fight this.
Ugh.
Lyla!
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo! Count it and the foul.
No sign of Lyla
anywhere. You?
John just told me
she got called away
on a last-minute
A.R.G.U.S. mission,
meaning she's never
even been here.
Maybe the Monitor deleted
her for going rogue.
Wouldn't that be so, so sad?
She's clearly helping him.
There's no reason for her
to switch sides right now.
So why reveal her hand?
It makes no sense.
All right.
You spoke with her.
Was there anything,
anything at all in
the conversation that stood out?
She said how I feel
towards her was on me.
Like it's my fault that
I'm stuck here.
I told you the Monitor's
punishing us.
I'm not so sure.
We've had to watch
Quentin die over and over again,
and we can't save him.
If I had to design hell,
this would be it.
But right before
Lyla disappeared,
she told me she was
trying to help me.
She also told you
you can't fight this.
It seems pretty clear to me
that we're not supposed to win.
The first time
that I met Mar Novu,
it felt... it felt
the same.
It was like I was put in a situation
where there was no way out,
but it was a test,
Laurel.
It was a test
just like I think that this is.
- A test of what?
- I don't know,
but there is
a way out of here,
and I'm gonna find it.
- You just never give up, do you?
- No, I don't.
Are you with me?
Fine.
What's our play?
We go back
to the mercs' hideout.
We know where the danger
is this time,
so we can do things
differently.
You grab Quentin,
and I'll meet you there.
Okay.
So you're telling
me we've been here once
and still came back
for more?
At least now we know
what not to do.
Okay.
All right. That should
disable the bomb.
Well, I certainly hope so
because I am getting
sick and tired
of getting blown up.
- All right.
- Okay. So now what?
We find out who hired
those mercs to kill you.
Money leads to a man
named Anderson White.
Never heard of him.
Looks like he's
been accused
of not too many
nice things...
money laundering,
racketeering.
Doesn't explain why
he'd want me dead.
Well, that's what we're
gonna find out.
CEO of a company
named Global Solutions.
They have a warehouse
down by the docks.
Let's go.
We need to find White.
Back this way!
- Come on, come on.
- I got you. I got you.
I'll take care
of the rest.
Err! Ugh.
Oh, I'm sorry, baby girl.
Looks like we lost
this round.
No. No! I am not
letting you die again.
- It's too late.
- No.
It... it's... it's time
to say good-bye.
I'm not giving up
on you, Quentin.
Quentin, I am not
giving up on you.
You never gave up
on me.
You believed in me
when nobody else did.
Well, that's what
dads do. They believe.
I want you to know
that you are the reason
that I'm trying to be a hero.
It's because of you.
Sweetheart...
you are a hero.
You are.
Thank you.
Thank you. I never
had the chance to tell you
how much you
mean to me.
- Well...
- Thank you.
I think you just did.
I love you. I love you.
Good-bye.
Damn it.
All right. Okay.
All right, Laurel.
We fix this next time.
We'll fix it.
I can't do this again.
I'm done, Oliver.
All I have ever wanted
was a chance
to say good-bye
to Quentin.
Now I have.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo! Count it and the foul.
Laurel?
Laurel!
She's not here.
- Where is she?
- Gone.
What did you... what
did you do, Lyla?
I didn't do anything.
Laurel got what she needed from this.
I don't have time
for these games, Lyla,
so whatever this is,
get me out of here right now!
I can't do that,
Oliver.
Mar Novu needs you
to understand
no good will come
from struggle.
The only way to win
is to accept the inevitable.
I have no idea
what that means.
Learn that,
and this will end.
Lyla!
So if me dying
is the problem,
maybe bringing me
into the lion's den isn't so smart.
Couldn't think of a better
way to keep you safe.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
Huh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Unless you want a hole for a head.
Are you
Anderson White?
You really think
Mr. White would be here?
He ordered a hit
on my friend. Why?
I guess
the clock's ticking.
Looks like a list
of hits.
And clients.
Coded and anonymous.
White's just
the middleman.
A CEO with a healthy
side business brokering
hits for wealthy asshats.
All right. We're back
to square one.
We have no idea how deep
this rabbit hole goes.
We got to get going.
Unh!
Get down! Get down!
Hey. You okay?
You all right? Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
Whoa!
Go, go, go,
go, go, go!
Aah!
- Get them.
- Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Get down, get down!
Over there!
Down, Quentin!
Ohh. Oh, it's
the last one.
How many arrows
you got left?
Not enough.
Oh, boy. Aren't we
the couple?
We are gonna find
a way out of this.
There has to be
a way to fix it,
and we are gonna
find it, Quentin.
It doesn't matter how many times.
We're gonna find it!
Yeah? Sure.
What's it gonna be,
60 times, 100 times?
It's gonna be however
many times it takes!
You know, getting
hunted like this
in a space like this
is kind of like
what I was doing to you
all those years ago.
Remember?
Sort of makes sense I'd go out
like this now, don't you think?
Would you please just
save your strength?
For what?
Oliver, you take care
of these guys,
there'll be more
behind them,
there will be more
behind them.
There is no saving me
from this!
Okay? You ever think
that's the point?
Maybe you're not
supposed to.
I'm not giving up...
and you're not
giving up either.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not giving up.
Maybe I'm giving in.
You see, I've been
outrunning death for a while now.
The siege, the island,
but when Diaz shot me,
that felt different
like I was finally
at the end,
and I made my peace
with that.
And maybe it's time
you did, too.
It looks like fate's
knocking.
You just get ready
to move.
I'll see you
on the other side, Oliver.
Quentin.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich
in the corner for three.
Bingo! Count it and the foul.
That's an 8-0 run
by the Comets,
who have stormed all the way
back to tie it up here
in the fourth quarter.
88 apiece.
What a comeback for the Comets,
and there's a timeout.
No way.
It tastes the same.
Dad, what are you
still doing here?
Hey, guys.
I'm just heading out the door.
Wanted to let you know,
all of you know
what a... just what a gift
getting to know
you all has been.
Dad, you're going
to a fundraiser.
It's not like you're
going into war.
Although I guess I can
see the similarities.
I think he's talking
about Crisis.
I'm just really
proud of all you guys.
I'm really proud.
I got to go.
Dad...
you're gonna be fine.
So are you.
All of you will be
whatever happens.
Hey, Queen.
What's the difference
between a cop... hey!
Yeah. Lovely.
Quentin, excuse me.
Hey.
What's the matter,
Oliver?
You look like you've
seen a ghost.
Maybe I did.
May I speak with you
for a second?
Sure.
Uh, yeah, you want to
go over the speech?
'Cause I was thinking
about adding a few lines.
I have a question for you.
Sure.
Back when I was
running around as the Hood,
you were trying to
arrest me.
You remember that?
Ah. Yeah. The good old days.
How could I ever forget?
The question is...
what made you decide
that I wasn't
your enemy anymore?
What changed
your mind?
Huh. Oh, you know,
my daughters for one.
Because I didn't
raise dummies,
and, uh, you know, if
they were okay with you,
then I figured
I should be, too.
- Yeah.
- They trusted me,
and you trusted them.
Yeah. They got me to listen
to what I always knew
in my gut, that we were
on the same side
and fighting
for the same goal,
and it just took me
a while to get there.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Oliver, is there
any particular reason
for this trip
down memory lane?
Yeah.
God, I've been
hanging on to something.
Someone told me
just recently that, uh...
it's about time
I made peace with it.
Okay. Sounds like
a smart someone.
Yeah.
Oh, I shouldn't have
to say good-bye to you again.
Good-bye?
Evening's just
getting started.
Yeah.
Thank you, Quentin
for everything.
Mr. Mayor.
We're gonna see
each other again, Oliver.
Mr. Mayor!
Hostage situation.
I hope so.
Congratulations, Oliver.
Now you understand.
I couldn't change
Quentin's fate.
I can't change
mine either, can I?
No. I'm sorry.
Why did the Monitor go to all
of this trouble just to...
just to prove a point?
You've always been
a man who needed to
see things for himself.
Telling you wouldn't
have been enough.
How long have you
worked for him?
A while.
You lied to us, Lyla.
You...
you lied to John.
Keeping this
from John has been
the hardest thing I've
ever had to do.
Then why do it?
The same reason you left
Felicity and Mia
in that cabin...
to protect my family.
Do you honestly
believe that working
with the Monitor
is the best way to do that?
It's the only way.
The Crisis is coming.
There is no stopping it.
All we can do is
try to survive it.
Okay, help me out
here, Lyla.
I don't even know
what it is.
I know,
but you will... soon.
What I can tell you
is there is an evil coming
that is greater
than anything we've
ever had to face.
Can we stop it?
I don't know...
but you are the only
chance we have.
So everything I've done
from the moment
I left that cabin,
this has all been some...
bigger part of a test?
He needed to be sure
you were ready.
He's just been sending
me on useless missions.
They weren't useless.
The dwarf star particles,
Dr. Wong,
even the antimatter
weapon,
they all have a purpose,
just not the one
you were expecting.
Why did he involve
my children?
Time is a gift.
What now?
You complete
your final mission.
I'll see you there.
Ohh.
Where are we?
You okay?
I have
a killer headache.
The last thing that
I remember is Quentin...
dying in
that warehouse.
I was wearing these
on the roof
when we got tranqed,
so does that mean that...
We got out.
How?
We learned our lessons.
I got out
after I said good-bye.
Why would the Monitor
let me see Quentin one last time?
It was a reward
for not betraying me.
Didn't really think
rewards were his brand.
No. We were wrong
about him.
And Lyla was right?
That's annoying.
So why did you
have to learn to let Lance go?
Because deep down,
I still believed
that I could fight
my fate.
Now I know I can't.
Lyla said we had
one last thing to do,
one final mission.
I can't wait to find out
what that is.
Where that is.
We're not
in Star City.
Dad.
You okay?
Where the hell are we?
We're on Lian Yu.
Greg, move your head!