My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell,
I have been released
from prison
and returned home
with only one goal...
to save my city,
but things have changed.
Instead of operating
outside the law,
I am now working
alongside the police.
I am no longer inmate 4587.
I am once more
the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Ricardo Diaz
is dead.
Whoever's been running around
dressed up as the Green Arrow,
that's your murderer.
Does she have any reason
to blame my family
for her mother's death?
Y'all did become
Starling City Royalty
while she and her mom were left
to struggle in The Glades.
What our father did to
you was unforgiveable.
I see now
you are different from him.
You and Oliver Queen
are getting along quite well.
He trusts me now.
It's time for you
to come home.
Archer is active.
I think that's more than a
security system you're working on.
I think you're on
to something big.
You're lying about
who you really are.
What makes you think
they will believe
a word you say,
Black Siren?
Where are we
supposed to go?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
This is our home, Robert,
one that you used to
be a part of.
You don't understand.
If I let you stay,
she will take everything...
my company,
my money, my children.
What about our child?
The movers will be here
tomorrow afternoon.
Tell Emiko I'm sorry.
- Emiko.
- Where are we going, dad?
You and your mom
are going to live
someplace else,
someplace better.
But I want to
stay here!
I know you do, kiddo,
but life isn't fair.
We don't always get
what we want.
I'm sorry.
Dad, please don't leave.
You OK?
Are you?
Where'd you learn that?
I'll tell you
if you tell me
where you learned
taekwondo.
I learned taekwondo
from a woman named
Talia in Russia.
Your past gets
more mysterious every day.
Could say the same
thing about you.
Your turn.
It's complicated.
I had a good teacher.
He, um,
showed me
how to protect myself.
He taught you well.
Nice trick.
The key is to watch
your opponent
and not the stick.
What are you
smiling about?
- I kicked your ass.
- Oh, no.
You most certainly
did not.
Thea and I used to
spar like this.
She always wanted
a sister.
So did I.
Rematch?
If you think
you can handle it.
Oh, come on, Smoak.
You got this.
You know you can be pregnant
and be ceo of a company
and a deputized vigilante
by night.
Women really can
have it all.
I'm talking to myself.
DNA match complete.
Identity confirmed.
Alena Whitlock.
Well, that is
ingenious.
Was not expecting
an entrance
or that you knew
my last name.
- Alena, hi.
- Hi.
Hi! Oh, it's been so long.
How have you been?
When you're
the known associate
of the evil and murder
genius Cayden James,
good to keep
a low profile,
so I'm working
at tech village.
Oh, no. Oh.
I have been there literally.
I know your pain.
The... the vests.
So, um, how did you
find me, actually?
It's part of a new project
I have been working on.
It started off as, like,
a home-based security system,
and now it's turned
into, like,
a DNA-tracking-based
surveillance system.
- Meet Archer.
- Sorry. So you located me
using my DNA?
When did you collect
my DNA? Heh.
- I know it's a little creepy.
- It's more than a little,
but it's also impressive.
I've been using it for Team Arrow,
but I think
if we scaled it up,
it could be so much more than that.
I mean, we could find missing persons,
we could track terrorists,
we could do crowd control,
we could do anything!
Just, I can't do it
alone.
I mean, whatever
you need, I am game.
I am so done telling
customers to use
the chip in their card when
they insist on swiping.
Great! How does cto of
Smoak Technologies sound?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh! You're not even
gonna ask about benefits?
I don't care
about the benefits
as long as there's
no crappy vest requirement.
- I am in!
- No vest. Huge benefit.
Music to my ears.
D.A. Laurel Lance
is at the front door.
- Allow access.
- Access granted.
It's open.
- Hey.
- Is your wife around?
No. She went out.
What's up?
Uh, nothing.
I'll just...
I'll come find
Felicity later.
Your bandage is
bleeding through.
Sit down. We'll get
you cleaned up.
Fine.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Looks like
an Arrow wound.
Because it is
Where'd it come from?
Your sister's bow.
- What?
- Look. I don't mean to
blindside you
with this,
which is why I wanted
to talk to Felicity...
you know, empathy
and all that...
but your sister is not the
hero you think she is.
What are you
talking about?
Ben Turner saw her
at slabside
The Night Diaz
was murdered.
It wasn't another inmate
that killed Diaz.
It was Emiko.
Heh heh heh.
That makes no sense.
Well, I figured
you'd say that,
so I did more digging,
and there are no records
of her that exist
past the age of 15,
no fingerprints.
And when I followed her last
night to find out more,
she tried skewering
me with an Arrow.
OK. I've seen her skills
up close.
She doesn't miss.
If she wanted you dead,
you'd be dead.
Oh. Maybe I should
be thankful, then.
Once upon a time, I actually shot
Roy Harper and Barry Allen.
It was to illustrate
a point.
My guess is that
her point is
she doesn't want to be
stalked anymore.
Or maybe sister has
brother wrapped
around her
little finger.
You know, the Oliver
I knew, he had
a blind spot
for family,
and I'm guessing
you do, too.
It's called loyalty.
I know that's a concept you
don't totally understand.
I have nothing
to gain here.
I am only trying to
do what's right.
Why can you
not see that?
There has to be
more to this,
and I will look into it
if you will promise
to stay out of it.
I already wish
I would have.
Good luck.
If I give this to you,
my family's
safe, right?
I can guarantee it.
If it's all there.
All that we'll need.
I believe we're
done here.
What the hell is that?
Uh!
Help!
Please.
Hey. It's OK.
It's OK.
I got you, I got you.
I got you.
Forget about me.
You need to stop them.
Who? Who? Stop who?
The Ninth Circle.
The Ninth what?
- Circle.
- Dante's a part of it.
Turns out he's not just a banker
for terrorists and cartels.
OK. Lyla and I have been
hunting Dante for months.
Why are we just
hearing this name?
Because The Ninth Circle
is practically invisible.
I mean, I combed the entire
dark web and came up with nada,
but then I remembered
this photo you sent me
from the ghost initiative's
last ride.
Right.
That symbol was on
all the weapons that
Virgil's goons used.
The symbol also pops up on
artifacts dating all the way back
to 14th-century Italy,
the real Dante's era.
The insignia is mostly
commonly found on ephemera
that is connected to times
of historical upheaval...
the Russian Revolution,
The Colonization of The Americas,
the war of roses.
So you're saying Dante
runs a secret society
responsible
for centuries
of worldwide
regime change?
Right,
but if that's true,
The Ninth Circle's
clearly way bigger
than just Dante.
OK. Well, how did you run into
Dante last night, Oliver,
and why didn't you
call for backup?
Laurel came to speak
with you and found me.
Suggested that...
Emiko has been hiding
certain parts of her past
and said that
she killed Diaz.
She killed Diaz?
Which doesn't mean
she's bad.
I followed Emiko,
and it led me
to Dante.
OK. Well, all we really
know about Emiko
is what she's told us,
which isn't much.
She's a vigilante.
For all we know,
she's gathering intel on The
Ninth Circle to take them down.
Also, why are we taking
Laurel's word about anything?
Hey. Laurel
has changed a lot.
I mean,
she's been a really good friend to me...
not to say that your sister's evil,
but she's changed a lot.
Be that as it may,
The Ninth Circle is clearly a threat,
and we need to follow up
every lead that we have.
Well, we know that they stole
8 military-grade drones,
which they could literally be
planning to do anything with.
OK. Can you use Archer to
pinpoint Dante's location?
Not without his DNA.
OK. Well, I'll talk to Lyla,
take this new intel back there,
and see if we can use
A.R.G.U.S.'s databases.
Yeah. We should be able
to use SCPD resources, too.
I'll get d
up to speed.
I'm gonna go speak
with my sister.
She deserves a chance
to explain herself.
And i... I will...
I'll be here.
What is so important that couldn't
be handled over the phone?
Do you remember
our conversation
about playing
by the rules,
about doing things the right
way is usually the hard way?
Why do I feel
a lecture coming on?
The Halcones Kingpin,
Ramiro Gonzalez,
we had a witness
who was ready to nail him
for criminal conspiracy
until we found out his confession
was coerced by the D.A.
You wanted the city
cleaned up, right?
I'm cleaning.
You are an officer
of the law.
You have to play by it.
You know, with Team Arrow
working alongside the SCPD,
this city has a real chance
of turning things around,
and it's never gonna happen
if our D.A. is a criminal.
All of those guys
are guilty.
You'd rather see them
kicked than me
bend a couple of...
of little rules
to make sure
their charges stick?
Yes, because if anyone finds
out what you've been up to,
they're all gonna get off
on technicalities,
and you're gonna
get fired.
Fine, but I'm sure
there's a reason
you brought this up
in the first place.
You have a second chance.
SWAT brought in one of Ramirez's
lieutenants last night...
Gustavo Hernandez.
He's looking to deal,
and I want you to put
that kingpin
behind bars.
Just need you to do it
the right way.
You really know how to take
the fun out of everything.
Uh, we don't have a training
session until next week.
I don't think family
needs a reason to stop by.
Going somewhere?
I, uh,
was just heading out for a bite to eat.
- What some company?
- Hmm. Not really.
Because you're
meeting someone?
What's with
the interrogation?
That teacher that you
were telling me about,
how long did you
train with him?
Since I was 11.
Where'd you meet?
It doesn't matter.
It was a long time ago.
Yeah. I mean,
if I was working with a known terrorist,
I'd want to keep
that quiet, too.
What are you
talking about?
I saw you last
night with Dante
outside
Palmer Technologies.
You were following me.
Mm-hmm.
So now you, uh...
you think I'm some
kind of criminal?
Trying to give you the
benefit of the doubt,
but... this guy
Dante is...
he's a monster.
I know who Dante is,
but i...
I didn't back then.
I was 11 when your father
walked out on me and my mother.
He chose your family
over mine,
and he left us
with nothing...
no home, no money.
Dante took me
under his wing,
and he... he trained me.
He taught me
how to survive.
By the time I knew who he really was,
it was too late.
You know, I owed him,
and I still do now.
I can help you.
You have no idea
what kind of power
he holds.
The organization
he runs...
The Ninth Circle?
Then you know there's
no way out.
On your own,
but if you're being
backed up
by a team...
just, I can...
I can help you,
but you have to
let me.
You can't,
and, trust me,
you will only
make things worse
for the both of us
if you try.
Delivery from
frank bertinelli.
I didn't know
the bertinellis
employed
child labor.
Pays better
than a lemonade stand,
and the cops
don't hassle a kid.
That'll be all.
I'll take my watch back.
Do you know who I am?
Dante. It says
on the package.
Do you know
who I am?
The suspense is
killing me.
- Emiko.
- Well, Emiko,
taking my watch is
a pretty risky move.
Well, I need money,
and it looks like
you have enough.
I earn it.
How'd you do that thing
with the knife?
Pretty simple,
actually.
I can teach you
if you want.
Come back tomorrow.
That was a good lift.
Steal from me again,
and I'll slit your throat.
Good news!
Lyla got a DNA sample from
the dagger used by Dante
to kill Director Bell.
Guess who now has
said sample?
John Diggle,
you give the best gifts.
Now that we have
Dante's DNA,
will Archer be
able to find him?
Well, with all the money I'm spending
on this program, that is the hope.
How's Emiko?
Did you find anything more
- about her being...
- Being on the wrong side.
She admitted
to being in very deep
with Dante
and The Ninth Circle.
Sounds like she could be
in some real trouble.
Boom. I got him.
Looks like he's
at the Star City branch
of szrek chemicals.
If we surprise
Dante now,
we could still
take him down.
And get my sister
out of trouble.
Let's suit up.
Hey, Jerry.
We still on for beers tonight?
Maybe we should
try Nelson's.
Better service.
I'm afraid Jerry's
not gonna make it.
Please don't kill me.
Of course not.
Unh!
Those.
- You told him we were here!
- I didn't.
Your allegiance
has shifted.
Now!
D, go!
We got you covered.
Agh!
Let's get out of here.
Grab her.
Let me go!
- You OK?
- Uh-huh.
I shouldn't be here.
Dante will find me.
It's just a matter of time,
and you will all be targets.
Yeah? Well, it won't
be the first time.
Think about it
like this.
It'll be a hell of a lot
easier to stop Dante
with all of us working
together than you by yourself.
OK, as long as I get to
be the one who takes him down.
That sounds fair to me.
Well, yeah, except
there's just one problem.
Archer just crashed,
which means I lost Dante's location.
Fine. We'll just have to
find Dante the old-fashioned way.
Easier said
than done.
Now that he knows I'm
working with you,
we should consider all Ninth
Circle locations burned.
But that op we just
interrupted,
I mean, Dante didn't get
what he was looking for.
You must know what he
was after.
Enriched uranium.
I told you he was
dangerous.
We need to figure
out where else in the city
he can get his hands
on that uranium.
Yeah. I'm on it.
Archer may have crashed,
but computers will
never replace people.
Do you have any idea what
he was planning on doing
with the drones
and uranium?
I wish I had
more intel,
but it was always on
a need-to-know basis.
That's how the
Ninth Circle works.
- Hey. You hurt?
- Not badly.
- You guys have some ice?
- Yeah.
This could not
be worse timing,
but I have to run
to the SCPD.
Go ahead, captain.
We'll handle it from here.
Hey. What's wrong?
Just be careful
with her, Oliver.
OK. I will.
Hey, guys.
Think I got something.
- That was fast.
- One point for the humans.
If Emiko is right
and he's after uranium,
there's only two places
in Star City that have it...
dunkirk power
and global energy.
Sounds like a divide
and conquer situation.
My thoughts exactly.
So are you just gonna
not ask me about it?
You have nothing
to say about the fact
that I've been secretly
working for The Ninth Circle?
I know you well enough
not to pry,
and you did try to keep
me out of your mission
when we first met.
I didn't want you to
get mixed up with them,
but i... I should have
told you the truth
so you'd know what you
were really getting into
working with me.
I bet you wish
you'd listened
when I told you
to stay away.
If you think I regret teaming up with you,
I don't.
We're still partners,
Emiko,
no matter who we're
up against.
You haven't practiced.
This is much harder
than last week.
No. You're just
not prepared.
I was busy. I was
working on something.
Oh, yes. Your plan
to impress daddy.
Being a father means
more than just blood.
I know, but he is
still my father.
So you would choose
a man who abandoned you
over The Ninth Circle?
Why can't I
have both?
The Ninth Circle is not
a place of split loyalties.
Once you join,
it is a lifetime commitment.
There is nothing else.
I can't give up
on my family.
The Ninth Circle is
your family now...
And that is
their gift to you.
You really want a deal
for this smug bastard?
Are you sure?
Bigger picture,
Laurel.
Mr. Hernandez,
do you know who I am?
You're the D.A. who
used to be a vigilante.
Yeah, I know you.
Good, because I know
you, too...
drug trafficking,
embezzlement, manslaughter.
Murder?
So this is the part where
you offer me a deal
to make it all
go away, right?
Hmm. If it were up to me,
I'd let you rot or worse,
but, luckily for you,
it's your boss who we're after...
Ramiro Gonzalez.
And you think that a plea
deal's enough to flip me?
Hey. I've got
enough evidence here
to convict you
of 3 felonies,
one using
a deadly weapon,
and that was in a day.
Imagine what I could do
in a week.
You know, your dad thought he
could convict me, too, right?
Must be
a family defect.
I would be really
careful if I were you
because we're not a family
that plays very nice.
How's that going
for you?
Captain Lance...
he's dead now, isn't he?
Say his name one more
time, and you will be, too.
Aw. Girl's got a soft spot for daddy.
Aw.
That's enough,
D.A. Lance.
We're done here.
Global energy
was a bust.
No sign of Dante
or the uranium.
Ah. You still
came back looking
like a prizefighter,
though.
We ran into a couple
thugs on the way back.
Ooh. Cute.
A little brother-sister
crime-fighting duo time.
- I like it.
- Any word from John and Rene?
They struck out,
too.
Global energy
and dunkirk power are
the only two spots in Star City
that manufacture uranium.
- Archer's still not working.
- Right.
I'm just about to go down into the deepest,
darkest,
most dungeony part
of this bunker
and give it
a full system reboot.
Then hopefully then, you know,
Archer can be back online,
we can find Dante,
and all my dreams
of Smoak Tech saving the
world don't have to die.
I'm gonna clean
this up.
Think I found
the problem.
Some kind of jammer.
Wonder how that
got there.
So you were never
under duress.
Sorry to
disappoint you,
but that's what family
does, right?
This is the reason that
Archer isn't working?
I couldn't let you and your
team get in the way again.
We don't give up
that easily.
You've been lying
this entire time,
everything
about our father,
your debt to Dante?
It was all true,
but I never needed you
to put me back together.
I just knew you'd try.
Can't resist playing
the hero, can you?
Unh!
You went looking
for a family,
and you chose
The Ninth Circle?
Better than living
as a Queen.
Always watch
your opponent.
You don't have to be
a part of this.
You have a choice!
I've made it!
Bye, brother.
I was married
to a junkie.
You'd think I'd know when
someone was lying to me.
At least now we know what
side Emiko's really on.
It doesn't matter.
The... The Ninth Circle are still out there,
and they are a threat.
You can take a minute to
process this if you need to.
I need to know
where she is.
How soon can you have
Archer back up and running?
Not as soon
as I would like.
Emiko's little device didn't
just jam up the system.
It wiped the entire memory card,
which means
I have to rebuild the
entire infrastructure.
Looks like we have
another problem.
There's been a break-In at the waste
treatment site at orchard bay.
I thought the only spots
that manufactured uranium
were the two sites
we just canvassed.
Well, that's true,
but how much do you want to bet
that Dante and his pals aren't
actually after uranium?
- More of Emiko's lies.
- What'd they get?
All the ingredients
to make a big batch
of sarin gas.
That plus the drones
that they just stole
makes one hell
of a murder party.
We have to know where
The Ninth Circle
is planning on
sending these drones.
- Oliver, we're on it.
- You might want to take 5.
I'm going to
Emiko's hideout,
see if she left behind
a clue or something.
Yeah, or you could
do exactly the opposite
of what your wife
recommends.
I'll go with him.
Are you here to give
me another lecture or...
The Halcones Lieutenant,
Gustavo Hernandez,
was found dead
an hour ago.
Really?
Am I supposed to be sad
about that or something?
Well,
we had him in custody to prevent that.
That is, of course, until your office
said we had to turn him loose.
Well, he made bail.
You're the one that said I had
to do things the right way,
so I let him loose,
and here we are back
to square one.
Well, actually, we're not.
Hernandez's death
spooked one of Gonzalez's
other lieutenants,
and, uh, he's
gonna testify.
Isn't that convenient?
You think I did this.
I'm not exactly
hearing a denial.
I shouldn't have
to give you one.
I think I've done
more than enough
to have earned the benefit
of the doubt from you.
I saw how you looked
at that man,
and it was the same look
that you gave Vinnie
right before you
executed him.
I have busted my ass
being a good D.A.,
trying to play
by the rules,
but no matter
what I do, you
always just see me
as the Black Siren.
You're right.
You're right,
and I am sorry,
but I don't know
who you really
are, Laurel.
I don't, and I don't think
that you do either.
I think that's what
scares me the most.
Didn't hurt you
too bad back there, did I?
No. It was a convincing
performance.
Did you, uh,
make any progress on who hired
Andrew Thorn... Ton?
You know I'm a man
of my word.
Once you've found and taken
care of your mother's killer,
you can go back to focusing
on the mission.
A deal is a deal.
This is really impressive.
Did you come up
with this yourself?
Yeah, I did.
Um, and Queen materials,
inc., could be profitable
in as little as 6 months.
If you look at page 7,
after an initial startup fee,
its projected
growth rate is at 14%.
I wish Oliver showed this kind
of interest in the business.
I inherited your
business sense.
Let me start Queen materials,
and I'll show you.
Well, i... I can't
approve this.
Why not?
Queen consolidated
is for Oliver.
He's going to inherit it,
and if anyone were to find out
that you're my daughter...
I need this.
Otherwise, I am
gonna have to find
the money
somewhere else,
and I need it
to help mom,
- something you never did.
- Emiko.
Do you ever even
think about us?
All the time,
and I wish things
were different.
I really do.
Since the day
you left,
I kept holding out,
thinking
one day you'd do
the right thing
and become the
father I deserved.
It's never gonna
happen, is it?
I have to go.
I have a trip planned
to China
on the Queen's Gambit.
And I'm sorry.
Is there something else you'd
like to talk to me about?
No. Have
a good trip.
You want to talk?
Not even to the guy
who found out
his long lost sibling
was secretly
an evil double agent?
Being reminded that
this has happened before
is not really
making things better.
I get that,
but I also know
that despite what
Emiko's done,
you're not quite ready
to give up on her.
That obvious, huh?
Only to someone
who knows you
and who's been there.
All I wanted was to bring
Andy back over to the light.
I don't have to remind you what
having that blind spot cost us.
No, you don't.
But please, John,
trust me when I tell you
that I am seeing Emiko more
clearly than I ever have.
Oliver, you're still
trying to save her.
John, my family
is to blame
for her current
situation.
My...
my father a-abandoned her and her mother.
She was 11!
She was 11 years old,
and no one's gonna
convince me that...
that her life wouldn't
be different now
if that had
never happened.
Andy tried to convince me
that I was the reason
for his bad choices, too.
He made me feel so guilty
that I was willing
to trust him again
even after knowing
he worked for
Damien darhk.
I held out hope, Oliver,
so much hope
that I put you,
my family,
my team at risk.
John, if I abandon
her now...
I'm no better
than my father.
If I can help
redeem her,
selfishly I feel like i...
I help redeem my family just...
A little.
Felicity got a hit
on The Ninth Circle.
Drones are at an abandoned
airfield north of the city.
And Emiko?
She's there.
Let's get the team.
Let's go.
All right. They're
still prepping the drones.
Good news is
we're not too late.
Bad news is
we're outnumbered 5 to 1.
Those are
my kind of odds.
- Got eyes on Dante.
- And Emiko.
Once the drones
are primed,
we can begin
the Demonstration.
Eight stolen drones,
which means 8 potential targets,
and each one runs
on a separate signal.
It's gonna take some time to
hack into the guidance system.
Oliver, that means that
you need to stop those things
before they take off.
You draw them out,
I'll get the drones.
Copy that.
Let's go!
Unh!
It's your brother.
I'll deal with him.
Pack up
the Demonstration.
No! The Demonstration
goes as planned.
Protect the drones.
Unh!
Dante!
Drive.
Damn it!
Emiko.
Get out of here.
Bad news, guys.
Those drones are airborne,
which means you need
to incinerate them mid-air
or else that's a lot of sarin
gas raining down on the city.
Overwatch, it would be very helpful
if I could see them.
OK. I'm working
on decloaking them now.
I'm in.
There's still
one drone left.
I'm working on it.
Emiko, it's not
too late.
Whatever you owe
Dante...
I owe Dante everything.
Dante taught me how
to take care of myself,
to cut the ties that bind us,
that hold us back,
which is why it's time
for us to say good-bye...
Brother!
Kill him!
Please tell me you got
that last drone.
By the time I locked on,
the gas had already been deployed.
Sorry, Oliver.
- How many casualties?
- None.
The target was an
abandoned building.
What about
the other targets?
Well, that's the even
weirder thing.
All of the other buildings
targeted were also empty.
Who goes to the trouble
of bombing empty buildings?
Seemed like some
sort of weapons test.
Well, imagine what would happen
if all the drones worked
instead of just one.
They'd be able to take out
multiple targets simultaneously.
If we couldn't stop
this test,
how are we gonna
stop the real thing?
Reacting
to the shocking allegations
about district attorney
Laurel Lance,
new photos show her with
notorious criminal Ricardo Diaz.
Could the city's
highest prosecutor
actually be
a wanted criminal herself?
Looks like
you've got a problem.
- You.
- Knocked off that Halcone?
I did.
Media's gonna have
a field day.
- You're a psycho.
- And you make me sad,
trying so hard to
become someone you're not,
and for what?
So that the city will take
you seriously as a hero.
That is almost as ridiculous
as you wanting to be one.
Get the hell out
of my office. Now!
I thought I was punishing
you for following me.
Maybe I just set
you free.
Oh, hey. Good.
You're still here.
I'm sorry.
It's been a day.
I assume that's
always the case.
Honestly, going over
Archer has made me happier
than I've been in months.
The algorithms you
programmed are like
this beautifully composed
rondo finale.
A rondo what, now?
Not into opera.
Got it.
Hey. So question
for version two.
- Mm-hmm?
- What happens when we
don't have the DNA of the
person that we are looking for?
- What do we do then?
- Well, that's a little trickier.
We could reprogram
the algorithm to highlight
any individuals whose DNA
we don't have,
but unless we hack into a
medical or criminal database
and collect all of
their DNA profiles first,
all we'd really be doing
is taking a couple pieces
of straw out of the haystack
we're looking in.
Ah. Guess we'd better
get to work then.
OK.
Felicity couldn't find her,
but you think you can, huh?
I just... I don't
want to give up.
Still trying
to redeem her?
Trying to stop her
before it's
too late.
You disobeyed
a direct order.
I gave you
that dagger.
The weapons test failed
because of your
brother's involvement.
Any more mistakes,
and the rest of The Ninth Circle
will mutiny.
- I am their leader.
- Then lead.
Where is your focus
at this critical time?
The family you swore to give up
to be part of The Ninth Circle.
Your absence
has been noted.
Thanks to my time
with Oliver,
I found something
even better.
The Archer Program,
cutting-edge
surveillance technology.
We can't stake our
future on technology
we haven't
even seen.
I need you
to trust my vision,
OK, trust that you
have taught me well,
but if you question
my authority again,
I'll kill you.
The Queen's Gambit sent
a mayday transmission
late last night
and has not been
heard from since.
Casualties of the
Queen's Gambit include
Starling City billionaire
Robert Queen
and his son Oliver.
While rescue teams continue
to comb the seas
in search of passengers...
Greg, move your head.