My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years I was stranded on
an island with only one goal--
to survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list of names
he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
The company Mrs. Queen
invested in doesn't exist.
Tempest purchased
a warehouse in Starling City.
Oliver, this is
my daughter, Helena.
The Starling City
vigilante comes and goes
as he pleases, doesn't he?
How did you know?
The minute I saw your eyes.
It's your fault
Michael's dead.
Not your father
for ordering the hit
or me for carrying it out.
That island changed you
in ways that
only someone like me
can understand.
I know it feels like
justice, but it's not.
Revenge is justice.
You feel the same as I do.
I know it.
[Dog barking]
[Speaking Chinese]
[Engine revving]
[Gunshots]
[Speaking Chinese]
[Car alarm]
[Brakes squealing]
Take your hands off me!
What the hell did you
think you were doing?
That man was the leader
of the Triad.
My father blames them
for the recent hits against his men.
These are men you killed.
That's right.
I take out Zhishan
and the Triad retaliates.
I have weakened my father's
organization to the point
where there is no way that
he can survive their onslaught.
What, and then you'll
have your revenge?
Then I have justice,
for what he did
to Michael and me.
It's not justice.
And what you do is?
Would you let me show you?
Get you anything else?
No, thank you, Carly.
Where's my brother-in-law?
It's late and this
is the Glades.
Shouldn't he
be keeping you safe?
She is tougher
than she looks.
I haven't been on a second
date in a while.
It feels good so far.
Look, um, we slept together,
and it was really nice.
And I needed it.
But I'm not looking for anything.
Right. Because you have
everything figured out.
I don't think
you're one to judge.
I saw you kill people,
remember?
I only kill people
when it is
absolutely necessary.
It's not
my opening move.
And the way
that you're going,
you're gonna get
somebody hurt,
like my mother
or yourself.
I'm sorry about your mother.
That was an accident.
How many more accidents
have to happen
before you're done
getting back at your father?
Hopefully none.
I am not getting back
at him.
I--I am stripping away
everything that
has meaning to him,
just like he did to me
when he had Michael killed.
What if I could show you
another way,
a way you could take down
your father's organization
without putting innocent
people at risk?
Thank you
for the coffee...
and the sex.
But I'm not interested.
I don't know where
the next Olympics are at,
but you might want
to think about signing yourself up.
So, you want to talk
about last night?
Okay. Last time
you and I spoke,
you were on your way
to stop Helena Bertinelli
from her one-woman war
against the Mafia.
How'd that work out
for you?
Nick Salvati,
Frank Bertinelli's right hand,
was found
with his neck snapped
along with a few
of his thugs.
Was that her or you?
I was with Helena
when somebody jumped us.
We didn't have a choice.
We?
She knows, Diggle,
about me.
It was my secret
or her life.
It's not just your secret
anymore, Oliver.
This woman is a killer. She's been
dropping bodies all over the city.
Diggle, she's not
what you think she is.
3 years ago she was gonna
turn her father in to the FBI.
She put everything
she had on him on a laptop.
Her father found it,
thought it belonged to her fiance,
and had him murdered.
All right, listen,
that's a heavy thing, man.
But it doesn't change
the fact that she is dangerous.
And if Bertinelli
retaliates against the Triad
or is perceived to, the Triad
is gonna rain down hell
and innocent people
are gonna be killed.
[Grunts]
She's lost, Diggle,
and whether she
knows it or not, I can save her,
stop her from
doing anything reckless.
That's just it.
You can't save her, okay?
Some people don't change.
I can.
I can help her.
All right.
Maybe you think you're more
persuasive than you are,
or maybe she thinks
she's fine the way she is
on her mission
of righteous fury.
Whatever it is,
either way,
all of this,
it ends badly.
Either way...
I got to try.
♪ Arrow 1x08 ♪
Vendetta
Original Air Date on December 5, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Where are you off to so early?
You just got home.
The trouble with traveling
overseas for a few weeks
is that a few weeks' worth
of work is piling up on my desk.
I just want to start digging
my way out from underneath it.
Of course.
What is it?
We haven't spoken
since you left.
Really spoken.
I know.
Well, I can imagine
finding out
that I had Robert's
yacht salvaged
and that he was murdered,
it was a lot for you to take in.
Yes, it was.
I just don't want you
to feel that you can't
trust me anymore.
I wasn't lying to--
to hurt you,
but to keep you safe.
I haven't changed,
Walter.
I'm still the woman
you fell in love with and married.
Do you see that?
Yeah.
Of course I do.
I just want us to agree
to be honest with
one another, moving forward.
Okay.
Yes, of course.
Walter.
Will you give me
a lift to school?
I like to mix it up sometimes
and actually be on time.
That would be
my parental privilege.
Or, you know, you could just
buy me a convertible
and then we could avoid this.
What, and miss out on all
those wonderful conversations
we have in the car?
I don't think so.
I'm so sorry, Frank.
The last thing you need
is me crying on your
shoulder all night.
I just can't believe
that Nick is gone.
Dina, look, you and Nicky,
you're like family
to me, okay?
And in my family,
we take care
of our own. Okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Nick was like
a brother to me.
Hey now, come on.
We'll talk to you
soon. Okay.
I'm gonna find
the son of a bitch who did this.
And on my life,
I'm gonna make him pay.
[Doorbell rings]
You know, that girl's
always forgetting something.
Frank.
Oh.
Sorry to drop by unannounced.
No, no, no, come on in.
It's all right.
Come on in. Um...
Look, I know, uh,
I know we've been working
on that construction deal,
and I'm sorry for
my dropping the ball.
We've had a death
in the family.
I'm terribly sorry
to hear that.
Thank you.
Actually, though,
I'm not here
to discuss business.
Oh. Okay.
Heh.
Well, this is, uh...
this is one merger
I won't stand in the way of.
Excuse me, sweetie.
A father knows
when he's not needed.
Was I not clear
that I wasn't interested
in talking?
You don't have to talk.
Who was she?
Somebody I knew a long time ago.
I--I was dating
her sister,
and it was getting serious.
But back then,
I did not do serious well.
But I was excellent
at screwing things up.
I started sleeping
with Sara.
I started sleeping with
my girlfriend's sister.
I brought her on the yacht
and she died.
Right in front of me.
And I hurt--
I hurt her family...
I just didn't care.
Before the island,
I wasn't a good person.
I was...
Selfish and thoughtless
and awful, and it affected--
really affected people.
People I loved.
'Cause, Helena...
You're on an island, too.
Oliver, I...
I want to let you in.
But...Michael was
the last man I opened up to.
I can't be hurt again.
I'd never hurt you.
I would never hurt you.
I promise.
Uh-uh. Relax.
Relax, relax, relax.
Now, pull back gently.
You need all 3 fingers
to come off the bowstring
at the same time.
Relax. Breathe.
And release.
[Clatters on floor]
This is a waste of time.
I'm trying
to teach you something.
What, the least effective way
to shoot people?
No. Control.
To use a bow and arrow
requires patience
and discipline.
[Thwack]
I can do this all day.
It's kind of fun.
I love a man with stamina.
Our crusades have
something in common.
Mine started
with my father, too.
He left me with a list.
People who need to be reminded
that Starling City isn't
theirs for the taking.
Anthony Venza is in here.
He works for my dad.
He deals illegal
prescription pills.
Diggle, this is Helena.
Diggle's my, uh...
Associate.
Well, any associate
of Oliver's is--
Absolutely nothing
to you, ma'am.
I'll leave you two
"associates"...
She knows my name.
That's lovely.
You can trust her.
Except I don't.
You sleeping
with this girl, Oliver?
Well, I don't think that's
any of your business, Diggle.
It became my business when
you brought me into this.
And when I signed on,
I told you I was gonna
keep your head straight.
Well, Oliver, you're lonely.
Lonelier than you want to admit.
And that's why you think
you can change this girl,
because you
need to think you can.
You're like a dope fiend
who thinks
he can deal with
his own addiction
by making another addict
go straight.
Oliver, what you do
is dangerous.
And getting confused about
who's good and who's bad
is a good way
to get yourself dead.
You done?
Yeah, I'm done.
With this.
Everything else, I don't know.
I don't know, Oliver.
You tell me.
[Telephone ringing]
I hope you don't have
plans tomorrow night,
because I just got us a rez
at that new restaurant,
Table Salt, opening night.
Isn't that place
ridiculously expensive?
Everywhere worth going is.
Ah, you have the cutest crinkle
in your forehead when you're worried.
Tommy, stop.
This is serious.
I thought you were going
to live more frugally.
Yeah, I know. Everybody
is grown up except for me.
Even Oliver has a job.
He's working on that new night club.
You have thinky face.
Why do you have thinky face?
Have you ever thought about
asking Oliver for a job?
Not even once.
This isn't a quality
that I love most about you,
but you do know the club scene
and how to have fun.
You make some
very valid points.
Look, I'll take care of it.
I'll talk to Ollie later
and we'll see
what he thinks.
He is gonna think
it is a great idea.
How was your trip
to Australia?
I've always wanted to go.
Down under. It's just--
I have this thing
about kangaroos.
More of a phobia.
They wig me out.
They look evil, and I'm
sure their picture's up
on like everything
everywhere in that country.
You had something
important to tell me, Ms. Smoak?
Yes, I did.
It's about Tempest.
Your wife's mysterious LLC,
the one she diverted
company funds to.
I appreciate your
diligence on this, but, uh,
it was a simple misunderstanding
between my wife and I.
Everything's been resolved.
No. See, it hasn't.
There was something
about the money transfer
that felt hinky to me.
The money your wife
withdrew from the company,
I wasn't the only one who tracked it.
She was being shadowed
by another entity,
and whoever it is,
they're good.
NSA good.
But, as you know,
I'm good, too.
So even though they
left almost no trace
of their presence
in our system,
I did manage
to find one thing.
Well, one image.
Does that symbol mean
something to you, sir?
No.
What means something to me
is one of my employees
prying into my wife's
private business
without authorization.
And should it happen again,
I'll have you suspended.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
Where's your friend?
Just the two of us
tonight.
Oh, really?
And what did you
have in mind?
An object lesson.
We're going after
Anthony Venza?
Yes. But we're doing it
on my terms.
Your father loses a piece
of his organization,
but no innocent people
get hurt in the process.
What is it?
I explained to you
that guns
were weapons of emotion
and unpredictability,
but since you are far
from an expert at archery,
this will have to do,
for now.
I like it.
You can't go out
like that.
Why? You got a spare hood?
Does it come in purple?
[Gasps]
I like purple.
This isn't crack.
Anyone can sell crack.
All you need's a street
corner and a hoodie.
This is pharmaceutical
grade Oxycodone.
It is caviar.
It is champagne.
And you sell this
with fancy houses,
at parties with rich kids
have got money to burn.
[Electricity crackling]
Check it out!
[Grunting, thwack]
Whoever you are,
you really think you're gonna
get out of here in one piece?
I was thinking
the same thing.
Anthony Venza...
You have failed this city.
Aah!
Uhh! The door!
Please...just don't hurt me.
Aww...
How about just a little?
[Groans]
[Sirens, indistinct
police radio]
Millions of dollars' worth
of illegal drugs confiscated,
a massive blow to your
father's criminal proceeds,
and nobody had to die.
Justice.
What do you think?
I think this feels good.
And not just
the justice part.
TV: Anthony Venza
was arrested last night.
The police confiscated
a warehouse
full of illegal
prescription drugs
with a street value
estimated in the millions.
Several unconfirmed
witnesses reported seeing
the Starling City vigilante
leaving the scene
with another
unknown accomplice...
[Glass shatters]
possibly a woman.
[Hits bar]
Bad year?
The scotch, I mean.
Yeah. Sorry.
Another business setback.
Wow.
You look beautiful.
[Chuckles]
Oliver Queen?
Oh...It's nice
to see you happy again.
It's been too long.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I heard about Venza.
Yeah, I know where
that leaves us!
I'm sorry to rush out.
I have this impromptu
Board of Directors meeting
with the Starling City
Modern Art museum.
I don't know much about art,
but I do know
how to pay for it.
No worries.
Whip them into shape.
Yes, sir. I'll see you
when I get back.
[Loud music, chatter]
Well, it's only been 30 minutes.
That's not too bad
for an opening.
If they don't seat us soon,
I'm going to write
a horrible review online.
Let me see what I can do.
Hey. I'm loving the Cavalli.
Uh, look, I'm Tommy Merlyn.
Is there any way that we can go
to the head of the class?
Is there?
[Clears throat] Let us know
when our table's ready, okay?
Maybe you can eat
some of those fancy peanuts
from behind the bar.
Hey!
Hi. It's the two of you.
Tommy, Laurel,
this is Helena.
Nice to meet you.
My pleasure.
Likewise.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Mr. Queen,
your table is ready.
When is our table
gonna be ready?
When it is.
Why don't you both
join us?
No, no, we're just
gonna have a drink and--
We'd love to.
Are you sure?
I'm sure I'm hungry.
That--[Clears throat]
That'll be great.
That sounds great.
There you go.
I had forgotten that you filled
your parents' pool with beer.
How many cases did that take?
Roughly a thousand or so.
You know, his father
was so pissed,
I thought he was actually
going to drown you in it.
Yeah, well, death by beer,
there's worse ways to go.
Right, Helena?
Well, there are
no good ways to die.
So, uh, how did you
and Tommy meet?
Actually, we've all known
each other since--
We've all known each other
forever.
You 3 have
a lot of history.
Sometimes a little too much.
Hmm.
So, how's the night club
coming along?
Slower than I expected
it to. I've, uh, I've been busy.
Well, then you must be happy
to have the extra help, then.
Laurel, I'm sure
that Oliver what do you mean?
Doesn't want to talk
about work right know.
You didn't ask him?
Ask me what?
Tommy wanted--Tommy said
that he was gonna talk to you
about working for you
at your night club.
[Oliver laughs]
Really?
Sorry. I didn't think
that you wanted
any responsibility at all.
Oh, yeah,
who'd believe that?
You've always wanted
to get into business with Tommy.
I mean, don't you remember
when we went to Aspen
and you wanted
to open a ski lodge?
The only thing
that I remember from Aspen
was your father being furious
we shared a room with one bed.
Wait, um...
So you two
were together...
And now you're dating
his best friend?
Yeah, we're just prime for
a reality show, aren't we?
Tommy, you working for me,
that could be fun.
I don't feel so good.
I'm gonna step outside.
I should probably
go check on him.
Helena, it was very nice
to meet you.
Tommy, why are you so upset?
Why did you have to say
something to Oliver about the job?
You were supposed
to talk to him.
Well, I hadn't.
Okay, I didn't realize.
I was only trying to help.
No, you were trying
to get Oliver to help.
It's typical Laurel.
Always running to a white knight.
It's Oliver and Laurel.
It always has been.
That's not gonna change.
Oliver and I are over.
Oh, really? Because you seemed
awfully bothered by his new girlfriend.
What, am I supposed
to like her?
I do not want to be
Oliver's charity case, okay?
To every day be reminded
that I can't give you
everything he could?
You know, losing a fortune
I think is going to be
easier than losing you,
so why don't we
just stop now.
Hey. I'm sorry.
How am I supposed to know
it's gonna get so weird in there?
No, I'm sorry.
Sorry I ever listened to you.
Helena, what--
you know what
I've been through.
I told you I couldn't
be hurt again.
I'm not trying
to hurt you.
So, making me have dinner
with the love of your life
is what, Oliver?
Laurel was the girl things
were getting too serious with,
the girl whose sister's grave
you used to manipulate me.
I saw the way
you looked at her.
That kind of love
doesn't die.
You still love her.
I don't.
[Scoffs]
Don't.
Hey.
Don't touch me.
I am done talking.
I came to apologize.
I know you were
just trying to help.
I guess I wasn't ready
to face reality.
This is just so new,
you and me,
and I didn't
want you to see...
I'm scared.
I'm almost 30 years old
and I've never been given
an ounce of responsibility
in my life.
You, you are driven
and intelligent.
You're a million times
too good for me,
even before I was broke.
And now I have absolutely
nothing to bring to whatever this is.
I never cared
about the money.
And truth be told,
billionaire
was your least
attractive quality.
I am so sorry if I pushed you
too hard on the job with Oliver.
I just--I thought you working
for him was a good idea
because
he's your friend.
And it's okay to ask
a friend for help.
You won't lose
your street cred.
I'm happy to lose
my street cred.
I just don't want
to lose you.
Well...
I'm not saying that
it's gonna be easy...
But I'm here for you
if you need someone
to lean on.
That's what people do
when they're together.
Together like
boyfriend-girlfriend?
Mm. Do not ruin
this moment.
It was going so well
for you.
[Laughs]
Didn't expect to hear
from you tonight.
Something happen?
[Sighs]
I think you were right.
Okay. About which part?
All of it.
I should have listened to you.
Oliver, you said you wanted
to help her change.
The thing is,
she already did change.
When her father
killed her fiance,
she changed into something
dark and twisted.
You see that now, don't you?
It's not that I--it's not
that I couldn't see it, Diggle.
I didn't--I didn't want to.
I'm living a double life,
and to do that,
I'm taking all these people
that I love
and I'm putting them
at arm's length.
I'm giving up a lot,
so maybe--
maybe I thought
the universe owed me one.
But I looked in
her eyes tonight,
and I can't stop her
from going over the edge.
She's--she's already past it.
[Cell phone rings]
[Cell phone vibrates]
[Cell phone beeps]
[Speaking Chinese]
[Caller speaking Chinese]
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
[Speaking Chinese]
I don't speak Chinese,
so I'm just gonna assume
you said good-bye.
[Groaning]
Tell your mistress
Frank Bertinelli sends his regards.
Ahem.
You wanted to see me,
Mr. Steele?
Did I mention,
it's almost Christmas,
and many of the suicides
this time of year
are due to sudden
and unexpected joblessness?
I want you to find out
all you can about that notebook.
Where it was made,
how it was purchased.
And what it could mean.
Yes, sir.
Felicity...
I asked Josiah Hudson,
our head of security,
to look into
the same subject matter.
He died the next day
under questionable circumstances.
What I may be asking of you,
this mystery,
are you sure
you want to do this?
I hate mysteries.
They bug me.
They need to be solved.
[Cell phone vibrates]
It's Dig.
What's the situation?
War.
Boss, we just got word--
somebody hit Zhishan.
He's dead.
All right. Then we know
what's coming next.
Tell everyone
to strap up.
[Rustling]
Uhh!
[Speaking Chinese]
Ricco's not answering
his walkie. Check it out.
[Thwack]
[Gunfire]
Frank Bertinelli--
this is for Zhishan.
Uhh!
Run.
Aah!
Ohh! Oh!
[Groaning]
Oh--Helena.
What is this?
Payback for Michael.
I know you had him killed.
Salvati told me.
I did that to protect
the family!
I had to take everything
away from you
because you took
everything away from me.
You finally know
what it feels like
to find out, your own blood
is responsible
for the death
of your entire world.
No!
Helena?
[Siren]
Helena.
[Indistinct police radio]
[Gasps]
Helena, easy. Easy.
You were lucky.
Am I supposed
to be grateful?
Helena--
He's a monster.
A criminal.
Why would you save him?
I didn't save him.
I saved you.
You think that because
you've killed,
you understand what it's like
to have blood on your hands.
You don't understand.
You don't understand
the toll
that it takes on you,
especially
when it's your father.
I'm not going to stop.
The police
have him in custody.
He's going to jail
and then on to prison.
They don't have
any evidence on him.
They do now.
The laptop.
He's going away, Helena,
for the rest of his life.
This...is justice.
Then I guess you were right.
I'm more interested
in revenge.
Stay out of my way, Oliver,
or I'll make sure your secret
doesn't stay secret.
Helena.
What I did,
everything that I've done,
I've done because
I care about you.
Too bad I can't say
the same.
Hey, you.
Thanks for the call.
What are
ex-sisters-in-law for?
Mm.
Chili cheese fries
with jalapenos. Hmm.
That's a cry for help
if I've ever seen one.
Ahh...
I don't know what hurts worse,
this or getting shot
with a curare-laced bullet.
Been there, done that.
Definitely the bullet.
Ah...
[Sighs]
You know, Oliver, I'm
no expert at this, but...
I don't think love is about
changing or saving a person.
I think it's about
finding the person
who's already the right fit.
One day you will.
I think I burnt
that particular bridge.
Napalmed it, actually.
So things didn't work out
exactly as you planned.
You did save
Frank Bertinelli's life.
He'll be doing time
for a while.
Justice wins out.
Helena
doesn't see it that way.
You opened up,
took a risk with your heart.
The Oliver I met
a few months ago
would not have been
able to do that.
And when you meet
the right person,
you'll be ready for her.
[Both laughing]
What are you doing?
It needs to be dark in here
for me to do this.
If I had had more time
to think of that sentence
it wouldn't have sounded
so dirty.
Look.
I don't see anything.
I got these
from applied sciences.
They're able to pick up
the subvisible variations
in the UV spectrum.
Now look at the book again.
[Thunder]
Hi.
Now, look,
I'm sorry about last night.
It just--I let it
get too far
sitting at the same table.
That was...
that was stupid.
No. I was stupid.
I haven't been
entirely honest with you.
My dad cut me off.
He froze all my funds.
I am living on fumes.
Really?
Why didn't you
say anything?
Embarrassment,
shame, jealousy,
probably a few other emotions
I'm not used to feeling.
Tommy, my trust fund
is your trust fund.
No.
That is the easy answer.
And believe me,
I have loved easy answers.
What I need is a job.
I'm trying to change.
Not sure into what yet,
but...
I don't want to be
what I was anymore.
It just so happens
that I have
a general manager
position
that is available.
You're probably
the guy for the job.
Will I be getting dental?
This smile wasn't cheap.
I'll look into that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You okay?
I will be.
Something happen with Helena?
We had a falling out.
But I have a feeling that
I will be seeing her again.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==