Previously on "Arrow"...
Who's the blackmailer?
He calls himself
the Calculator.
Well, Calculator
now has everything he needs
to melt the Internet.
Oh, my God. Dad?
Taiana, I need to
tell you something.
I killed your brother.
Thea!
What's happening?
It's the wound
from Ra's.
If the life she
owes doesn't come
from taking others,
it will come
from the life
of the host.
Thea, please don't go.
There's only one way
to prevent that.
My father once told me
of an elixir known
as the Lotus,
and I will freely give
it to you on one condition.
I want you to kill
Malcolm Merlyn.
If you cared
about Thea,
then curing
her bloodlust
wouldn't come
with any conditions.
Thea is my
sister-in-law.
You are my husband.
I'm not your husband.
But war does not know
family bonds
nor friendly sentiments.
Who are you
at war with?
I just told you I want you
to kill Malcolm Merlyn.
Try to guess.
Hey, hey.
If you have
a problem
with Malcolm Merlyn,
deal with it
yourself.
Do not involve me
or my sister.
You put the Demon's Head
ring on Malcolm's hand.
You--
You can't
defeat him.
But you can.
You have.
And that was
before I knew
that he was
my sister's father.
So he dies
so his child might live.
Didn't your father make
a similar bargain?
I'm sorry, Oliver.
I would not resort
to this
if I had
any other choice.
Nyssa, my sister
is dying
because of something
that your father did.
I think you have
every choice.
Thea is dying because
of what her father did.
I am only following events
to their inevitable conclusion.
♪ Arrow 4x13 ♪
Sins of the Father
Original Air Date on February 10, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You know, it's strange,
watching your baby girl
drink coffee.
Yeah. It would probably
be a little less strange
if you'd seen your
baby girl in the last 18 years.
You're right.
I don't suppose it
helps
if I say that I thought
staying out of your life
was the best thing
for you.
I was protecting you
and your mother.
You were protecting
yourself.
You were wanted
by the police,
and you didn't want
to go to jail.
That is why you
stayed away.
And you know why
the police were after me,
the type of criminal
I was?
Mom never went
into detail.
I assume petty stuff.
Anything else requires
commitment.
Well, I'm here now,
and I want us
to speak openly.
I'll answer
any questions you have.
Ok. I just have one
at the moment.
Why now?
I was doing a job
for someone.
Almost got beat, almost.
My adversary had
exceptional skills.
My curiosity piqued.
I investigated further.
Imagine
what I discovered...
Overwatch.
Bye.
See you never.
Felicity, wait.
It is not
what you think.
My employer, my work
is hardly diabolical.
I'll be sure to tell that to
my friend who you blackmailed.
Short-term legal mischief
for long-term societal game.
Isn't that kind
of hacktivism exactly
what you did at MIT?
Is it really
all that different
from the vigilantism
you practice today?
We are the same,
you and I.
I am pretty sure
that I didn't try
to kill 8,000 people.
An empty threat,
I swear to you.
I know I have no right.
I'm asking for a chance,
a chance to prove to you
that I'm not a bad guy
and that I'm not
a "bad guy."
What is that?
A record of some
of the hacks I've done
throughout the years.
I've selected ones that
could be verified
by news accounts
so you know
I'm telling the truth.
This is very simple
for me, Felicity.
I want to be back
in your life.
I know that doing that
will require
earning your trust back.
I hope this is
a first step
down that very long road.
So Nyssa's holding
Thea's life hostage
until you kill
Malcolm Merlyn?
I would be surprised
if she wasn't
the daughter
of the Demon.
That's not funny, John.
No, it's not.
Thea's dying.
She has one,
maybe two days,
and if we can
save her
by killing the man
that killed my sister,
then how could you
even think twice about that?
I'm not gonna
defend Malcolm.
He orchestrated
your sister's murder,
he killed Tommy.
Nothing is ever gonna
changed the fact
that he is Thea's family.
I don't know how much
you remember of my father,
but he was not
a good man,
he threw in
with Malcolm Merlyn,
and all of that being said,
there is nothing
that I wouldn't do
to have him back.
So you tell me how am I supposed to
take that away from Thea?
But, Oliver, what's
the difference if Thea dies?
It doesn't have to
come to that, John.
There's more than
one choice here.
Like what?
Diplomacy.
What does Nyssa want?
I mean, all Nyssa really wants
is control of the League,
so I need to convince
Merlin to give her the ring,
she gives us the cure,
and no one has to die.
Laurel, can you convince Nyssa
to go along with that?
Yeah. It's easier
than talking Malcolm into it.
Well, let me worry
about Malcolm.
I don't understand.
Why would you save me
only to kill my brother?
Vlad attacked me.
Vlad would never do
such a thing.
I was defending
myself,
and I did not know
he was your brother.
Would that have made
a difference?
I didn't
have a choice.
There is always
a choice.
I couldn't just
let him kill me.
I'm done with you.
Taiana, I have
something that Reiter wants.
Where did you
get that?
It doesn't matter.
I think that we can
use this against him.
I have a better idea.
- Hey!
- Hey, Tai--
Get Reiter.
Tell him I want to
talk to him.
I have something
that he wants.
Let me see if I've
got this right.
There's a magic potion
that could cure Thea's bloodlust
that we've never
heard of
but Nyssa
conveniently has.
I've been holding off
telling you this for years, Oliver.
You're very handsome,
not especially bright.
Bright enough
to have checked.
It's called the Lotus.
Tatsu Yamashiro is part of the order
who guards it--or did.
They gave it to Nyssa,
and if we don't get her
to give it to Thea now...
We're gonna lose her.
Even assuming such
an elixir existed,
even assuming
Miss Yamashiro's order
parted with it
willingly,
even assuming
Nyssa Al Ghul's words
could be trusted,
then yes.
Of course I'd do anything to
save my daughter,
but none of that
is true, Oliver.
Look. I appreciate
you're trying to embrace
a more optimistic
viewpoint these days--
Malcolm, we're talking
about your daughter.
Yes, and I need to do
something to save her,
and you need to stop
wasting my time
with Nyssa Al Ghul's
games.
We found her
at the perimeter.
She claims to be
a friend.
And she speaks
the truth,
at least until she
defiled my beloved
and stood idly by
while I was left to rot
in a dungeon.
Leave us.
Nyssa...
How is my beloved?
Sara's good.
She's whole.
I think she's happy.
If you're here
about Thea--
Nyssa, what are
you doing?
Protecting
my birthright.
By holding Thea's
life hostage?
You say that as if
she didn't fire the arrows
that felled
your sister.
You and I both
know that wasn't her doing.
Yes. It was
Malcolm Merlyn,
and the time has come
for recompense.
I will never
forgive Merlyn
for all the horrible
things that he's done.
He's taken people,
two very special people
away from me.
Don't you think
I want him dead?
Then why are you here?
Because if you want
Merlyn dead,
then you have to
drive that sword,
and if you can't
or if you won't,
then we'll need to
negotiate a compromise.
You have my attention.
Oliver convinces Merlyn
to give up the power,
and you...
And you give us
the cure.
I would accept
those terms,
but Merlyn
never will.
Let us worry
about that.
And by "us," you
mean my husband?
Oliver's speaking
with Merlyn right now,
and Merlyn--he is
a bastard,
but there is nothing that he wouldn't do
to save his daughter.
I hope so
because if he doesn't
it won't just be
Thea's life that is forfeit.
What do you mean?
There will be war,
and the streets
of your home
will run red
with the blood
of our enemies,
whomever
they may be.
How'd it go
with Merlyn?
Not good. Nyssa?
She brought an army,
but if you get her the ring,
she'll play ball.
We can get this done
with no one getting hurt.
Everything all right?
No, not really.
I mean, it's not great.
It's just not quite
at the level
of "my sister's on her deathbed"
kind of bad, so...
What happened?
My dad came back.
And why is
that a bad thing?
Well, it's an extremely
long story,
but you remember the superhacker
who blackmailed Roy?
- Same guy.
- What?
Your father is...
Calculator.
He showed up
at my Palmer Tech
presentation.
I had coffee
with him yesterday,
where he dropped
the Calculator bomb on me.
And why
would he do that?
Apparently now that
he knows what I do,
that we're both
"vigilantes,"
we have something
in common.
The sickest part is
I want to believe him.
I wish there were
some sort of test
I could do that would
prove that he is who he says he is.
A test is
a good idea.
It's a good idea
for you and for us.
I've got a way
to bring Merlyn
to the bargaining table.
I'm not usually one
to be summoned by my prisoners.
I heard you had
something for me.
Taiana, please. No.
I have something
you want.
Let me out of this cage,
and it's yours.
Show me
what you have.
Magnificent.
Do we have a deal?
A deal?
You misunderstood.
It's mine
either way.
Ohh!
I cannot stay here,
Reiter.
This man killed
my brother.
And you will continue to
care for him
as if he were
your brother.
Mr. Queen is
an important piece
of my endeavor
on this island.
You'll stay with him
until he's well.
If his health gets worse,
you'll join him
in his fate.
Your left-side block
is slow.
Your next opponent
won't have my patience
or my mercy.
Clearly you don't
understand how this is
supposed to work,
my husband.
You were supposed to bring
the Magician with you.
Well, I need something
from you first--
proof that what
you're offering is real.
A stalling tactic.
Al Sa-Her thinks
me the fool
or that you're one.
Or maybe he doesn't
trust the woman
trying to take the Demon's Head
ring from him.
Can't imagine why.
Bring me a sample
of the Lotus.
I recognize
what you are doing.
Part of me
even respects it,
but the leadership
of the League of Assassins
is in the balance here.
It is naive to think
this can be resolved
without bloodshed.
This amount is not sufficient
to cure her permanently,
only to provide
the assurance Merlyn seeks.
Thank you, Nyssa.
As I said, someone
is going to die.
I pray it won't
be your sister.
Was it difficult to
get her discharged from the hospital?
No. I spoke
to Dr. Lamb.
Friend of the family.
Nyssa...
She hooked us up
with a sample of the cure.
This buys Thea
some more time,
and you get the proof
that you need.
Let's see it.
What are
Nyssa's terms?
You hand over the ring,
she gives us the rest
of the elixir,
and Thea lives.
When can we meet?
Tonight.
Laurel's with her now.
Hi! I got your--
Oh, no.
Oh, no. You have
Mr. Square Bear face.
What?
Mr. Square Bear.
Oh, my God.
You don't remember.
You lost him when you
were, like, 4 years old,
and you had
that exact--
you had that exact look
on your face.
Oh, baby.
Is it too much
to hope that you lost
a plushy toy?
No, but adjusting
for age and inflation,
might be just as bad.
Huh?
You want to sit?
What? What's up?
It's dad.
Noah--he's
in Star City.
What? How do you know?
He came to see me.
Did you talk
to him?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Yeah. You sound like
you think he'd hurt me or something.
Yeah.
I've just been
doing some checking.
Is it possible
that he's not
the guy we
thought he was,
that maybe
he's better
than we thought
he was?
No.
Felicity, I would love
to think that your father
didn't show up
with some ulterior motive
in your life right now,
but I've been
where you are more times
than I care to admit,
and it always ends the same way.
He tells you exactly
what you want to hear,
and you get sucked in,
and the next thing you know,
you have no job,
no money,
and a sweet
7-year-old daughter
who needs
a new pair of shoes
and wants to go
to Space camp.
People don't change,
even if you
want them to.
Ok.
You're doing
the right thing.
I'm only entertaining
Oliver's naive plan
out of respect
for our marriage,
but his hope blinds him
to reality.
You come dressed
for battle, Al Sa-Her.
Just
for the occasion.
In exchange for
my daughter's life.
I'm glad you've
finally seen reason.
Sadly, the only
thing I have seen
is your quick
and speedy death.
Malcolm!
I knew you couldn't
be trusted.
You knew, and you
didn't prepare,
and here you are
outnumbered, outgunned,
out maneuvered
per usual.
Nyssa, don't!
Kill him!
We need to stop them
before they kill each other.
Retreat!
Don't let her
get away!
Malcolm,
stop this now!
Get out of my way,
Oliver!
Think about Thea!
Do not question
my love
for my daughter.
Everything I do,
I do it for her.
I'm not moving.
So much
for the Gandhi method.
Given who
we're dealing with,
we shouldn't be
surprised.
I can't believe
that being Ra's Al Ghul
is more important
to Malcolm
than saving
his daughter's life.
I know that you're
trying a new approach,
but just because
you've changed,
that doesn't mean
everybody else has.
We cannot allow
a League civil war.
Too many people
will be collateral damage.
And the 4 of us
definitely can't take on
two armies
of assassins.
Then we take down
the generals.
We need to work on
locating Nyssa and Malcolm.
But mainly Nyssa
because she's got
that whole Lotus
cure thing.
We find both of them.
No one else dies
tonight.
Especially Thea.
You need this to keep
your fever at bay.
If it comes back,
well, that would be
very bad.
I'm surprised
you still care.
Baron Reiter made it
very clear
what happens to me
if you die.
Taiana, I know what
you're going through.
It's this feeling
in the pit of your stomach.
It's an emptiness--
Don't you dare try to
help me mourn
my brother that
you took from me.
Please just listen.
You know nothing
about how I feel!
A man with a heart
as small as yours
is incapable
of such things.
My father sacrificed
himself
so I could survive,
so that I could
right his wrong.
He did it
by pulling out a gun
and shooting himself
in the head
not 3 feet from me.
Since that day,
I have lost
4 more people
that I love,
that I cared
so much about.
It never
gets easier ever.
I could see it
in your eyes
from the moment
we first met.
That I was good?
No. That you were lost,
shattered.
There is a Russian saying--
"tot zhe molot chto
drobit steklo, kuyet stal."
"The same hammer
that shatters glass forges steel."
If you want to be the man
that your father wishes you to be,
then this is how
you'll get there.
You save us
from Reiter,
but you cannot
do that shattered.
Hey. Everyone's
telling the same story--
guys in black robes
fighting each other.
Yeah. League
of Assassins.
They're working on
some leadership issues.
Yeah, but how many
more people are gonna die
before that happens?
Yeah. We're working
on it.
You got to work faster.
This is just
the beginning.
Hey.
I think we need
to talk.
About what?
About the elephant
in the room.
The way this is going down,
it ends one way--
Malcolm Merlyn.
He has to be taken
down, Oliver.
You're the only man
who's ever done it.
Malcolm's killed
hundreds of people.
He killed Tommy,
he killed Sara.
Thea is dying
right now because
of events that he
set in motion.
I have never
hated anyone
the way that
I hate him.
You've been
in denial, Oliver,
holding onto hope
with both hands
that you don't have to
give in to that hate,
use that hate to do
what needs to be done,
but, Oliver, this
needs to be done.
You have to kill
Malcolm Merlyn.
I'm glad you called.
Well, all your
files checked out,
and I did some additional
digging myself.
You're right.
You and I, we're
not all that different.
This facility is
really amazing.
Yes. After numerous
false starts
we finally got the R&D section
working like a Swiss watch.
This floor contains most
of our bleeding edge projects.
Ah.
That is an autonomous
communications device
3 generations
beyond Bluetooth.
But there are no seams
in the casing.
I know. It's built
from a single piece of aluminum.
The entire surface connects
to an induction charger.
How did you achieve
the heat sink?
Curtis Holt achieved
it actually.
He's quite the genius.
Don't sell
yourself short.
You're the Steve Jobs
in this equation.
Heh.
Thank you for agreeing
to give me
a second chance.
Baby steps then.
Baby steps.
Hmm.
I have eyes on Nyssa.
Abandoned complex
at 7th and Rucka.
Put the word out
among our assets in Star City.
Whoever leads us to Al Sa-Her will be
rewarded handsomely.
Keep her there.
We're on our way.
Nyssa, stop!
- Step aside, Laurel.
- No.
I will not let you wage
your war in my city.
I bargained
in good faith.
I'm only finishing
what he started,
and I aim to end
it swiftly.
To what cost?
How many lives
will you sacrifice
for what?
I will only say
this once more.
Step aside.
No. You're coming
with me.
Am I?
We're under attack!
We have to get
out of here.
Run!
Go! Get inside.
Cowards just like
their master.
Sorry, Nyssa.
For what?
For that.
I was in a cell
much like this one
barely a year ago.
Nyssa, where is
the Lotus?
Safe.
This isn't a game,
Nyssa.
Thea is dying,
innocent civilians are dying,
your own men
are dying.
And surrendering
my only leverage
will not save
their lives.
No, but it will
save Thea's.
How could you be
so selfish?
A question better put
to Malcolm Merlyn.
He doesn't have
the cure, you do.
Using Thea's life
as a bargaining chip,
letting people die
for a lost cause--
Nyssa, this isn't
who you are.
It's who
your father was,
but he's gone,
he's dead,
and you can
finally be free.
Any luck?
Malcolm and the League
have gone to ground,
Nyssa is a brick wall,
John and Laurel are out
searching for the Lotus,
but we are running
out of places to look.
Well, that's
depressing.
Well, we will find it.
We have to.
Mm-hmm.
Is everything
all right?
Not really.
I mean, it's not
as bad as your sister being
unconscious in our sublevel,
but...
Did something happen
with your dad?
More like something
didn't happen.
What's that?
It's an IR burst
receiver,
incredibly advanced.
It can suck the data
out of any room
you put it into.
Don't worry.
I turned it off
before bringing
it down here.
It's not yours?
It's my father's.
I gave him a little
tour of Curtis' R&D lab,
and he left this
behind as a souvenir.
He's trying to steal
from Palmer Tech?
It was your idea
actually.
You needed proof
about the Lotus,
I needed proof
about my dad.
You set a trap
for him as a test.
Unrestricted access
to Palmer Technologies' R&D lab.
He flunked
with flying colors.
I don't even know
why I'm surprised.
You're surprised
because you're hoping
that he's the parent
you've always wanted him to be,
the parent you deserve.
In an extremely
ironic role reversal,
my mother was
smarter than me.
She said, "People
don't change,
no matter how much
you want them to."
Some people don't.
Uh-huh.
I'd like to think that
there's hope
for the rest of us,
or I did
as far as Malcolm
is concerned.
John thinks
I should kill him.
If it'd help save Thea,
I agree.
Yeah, and I'd agree
if he wasn't Thea's father,
but he is.
We are in this mess
because of him
on, like, a million
different levels.
Let's not pretend that
this is a typical
father-daughter
relationship.
He brainwashed her
into killing a friend.
I know all this.
I do,
and I'm still
holding out hope
that with--with--
with time
and with how much
he says that he loves her
that maybe they have
some chance
at some type
of normal relationship.
If I kill him...
My sister never
gets that chance.
Thea's father is no more likely to
change than mine is.
What now?
Found Malcolm.
Where?
Right underneath us.
Malcolm!
The Lotus effect
is wearing off.
She will pass by sunrise.
I would like to be
by her side.
This has to end.
No more games.
You give Nyssa
the damn ring!
She was 4 months old
when we first met.
Your housekeeper Raisa,
I believe,
was picking you up
from our house
with Thea in a stroller.
I peeked my head
into the bassinette,
and Thea, all
of 16 weeks,
she stuck her tongue
out at me.
I always knew I was
connected to her,
as if on some primal level
I knew I was her father.
A real father wouldn't let
their child die
just to keep
his hands on power!
That is not
what I am doing.
What's unfolding here
is larger than I,
and it is bigger
than my daughter.
It's not just her life that hangs in
the balance, Oliver.
For all your dealings
with the League,
you still remain ignorant
to what it is
they do for the world.
Enough
about the League.
You're a group
of Assassins.
It is a force of change
silently manipulating
global events
for hundreds of years,
and I cannot,
I will not put
that kind of power
into Nyssa Al Ghul's hands!
Let me ask you
something.
If Damien Darhk came
to you and told you
to lay down your bow,
let him finish his plan for Star City,
would you do it?
Even if it meant
saving William's life?
I know everything
about you, Oliver.
I am Ra's Al Ghul,
but back
to the matter at hand.
You will never sacrifice
your city to save your son,
and believe me
when I tell you
that I am only making
the same choice.
No. I would look
for another choice,
and I wouldn't
stop looking
until there was
a third option!
Malcolm, what if--
what if you could
have the Lotus
and keep your ring?
I don't see how.
Nyssa's forces are stronger
than I care to admit.
Not by herself.
You challenge her
to a trial
by combat.
You do realize your plan
would end in her death?
We're all backed
into a corner, Malcolm.
Nyssa made her bed.
This is one of your
crazier ideas,
and that is
a competitive field.
Well, sit tight.
I have a crazier one coming.
In deference
to good taste,
we will forego
the removal of shirts.
Let us be finished
with this charade.
As you wish.
Hold!
In the eyes of the League,
this woman is my wife.
As your husband,
I wish to fight
on her behalf.
I have never allowed
anyone to fight
my battles for me.
Do you want to
become Ra's,
or do you want
to die?
Why are you doing this?
You told me yourself you
couldn't defeat Merlyn,
and if I am forced
to choose
between your life
and his...
Then I will see
justice done.
I'm a little
disappointed I must say.
You're the one who put us
in this position, Malcolm.
Can I remind you
the role you played
in putting this ring
on my finger?
Oh, I remember.
Tonight I correct
that mistake.
I can't believe it.
You've grown even more foolish
with experience.
3 years!
Let's finish this.
Unh!
Last chance, Malcolm.
Yield!
Never.
To end this,
you must kill me.
But you always
knew that, Oliver.
I didn't want it
to end this way.
Spare me
the false sympathy.
Just do it.
Aah! Err!
Bring me the Lotus.
You are Ra's Al Ghul.
Thank you, husband.
What--what is
going on?
Is everything ok?
That, uh, depends.
How are you feeling?
I'm--ahem--I'm
a bit tired,
but--
What am I doing here?
It's a long story,
but to shorthand it--
Is that you're
gonna be fine.
The cure worked.
No more bloodlust.
Come on. Let's go get you
into some regular clothes.
Yeah. Um...
Oliver, you did
it, man.
Thea's fine,
and Nyssa and Merlyn
didn't have to die.
Ooh, yeah. Not to be
the buzzkill,
but when are we gonna
tell Thea about Malcolm's mmmrrr?
Baby steps.
Right.
What's up?
Something my father said.
Brought you
a portable ramp,
so anytime you come
across a higher surface,
just unfold it.
This will get you
over almost anything.
Look. I have
a meeting in a few.
I just wanted to
say good-bye.
Good-bye?
We're just starting
to get to know each other.
I think I know everything
I need to know.
Felicity, what
is going on?
I--I thought we
were making progress.
When I was a girl,
I hated myself.
I thought I was broken,
that no one could
or ever would love me.
It's the only way
a child can grow up
when their father
abandons them.
Felicity--
All I ever wanted to
know was why.
What was so wrong
with me that you would leave?
There was nothing
with you, sweetheart.
There was everything
wrong with me.
The police, the FBI,
they were never going to
stop looking for me.
I realized a life
on the run,
that wasn't the life
that I owed you
or your mother,
so I disappeared.
You thought you were
doing the right thing for us.
Exactly.
I have waited
my entire life
for that explanation,
and the thing is
I don't even know if I believe it.
It's the truth.
There is only one part
of your story
that I know to be true,
and that is that you
are wanted by the police.
Felicity--
I just need you to know
one thing.
You are wrong.
I am nothing like you.
Felicity.
Noah Kuttler,
you're under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
- Anything you say can...
- Felicity, no.
And will be used
against you in a court of law.
Don't do--
don't do this.
Thank you both
for coming.
How is Thea?
Don't pretend
like you care.
I do. She's
my sister-in-law,
and her condition is
the result
of my father's blade.
You were right.
Even after his death,
I remained
my father's prisoner.
I allowed him to turn me
into someone
you showed me
I don't have to be...
And you showed me, as well,
when you took up the sword
to save my life.
You both showed me
what needed to be done.
And what's that?
Patience, please.
We're waiting for one other.
Thank you for coming,
Al Sa-Her.
You're Ra's.
I had no choice.
And so you are
mistaken once again.
What are you doing?
Earlier today,
I disbanded
the League of Assassins.
I released its forces
much as my father
had released you long ago.
No one will be held prisoner
by my father any longer.
I thought of you
as a son once, Oliver.
I had more in common
with you than my own blood,
but that's not the reason
why I'm not going to kill you.
Neither the fact
that you are
my daughter's brother.
The reason you get
to live
is because death
would be a mercy compared
to the debt I now
owe you.
Don't you dare
threaten me, Malcolm.
Taiana.
I promise I will
free your friends for Vlad.
Vlad is dead.
We do this for them.
Mr. Queen.
I hope you have
regained your strength.
The stone you gave me
was the final piece of the puzzle,
the final map.
We are going to dig.
Dig?
The heaven I seek
is not above
but rather
beneath our feet.
We dig at daybreak.
Hey.
You feeling
any better?
I don't even know
why I'm so upset.
Doesn't every
long-awaited
father-daughter
reunion end
with the dad being taken away
in handcuffs.
You don't have to be
funny for me.
You know that, right?
I know.
And I know I did
the right thing,
but...
The look on his face
when he realized
I had turned him in,
it's gonna haunt me
for the rest of my life,
and I can't help
but think he doesn't
even deserve that
kind of remorse.
I think that remorse
is a pretty clear indicator
that you are a very different
person than him.
Maybe Thea and I
could make T-shirts.
We could join a club.
Listen to me.
Don't make the mistake
of thinking that this thing
with your dad is over.
I can tell you
from experience
that closure does not
come that easily.
Hmm.
Speaking of closure,
are you punishing yourself
for betraying Malcolm?
Is that insane?
Yes,
but it's part of what makes you
the man I love.
John was right.
You were faced
with an impossible situation,
and you found
the best way out of it.
Will you marry me?
I think I already answered
that question.
Thea's better,
Andy's better,
things are quiet
on the Darhk front.
I feel like this might
be our window,
and with everything
that we have gone through
over the past few months,
I want you to tell me
why are we waiting?
Well, we'll have to plan it.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe just
a small ceremony
with a few of our friends
and no caterers.
My mom will
hate that.
I'm in.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I don't like to be
kept waiting.
My apologies.
I don't have the resources
I once had.
Yes. I'm aware of your recent
reversal of fortune.
I take it that's why you asked
for this meeting.
Well, I haven't come
empty-handed.
So to speak.
I have some information
that you might find
of particular interest.
I know who Oliver Queen
cares about more than
anyone in the whole world.
Yeah, so do I.
We did a pretty good number on her
over the holidays.
It's not Felicity Smoak.
Who?
His son...
William.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.