Previously, on "Arrow"...
I got an ID on our Mr. Creepy.
I'm not sure what
that symbol means.
It means anarchy.
Lonnie Machin.
Full time crazy pants.
Speedy, don't!
Sometimes, the best way to teach
someone a lesson isn't to punish them;
it's to punish the ones
he cares about the most.
Felicity Smoak...
Would you make me
the happiest man
on the face of the Earth?
Yes!
Now I know...
That it's not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility?
To do what?
To end it.
I'm going to kill him.
Where is Damian Darhk?!
Where's Darhk?!
Where is Darhk?
♪ Arrow 4x10 ♪
Blood Debts
Original Air Date on January 20, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Any luck?
Just more Ghosts
who would rather die than talk.
Nobody--nobody is going
to give up Darhk.
John, we got to talk
to Andy again.
I don't think Andy is in a very
cooperative place.
Darhk is gone to ground.
Right now, unless things change,
Andy is our best chance
of catching him.
Felicity's going in
for another surgery.
If we hurry, we might be able
to see her
before she goes
into prep.
No. No.
Darhk's in the wind.
The longer he's there,
the harder he's going to be to catch.
I'm going to stay here,
find something useful from the tip line.
It's what Felicity
would want me to do.
Can't lie your way
out of this one, pal.
Reiter might have
bought your B.S. before,
but now,
with these maps,
and ol' Miss Ukraine
over here still being alive,
it's game over.
He needs to rest--
for a moment.
Don't care.
Keep movin'.
And when he passes out,
do you plan on killing him?
Fine. Quick.
Hey, hey.
You need to make a run for it.
I'll distract Conklin.
By doing what?
Bleeding on him?
Well, isn't
this touching?
All right, come on,
let's go.
Don't get too attached
to him, sweetheart.
His prospects for a long life
don't look too good.
Hey.
How are you
feeling?
I have never
been more ready
to have a bunch of guys
poking around inside me.
Doctors.
Doing doctor things.
Um, they think
the last surgery
will fix the nerve
damage, so.
Mm-hmm.
These are from Oliver.
Well, that's really nice
of him to stop by.
Yeah, it's ok.
I know he's doing
everything he can
to track down
the, uh...flowers.
Which is much
more important.
Plus, I got all the support
I need right here.
Felicity?
Mm-hmm?
I'm here to prep you
for surgery.
I'm going to be fine.
Aren't you tired
of this?
Same dead end
conversation.
I'm not talking,
I'm not helping.
So how about you stop wasting
both our time?
The Green Arrow
told me to have
a conversation with you
about Darhk.
Wow.
I'm surprised, John.
I didn't think
you had it in you.
I didn't.
So what changed?
Her name is Felicity.
Yeah, listen, I know,
I know, all right?
Just--just do--
listen, I got to call you back,
I'll call you back, bye.
How's she doing?
She's in surgery
again.
Then what
are you doing here?
Looking
for Damian Darhk.
There's a card
that we haven't
turned over yet,
and we haven't turned it over,
because when we do,
he will know that you are
working with us.
You want to know where I've been
meeting with Darhk.
Yeah.
You won't be able
to go home.
Luckily, we have
space in the bunker.
There are
living quarters.
What about Laurel?
She can take care
of herself.
Yeah, she can do that.
Ok--office building,
832 Sixth Street,
30th floor.
But with Felicity
in the hospital,
me and Laurel watching our backs,
your team gets mighty small.
None of it matters
once Darhk is off the board.
So you're back
to dropping bodies?
It's just this one.
Lonnie Machin.
The symbol that I found
in Darhk's lair
is consistent with the symbol
that Machin left
near the bodies  of two paramedics
a few months ago.
Ok, but why is Machin
still targeting Ghosts?
When he kidnapped
Danforth's daughter,
Darhk was the one
who gave up his location.
This is payback.
Darhk cleared out
before Machin got there;
Darhk is one step
ahead of Machin.
But Machin is one
step ahead of us.
Yeah. And I'll keep
chipping away
at my stone wall.
Wait.
How did you suddenly find
Darhk's base
of operations?
Finally had an interrogation
that went somewhere.
I'm going to bring up everything
I can on Machin.
I'll ask my dad if SCPD found
any leads at the crime scene.
Mr. Conklin.
I trust there was
a reason for this?
It's like I've been
telling you--
Queen's a liar.
Told me he killed this one.
Turns out he's just been keeping
her stowed away.
What you and your men do
to satisfy your needs outside of camp
is no interest of me.
I thought
you might say that.
That's why I made
sure to bring these with me.
I found these two coming up from
a shipwrecked freighter.
Must have found
them inside.
Now, if he's
been on this island
the whole time
like he says...
How did he know
where they were?
I got those
for you.
For...whatever it is
you're doing here.
And yet you waited
all this time...
With someone
you claimed to kill.
I've defended you,
Mr. Queen.
At the cost of my credibility
with my men.
No more.
You can kill him now
if you'd like.
Nah.
I got something else in mind.
You can't do this!
Aahh!
How's Felicity?
She's in surgery.
It's a long procedure.
I'm going to go
to the hospital in a bit,
but I needed to come here
and get something first.
What?
I'd hate to see
the other guy.
The other guy's Andy.
We had to get
information on Darhk.
I thought that was
Oliver's vendetta.
Oliver does have a vendetta.
I'm just trying
to keep my friends safe.
You feel betrayed.
I do feel betrayed, Lyla,
he was my brother. My family.
I think that's
your problem.
Ever since you heard
about what Andy did
back in Afghanistan,
Andy stopped
being Andy to you.
He became a traitor.
The enemy.
Yeah, and then
he doubled down
and became one
of Darhk's Ghosts.
And you've been treating
him like a Ghost ever since.
How's that working out for you?
What's your point, Lyla?
If you're not getting through
to Andy as a Ghost,
maybe you should try
reaching him as your brother.
No. No.
I can't do that.
Sure you can.
I've seen the love you have
for your brother, Johnny.
The strength of it.
It's iron.
Before you give up on Andy,
just make sure he sees
what I do--
a man who'd go to
the ends of the Earth
for the ones he loves.
And if it helps...
Consider it an order, soldier.
You doing ok?
You mean now
that Machin's back?
I'm sure he's
not after you.
Why would he be?
I only burned his face
off in a fiery fit of Lazarus rage.
Thea...
Look, you know those
crime scene photos
that Ollie showed us
with paramedics
and writing symbols in blood?
Whoever is out there now
is a complete monster.
A monster that
we're going to catch.
I don't know anymore!
And lately, I can't seem
to win for losing.
What do you mean?
When we got John's brotherr
out of HIVE,
I ran in to Damian Darhk.
And he--he tried to use
his creepy magic mojo on me,
but...
After that,
my blood lust was better.
It was almost
completely gone.
I don't know; I really
just thought I was starting
to get
on the other side of this.
Hey. Sounds like
you already are.
Except now Machin's out there
and he has a blood lust
of his own.
And it's completely
my fault.
No, Thea, you can't
think that way.
It's far too late
for that.
It's all right, sweetheart,
it's all right.
Dad!
Ahem.
What...are you...
I had no idea
that Felicity's friend
was...Quentin's daughter.
It's such a small world.
Microscopic.
Um, Thea, I've been--
I've been trying to get Donna
to eat something
up at the cafeteria,
but maybe you'd have
better luck.
Uh...Yeah. Yeah.
Sure, sure. Come on.
Yeah, ok.
I was--I was going
to say something,
but then everything
with Felicity, and...
Dad, Dad...
It's fine.
Really?
I want you
to be happy.
Ok, so Oliver found Darhk's
base of operations,
and I'm guessing
that's thanks to you?
Well, there's no use
being on the inside
if I can't provide
inside Intel, right?
Darhk's going to realize
that you're helping the Green Arrow.
I think that ship's
probably already sailed.
Don't worry, I can
look after myself.
I'm more worried about you.
I though we already
worked past this.
There's no working past
a father caring
about his daughter.
Hmm, text from
the new girlfriend?
Easy, get out of here.
Crime lab.
I have half the CSIs I got working on
the HIVE crime scene.
I doubt they'll
find anything.
The Ghosts have
their DNA scrambled.
Which makes this
particularly strange.
The blood Machin used for his graffiti
didn't come from the Ghosts.
How do you know?
The CSU got a match.
Two of them,
actually.
Michael and Crystal Olguin.
Machin's foster parents.
Kidnapped
three days ago.
Machin's settling
old scores.
He planted their blood at HIVE,
so clearly Darhk
is next on his list.
But Machin's got to be
laying low somewhere, right?
You think
his former home?
Well, I mean,
it's vacant now.
Yeah, maybe they have
a security system we can hack into.
I've got it.
Or not.
Here, let me try it.
Ok, wait, who is that?
That's him.
Suit up.
Well, that's not
at all creepy.
Front's clear.
Same.
Except for trash, flies,
and some bad graffiti.
Wait, I think
we might have something.
I was expecting
Mr. Darhk's friends,
but...you guys
are a pleasant surprise.
Especially you, dear.
Hey!
Don't move.
Funny...
I was going to tell
you the same thing.
It's a motion sensor.
Oh, did you think
I was going to kill you?
Why would I do
such a thing?
You're the one
who saved me from myself.
Come on, then.
Hit me with
your best shot.
Oh, that's pretty.
Did you take
voice lessons?
Move, Thea.
Stay away from her!
Oh, I would
never hurt her.
You, on
the other hand...
Speedy, you ok?
Now what?
Find out what he knows.
Aren't we risking
some crazy
Bond villain
stupidity here?
I mean, this guy needs
to be put away.
Far, far away.
Machin found Darhk's
base of operations without any help.
I need to know how;
I need to know where
Darhk is right now,
and the cops can have him
when I am done with him.
Machin is about ten different
kinds of deranged.
Why would you believe
anything he tells you?
I don't have
any other choice.
Now I am done
talking about this.
Give me the room.
I thought we've
moved past this.
Sorry to disappoint.
Wake up.
Where's
Damian Darhk?
He went home.
Ahem.
I was planning
a party for him.
You interrupted my--
Tell me where he is!
Or what?
Look at me.
What could you possible do
that I haven't already enjoyed?
Hey!
Get out!
No.
Look, there's something
you need to hear.
What?!
Felicity's
out of surgery.
Donna just texted me.
They didn't say
what was wrong.
But I--I don't
think it's good.
You need to go there.
Back for more?
Does beating up
on your little brother
give you
a little thrill?
I'm not proud
of what I did, Andy.
In fact, I'm ashamed of it.
You, John?
Mr. High and Mighty?
Do you remember
the last time
you beat on me until
your knuckles bled?
Yeah, I do.
Ten years ago.
When I found out
you were dealing.
Yeah. You convinced
me to enlist.
To go the straight
and narrow like my big bro.
And I tried.
Honestly,
I tried, man.
Enough to fool you.
That's just not
who I was.
'Cause it's always been
about you, John.
'Cause I'm such
an embarrassment,
and my bad deeds
look bad on you.
No, Andy, no,
that's not true.
I did what I did
because I love you, man.
No, I do, Andy.
Then, now.
Andy, you're still
my little brother
who I stayed up late
playing cards with.
You're going through
this, that's on me.
But do you really think Damian Darhk
gives a damn about you?
He believes that the world
needs a reset.
And honestly, John, after what =
we witnessed in Afghanistan,
can you tell me otherwise?
Ok.
All right, so you and Darhk are
burning the village
in order to save it.
I get that.
Malcolm Merlyn was
talking the same tune.
But Andy, Darhk hurt
a friend of mine.
A close friend.
A woman better
than you and me put together.
It doesn't matter if Darhk wants
to save the world--
he crossed a line.
So I'm asking you,
Andy--
begging you, man...
Brother to brother.
Where can I find Darhk?
He, um...
Likes to talk about Stonehaven.
About how the leaves
look there...
in autumn.
Thanks, Andy.
Don't thank me.
You're ashamed.
Now we're even.
Speedy.
That is what the blonde
with the black leather
and the big mouth
called you, right?
Hard to look at me, I know.
Your doing.
I owe you a thank you.
Baptism by fire,
it's transcendent.
You burnt away my weakness
like a Phoenix
rising from the ashes.
If you thought burning your face
off was fun,
keep talking.
I'll put an arrow
through your eye.
So why hold back?
I know you want to kill me.
Because I can
control myself.
No, you can't.
Look, you think you can,
you say you can,
but I can see it
in your eyes.
The hunger to deliver death.
Oh, delicious.
Told you.
Bye, dear.
...downtown
Star City where the SCPD
has apprehended a fugitive
wanted for murdering...
Hi, Donna.
Where have you been?
I...
I should
have been here.
Thea said that
Felicity is out of surgery?
Yeah, yeah, she's, uh,
well, she's got
a new diagnosis.
What?
They can't...
They can't fix her.
What do you mean,
they can't fix her?
The damage to her
spinal cord, it's...
Oliver, it's permanent.
She's never going
to walk again.
No. No.
We'll talk
to another doctor.
No, no, no, see, you don't--
this--this is
the other doctor, ok?
This is the doctor that came
all the way from Central City.
This is the doctor.
Where is she?
I need to see her.
She's in recovery.
We have
a special report.
Lonnie Machin has
just been apprehended
by the Star City
police department.
D.A. Laurel Lance was onsite
to oversee his detainment.
We'll have updated  information you
upon his release.
Aahh!
Stop!
What?
Stop.
You said he was mine
to do whatever I want with.
That was before I saw
the signs on his abdomen.
Hmm. Well, you can
look at it all you want
after he's dead.
I have a need of him.
No, no, no,
everyone stay back.
Well, I count five guns.
And you got one.
What you going to do?
You can't run.
I'm not running.
Ah, long time,
no see.
We didn't finish
our conversation.
And what, I'm supposed
to be so grateful,
I'm just going to give up what
I know about where Darhk is?
Not likely.
You make sure he's dead.
Have you completely
lost your mind?
I don't have time
for a debate.
Good,
because there's nothing to debate.
What you did--
What I did?
I did what I had to do
after you made it necessary.
Machin was only arrested
by the SCPD
because you gave him up.
You were holding
a man prisoner
as some sort of
personal vendetta!
Do you have any idea
how many people
Damian Darhk and HIVE
have killed over the past six months?
This might be a vendetta,
but it's not personal.
I don't know
what's worse--
you actually believe that,
or you expect me to.
I put a tracker on Machin.
He will lead us to Darhk,
and then we will take
both of them down.
And when your master
plan doesn't work,
you just sent a murdering psychotic
back on the streets.
Like you did with Sara.
That's not fair.
What's going on?
Oliver broke Machin
out of custody.
What?
Using Machin to get
to Darhk, period.
If either of you
has a problem with it,
you know where the door is.
Laurel,
give us a second.
I don't have time
for a lecture, John.
There's no lecture
here, Oliver,
but you should know
that Andy gave me a lead on Darhk
and I've been working on it.
Good. What have you found?
Unfortunately,
it was a dead end, but--
But nothing. But nothing.
Oliver, I know
you're hurting, man,
but you should know
that whatever
your play is...
I got your back.
But?
But you've come
so far, Oliver.
You've recovered
a humanity
that you lost
when I first met you.
I know you want payback
for what Darhk did
to Felicity, and you should.
But don't lose what made her fall
in love with you in the first place.
Oh, hey.
What are you doing here?
I came by to tell you, um...
I can't do this.
My anger management issues,
they are less manageable
than I thought.
Look, I called what's
going on with you anger management
because I don't know
what else to call it.
All I know is that there's something
that's really bothering you
and if I know
what it is,
maybe I can help.
You can't.
This...This can't
really be helped.
I don't
believe that.
I don't believe
that for a second.
Thea, you've lived
through more tragedies
than a person has
any right to.
Instead of crumbling,
here you are.
Every single day, working to
rebuild your home.
You've got steel
inside of you, Thea.
That's what drew me to you
in the first place.
Thank you.
I'm...
Just not ready.
Well, hey,
when you are,
I'll be here.
Ok.
Oh, boy.
What did I miss?
That's a long story.
Short version--
Machin's gotten loose;
he's after Darhk
and we're tracking him.
Wait, what?
What happens if he gets out
and starts
hurting people?
That's exactly my point.
It doesn't matter.
You sound like him.
No, I mean,
the tracker's gone dark.
I mean, we just lost his signal,
he must have found the tracker!
We lost him.
Ok, so, what
do we do now?
I don't know.
That was
the whole plan.
Oliver, go
see Felicity.
Not right now,
John, not with--
Then when?
She needs you.
And right now,
I think you need her, too.
We will find Machin.
Look...
They are right, ok?
We are going
to figure this out.
But right now,
you need to go
and be with her.
Hey, stranger.
Sorry I didn't...
come by sooner.
It's...
It's unforgivable.
Only if you were
in Bali or something.
Were you in Bali?
No, I was, uh...
Beating the streets.
Probably a lot of people
looking for Darhk.
I didn't want
to come and see you
until Darhk
was off the board.
Any luck?
Working
some leads.
Tell me you haven't
gone off the rails.
Well...
I just...
I can't help
but think that...
The reason that
Darhk is winning
is because I haven't
been willing to go far enough
and that if I was,
if I had,
maybe you wouldn't be
in here right now.
And I don't know
what the point...
of what I'm doing
as Green Arrow is
if I can't protect the people that
are closest to me.
Well, what's the point of doing it
if you lose yourself in the process?
Yeah.
There's something else
we need to talk about.
The doctors...
They say that I'm, uh...
I know.
My point being is we didn't
really exchange any vows,
so the whole for better, for worse thing
doesn't really apply here.
What are you
talking about?
And maybe the real
reason you haven't been here
is because--
Felicity.
The nurse, she took this
off of you in the E.R.
How dare she.
For better,
for worse.
Ok.
He's bluffing.
Reiter, I can help you
find what you need...
On one condition.
What do you want?
I want
Taiana's safety.
So long
as she is alive,
I'll cooperate.
He's manipulating you.
What do you think
he's been doing this whole time?
You give him what he wants,
he's going to turn on you.
Do we have
a deal or not?
Take them both to prison.
You can't trust him.
Remember, Conklin...
There's no part
of my plan
which requires you
to be alive.
You know, we go out
every night...
Suiting up,
risking our lives,
fighting assassins
and meta-humans
and all the worst
kinds of people.
She's stronger
than all of us.
You won't get
an argument from me.
Oliver, we might
have something.
John's brother said Darhk could be found
in a place called Stonehaven.
Dig said that lead
was a dead end.
That was before we cross referenced
the tracker's location
and came back
with a residential address.
Machin's going after Darhk
where he lives.
We're going to roll out.
I thought...you might
want to tag along.
Thank you.
Let's go.
All righty.
I just spoke
with Mr. Darhk.
He's on his way.
Traffic's a bitch.
Could take a while.
I really don't see why
we can't have some fun
in the meanwhile.
Just so you know,
this isn't your fault.
You see, daddy
done me wrong.
There needs to be
recompense for that.
He's not
responsible for what--
for what happened
to my face.
Not directly,
but incidentally.
And isn't that
what anarchy is?
The intersection of seemingly
unconnected events?
Who owns the house?
It's owned by
a dummy corporation.
Couldn't work
through all the layers
without Felicity.
And we're sure
that Machin's inside?
Oh, yeah.
We're sure.
Hey.
Get on the ground!
First, you catch me.
Then, you break me out.
Now, you want
to catch me again.
Make up your mind.
Let's take him.
Get them
out of here!
Come on!
Split up.
There it is.
Shut up.
A little piece
of me inside of you
just begging
to come out and play.
Where's my family?!
I saved them.
I want to be clear
about something--
I have shown you repeatedly
that you cannot beat me.
You saved my family.
So I'll give you a few weeks
to spend with yours.
Enjoy your time.
What's left of it.
You missed.
On purpose.
I'm disappointed in you.
Are Darhk's wife and daughter
in police custody?
They told police they weren't
his wife and daughter.
Had fake ID and everything.
Speedy...
You ok?
Yeah.
I'm just sorry I let
Machin get away.
I'm just glad that
you're all right.
I'm going to go
see Felicity.
The Chinese use
this island as a prison.
Bet you didn't know that.
Said being sentenced here
was worse than any jail.
Guess I'll just have
to see if I can give
those Chinese a run
for their money.
Reiter's going to get through
with you eventually,
and then you and me
will have a little uninterrupted time.
You've lost
a lot of blood.
You shouldn't let these wounds
sit open like that.
Thank you.
You saved
my life again.
Really, at the expense
of your own.
Well, you didn't
deserve to die.
You're a good man.
My brother would
have liked you.
I already told you
everything I know, John.
I'm not here to ask you
any questions, Andy.
Thank you for coming.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
Glad I did.
And glad you called.
You know, this is
a little bit confusing.
Yeah.
First we're on,
then we're off,
now we're...
Drinking wine.
Look, um...
Something happened
earlier today,
and...
I guess I just wanted
to say that
you were right.
I am stronger
than I think I am.
Well...
Here's to being
stronger, huh?
Mmm.
How you feeling?
How long you been
sitting there?
Not long enough.
Sorry I went away.
I think you
apologized already.
Nowhere near
done apologizing.
You know...
I think I want to go to Bali.
Yeah.
Want to come with me?
I'd go anywhere
with you.
Yeah?
Just one question.
Mm-hmm?
What's Damian Darhk
doing in Bali?
I only ask, 'cause
if he's still here,
we have
some work to do.
How'd you get to be so strong?
I took my lead
from you.
Shhh.
I've bought out
the Fairmount for the month.
You'll be safe there
until we find a new home.
And what about the man
that attacked us?
Lonnie Machin?
He'll never
hurt you again.
Those vigilantes saved us.
My dearest Ruvé,
do I detect a note
of criticism in your voice?
Yes.
But not the one you think.
You should have killed
the Green Arrow tonight.
As you said,
he saved your life.
It would be bad form
to take him out now.
Genesis is almost ready.
We're much too close
to play games.
Do you remember
what I promised you?
A new beginning.
And you will have it.
Once we've brought
this world to its end.
Are you ok?
Are you?
No.
You know what
you have to do, right?
You have to kill
the son of a bitch.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.