Previously on Arrow:
Tibetan pit viper venom.
Constant dose of that
can't be good for you, right?
It'll keep him sedated like it did Slade.
No mention on Isabel Rochev's death?
- Not a thing.
- Aah!
- Choose. Choose.
- No! No!
No, Mom.
Mom, what are you doing?
- Both my children will live.
- Mom, what are you doing?
You possess true courage.
Aah! No!
There is still one person who has to die...
before this can end.
No.
I do solemnly swear...
that I will support, defend...
and abide by the Starling City charter.
And that I will faithfully...
discharge the duties of the office
of Mayor of Starling City.
That I will tirelessly pursue justice
on behalf of all Starling citizens...
impartially, to the
best of my abilities.
So help me God.
Thank you.
Thea.
Hey.
- I'm here for you.
- I know.
Ms. Queen.
I wanted to offer my sincere condolences
on your loss.
Your mother was a good woman.
She would have made a wonderful mayor.
Thank you.
I'd love to speak with Oliver.
Well, if you see him, tell him he
missed his own mother's funeral.
No one's seen Oliver for a few days.
We all deal with grief in different ways.
And the loss of a parent is...
Well, it changes you.
When you realize that your ancestors
now look to you...
that your family's legacy,
their continuing works...
are solely in your hands...
If you see Oliver, please
tell him that I came by.
Of course.
Hey.
Thanks.
I don't even know why I'm crying.
I didn't even like Moira.
Terrible thing to say about
someone after they just died.
In my defense, she was not nice.
She was diabolical.
Not a word you often hear
at someone's funeral.
You're not crying for her, Felicity.
You're crying for Oliver.
Where is he?
How could he not be here?
I don't know.
If Oliver's smart,
he ran back to his island to hide.
But maybe he'll attend your funerals.
I always loved this photograph.
I thought your mother
looked particularly beautiful.
She didn't.
- She thought she looked bug-eyed.
- Heh.
She never said.
How are you holding up?
I'm not.
Your mother gave her life for you, Thea.
She showed you how much she loved you
in ways very few parents ever could.
I know. She died thinking I hated her.
All we ever needed was the truth.
- It was a lie that killed her.
- I don't understand.
Slade Wilson.
He was on that island with Oliver.
And despises him for some reason.
There was a psychopath in our lives
and my brother never warned us about him.
Thea, your brother loves you
more than life itself.
You should keep that photo.
This sub is over 60 years old.
It was carrying the Mirakuru during the war
when it ran aground.
- Blood.
- Slade's.
He was bleeding out. Dying.
Until we decided to give him the Mirakuru.
Not one of your better ideas.
What about my idea for
you to fix the sub?
- You were in the navy.
- The Russian navy.
They taught us how to sink
Japanese subs, not pilot them.
Anatoli, please. I know it's a longshot,
but if we get the sub operational...
we can blow Slade and
the Mirakuru out of the
water and get the hell
off of this island.
Unless you have a better idea,
this is our only chance of getting home.
Okay, I try.
No one has seen Slade Wilson
since the night of the attack.
He hasn't made any further
threats on the Queen family,
but we gotta find
this son of a...
Excuse me. Hey.
Missed you at the reception.
Yeah, I had to get back here.
- See what's happening with the case.
- Any leads?
Nope. Wilson's a ghost.
He's not the only one who's disappeared.
You heard from your sister?
Nothing apart from a text that
she needed a change of scenery.
Hm.
Something else on your mind?
It's Sebastian Blood.
There's something that doesn't seem right.
- Laurel...
- Dad, I know what you're thinking.
When I accused him of killing his father,
I was upset.
But just because I had a problem
doesn't mean I was wrong about Sebastian.
Please, don't go down
this road again, okay?
- I mean, what's bringing this on?
- I saw him at the reception.
And it struck me that the only reason that
he's mayor now is because Moira was killed.
- By Slade Wilson.
- What if there's a connection?
You once told me a cop
is only as good as his gut.
Well, I'm the daughter of a cop.
And I know in my gut, Sebastian
is not the man that you think he is.
Are you sure?
- Baby, last time...
- I was a drunk.
And you were right not to trust me.
But, Dad...
I need you to trust me now.
This legislation is the
first step toward making
Starling City the jewel
that it once was.
The jewel that it can be again.
Phone call for you, Mayor Blood.
I'm still getting used to people
calling me that, Alyssa.
- Please take a message.
- The caller insisted.
- He said he's your father.
- That's impossible.
Never mind. I'll take it.
- Hello.
- Hello, Sebastian.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I just wanted to check in
and see how your first day is going.
Very well, thank you.
But I'm a little busy right
now, so if you'll allow
me to call you back, I'll
do that as soon as I can.
No need. I'm sure you have
quite a lot of business to attend to.
You are the mayor now after all.
So get to work.
We're almost out of snake venom.
Seeing Roy like this reminds me of Barry.
And Barry reminds me of S.T.A.R. Labs.
S.T.A.R. Labs reminds me
of the Mirakuru cure that
they're working on which we
could really use... right now.
Yeah, especially since Isabel Rochev
was clearly injected with the stuff.
How do you know?
Cause there's no way she
could be walking around...
after being shot dead on
with a 9 mm hollow point.
Left about a dozen messages for Oliver
about Isabel being back. No response.
- You have any luck finding him?
- Tons.
All of it bad.
There's been no activity on his passport,
cell phone...
or bank accounts.
What's left of them anyhow.
And facial recognition hasn't spotted him
at any airport, bus or train station.
Right. What about Sara?
Nothing either.
Dig, people don't just go missing
like this unless...
Don't go there, Felicity.
What if she is?
What if Oliver is?
Maybe the reason we can't find him
is because...
He's alive, Felicity.
If he wasn't, Isabel Rochev
wouldn't be so shy about
rubbing it in our faces,
belive me, he's alive.
Well, I hope you have some way
on how to find him...
because I am running out
of places to look and people to ask.
I know who to ask.
Thanks for agreeing to see us.
Mr. Diggle.
Thought I made it clear
after our last meeting.
As far as A.R.G.U.S. is concerned,
you're out of favors.
I'm not asking for myself, Amanda.
I'm asking for everyone in Starling City.
I need you to find Oliver Queen.
Dig. That computer
is running an XK-15 processor.
Felicity.
But that's not even
supposed to exist yet.
- I want one.
- Let me know what you find.
I don't have time to keep track
of your friends, Mr. Diggle.
We deal with more
pressing issues here.
You don't understand.
Oliver's disappeared.
Maybe he needs some time.
Or is it possible that the two of you simply
haven't been looking in the right place?
- Did you try facial recognition?
- Yes, I ran it three times.
Amanda, please.
Slade Wilson has an army of men
just like him.
How many men have been
exposed to the Mirakuru?
Enough to lay
waste to this city.
- We need to find Oliver right now.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Have you heard from Sara?
- No.
Can you just call Mandy
and see if she can cover the bar?
Okay.
Isabel Rochev.
I know who you are.
- What can I do for you, Ms. Rochev?
- I'm sorry for your loss, Thea.
Is that why you came here?
Offer me your condolences?
My condolences and to give you this.
It's a notice to vacate the premises.
This club and the steel factory
in which it's located...
are all assets of Queen Consolidated.
- No, you can't do this.
- It's already done.
How long do I have?
A couple days.
Councilman Tyson is asking about dinner.
- I already have plans tonight.
- Hi.
Excuse me, I didn't mean to barge in.
It's just that nobody
was at your front desk, so...
Laurel, of course please come in.
Give us a moment.
Twice in two days.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I wish I could say that this was pleasure,
but it's about a case.
I'm barely moved in and people are asking
me for favors. Guess I really have arrived.
- You certainly have.
- Ha, ha.
So tell me. How can I help you?
Murphy vs. Dunleavy.
The state charged a real estate developer
for turning away low-income tenants...
based on his so-called morality.
Have a seat.
So let me guess.
Our dear Fair Housing Commissioner...
isn't willing to testify
as your expert witness.
Exactly. And your predecessor
wasn't willing to lean on him.
Well, lucky for you, I'm
not my predecessor.
You know, this actually
reminds me of one I
had during my days as a
community organizer.
I was hoping that it would.
I've seen dozens of cases
like this at CNRI.
Well, it's a good thing we both remember
where we came from. I'm happy to help.
Thank you.
Laurel.
I'm really glad you got your job back
at the DA's office.
I look forward to us working together
for a long time.
As do I.
Is it working?
Using the bug to remote
access the computer right now.
Yeah, you listen, if you ever
get tired of practicing law,
you'd make a pretty decent spy.
- You guys have a warrant for this, right?
- Just...
Terrific. Could you at least tell me
whose computer you bugged?
- You're kidding. I voted for him.
- Yeah.
I need to know if there's anything
incriminating in Blood's files.
What the hell?
This was a dead-end job anyway.
This all looks pretty benign.
Lots of policy papers.
All documents transferred
from his campaign office.
Drafts, press releases.
Wait, wait, wait. Click back.
"For immediate release. My thoughts
and prayers are with the Queen family...
in the aftermath
of this unspeakable tragedy."
So he worked up a press release
after Moira was killed.
No, he didn't.
He wrote that the day before Moira died.
She's right. Look at the time stamp.
- Oh, my God.
- Sebastian knew Slade was gonna kill her.
Is that the Satellite Frequency
Communicator TX-50?
Can I touch it? I know
that sounds a little weird
and creepy, but I've never
seen one in real life.
It's classified equipment, Ms. Smoak.
You must feel very powerful.
Knowing everything about everyone.
Not powerful in an evil
dictator, Stalin way.
More of a "knowledge is power" way.
- Ma'am, we have something.
- Ahem.
I should have known.
- What?
- Oliver's at the lair...
from which he conducts his operations.
But we were just there.
Not that lair.
His other one.
Like riding bicycle.
Underwater.
What's that sound?
We're stuck.
- Like Japanese were.
- Submarines have torpedoes, right?
Can we blast our way out?
I can see why you two are made for
each other. You like your explosions.
Yes, torpedoes.
- What?
- These are Kaiten torpedoes.
Manually operated.
Someone needs to steer from inside.
Okay, but then how do they get away
from the explosion?
They do not.
How did you find me?
Waller.
- We were worried about you.
- After you missed your mother's funeral.
I'm sorry that I didn't go.
I left for the cemetery.
But I ended up here.
- And here is...?
- Here was a secondary facility...
in case the foundry was compromised.
But it became somewhere
that I could just go and...
be alone.
She's dead because of me.
Five years ago...
I could've cured Slade.
And that would've prevented all of this.
And now...
all the people left that I care about...
we're all in his crosshairs.
That ends tonight.
How?
I turn myself over to Slade.
I end this vendetta.
Oliver, you think this ends...
with you turning yourself over to Slade?
Yes, I do.
After she was gone...
he told me that one more person
had to die.
And then it would end.
This ends for Slade when he kills me.
I don't accept that.
You shouldn't either.
You can't just accept things, Oliver.
If I'd accepted my life, I would be a
cocktail waitress in Vegas like my mother.
And I never would
have gone to college.
And I never would have moved away a thousand
miles to work at Queen Consolidated.
And I never would have believed
some crazy guy in a hood...
when he told me that I could be more
than just some IT girl.
Please don't do this.
Felicity.
Someone once told me...
that the essence of heroism
is to die so others can live.
- It's not that simple, Oliver.
- Yes, it is.
Slade's whole plan...
was to take everything from me.
He did.
He wins.
All that's left is for me to die.
There has to be another way.
There isn't.
Thea, please. I understand you're upset.
This is an emotional time for all of us.
I'm not being emotional. I'm...
I'm an orphan.
I'm a jobless and homeless orphan.
- There's nothing left for me here.
- I'm here.
I thank you for that,
but honestly I need to start over.
Oliver.
We missed you at the funeral.
And the reception.
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there.
What's going on here?
- Thea's thinking of leaving Starling City.
- No, I am leaving.
Walter, can I speak to my sister
for a moment?
Perhaps you'll have better luck.
Ollie, please, just don't even try
to convince me to stay.
I won't. I think it's a good idea.
You should get as far from Starling City
as you possibly can.
In our family, out of you, me, Mom and Dad,
you are the best of us.
You have the purest heart.
And I can't ever have you lose that.
Okay? You promise me?
Okay.
And I know that I haven't always
been the best brother.
Or friend,
or whatever you've needed me to be.
But there has not been a day
since you were born...
where I didn't cherish having you
as a sister.
I'll get in touch
when I get settled somewhere.
It's Oliver.
This ends now.
I'll be at the pier. I'll be alone.
I'll do it.
Peter, you'll die.
I'm already dead.
Radiation poisoning.
Ivo's little gift.
Said he needed to find out
if Mirakuru could cure cancer.
Guess we'll never find out.
I'm sorry, Peter. I didn't know.
Ivo said the essence of heroism
is to die so that others can live.
I held onto that.
It's the only thing that gave me hope.
So I'll go.
It may not be saving millions of lives,
but I'll be saving yours.
This is where it all started.
Got on the Queen's Gambit right over there.
Should have died on that boat.
If I had, none of this would have happened.
I never would have met you.
Shado and my mother would still be alive.
No one else is gonna die because of me.
Diggle, what the hell?
Slade Wilson...
he told me who you were.
- Did he hurt you?
- No.
He was trying to hurt you.
And when you went missing...
I reached out...
to your partners.
They told me what you were
planning on doing.
It's what I have to do.
Will you give us a moment?
You thought about telling me...
the night of the Undertaking.
Thought about telling you
almost every night.
Why didn't you?
Tommy knew...
didn't he?
You were with him.
You were with him at the end.
His last words were about you.
He wanted to know if you were safe.
I'm sorry I couldn't save him.
And my mother.
But I can save you.
And Thea.
- I can save the city if this ends tonight.
- No.
No, you can't commit suicide, Ollie.
You won't do that to me.
Or to Sara, or to your friends,
or to Thea.
Oliver...
she just lost her mother.
Losing you would destroy her.
She'll be alive.
I don't know anything about
hoods and masks...
or human weapons or any of this...
but I know you.
I know you like I know my own name.
And I realize it may sound crazy
in light of your secret...
but I know who you are
in your bones, Oliver.
And that person,
that person doesn't give up.
That person, he always finds a way.
- Not this time.
- You're wrong.
You wanna protect the people
who you love?
Then the only way to do that
is to stop Slade Wilson...
- Laurel, I can't.
- Yes, you can...
by stopping Sebastian Blood, because
Sebastian is working with Slade Wilson.
I have proof.
Slade Wilson killed your mother
so that Sebastian could become mayor.
You were right about him.
The man in the skull mask
works for Slade Wilson.
And this entire time...
it was Sebastian?
What's happening
is bigger than you and Slade.
This city needs the Arrow.
What's this for?
I don't want you to be in here.
- No, I'm gonna stay with you.
- Sara...
if this doesn't work,
I need you to be safe.
We will come for you when it's over.
Okay.
Do you know how the torpedo works?
I get in, he fires, I steer, you pray.
- Peter, what you're doing is...
- Practical.
- My time's already up.
- Brave.
You need to know that.
I don't think I could
do something like this.
You have.
What you did for us, coming back
to that boat, setting us free...
I came back to the boat
because I want to go home.
I wasn't thinking about
saving anybody.
It's not who I am.
Maybe not yet.
Launch?
- Is Sara clear?
- Yes.
Yes.
Hello, good to see you.
Clinton, you can wait in the car.
- Are you sure that's a good idea?
- Nothing's going to happen to me here.
- How are you doing Mr. Mayor?
- Hi.
Good to see you.
Hey, thank you.
- Hi.
- Good to see you, sir.
Congratulations.
Nice to see you.
Sebastian, may I join you for dinner?
Hey, can you hold that?
Oh, thanks a lot, man.
Appreciate it.
Clinton Hogue...
I have some questions for you.
- Go to hell.
- You sure that's how you wanna play it?
You think I've never
taken a beating before?
Pal, you're gonna wish I beat you.
Hi, I'll be your interrogator.
- Is this a joke?
- Clinton Hogue.
Social Security Number 306-00-3894?
What the hell's this supposed to be?
Well, look at this.
You have a bank account
in the Cayman Islands.
Wow.
Two million dollars,
quite the little nest egg.
But looks like you just
approved a wire transfer
of $1 million to a charity
here in Starling City.
Very generous.
- And what should I do with the rest?
- Greenpeace.
Great cause.
And they really appreciate the support.
- Bitch.
- Bitch with Wi-Fi.
Hey Clint, looks like your mom and dad have
a really nice retirement portfolio too.
But they, oh, no, are just about to make
some really bad investments.
Okay, wait, just wait. Just stop.
What do you wanna know?
I missed you at your mother's
memorial service.
I wanted to offer my condolences.
You're the mayor.
Congratulations.
You've always wanted that.
Believe me, Oliver,
I wish it had happened a different way.
Your mother and I,
we didn't agree on much...
but we both wanted
what was best for Starling City.
I will help this city find its heart again,
I promise you that.
Do you really think that he...
will let that happen?
Slade Wilson.
How do you know I've been
working with Slade Wilson?
Because I'm the Arrow.
Of course. Heh.
It all makes sense now.
It was right in front of me.
You came to my office
and you shook my hand.
You said that together
we can save this city.
You think that there will
be a city to be saved...
after you unleash Slade's Mirakuru army?
They'll only cause enough damage
to make this city ready.
Ready for your leadership?
For my vision of what this city could be.
A better city.
And after the storm they're about to
suffer, the people of Starling...
will support and follow me to that city.
Whatever Slade promised you,
he will not deliver.
He wants to hurt me.
You are a pawn in a much larger game.
Slade promised me City Hall...
and he delivered.
He makes good on his promises.
I understand he made you a promise too.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna stab the mayor
in a restaurant full of people?
It's a new day in Starling City, Oliver.
And there's nothing you can do to stop it.
Slade's men are taking the city tonight?
They can try.
He has more men than we thought,
all on Mirakuru.
- It could be a massacre.
- Not if we get to them first.
We stick to the plan, no matter what.
Slade's using the sewer system.
You can drop in at Rock Avenue,
then head southeast.
The lines converge
at Water Street.
If Slade's army's underground,
that's probably where he'll be.
Good. Let's go.
Diggle, you ready?
- Never not.
- I'm coming too.
No, you're not.
Felicity can give me a radio.
I'll just be your eyes and ears.
I'll stay out of your way, I promise.
Nothing will happen to me.
What if it did?
Slade's men, one-on-one,
they are nearly impossible to stop.
I need you to trust me...
and I need you to be safe.
But not them?
This started with the three of us.
It's time we got back to that.
Tonight we rise up as one
and take back this city.
I have eyes on Blood's army.
Got it. I'm forwarding
Dig your ping along with
the foundation schematics
of the Topside Avenue.
Follow the route I laid
out in the blueprints,
you'll see structural
joints in the concrete.
Blow them all, Blood gets buried.
Got it.
The market opened today up 400 points...
thanks in part to the surprise rally
of Queen Consolidated.
New leadership...
has investors excited about the company's
future in spite of its recent tragedies.
- Excuse me, why can't I board my train?
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
This is business class right now.
Coach will be boarding soon.
Okay.
Come on, pal.
Isn't that one of the
Iron Heights escapees?
Dumbass here tried to rob a convenience
store, gave up soon as I pulled in.
Mind if I just stick
him here for a minute?
No, no, go ahead.
I'm just asking here.
Oliver, you've worked really hard
not to kill anymore.
Dropping an entire block on these guys
is murder. Manslaughter at least.
They're not men.
Not anymore.
Have Diggle blow the charges
the moment he's ready.
Oliver?
We will lead this city
out of the darkness...
and each one of you will help me.
Come on.
Oliver, where the hell are you?
You killed me.
Let me return the favor.
Hey, you got the time?
- It's, uh, 9:00.
- Thanks.
Oliver, please.
Cisco, now is really not a good time.
There.
Ollie...
there's too many of them.
We can't fight.
We're not going to.
Turn the wheel.
- What direction?
- It doesn't matter. Just turn the wheel.
- I can't.
- That is not an option.
- I got it!
- My God, we're moving.
Good, good. Good.
Sara, we did it.
- Sara.
- Oliver!