Subs fixed and enhanced by Treviso.
Missing dialog added and some minor fixes by Tronar.
My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years on a hellish island...
I have come home with only one goal:
To save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on Arrow:
Time to choose, Oliver,
who lives and who dies.
- You got what you came for!
- Time's up.
- No!
- I guess you made your choice.
No!
Ivo killed Shade because of me.
Nothing good comes from telling Slade
you think you're responsible...
for the death of the woman he loved.
The man who killed Shado
is still out there.
Not for long,
because we're gonna take the freighter.
We're all gonna die here.
Just like him.
No, we're not.
I think I found our way onto the freighter.
Parachute.
- I'd like you to meet Slade Wilson.
- It's a pleasure to meet you...
Mr. Queen.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Wilson just made a sizable contribution
to my campaign.
How generous of him.
Well, I felt compelled. And it was the
least that I could do for your mother.
What this city needs
is a pro-business mayor like Moira...
to spur growth through urban investment.
And we were just discussing
how to combat the rising wage gap.
And the answer lies
in your budget proposal.
You know, when I look at your mother...
I think about everything you
went through after the quake.
All I can say is,
you and I have something in common.
What's that?
I know how difficult it is
to pick yourself back up...
when other people have written you off.
Indeed.
What's wrong, Mr. Queen?
You look a little piqued.
I'm fine, thank you.
Ah. Thank you, dear.
Oliver, Mr. Wilson was kind enough to bring
a bottle of authentic Australian rum.
Will you join us in a drink?
Yes, of course.
Wonderful.
What shall we drink to?
To friendship.
Ah. Delicious.
Uh, this here is a beautiful piece.
Tell me, does your family spend
much time on the water?
No.
Not since my late husband.
I'm sorry, Moira. Forgive me.
I do remember reading about that accident
in the paper.
You were a brave soul.
I don't like to talk about it.
I can understand.
All that time on that island.
It must have been hell for you.
- Shado would be proud.
- Thank you.
But those trees don't move or shoot back.
Ivo's men on the freighter will.
Then shoot first.
Ivo's freighter is located here.
He keeps eight men on deck.
Three on the starboard,
three on the port and two up on the bridge.
But our bigger concern
are these GP-25 grenade launchers...
that they're walking
around with at all times.
Do they have night vision?
Not according to Blondie.
That smells awful.
- It'll taste even worse.
- But it'll work?
I spent a year with Anthony Ivo.
I know how he thinks.
It'll work.
Hey, what about the Mirakuru?
- What about it?
- Well, look, I mean, it can cure...
I don't know, maybe anything.
Maybe... maybe it's a miracle drug.
But it's also something else.
Something that people like Ivo
should never be allowed to control.
What about Slade? He might not let us.
Might not let you do what?
You think we should destroy the Mirakuru.
If this thing doesn't go our way...
we can't let Ivo have it.
You're right.
We should burn it.
Anthony devoted his
entire life to finding this.
Nobody even thought it was real.
It was his dream.
Did he ever say why?
He wanted to save the world.
We need to talk about tomorrow.
About what to do with Anthony
once we take the freighter.
What do you mean?
Slade wants to kill him.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
No, Slade wants to kill him for Shado.
Oliver, you don't know him like I do.
Look, if he's given the chance,
then he's gonna turn this around.
He's gonna make Slade think
that it's your fault that she's dead.
That you chose to save me instead of her.
You can't give him that chance.
- Sara, I can't.
- You've killed before.
That's not what you are talking about.
You are talking...
about executing somebody in cold blood.
Look, Slade has the Mirakuru in him.
He's unstable.
If he loses control, if he snaps again,
then we're both dead.
You have to kill Ivo.
Who's thirsty?
- Where'd you get that?
- Who cares? Let's drink it.
Ah, this is one of the few precious pieces
of cargo to survive the crash.
Billy Wintergreen and I were planning
on saving it for a rainy day.
But considering, God willing,
this is our last night on the island...
To taking the freighter.
To getting off this island forever.
To Shado.
Mm.
You know, if something happens
to me tomorrow...
You can't think like that.
If I don't make it...
I need you to...
To tell my mom and my sister...
that I wasn't that same stupid kid
who got on that boat.
Tell them I was different.
Okay.
Hey, and if I don't make it...
tell my family that
I died on the Gambit.
Why?
Let them remember me the way that I was.
We should all get some sleep.
I've missed you.
Shado?
How are you still alive?
I'm not alive.
Remember?
I'm dead.
Because you chose Sara over me.
Why didn't you choose me?
Rise and shine, kid. it's time.
Better luck next time, Hendrik.
You cheat.
He cheats.
So do you.
He just cheats better.
Get up, preacher boy.
I said, get up, coward.
Ivo wants to see you.
Have faith, my friend.
God will protect you.
There is no God.
If there was...
he's not on this ship.
- How is she?
- I'm sorry, Anthony.
I wish I had better news to give you...
but her condition is progressing quicker
than we anticipated.
Have you tried upping her dosage?
Twice already, but we both know
that modern medicine has its limitations.
Oh, yes, I know quite well.
Thank you, doctor.
No. No, wait. Wait, Mr. Ivo.
My family is Bratva, Russian mafia.
They pay millions for me.
I'm sorry. I have very
little use for money.
I do, however, require an eye
for my research.
No.
Well, we don't have all day.
There's a breeze.
They're on the beach. Take them. Alive.
What about him?
Eh.
They're coming. Two men. Armed.
You know, when we first tried
to get off this island...
it was as strangers.
But now it's as brothers.
See you on the freighter.
There!
You're lucky Ivo wants you alive.
I told you I'd come back.
Fantastic. We're saved.
He likes you.
Don't worry. He won't bite.
Reverend Thomas Flynn.
Oliver Queen.
And this is Abraham.
I remember you from before. You escaped.
- With that blond whore.
- That's Hendrik.
- He's a charmer.
- Yeah, I hope she rots in hell.
Hey, Sara was a prisoner.
Just like all of us.
Right. Funny, I never heard her scream.
- How long have you been here, Thomas?
- A little over a year.
I was working as a missionary in Maliku
just off the coast of India.
A ship docked there for supplies.
Dr. Ivo asked me to come aboard
to administer last rights for a dying man.
- My mistake.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Can you imagine a better place
for a man in my line of work?
Hey, prochnost.
Mr. Queen.
Welcome back.
My men are still searching the beach
for your friend and Sara.
They have the Mirakuru.
So where are they?
You go to hell.
Maybe you'd like to rethink that.
Ivo, you torture me all you want to,
I am never gonna tell you where they are.
No, not willingly.
What is that?
Oh, this? See, this is sodium pentothal.
Its more colloquial,
yet very descriptive name...
is "truth serum."
Wait, no. Wait, wait.
I'll tell you everything!
Let's begin.
Are you married, Mr. Wilson?
Do you have any children?
Certainly neither.
Well, there must be someone special
in your life.
There was.
But she passed away a few years ago.
I'm sorry.
My mother and I have had to deal
with a lot of loss, unfortunately.
And eventually we learned...
that you just have to move on.
I don't believe that.
You know, I heard that your family
has an affinity with the fine arts.
Yes, my husband amassed quite the collection
of 19th century American landscapes.
- I'd love to see them.
- Maybe another day.
Ahem. We have some family business
that we need to discuss right now.
I'm sorry.
My son seems to have forgotten
all his manners. Heh.
Let me just get my staff
to open up the rest of the house.
Thank you.
Mom?
Ollie?
Not yet, kid.
I'm still to meet the rest of your family.
Hello?
Hey, Ollie, have you and Mom talked?
Because this whole not speaking thing...
- Thea, now is not a good time.
- Who is your friend?
Slade Wilson.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You know, I've heard
such wonderful things from your mother.
Heh, heh.
- About me? Heh.
- Thea.
What perfect timing.
This is Slade Wilson...
They've met.
And I was about to
show him our collection.
- But you're far better suited. Come.
- Oh. Heh, heh.
Senior year, I was obsessed with art.
My teacher made me bring my entire art
history class over here to show our pieces.
It was exactly as mortifying as it sounds.
Oh, I'm sure it wasn't. You're a very
lucky girl to have known such privilege.
And I'm fortunate
to have your entire family here. Heh.
Oliver?
Oliver, what's your name?
Oliver Jonas Queen.
Oliver, where were you born?
Starling City.
Why did you build a bonfire on the beach?
So you'd see it.
I told you.
Was the bonfire a trap?
Not a trap. It was a...
A distraction.
How was the bonfire a distraction?
Where are Sara and Slade right now?
Where are they?
They're on the freighter.
Where on the freighter?
They're in the engine room,
because we have a raft.
Sound the alarm. I want every man
on this freighter down in that engine room.
Search the entire floor. Go.
Oliver Jonas Queen.
You're with me.
Secure all decks!
It'll taste even worse.
But it'll work.
I spent a year with Anthony Ivo.
I know how he thinks. It'll work.
And what is it, exactly?
Cocculus indicus.
It's a natural source of picrotoxin...
which will counteract
the effects of barbiturates.
- Like sodium pentothal.
- Ivo's favorite.
But you still gotta
act stoned to sell it.
Lucky for me...
before all this,
I had a lot of practice.
They're clearing the deck.
The top of the ship's empty.
Are you ready?
You really don't want
an honest answer to that.
You've done this before, right?
- Nobody's done this before.
- Aah!
Here. I think these belong to you.
We're on a clock,
and she needs to free the prisoners.
Ivo sent his men to the engine room
just like we planned.
More convenient for me to take them out.
Go find Ivo.
He can't get off this ship.
But don't kill him.
That son of a bitch is mine.
And here we have a Curtis Swan from 1882.
Fun fact about this one. He actually
painted it with his left hand...
due to severe arthritis.
- It's absolutely exquisite.
- Mm-hm.
I can't tell you how many offers we've had
from private collectors for it.
But it was one of Dad's favorites.
Wasn't it, Ollie?
Yes, it was.
He loved that one.
Then you must never sell it.
I believe that
when we lose someone we love...
we have the obligation
to honor their memory.
- You'd think eventually I'd hit something.
- Be patient. Ollie makes it look easy.
Is anyone going to get that?
I'll take that as a no. No worries.
No matter where I go,
I'm just answering phones.
Hello?
Oliver?
Well, I do think we've been butt dialed.
And here is a Joseph Kubert from 1890.
Hey, that's Thea.
That's gorgeous.
Wait, hold on.
I know that voice.
I actually have a painting
from his first solo exhibition in Boston.
Oh, God, no.
Who is that?
His name is Slade Wilson.
And unless we stop him, he's gonna
kill Oliver and his entire family.
- We have to move. Now.
- Are you sure it was Slade Wilson?
- I thought he was dead.
- I'm sure.
That's not a voice I'd ever forget.
What's the biggest gun
you've got down here?
That might work.
Might?
He has the Mirakuru in him.
So do I.
Can I trust you?
I'll be fine.
Slade was a trained killer
before he was injected.
You get the chance, you get a shot,
you put him down.
Please save Oliver.
Why are you doing this?
I'm with Oliver now.
- Why should I believe you?
- Because you don't want to die. Go.
You helped that maniac torture us.
Follow me.
- Where's Ivo?
- He's heading to the bridge.
Answer the phone.
Please.
Hello?
Jessica, it's me.
Who?
It's Anthony.
Anthony.
I was married to a boy named Anthony.
- I know, sweetheart.
- But he went away.
I went to find a cure.
And I found one, sweetheart.
I found it. And soon...
He was a doctor.
But he went away.
It's harder than it looks, isn't it?
Ah.
Killing an unarmed man.
Seemed pretty easy
when you murdered Shado.
- I didn't murder her, Oliver.
- Ivo, you shot her in the head.
I gave you a choice.
You chose Sara.
You blame me.
But that's because you can't face
your own guilt.
I loaded the bullets, yes.
I pulled the trigger.
But you...
You aimed the gun.
And you hold yourself responsible.
Don't you?
Yes.
That doesn't mean I won't kill you.
The question is...
what will he do?
Is it true?
Tell me.
- Slade, I tried to tell you...
- Tell him, Oliver.
I was angry.
Like you are right now.
- I wasn't thinking clearly.
- Shut up.
I acted rashly. I told him to choose
between Shado and Sara.
Don't listen to him.
He's a monster. He will say anything.
You know that he will.
Tell him I'm lying, Oliver.
Say it.
I can explain.
You chose.
Slade.
Please. Ivo...
He's dead.
As dead as you are.
How many?
This one time, you can pray for me.
Behind you!
Ollie, are you okay? Where's Slade?
He knows.
Get down, get down!
- We gotta get off this ship.
- No.
Ollie, it's over. it's over. We gotta go.
We can still swim back to the island.
She's right, my friend.
We must hurry.
Unh. Slade, wait.
Stop. Don't move.
Get in the cell.
I do not take orders from you.
I am this ship's captain.
Not anymore.
This is my ship now.
Any objections?
Slade Wilson is dangerous.
No chances. No mistakes.
I'm in position.
When Slade comes out,
I'll have the shot.
Thermal imaging's coming up now.
They're in the northwest hall.
Roy, remember,
just get Thea and Moira away from Slade.
Don't start a fight. You'll lose. Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Ha-ha-ha. Thank you again...
- for such a wonderful and insightful tour.
- Of course.
You were a remarkable guide.
Did you have a favorite?
I found The Promise...
to be particularly compelling.
Thea? You home?
Roy? I thought I was
meeting you at Verdant.
Oh, yeah.
- Uh, this is, uh...
- I'm Roy Harper.
Slade Wilson.
That's a particularly firm handshake
you have there, son.
Yeah, you too.
Ollie.
There you are.
Sara, we didn't hear you come in.
I didn't want to interrupt the tour.
Mr. Wilson, this is
my son's friend, Sara Lance.
Of course.
You're the girl who came
back from the dead.
We're just glad to have her home.
Oh, I can see.
It's hard to find that special someone
who means everything to you.
You're very lucky.
So...
what would you like to do now...
Mr. Wilson?
Well, I hate to break up the party...
- but I think I should be going.
- Hmm.
I look forward to seeing
more of you, Moira.
Oh.
And your lovely family.
Dig's got a shot lined up outside.
Mr. Wilson.
May I walk you to your car?
Cyrus Gold...
the man in the skull mask.
All this was you.
They worked for you.
Well, I have my allies.
Just as you have yours.
John Diggle, for example.
I suppose you're wondering
why he hasn't taken his head shot.
Don't worry.
He's still alive.
For now.
Slade.
What do you want?
Hmm.
Five years ago, I made you a promise.
Do you remember?
Well, I'm here to fulfill it.
I'll see you around, kid.
We made it.
Where's Oliver?
I need you to see something.
Okay. Wait.
You need me.
Okay? You have the Mirakuru in you.
Not just in me.
You burned a box full of dirt.
Okay, look.
I can help you understand how it works.
I've spent my entire life
studying it, all right?
It was you.
You were the one who killed Shado.
No.
No, he chose. It was him.
Give him your gun.
Take it.
And show me...
how you killed Shado.
Show me!
Slade.
This isn't you.
It's the Mirakuru...
and you're sick.
I don't care.
I was trying to protect Sara.
But I didn't want Shado to die. I cared
for her too, and you know that I did.
I don't care.
You said we were brothers.
You said that.
Is that how you did it?
- Is that how you pointed the gun at her?
- Yes.
Get him out of here.
Why don't you just kill me?
If I kill you now...
it would be a mercy.
You cannot die...
until you have suffered...
the same way that I have suffered.
Until you have known...
complete despair.
And you will.
I promise.
Mr. Wilson leave?
Yeah.
It's getting pretty late.
I'm gonna go too.
Mm.
Oliver.
I know you and I have our differences, but
they hardly excuse your behavior tonight.
If this is the way you're
gonna act around me from
now on, then don't come
by the house any more.