My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But my old approach
wasn't enough.
I had to become
someone else.
something else.
I had to become
the Green Arrow.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
I am not going
to kill you,
but you need to trust me,
or we're both dead.
What this city needs
is someone willing to stand up
in the light of day,
not a guy lurking
around in the shadows.
I'm going to run for mayor.
What a pleasant
surprise.
I want you to bring
my sister back to life.
Even if Sara went into the Pit,
even if it worked,
what came out of the Pit
would not be Sara.
We are in uncharted
waters here.
I suggest...
You prepare yourself for the worst.
Leave a couple
of those on the table, Junie.
I thought you said we were
delivering 40 kilos.
So they'll get 38.
Dumbasses can't count, anyways.
Whoa!
Get down, now!
SCPD! On the ground!
Clear!
All clear!
We're good
to go here.
SCPD, hands in the air!
Relax,
we've got this.
What are you guys
doing here?
We didn't hear a call
from ESU to go out.
You guys aren't supposed
to be here, either.
Yeah, well,
we got a tip
from one of our CIs.
Sons of bitches!
Let's go.
♪ Arrow 4x04 ♪
Beyond Redemption
Original Air Date on October 28, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, this is
horrible.
What type of secret
lair has windows?
Well, you know,
Oliver said he wanted
to do things differently.
I think I just saw a cockroach.
Listen, about Oliver--
No, look, it's fine.
He still thinks
we spent the weekend
at a spa.
But why can't we
tell him about Sara?
Sara, she needs more time,
and I don't need
Oliver's judgment.
Just a couple more days,
and she'll be back to herself.
I promise.
Guessing he didn't tell you
what we're doing here, either.
No.
He just had a perma grin
on his face the whole way here.
Ok, now I'm worried.
He said he had some
big announcement to make.
Oh, my God, wait,
where is it?
Why aren't you
wearing it?
Wearing what?
Uh...
What is that
you wanted to tell us?
And why are you
telling us here?
Remember
this office?
Yes. This was Sebastian blood's
campaign office.
And now it's mine.
Anyone who's qualified
is afraid to run,
for a good reason.
But I can
protect myself.
So...
I'm running
for mayor.
Uh, don't everyone
congratulate me at once.
Oh, you're
serious!
Yes! The other week,
Lance was saying
that this city
needs someone
to stand up, who isn't hiding
behind a mask. It needs a leader.
But why does that person
have to be you?
I mean, don't get me wrong,
but you're not a politician.
Well, maybe that's the best reason
for me to be elected.
What are you going
to do for a staff,
or campaign manager--money?
Money part's taken care of.
Palmer Tech has funded enough
to kickstart the campaign.
Another decision my board of directors
are going to be thrilled with.
What platform
are you going to run on?
I'll figure it out.
What qualifies you
to be mayor?
I care about
the city.
But you can't say
that you're going to run
because being the Green Arrow
isn't enough.
I'm working on that.
We are going to brush up
on those answers
before the first
press conference.
Obviously.
I kind of thought
everyone would be
a little bit more supportive.
Oh, it's not that we're not supportive,
Oliver, it's just that--
we just want to make sure that
you're not in over your head.
Maybe the other announcement
will go over better.
Ok...
Ha!
For real?
There's a reason we had
Felicity buy Blood's campaign office.
Blood also needed
his own lair.
Don't--don't worry,
I--I burned
a lot of incense.
Oliver, how did you--
How did you do this
all by yourself?
Oh, I had help.
He had a lot of help.
Cisco and S.T.A.R. Labs.
Four polycarbonate
cases, each keyed
to your individual
biometrics.
Ha! God, I didn't even think you could
pronounce "biometrics."
I had some
design input.
Wow.
Oliver,
this is amazing.
Well, when I set up
shop in the foundry,
it was just me.
That's not the case anymore,
so I thought we could
use a little more space.
What was that?
What--did it break?
No.
You ok?
Yeah, I'm just not used
to this chair yet.
I'm feeding police
emergency services
and Homeland Security
radio transmissions
through a processing
algorithm 24/7.
This way, if anything
happens in the city,
we will--we will
know about it.
Two police detectives
found shot to death
responding
to a code three.
Um, there's no record
of them calling
dispatch for back-up.
Which means either
their comms failed
or they were ambushed
the moment they arrived on the scene.
Thea and I will do recon,
see if there's anything
the CSI missed
at the crime scene.
All right.
I'll talk to Lance.
Maybe skip the part
about running for mayor,
because I'm pretty sure
you're not going to have his vote.
That'll have to change.
Can't run the city
without the help
of the SCPD.
Ok.
Hmm.
What did Thea think
that you were wearing?
No idea.
Fast track ballistics
and have CSI dust
every shell casing
for latents.
Ok, forensics recovered
this SIM card.
Probably belongs
to one of the doers,
but CSU says they need 48 hours to
get a full work-up.
What? How is evidence
in a crime scene
where two detectives
were killed not a top priority?!
We don't have
the manpower.
Ohhh.
You spend
more time here now
than when you were
getting collared for hitting paparazzi.
You got a moment for me?
Yeah.
So these visits, are
they going to be a, uh,
weekly thing?
Well, I was trying
to help with, um...
What's that?
I wouldn't know.
City hall has cut
my budget so tight,
I can't get evidence
turned around before I'm 80.
I'm hoping that's something
I might be able
to help with eventually.
Yeah?
I've decided
to run for mayor.
Really?
And I know
it's a long-shot,
but it would mean a lot if you would
endorse my candidacy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
After what happened
to the last few mayors,
I'm hoping you win
in a landslide.
Till then, I'm trying
to catch a cop killer
and I don't have time to wait for my
understaffed crime lab.
I want you to wait
till nightfall to light a fire.
Otherwise, you're going
to draw attention.
All right,
there's fresh water
coming off a stream
at the base of the hill.
There's edible plants
maybe 50 feet to the north.
Hey, do not eat
the red berries,
and do not let
anyone see you.
Why are you
doing this?
Risking your life
to save mine?
It's complicated.
They may think
I'm dead,
but they're going to come
looking for you.
They're not going to come looking for me.
I'm going back to camp.
I've watched
those men.
They're like brothers
to each other.
They have
a history, a bond.
You're not
one of them.
That's why you're going
to have to do something for me.
And you're not
going to like it.
Ahem!
All right,
so I figured it out.
It's Neal Adams
in data processing.
He won the archery medal
3 years running at his summer camp.
He has a problem
with his temper,
and he likes
the color green.
You think that Neal Adams is
the Green Arrow?
He's--he's 5'2!
Lifts?
I am not telling you
who he is!
Oh, and B-T-Dub,
next time you want to prank your boss--
worst career move,
but whatevs--
you might want to
try a little harder.
And you lost me.
I've been receiving
these all week.
Ok, well,
I didn't send this,
and trust me,
if I were going to prank you,
it would be
a lot more creative.
This code is from 2013.
But the IP address
is coming
from Palmer Tech,
from a terminal here
in your work space.
I believe
the term is,
you are so busted.
I'm not busted.
I can't be busted.
I didn't send you
two-year-old code.
Though it is elegant.
And familiar.
Hmm?
I was going through some
of, uh, Mr. Palmer's old prototypes,
and I found this.
That was Ray's.
I mean...Mr. Palmer's.
I mean, this has code
that's like identical
to what you have
on the phone.
I mean,
the question is,
why is Mr. Palmer's
prototype OS
sending you texts
on your phone?
Ray must have connected
the prototype's computer
to the company's
local area network.
It did!
It uploaded a crash log.
I mean, the equipment's
programmed
to record the user's voice right before
a fatal malfunction.
Sorry.
Poor choice of words.
The point is, is that
Mr. Palmer's last recorded statement
could shed some light
on how he died.
Looks like
it's password protected.
I already know how he died.
I don't need to re-live it.
But--
But, Ray and I were close.
We were, um, friends.
He died 6 months ago.
I don't really want to open that
particular wound.
It did it again?
Nope.
Different mystery.
Lance gave us a SIM card
recovered from the crime scene.
Where's Laurel?
She said she had something she
needed to deal with.
Wow, it's a good thing you guys aren't
short handed these days.
This SIM card
isn't from a cell phone.
Looks like some kind
of walkie with GPS.
GPS as in we can track it?
As in, I can figure out
all the places it's been
and triangulate from there
to determine...
Where it came from.
Gear up.
Fifth floor is clear.
Yeah, this place
is completely empty.
I think I found something,
third floor.
Headed your way.
Every door here
is open or unlocked,
except for this one.
Clear.
It's not empty.
M4s, Kevlar,
flash bang grenades.
Some of this stuff is military-grade.
Well, do you think
we found the Ghost's armory?
No.
Wait...
Star City
police department.
The people who killed
those detectives were police officers.
All right,
all right, I'll bite.
What are we doing
down in your basement?
It's better
if I just show you.
After what happened between
us last year,
I swore that I would
never keep secrets from you again,
especially when it has
to do with our family.
Family?
Baby?
How is--
how is this even possible?
The League of Assassins.
They have something
called the Lazarus Pit.
It can bring someone
back from the dead.
Back from what? From the--
this isn't back, Laurel.
Look at her. Look--
look at my baby.
I--I don't--
Dad, she's alive.
Your daughter
is alive.
This isn't my daughter.
Daddy, it is.
She's just been
gone for a really long time.
It's ok.
She'll remember
who she is.
We just have
to be patient.
And we'll help her find
her wait, right?
Do you remember me?
I'm Laurel,
your sister?
Look.
There's me,
and this is you.
Do you see that?
And who is that?
Is that Daddy?
We're your family.
We love you.
Who--who am I?
She's speaking
because she's
remembering.
Laurel!
You all right?
I'm fine!
She just...
She needs
more time.
I think you better add "get an entirely
new police force"
to your campaign
platform.
It's not the entire
force, but...Yeah,
we don't know
who's compromised.
Except for Captain Lance.
Yeah, well, Captain Lance
is Mia right now.
I think it's safe to assume
that whatever help
we're going to get,
it's right here in this room.
I'm working on something.
Cisco said
we were still working out
some of the kinks.
In the last two months, there's
been a huge spike
on gangs stealing
drug shipments from other gangs.
Yeah, but it's not these gangs,
it's these bad cops.
Who steal the drugs
to sell them back
to the gangbangers
they stole them from.
So these corrupt cops
are taking down big drug scores.
Mm-hmm.
Let's give them one.
How?
That depends on how
close you are
with your former drug dealer.
Oh.
Depends which one.
We're going
to need some money.
Don't you mean
more money?
Mm-hmm.
Queenie.
I haven't seen
you in forever.
This your boyfriend?
Bodyguard.
Didn't realize
the Queens
could afford that kind of
help these days.
Well, I recently
came into my inheritance
and was hoping
to throw a party with it.
So can you
help me out?
To the tune of...
80 keys?
You know how
I like to party.
I might have
a hook-up.
But he doesn't
take credit cards.
Let me make a call.
I've been trying
to get in touch with you.
Ah, yeah,
phone's been off.
What, are you
going to tell me
you're running
for president now?
Your detectives aren't dead
because of gang violence.
They were killed by cops.
What are you talking about?
The SIM card that you gave us;
It led to the killers' armory,
and all the equipment, the weapons,
it was all SCPD-issued.
Who is it?
It could be anyone
in the department.
These guys have been
taking down drug busts.
So I've had Thea procure
a couple kilos of cocaine--
Your mayoral campaign's off to
a fantastic start.
We're keeping the drugs
in a warehouse on Meldrum.
I need you to subtly
get the word out.
All right.
Listen, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
I want to be there
when they show.
I'm not sure
that's a good idea.
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
I really give a damn,
because if I got bad
cops in my precinct,
I'm going to be there
to bust 'em.
The hell
happened to you?
The woman tried
to escape.
We chased her, but she
went through a minefield.
Thought I heard
an explosion earlier.
That one got Richards.
Son of a bitch.
I caught her...
Eventually.
Made it memorable.
What, I'm supposed
to kill her, right?
Her, yeah.
Richards, not so much.
I didn't kill Richards.
I told you--
A landmine.
I know.
You know
what's funny?
We've been here
months without a problem,
and here you come and two guys get
wasted by landmines.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means
I want to see her.
The woman.
I want to see
the body.
Ok.
I know this is
a trap and all,
but something
about the drugs,
the club...
Makes me feel like I'm back in
high school again.
What?
Just thinking about how much
I hate raising a daughter in this city.
Heads up!
I'm reading a truck
closing in on your position.
The make matches a profile
for an ESU strike vehicle.
Copy,
we're ready.
Two minutes out.
Captain Lance.
What, I don't get a code name like
the rest of you?
Detective...
Get ready.
Target's on site.
Let's go.
We've got multiple
Tangos, move!
Move out!
Oh!
You ok?
The training, the equipment,
those were cops.
And no, I'm not ok.
You have got
to be kidding me.
Oh, no, um, not to complain,
but you do know that
you just brought a police captain
into our secret lair?
Don't worry; I got enough to put you
away for 25 years.
Kidding.
Captain Lance isn't the police
we should be worried about.
Wow. No wonder there's
corruption on the force.
Everyone else has got
better resources.
I don't know.
Those ESU
had some pretty
fancy toys tonight.
That definitely weren't
standard police issue.
Well, they were
police issue, all right,
but just not standard.
Those were specialized
anti-vigilante
task force gear.
I thought the task force
was disbanded.
Yeah, I might have
reinstated that,
um, last year.
How many officers are there?
40 or so.
Well, that definitely
narrows things down a bit.
We should check
their conduct records.
Maybe that'll narrow it
down a little bit more.
Yeah, that's going to take a little bit
longer than usual.
Well, I can give you
unrestricted access
to the department's
computer network.
Might speed things up
a little.
I'll see what I can
dig up at the precinct.
Looks like 80 keys here.
Idiots baited the mouse
trap with real cheese.
Because they knew we'd
sniff them out otherwise.
Well, it's a good thing
we decided to pack the special gear.
We weren't the only ones showing up
with a little surprise tonight.
Captain Lance?
There's no way he didn't
peg us as cops.
We got to take him out.
We don't kill cops.
Tell that to the two gold
shields we wasted last night.
They were in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
I'm not killing fellow
officers in cold blood.
Our advantage was the force
thought we were gangbangers.
We should put this
to a vote.
My vote? Nine millimeters,
and the only one
that counts.
We are not criminals.
Let's all just try to remember that.
We went this route
because the city is dying,
and we need to be able
to provide for our families.
Still doesn't change
the fact that Lance is a problem.
No, he's not.
He's a solution.
Curtis?
There you are!
Why haven't you been
answering my texts?
Your texts were
"911," "OMG,"
"ASAP," and five
exclamation points.
I do not have time
to respond to something
that doesn't contain
at least one actual word.
I need your help
with Mr. Palmer's crash log.
I thought I told you
to let that go.
Look, I've tried brute
forcing a password,
but nothing works.
But there is a subkernel
that contains
a programmer note.
Oh, my God, this must be
what talking to me is like.
And that programming note suggests that
you know the password.
I mean, which makes sense,
right? You and Mr. Palmer were friends.
Yeah, I know the password.
You do? So tell it
to me so we can--
No! I...
I do not want to listen
to a recording
of my ex-boyfriend's
final moment before he died.
You and Mr. Palmer
were together?
Now do you understand
why I don't want to hear his voice?
No.
My brother died
six years ago.
Pancreatic cancer.
To be
able to hear
something from him I've
never heard before...
God, I'd--I'd
give anything.
Captain Lance.
What a pleasure it was
to receive your message.
And for you
to initiate contact,
well, made me feel
like our relationship
took an important
step forward.
I need your help.
I'm sorry,
say that again.
It's for my daughter.
Not the one
that you're holding
over me as leverage.
Sara, the one
you lost last year.
Yeah, she's back.
This thing called
the Lazarus Pit.
I'm sure
you've heard of it.
What, you did your
homework on me;
you don't think I
did a little digging around on you?
You used to be
a member
of the League
of Assassins.
What is it you want,
Mr. Lance?
It's my daughter.
She's not right.
She's--she's come back
and she's different.
She's crazy!
It's a miracle
she came back at all.
It doesn't feel like a miracle.
All right?
Now you know
about this stuff.
Is there anything
I can do?
that you can do?
I can give advice,
father to father.
I can tell you that if it were
my daughter,
I'd put her down.
She's my baby girl.
No, she isn't.
She may look like your daughter,
but she doesn't
possess her soul.
The most loving act
you can commit
is to return Sara
to her final rest.
I'm sorry.
Ohh.
Oh, I am so glad
we came back.
You all right?
Hmm?
You're doing that,
um, crinkly thing
with your eyebrows.
Oh, just, um,
ha, no,
just something at work.
It's no big deal.
Um, this work.
Big deal.
Liza Warner.
I pulled her SCPD
personnel file
using my computer
at Palmer Tech since ours is fritzing.
One of the original recruits to the
anti-vigilante task force over 3 years ago.
Hand-picked by then
Detective Lance.
Do we think
she's a suspect?
I think that Sergeant Warner
has deposited over
a quarter of a million dollars
into offshore bank accounts
in the last three months.
Where can we
find her?
I am working on that.
I used the network access
that Captain Lance gave us
and I turned on every uniform
and squad car camera
on the force
in the last 12 hours.
I'm running facial recognition
looking for Warner.
Do you see something?
No, someone.
Pause.
Zoom in.
Mm-hmm.
The man that Lance
is talking to...
That's Damian Darhk.
Aye yi yi.
Oh, jeez. Heh.
You know I got a heart
condition, right?
For years, you've looked at me
with such contempt.
Utter disdain.
So I'm wondering...
Do I have that same
look on my face now?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking
about you...
and Damian Darhk.
Ok, it's, it's--
I didn't know
if you knew who he was,
or what he's been
doing to this city.
And now I see this
look on your face.
You know.
It's complicated.
No, it's not.
Do you have any idea how many
people he's killed?
Yeah, I got more
of an idea than you.
And listen, you,
you of all people,
you don't get
to come in to my house
and pass judgment on me,
all right?!
No, you always held yourself out
as better than me.
More righteous.
And you were.
Until tonight.
Actually, it's been a little more than
two months now,
me working with Darhk.
It started out benign.
He said he had resources;
he had people, money.
He held himself out
as just another guy
who wanted to help this city.
And we needed the help.
You weren't here.
By the time I figured out
who he was,
what he was...
That's when
he threatened Laurel.
Laurel can take care of herself. You see
what she does out there.
That's what I thought
about Sara, too--
Stop, stop it!
Stop hiding behind
your daughters!
They would be ashamed of what
you're doing right now.
You don't know what
I'm going through.
You were the main reason behind me
running for mayor!
A part of me
has always
wanted you to see
what kind of man
I really am.
I didn't expect
to wind up finding out what kind of
man you really are.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
How'd you do it?
Kill the woman.
Strangled her.
I thought you said
you made it--
what was that
word--memorable.
Ah, she won't forget it.
What?
You going to propose?
You don't sound like a guy who
just committed his first murder,
and I'm guessing you didn't have
too many opportunities
in that posh boarding
school you grew up in.
You think I'm lying?
I think if you're not, then you're
a stone cold killer.
Even if you didn't off her, even if
you're messing with me--
which I do not
recommend...
I see it
in your eyes.
Reiter saw it, too.
It's probably why
he recruited you.
Saw what?
You are one
dark bastard.
Something very cold
inside of you.
You're terrified of it.
Ok, Conklin,
tell me something.
If I'm this dark person...
Shouldn't you
be afraid of me?
Nah.
I'm the exact
same way.
If you're lying to me, you're going
to find that out.
Nice sign.
Arrived this morning.
You all right?
Just thinking.
About?
Going to Sentinel
Games as kids.
Do you remember
Papp Stadium?
Oh, yeah.
I loved the popcorn.
Every time a Sentinels
player hit a homer,
every single person
in that stadium stood and cheered.
Every single one.
United.
And I wanted
to run for mayor
because I wanted to be
the leader of that city.
Wanted?
Thea, I don't know
if that city exists anymore.
I think that it might be
beyond saving.
So what
are you saying?
That I don't have
to run for mayor.
I'm sorry, baby,
but you're not her.
You're not her.
Dad!
Dad, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm doing what
I got to do.
You got not idea what terrible things
I would do for both of you.
No, no, you are not
going to kill your own daughter.
She's not my daughter!
Dad, it's Sara.
It's ok.
Oh, God.
Dad.
What am I doing?
It's ok!
What am I doing?!
Look at me, it's ok.
It's ok.
What am I doing?
I'm sorry, baby. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Captain Lance.
Liza. What--
what are you doing here?
I heard you were
looking for me.
Thought I'd make it
easier for you.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Dad!
Ever been here before?
It's the SCPD's contraband
disposal facility.
Thousands of pounds
of Slam, Vertigo,
heroin, all incinerated.
That's just literally burning money.
Yeah, and the site requires the precinct
captain to gain access,
and that's
not happening.
What was your plan, Quentin?
You have to know
the city's dying.
Were you just going to stay at your desk
until there was no city left.
I'll tell you what I
wasn't going to do--
I wasn't going to
dishonor the badge like you have.
I'm no Saint, but at least
I'm not a criminal.
Neither am I.
I'm just a desperate cop
that got backed into
too tight a corner.
What do we know?
Liza Warner and her posse
took Lance outside
of Laurel's apartment.
We need to find
my father.
I'm working on it.
Just a little hampered.
I think I got something
before the latest glitch.
Captain Lance's ID was just to access
the SCPD contraband
disposal facility
3 minutes ago.
Thank you, Quentin.
Sorry about all the paperwork
you'll have to fill out
when they find you.
Word of advice--put
a bullet in my head now
'cause I am coming after
you with everything.
By the time they find you,
we'll be long gone.
We're leaving this city
like everybody else.
New frequency, same cry.
Let's get out of here!
Sergeant Warner,
you have failed this city.
Is that all you got?
Nope.
Get out of here.
All I got to do is push
and I'll sever your spinal cord.
Aah!
But you're not going
to do it, Liza.
You said you're
not a criminal.
You kill that man,
you are.
I told you I wasn't
a criminal.
But I also told you
I was desperate.
We all are.
Living in this city,
dealing with what we're
dealing with right now?
We're all desperate.
We've all been made
to do desperate things.
Terrible things.
But I got to believe
that we are not
beyond redemption.
And I got to believe
that this city can still be saved.
'Cause once
we stop believing,
that's when this
city really dies.
And us, us, right
along with it.
Maybe, just maybe,
we start saving
our home
by saving
ourselves first.
And that means facing up
to our mistakes.
That means
facing justice.
You put on
that uniform
'cause you
believe in justice.
Ask yourself,
Warner...
Is that still
the case?
Do what
you got to do.
I guess you know
your Miranda rights.
You got your own key
or something?
What you said to Warner
saved my life.
I...I didn't know you had such a way
with words.
Well, I don't do encores.
You believe
what you said?
Yeah.
Every word.
Especially the part
about facing justice.
When One Police Plaza
opens this morning,
I will be there
turning myself in.
I can't
have you do that.
We haven't been
able to get close to Darhk.
You have.
I'd like you
to stick around.
Stay on the inside.
Wow.
Well, that's only a smart plan
if you can trust me.
I trust the man who said
we can't stop believing
we can save this city.
Like I said--
stone cold killer.
You satisfied?
Get rid of the body.
This cave might be
useful for something.
It's ok.
You're ok.
How did you--
where did you learn to do that?
I learned it here.
I haven't always
been alone on this island.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, my God,
he's here.
Hi.
How you doing, man?
Oliver Queen.
Hi there.
It's, uh,
absolutely wonderful
that--that all of
you are--are here.
Just--just wonderful.
And surprising.
So, what do you think?
Um, hey, did you--
did you hire all of these people?
No, that's what makes
them interns, Ollie.
Where did we get all
of these interns?
Easiest way to get
a lot of followers on social media
is to own a very
successful club.
All I had to do was tell them
what I've already known for 3 years.
Oliver Queen is going
to save this city.
What's this?
This your speech.
You're announcing
your candidacy this afternoon,
so you better get your suit
out of moth balls.
Did you write this?
I wrote it down.
Just with what you told me,
about this city being united.
United.
That's what
this city used to be.
It's what it can be.
It's what it must be again.
Now, I know that
I'm not the obvious choice for mayor.
I'm--I'm not
a politician.
I signed away
my family's company.
I didn't even
graduate from college,
although, in my defense,
I did go to four of them.
I certainly don't have a traditional
background for leadership,
but I can tell you this--
after five years in hell,
I returned home
with only one goal.
I wanted to save my city.
And with your help,
I can.
With your help,
we will restore our home
to the shining beacon
we know it can be.
But how we're going to get
there isn't a mystery.
We will overcome
our challenges
with help from our friends,
our family,
our loved ones.
I'm sorry, Felicity,
this is my fault.
Those we trust,
and those we will need to trust again
in order to prevail.
Because the only way that we are
going to return our home to greatness
is to do so together.
United.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.