Previously on "Arrow"...
Kanjigar
septum vohnostrum.
Mr. Darhk will be held
without bail
or possibility of release.
You may now call
your organization
and have that
other message delivered.
He said you were
his ace in the hole.
Is that what you'd
like me to call you...
Or do you prefer
Mr. Diggle?
Andy.
What are you doing
in the dark, man?
Didn't want to wake
Sara up.
Thanks for letting
me know where this was.
I want you to
feel safe.
You sounded pretty
rattled on the phone.
What the hell's
going on?
HIVE knows I'm
alive, John.
Did they come
after you?
In a way. I mean,
one of them reached out,
some guy with perfect teeth
and a missing hand.
I didn't--he didn't
tell me his name.
Malcolm Merlyn.
The head of the League
of Assassins?
Well, not anymore.
Yeah. Well, now he
works with Damien Darhk.
Since when?
Two nights ago.
Andy, you should have
told me this earlier.
I know, man,
and I'm sorry,
but this whole thing
has got me thrown, man.
I didn't think HIVE
knew where I was.
What did Merlyn want?
I think there's some
kind of friction going on
between HIVE and Darhk.
Have you noticed they
haven't even tried
to bust Darhk out
of prison?
Yeah, I've been
thinking about that.
And now this Merlyn guy
asks me to help him.
Help him what, bust
Darhk out of Iron Heights?
DoD's scheduled to run
Paveway missiles
through Pennytown
tomorrow night at 2300.
Merlyn wants me to help
him hijack the shipment.
Yeah? Well, just one
of those Paveways makes
for a pretty good
get out of jail free card.
And that's why I'm
asking you, man.
What do I do?
First, kidnapping,
then stealing missiles.
Merlyn's trying really hard
to be friends with Darhk.
Malcolm's convinced Darhk is
on the winning side.
He's even trying
to protect me
from whatever
he's planning.
The only thing Darhk
should be planning on
is getting convicted
at trial.
Why does that thing
creep me out the way it does?
Because it's creepy.
There's something
that I haven't told you guys.
Shocker.
Sorry.
I've seen this
idol before.
What? Where?
Lian Yu.
You really love
not talking
about that place,
don't you?
Where are we
with the security upgrades?
Everything's in place.
We're good to go.
Because Merlyn knows
the bunker's location.
If he's working
with Darhk--
Then that means we
have to worry about him
coming down here
and stealing
this creepy
stone thingy.
And what about his plan to hijack
the missile shipment?
Oliver, I think we keep
Andy right where he is.
That way, we have
someone on the inside.
Are you sure that's
a good idea?
Well, he's out from under
the influence of Darhk.
We can trust him.
Trust is one thing.
Installing him as a double agent,
that's another.
That's a lot of pressure
to put on someone,
especially someone
that is still in recovery.
Oliver, Andy is
a standup guy.
He's got this.
And you've got this.
You could
blow that off.
You don't owe
Ruvé Darhk anything.
Tradition. Loser attends the winner's
acceptance speech.
You didn't lose.
You pulled out of the race
because of her husband.
Which I will try
not to mention to the press.
Let's get this
over with.
We worked hard
to get to this moment,
but now the real work begins
to make this city
great again.
Thank you.
Mr. Queen, have time
to answer a few questions?
I'm not
a candidate anymore.
I'm just here to support
the new mayor.
So no comment
on the write-in results?
Uh, what write-in
results?
48% of the electorate
wrote in your brother's name
on their ballots.
That's a historic
showing for a candidate
who pulled out
of the race.
I'll let you and your former
opponent catch up.
Well, thank you for
coming out tonight, Mr. Queen.
It's a very
gracious gesture.
I am always gonna
have this city's
best interests
at heart.
Well, let's hope the same can be said
for your friends.
Miss Lance, I am
so pleased to meet you.
I was very impressed
by your handling
of the Damien Darhk
hearing.
I was just getting
warmed up.
Well, my hope is
that you'll be too busy
to handle the trial.
District Attorney Remz
has taken on
a new position
as my deputy mayor,
and I would like you
to succeed him as D.A.
Think about it.
I think that we could
do great things
for this city
if we worked together.
Take care.
Listen. Reiter's
men outnumber us.
We have guns,
but so do they,
so when we get up there,
we cannot hesitate to
kill, do you understand?
Taiana?
Just months ago,
I was a dive instructor.
Couldn't dream
of taking a life.
I wouldn't.
This place truly
is Hell.
It makes monsters
of us all.
Who's in the photo?
Me and my brother.
I forget sometimes that
we were once this happy
and this innocent.
When I first got here,
I used to look
at a photo from my past.
It helped for a time,
reminded me of the person
that I used to be,
but I'm telling you now
that that person
wouldn't survive here,
and you won't either
if you stay focused on the past.
Do you understand?
Da.
How do I take
those bastards out?
Follow me.
It's past 11:30.
It's the U.S. Army, man.
Late means on time.
Or we're staking out
the wrong place.
If Andy says this is
where it's gonna be,
this is where
it's gonna be.
No movement yet
on the missiles.
Yeah. We should be
out there with them.
Even with John's
fancy Argus toys,
this place is more secure with us
watching over it.
So are you gonna do it,
be district attorney
by day
and Black Canary
by night?
I don't know.
I mean, it would
help having eyes on Mrs. Evil.
Yeah. Well, if you
believe Malcolm,
it will be
a short-term job anyway.
Won't be any need for a D.A.
once the city's destroyed.
You stopped
calling him dad.
Well, that's because
he's not dad.
Look. I know I've said
that before,
but this time,
it's different.
This time, it's mutual.
That couldn't be
further from the truth, dear.
Mr. Diggle's
upgraded security
needs a few upgrades
by the way.
You know why
we're here.
Hand over the idol,
and there won't be
any trouble.
Well, there's gonna be
trouble then.
All right.
That's the signal.
Guy's dressed like
a League of Assassins.
Merlyn probably has
a few loyalists left.
Get me in position.
Hyah!
No, no, no, no!
Hold on!
It's me, it's me,
it's me!
Are you always
this quiet?
Come on. We just saved
the shipment,
and you made it
look easy.
That's because
it was easy.
Err!
Unh!
The idol.
It's gone.
♪ Arrow 4x18 ♪
Eleven-Fifty-Nine
Original Air Date on April 6, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You two can
stand down.
He's gone.
- Merlyn?
- Yeah.
And a few League
of Assassin members.
He took the idol.
I should have stopped him.
We should have
been here.
We--I'm sure you
did everything you could.
Merlyn's gonna
give that idol
to his new friend
Darhk to get his mojo back.
We've been scouring
the streetcams.
It's like
he just vanished.
That's why the League calls
him the Magician.
I'm gonna go hit
the streets.
Thea, no one
is gonna give up Merlyn.
Well, then I'm gonna
hit people on the streets.
I'll check
with Andy,
see if he can get
a 20 on Merlyn.
Uh, John.
Andy has already
risked a lot.
I don't want to put him
in a compromised position.
Oliver, he's already
There's a direct
line between him
and the man
we are looking for.
Let's use that.
Yeah.
Talk to me.
This missile job
was too easy.
It was like Merlyn's
men weren't even trying.
Meanwhile, it pulled
our focus,
Merlyn was able
to come down here
and get exactly
what he wanted.
You think Merlyn
played Andy?
What if Andy is
playing us?
Look. I'm not saying
it's not possible,
but this is John's
brother we're talking about.
I mean, he's done
so much for us.
He--he saved Lyla.
Should I just trust
him outright?
No, but you better
be sure
before making
an accusation
that you and John
can't recover from.
It's my dad.
I have to take this.
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Please. You have to
help me!
What is it?
What's going on?
Conklin, or what
remains of him,
the thing that
killed those men,
it killed Oliver.
It has Reiter trapped
down there.
Come on!
Tea. Hey.
Don't be too
impressed.
That's the only
Chinese I was able
to pick up
from Sara.
So listen.
You thought about how you're
gonna tell our
newly elected mayor
that you're turning
down her job offer?
I have,
but I'm not sure
that I will.
Well, this one's
a no-brainer, sweetie.
You can't go work
for a murderer.
This job would put me
in the inner circle.
Yeah, at the cost of being
the Black Canary.
Look. ever since HIVE had
D.A. Bray killed,
the district attorney
has 24/7 protection.
They would not let
you out of their sight.
I'll waive it.
You think Ruvé Darhk
will let that happen?
Listen. I--I never
thought I'd say this,
but I am glad that you
are the Black Canary,
I'm glad for all
the good you're doing,
and I'm glad for the good
it's done you,
but you got to know
that taking this job,
that means taking off
that mask forever.
Careful. Could hurt
yourself with that.
It's not myself
I'm planning on hurting with it.
Andy. Yeah?
I got eyes
on Merlyn.
Ok. Where are you?
In some old box
factory, I think.
You sure
this is the place?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure.
Come on.
Merlyn's this way.
Why didn't you have
him radio us in?
I had him stay
behind for backup.
Merlyn!
Look out!
You ok?
Swell.
What happened?
He took an arrow
for me.
Let me see,
let me see.
Don't worry about it, man.
We deal with this
kind of stuff every week.
- Come on.
- No, no, no, no.
You got to get
to Iron Heights now.
If Merlyn's not
here, then that--
that means he's
on his way there with the idol.
If Darhk gets
that idol,
no prison will be
able to hold him.
Ha ha. Heh heh heh.
One of these days,
you're gonna tell me
how you get in
and out of here.
A magician never
reveals his secrets.
So what next?
You gonna make a coin
appear from behind
my ear?
You know, you're
awfully flippant for a man
who's asked
a great deal of me.
Do you have it?
Perhaps now's
a good time to remind you
of our terms.
Yes. You and your daughter
get spared from Genesis.
Is that still
the play?
I don't think you
appreciate what this cost me.
Oh, come on.
Stop being so high-handed.
What's wrong?
Mr. Merlyn, do you know
what the Khushu idol is?
Khushu is an old
Arabic term for humbleness,
suffice it to say, something
I wouldn't associate with you.
When the earliest
homo magi forged these idols,
they did so
in the image of those
whose powers
they wished to channel,
so attention
to detail is essential.
It's missing a piece.
The Ribalvei stone.
They must have hidden it
someplace else.
Find it,
or Genesis is not
what you and your daughter
have to fear.
All right.
You're gonna need
a few stitches,
but, uh, this should
hold for now.
I'm gonna need a whole lot more
than a few stitches.
Merlyn's men saw
you fighting for your team.
Darhk's now gonna
know that I'm on your side.
I'm a dead man.
I mean, he's just
not gonna stop with me.
He's gonna come
for you,
he's gonna come for Lyla, Sara.
Oh, God.
Listen. He's not gonna
come for anybody.
Ok? He can't.
Merlyn has the idol.
Look. He's probably
delivering it to him right now.
No, Andy.
No, he doesn't.
- There's a piece missing.
- What?
We separated a piece of it
and put it in another location.
Only thing Merlyn's delivering is
a big, ugly paperweight.
Darhk will find it.
He finds everything.
Listen, listen.
Andy, listen to me, man.
He won't find
anything.
I hid it myself.
John.
Can I speak to you?
This information needs
to be compartmentalized.
Listen.
He's scared, man,
and for good reason.
He's entitled to
know that we have
the situation
under control.
Well, that control is
only as strong as the secret.
The less people
who know, the better.
He risked everything,
everything for us.
He took an arrow
for you.
He has my trust.
Why doesn't he
have yours?
Malcolm's gonna try
and get the idol to Darhk
if he hasn't done it
already.
I can go there
as A.D.A.
and have the entire
cellblock searched.
Do it.
Speedy, you
and Spartan go back
to the bunker,
work CCTV,
work facial recognition,
do anything
that we can do
to get a line on Merlyn.
Ok.
And what can I do?
You should go home
and rest.
You've done enough
for tonight.
What about you?
I'll be right behind you.
I'm just gonna run down a lead.
You guys,
get to the surface,
gather the others,
and go for the boats.
Go! Come on!
What about you?
Reiter's still
in the catacombs.
If he's found
that idol,
you won't be able
to stop him.
We don't need
We need to trap him.
You guys are doing
a wonderful job in there.
You know, I have been meaning
to redecorate the place myself.
You know, my office
received an anonymous tip
that contraband
intended for your use
was smuggled
into this prison.
- Hmm.
Find anything?
All right. Search
every cell on this tier.
I want to make sure none of his
friends are stashing anything for him.
You know, you're lucky
I'm not the man
that you think I am,
Miss Lance.
If I were the man that your
father so vehemently claims,
you'd be in a lot of trouble right now,
wouldn't you?
Are you threatening an assistant
district attorney?
Oh, no, no, no.
Not at all.
Just merely trying to
figure out
where your father
gets these vicious ideas from.
Ooh! Oh.
I hope his mind
isn't starting to go.
You know, dementia
is sometimes
an aftereffect
of long-term alcoholism.
You're a son
of a bitch.
Regardless, it's
comforting to know
that his heart is
in the right place.
A father would do
anything to protect his daughter
from the dark.
I'll see you in court.
Looking
for something?
Oh, jeez, man!
Do you know
how to knock?
Any luck finding
Merlyn?
No, but I think you
already knew that.
I'm gonna ask
you again.
What are you
looking for?
Surveillance.
Ok. Look.
HIVE knows I'm
John's brother.
They could have hidden
bugs here.
Maybe that's how that
one-handed friend of yours
found me
in the first place.
You always have
an answer for everything.
Hey. What are you
talking about?
I think that you've
been working with Darhk
since the beginning,
that you and Merlyn have been
playing us this entire time,
and now you're here, looking for
the missing piece of the idol!
I'm on your side,
remember?
I even got hurt
trying to protect you.
I remember.
I told John
to trust you,
to give you
another chance,
but I was wrong
because men like you
don't change.
Now you tell me
what does Darhk
have planned?
If I'm the man that
you think I am,
then you know torture
is not gonna get me to say anything.
I haven't started
torturing you yet.
Aah!
What the hell
are you doing?
Showing you who
he really is!
Tell him!
John, he thinks
I'm a traitor!
I know exactly what
that Kevlar won't protect.
Let him go.
Unh!
Dig, you can't
trust him.
- Get out.
- John--
Now.
You had no right!
I had every right.
This is
about keeping us safe.
No, it's not, Oliver.
This is about you
controlling
everything and everyone
around you.
Andy tipped us off
to the missile heist.
We go there,
Merlyn comes here
and takes the idol.
Then he brings us
to Merlyn's hideout,
where we are met
with an ambush.
Where he took
an arrow for you.
That could have
been a feint.
When I confronted him
at your apartment,
he was tearing it
apart.
Looking
for surveillance.
Or he was looking
for the last piece of the idol.
John, you are the one
who always tells me
do not have a blind spot
when it comes to your family.
And you're the one who told me
to give Andy a second chance.
You're the one who wanted
to extract him from HIVE.
You're the one who
said he could come back
from the darkness
the same way you did.
But I didn't.
I've tried.
I've tried harder at this
than I ever have at anything,
but at the end
of the day,
I am who those 5 years
away turned me into,
I'm what they
turned me into.
So what, Oliver,
just because Felicity left you,
I'm supposed to
believe that all men
are incapable
of redemption?
Not all men are
like you, Oliver.
Some of us change,
some of us grow,
some of us evolve.
You are stuck, man,
stuck in your self-pity
and your
self-righteousness,
and that is why
Felicity left you.
My brother
is my business.
You have no idea
what he's been through,
and you sure as hell
had no right to judge him.
I'm sure he didn't
mean that, Ollie.
Yes, he did.
How'd it go
in Iron Heights?
Turned up a few
burner cell phones,
6 bags of heroin,
an no idol.
Well, we hacked
into the security system
at the prison,
so if anything happens,
we'll see it.
Right.
Hey.
Are you ok?
John and I had
a difference of opinion.
About Andy?
I confronted Andy,
and dig walked in.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Probably should have
taken your advice,
district attorney Lance.
I'm still just
an A.D.A.
I'm turning down
the promotion.
Because it's being
offered by Ruvé Darhk?
No, because taking the job
means giving up my place here
with you
and the team.
The team's falling apart.
John's furious with me,
Thea's consumed
with a rage for Malcolm,
and...
Well, Felicity's gone.
Becoming district attorney's
something that you've worked
the better part
of 3 years for.
I might have wanted
to be D.A.,
but that was
a lifetime ago.
Sara's lifetime?
You channeled your grief
and became the Black Canary,
but Sara's not dead
anymore.
Maybe you owe it
to yourself
to pursue the path
you were on.
You're serious?
This city has enough
heroes with masks on.
With Ruvé Darhk
as mayor,
it needs a hero
without a mask.
It needs Laurel Lance.
Rec time.
20 minutes. 20 minutes.
Ahh. Uh, are you
in touch with the land,
spend much time
in mother nature?
No? Well, your
ancestors did.
They knew that life
is a series of phases.
"A time to be born,
a time to die,
"a time to plant,
a time to uproot,
a time to kill."
Master the paradox
of change with inconstancy,
and the primordial force
of nature itself
will be at your
beck and call.
Ah. My idol--
Julius Caesar.
"Cry havoc! And let slip
the Dogs of War."
What happened?
It was rec hour.
The prisoners were out
of their cells.
He's holding
the guards hostage.
- How many?
- Doesn't matter how many.
We have to put Darhk
back in his cage.
Let's gear up!
Oliver, I can't
prosecute him
without getting him
into custody first.
One last time.
What the hell's going on
around here?
Can't just stand around here
waiting for something to happen.
Who's in charge?
Not you, captain.
You've been suspended.
Heh heh heh.
Pike, right?
Well, that figures.
Wait it out till we've
got a stack
of dead bodies
on our hands.
I'm sorry, sir. You need to get back
to your vehicle.
No. I want to
speak with him.
I need to speak
with him now!
- I can't do that.
- Yes, you can do that.
You can do that.
Go get--never mind.
- I see him.
- Sir!
Pike! Hey! I see
you overhere!
How are we gonna
get through all those cops?
Looks like Lance
has it covered.
By laying into
Lieutenant Pike apparently.
And he just knocked
him out.
As a distraction
to give us an opening.
Let's move.
Thought
I told you to come alone.
You did,
and I didn't.
Look. I know
you don't trust me,
but that's why I'm here--
to prove you can.
Darhk has hostages
in the mess hall.
Let's fan out and hit them
from all sides.
I remember this guy.
Those lips.
Gross.
Not a bad warmup.
It seems like you're
ready for a rematch.
Go get the others.
I've got this.
- No. Let me take him.
- Go!
Let's see how well
I taught you.
Huh.
You know, the police
took me seriously
when I said I would start
killing hostages
if they moved
upon the prison.
It's too bad our
masked vigilante friends
didn't get the memo.
Well, too bad
for you really.
Kill them.
Unh!
You no longer have
the drive to kill, and it shows.
You lost part of yourself
when they cured you of that bloodlust,
and that is why
you will never beat me.
Andrew Diggle,
it's been a while.
Let him go!
Drop your weapons.
Don't do it.
Suit yourself,
but on the count of 3,
I'm gonna turn
that wall into
a Jackson Pollock
painting with his brains.
1...
2...
Ok.
Now was that
so hard?
I believe you have
something for me.
An--Andy.
I'm sorry, man.
Heh heh heh.
Andy.
I've been tracking
your movements for months.
I know everywhere
you been.
All I needed to hear
was that it was you
that hid the stone.
Was there ever
a chance for you?
Your brother's way beyond
reach, Mr. Diggle.
It's all over now.
Unh!
Took the words right
out of my mouth!
I need to sacrifice.
Not enough.
You know what to do.
Ohh.
Kanjigar septum
vohnostrum.
Ha ha ha!
Ohh! Oh, I feel
so much better.
Hey. I am sorry
about your buddies,
but omelets and eggs
and all of that,
but I know how to make it
up to you, though.
Who wants to go
for a walk outside?
Heh heh heh.
Andy here
might have mentioned
that his brother John
worked for the Green Arrow,
or should I say
Oliver Queen?
Oh, oh, oh, see, I know
what you're all thinking,
but, no, he didn't
tell me.
It was really just
a hop, skip, and a jump
from the whole
Diggle connection
to you to your little sister
to your ex-girlfriend,
but when you came
to rescue that boy William,
that look on your face,
that was a father's look.
I should have recognized
it there and then.
We need to
get out of here now.
Patience.
I've been waiting
for this moment for a long time.
Ms. Lance,
9 months ago,
I made your daddy
a promise.
I told him what I would do
if he betrayed me.
Unh!
Impressive.
Now where was I?
Oh, yeah. I want
you to give your father a message
from me.
I want you to tell
him--unh!
I'm a man of my word.
Ohh.
Hey, hey.
It's all right. It's ok.
Hey, hey. Look at me.
You're gonna be all right.
Come on.
Help!
Help in here, please!
You have to help
her, please!
She's lost a lot
of blood.
I need a crash cart
and a trauma team in here stat!
- Let her go.
- What?
I need you to let her go
so I can do my job.
Now leave!
The trauma team
will be in here any second,
and the last thing
she needs right now is a circus.
Go! Go.
How do you know
how to do this,
to bury a man alive?
You were right
how this island changed you.
Do you still look
at your picture?
She's beautiful.
Who is she?
Her name is Laurel Lance,
and she was my home
before a this.
I don't know what
she'll think
of the man
I've become.
If I don't make it
off this island,
you will go to Russia
and find my parents
and tell them what
happened to me and Vlad.
If you don't make it,
I will find this Laurel
and tell her
how you saved us all.
Deal?
Deal.
Baron, we've got to
get out of here.
There is
no getting out,
but with your deaths,
I might yet just live.
What are you
talking about?
Kanjigar septum
vohnostrum.
Today's prison riot
at Iron Heights
has left the city on edge.
Hey, Lopez, Lopez.
What happened
at the, uh--at the prison?
Uh, you punched out
a lieutenant.
Yeah. I mean,
after that.
Did they keep those
inmates from escaping?
Too many of them,
and one--Darhk--
he hurt one of them.
What? What?
Who--who'd he hurt?
The vigilantes.
The Black Canary.
Supposedly, he hurt
her real bad.
I--um, listen. Uh, I got
to get out of here, all right?
It's--it's
real important,
so please get me, uh--
see if you can get
Lieutenant Pike
on the phone.
He's out supervising
the manhunt
for the escaped
prisoners.
You got to get him
on the phone, all right,
because I got to
talk to him,
because I got to get
out of here just for an hour.
I'm gonna surrender
myself back in, all right?
That's fine,
but just--just
get Lieutenant Pike
on the phone, please.
Hi.
Laurel--is she--
Laurel's in surgery.
Um...
I don't know.
I've tried calling
Lance, too, so...
What happened
with Darhk?
He's in the wind
along with 50 or so
inmates.
And Andy.
You warned me,
and I didn't listen.
I'll never be able
to forgive myself.
Oh, my God.
Just out of recovery.
She's gonna be fine.
She's a strong woman,
your friend.
The strongest.
She's been asking
for you.
Hi.
Hey yourself.
Did Darhk--
Don't worry
about him.
Just worry about
getting better, ok?
It's not exactly how
I wanted my last night to go.
What are you
talking about?
It's a long story.
I was gonna give up
being the Black Canary,
but I realized I didn't
know how I could
because going out there
and fighting alongside you guys,
it's what makes me
feel alive inside...
And I love you guys
so much.
We love you.
We should probably let you
get some rest.
We'll be right
outside, ok?
Ok.
You should probably
get some rest, too.
No chance.
I'm gonna stay
right here.
There's...
Something in my
left pouch.
Will you bring it
to me?
Yeah.
May I?
You kept this?
Yeah.
Just a little reminder
of when things
were simpler
for us,
the way we used
to be.
I'm really glad that
you found Felicity,
and I hope you find
your way back to her,
and, Ollie, I know that
I am not the love of your life...
But you will always be
the love of mine.
Why are you
telling me this?
Why now?
Because tonight it was
just a reminder that...
Anything can happen,
which why I need you
to promise me something.
I just got off the phone
with Captain Lance.
He's on his way.
I--I told him that she's doing fine.
Out of the way!
Embolism. I need 5,000 units
of heparin bolus!
What happened?
Uh, I--I don't know.
She was fine.
Paddles!
Charging.
- Clear?
- Clear.
Come on.
Come on!
Time of death 11:59.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.