This season on "Arrow"...
Oliver: I was told
once that a man
cannot live
by two names.
I thought that I could be
me and the Arrow,
but I can't.
Ra's: I see it
in your eyes--
the struggle you have
with your dual identity.
I am the Demon's Head.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
Oliver Queen is the Arrow.
I got you now,
you son of a bitch.
There is no more Arrow.
Ra's took that from you.
Maseo: Take your rightful place
as Heir to the Demon,
and Ra's al Ghul
will bring your sister back.
Oliver: All this time,
I've been struggling with who I am.
Do you
recognize this?
The Alpha and Omega bioweapon.
You will unleash this
on Starling City.
Tatsu: My son was
killed by the virus
Ra's intends to use
on your city.
[All screaming]
Felicity: Oliver...
You asked us to trust you
and we trusted you!
No, Oliver!
[All coughing]
You were asleep.
I was dreaming.
IBN Sirin once wrote there are
three types of dreams--
there are ones about truth;
there are ones
about desire,
and there are
ones about temptation.
What did you dream of?
Rebirth...
as Ra's al Ghul.
There is no greater burden
than the one
you're about to take on--
the annihilation
of one's home.
It is necessary
to complete my ascension.
And I will be there to steady your hand
when the time comes.
I appreciate
your assistance.
Soon you will wear this.
And you will command
a multitude,
and I shall call you Ra's.
Something's wrong.
[Gasping]
[All coughing]
Not that
I'm complaining,
but shouldn't we
be dead by now?
Oliver tried
to kill us.
Ra's tried.
Oliver was forced
to let him appear to be successful.
So now we're back
to trust Oliver,
and while we're at it,
trust you, too?
Yeah, because
the last time I checked,
you tried to make a deal
with Ra's to save yourself.
In order
for our plan to work,
Ra's trust in Oliver
had to be complete.
And after that plane
fiasco, it wasn't.
Oliver needed
to demonstrate
one more time
his loyalty to Ra's.
Which I guess
brings us back to...
why aren't we dead?
Not that
I'm complaining.
Oliver...
was vaccinated against
the Alpha Omega virus five years ago.
An associate was able
to draw a version of the vaccine
from his blood.
A synthetic
skin graft.
Upon our incarceration,
I was able to vaccinate
each one of you cutaneously.
I saved your lives.
I believe the words
you're searching for
are "thank" and "you."
[Clears throat]
Ok.
Assuming this
is all some part
of a brilliant
double double cross
or triple cross--
I'm losing count--
your master plan still
has one major flaw,
since we're still
chained in a dungeon.
Patience, miss Smoak.
All we have to do is wait.
Wait for what?
[Thunder]
The thunder.
Guard:
Keep walking.
It's time.
Barry: All right.
You guys have a hot tub?
Nice.
Hi, you guys!
Wow!
I mean, this is like
a real dungeon!
Barry!
Thank you, Felicity.
You just outed my secret identity
to a super villain.
No offense.
None taken.
Now get us out of here!
All right, uh,
stand back.
[Glass breaking]
Excellent.
How many assassins,
do you figure?
Uh, none. They're all
taking a little nappy time.
Thank you.
And not to be greedy,
but we could really use
your help on this whole
Starling City
super virus thing.
And you know I would,
but I am overdue
for a very pointed conversation
with Harrison Wells.
I'm sure
Oliver's got this.
I wouldn't count on it.
Oliver hasn't been
very forthcoming
with his plans
lately.
Well, I don't know
what's been going on
with him lately,
apart from a recent
wardrobe change,
but one thing that
hasn't changed is,
he needs you guys.
Even if he
doesn't think so.
Good luck.
I'll never get used to that.
Well, there goes
our ride home. John?
The plane we came in
is still secure,
but we need to get
to it quickly.
Come on.
Tatsu. Let's go,
we're leaving.
I left a life of solitude because
Oliver asked it of me.
It's time to return to it.
I'm wired.
In direct communication
with my men outside.
I'm going
to count to five.
One...
[Gunshots]
What's happening?
Two engines are down.
We're trying to compensate,
but they've been tampered with.
Sabotage?
You!
This is all your doing.
Oliver: Don't!
Nyssa had nothing
to do with this.
You were delivered
by the prophecy.
You wed my daughter.
Your name is Al Sah-him
and you are
Wareeth al Ghul!
My name...
is Oliver Queen!
Oliver Queen is dead.
And soon,
you will be, too!
I handed you
my crusade!
My only mission!
I already have one.
[Beeping]
Survive this,
and I will come for
you again and again
until your end of days!
But first,
your city will perish!
♪ Arrow 3x23 ♪
My Name Is Oliver Queen
Original Air Date on May 13, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Took the only parachute.
[Instruments beeping]
Stay strapped in
and do exactly as I say.
All right, we've
lost hydraulics.
Is there a red lever
by your right leg?
Yes!
Ok, on my go,
you'll pull it up,
you'll turn it clockwise,
push it back down.
You understand?
Yes!
3, 2,
1. Now!
Now back down!
This is going to hurt.
[Woman speaking Chinese on TV]
[Speaking Chinese]
Oh, no.
I couldn't.
He loved you.
You were his friend.
Excuse me.
My people will be
looking for me.
It's just a matter of time
till they find me.
Do it.
Do you remember
Amanda Waller, hmm?
She's the reason
that I'm in Hong Kong.
She thought I had
a special talent.
She taught me things.
Let me show you.
We don't have
much time.
For what?
I thought you said Oliver
had a plan.
Yeah, and in the event
that it doesn't work,
he has a back-up--us.
John, let's determine
the status of our arsenal.
Laurel, go to your father;
Start mobilizing the police.
Mr. Palmer, I need you
to find something that will neutralize
an airborne contagion.
Miss Smoak, let's find out
where our League of Assassin
friends might be.
I'm sorry.
Did I mumble?
We follow his lead.
For now.
Ah, guys, I set up
a proximity alarm
to detect an unauthorized
entry to this level.
It's going off
like crazy.
Nyssa.
John--
You son of a bitch!
[Oliver groaning]
Maybe we should give
these guys the room.
Nyssa looks happy. You two
on your honeymoon?
What the hell's
going on, Oliver?
Start talking!
The reason that I have
kept Malcolm close
for the past several months
is because he had
critical Intel on our enemy.
He knows Ra's.
He knows the League.
And he knew that if I was
appointed his successor,
that meant Starling City
was marked for death.
The only way that we were
going to defeat the League
was from the inside.
I had to get close enough to Ra's
to find out how he was
going to destroy
the city...
And stop him.
You trusted
Malcolm Merlyn more than
you did the two people closest to you!
John, it wasn't
about trust!
It was about making sure that
you and you were safe.
I had to keep the circle
as small as possible.
How did you expect to repair all this
once you got back?
I didn't.
I flew with Ra's
and the virus to Starling
and I sabotaged the plane.
The plan...
was to kill Ra's
and destroy the virus.
It didn't work.
How did you expect to survive
the plane crash?
You didn't.
You never expected
to have this conversation.
You were planning
on dying.
So that was your big plan.
Sacrificing yourself
to take out Ra's.
It's the only way.
At least now
that it didn't work,
I get a chance
to tell tell the both of you
how sorry I am.
Sorry won't cut it Oliver.
Not this time.
But we have bigger problems.
It hurt feeling
and broken trust.
Laurel needs
to contact her father.
Ray needs to find a way
to counteract the virus.
I'm sure Malcolm told you...
We don't have
a lot of time.
Oliver!
What have you done?
He failed
this city.
And I'm giving him
the justice he deserves.
This isn't
justice!
It's...wrong.
He's still alive.
Just passed out
from the pain.
What'd you find?
My father isn't using
any of the League's
ordinary redoubts
in the city.
If Ra's is here
with the virus,
why hasn't he
used it yet?
Where are we?
Nowhere. Ra's
is old school.
Every way I have
of finding him is new school.
Oliver, maybe we need
to change the way we're looking for him.
If we're trying to find
a sub that's gone dark,
we should look
for what's out
of the ordinary
in the water.
So we look
for what's unusual
and maybe
that points us
to how or where
Ra's plans to release the virus.
Traffic lights were down for
20 minutes at Adams and O'Neil.
All computers at Starling
National Bank are offline.
The entire top floor
of the Essex Hotel is closed.
There's an electrical spike
at 52nd and Robson.
Wait, go back. The top floor
of the Essex is closed.
My father doesn't
frequent hotels.
According to internal emails,
the floor was shut down
for a Damien Darhk.
A name like that
has to be an alias.
Damien Darhk is
in Starling City.
My father's
most bitter enemy.
That's why Ra's
hasn't released the virus.
He wants to use it
to kill Damien Darhk.
This was never just
about my ascension.
Ra's wants to take out
his Nemesis.
Looks like you weren't
the only one
with a hidden
agenda.
[Sighs]
This can
work for us.
Ra's wants Damien.
So we give him
Damien.
We trade Damien
for the virus.
That is remarkably
ruthless and cold-blooded.
I approve.
Count two on the roof,
one on the penthouse floor.
I got two guarding
the elevators,
another three going in and out
of the service entrance.
And a patrol
in the stairwell.
Same for the northwest
corridor.
Keep Darhk's men
from joining the party.
Getting into position.
[Elevator dings]
Damien Darhk.
You know, the hotel's
going to bill me for that window.
Turn around!
This is bold,
even for Ra's.
Ra's al Ghul
wants you dead.
He's planning a bioweapon
to take you out.
Well, that's a considerable
amount of work to go to.
Ra's certainly must want
Mr. Darhk off the board.
Oh, you seem surprised.
Mr. Darhk left Starling
the moment he learned
of Ra's' intention.
It's amusing
the Demon's Head
thinks he can catch
my employer unawares.
[Cell phone vibrating]
It's just my phone.
Ra's: Hello, Al Sah-him.
Apparently both our plans
did not go as we'd hoped.
I'm going to find you.
It was a bold gambit,
hoping to leverage Mr. Darhk,
but one which had
done you no good.
I set in motion
the death of your city
10 minutes ago.
The Alpha Omega shall be
disseminated by means of four vessels.
Four instruments of death.
And I doubt that you and your friends
will have time to stop all of them.
Unlike you,
Oliver Queen,
I'm a man of my word.
And I swore that
you would see your city perish.
I told you I needed
the DD-5 for the Andreyko case
on my desk, and unless
I recently went blind, they're not here!
Now what--
I got to put you
on hold for a second.
Won't be long.
I thought you and I agreed
to give ourselves
some space.
Not when the city's
in danger.
[Scoffs]
I don't have time for this.
Wait. Do you remember
that chemical spill
in Hong Kong
five years ago?
It turns out, it was
a biological attack
and that bioweapon--
Let me guess.
This is coming
from your buddy Queen, right?
The city's under attack?
Must be May?
What do--
You still keep it in
the middle drawer?
What?
The bottle?
I'm going to bet
that it's scotch.
It's not what
you think it is.
Don't.
If you want to drink,
then drink.
But don't just stand
there and lie to me right to my face.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
It makes you thirsty.
I love you.
No matter what happens between us,
that'll never change.
You can hate me
for lying;
you can blame
Oliver for Sara,
you can even blame me.
But falling off the wagon,
that's on you.
I got it under control,
all right?
It's two drinks
a day and that's it.
We're alcoholics,
dad! Drunks!
There's no such thing
as two drinks a day.
And now you have
a choice.
You can keep drinking
and keep being angry
at me and Oliver
or the rest
of the world,
if you want.
Or you can make both
of your daughters proud
and throw away
the bottle and help save the city.
John, Malcolm, and Nyssa
are on their way back.
What happened with Darhk?
He was gone.
Man that I found
was a cut-out.
Ra's plans to release the virus
at four points across the city.
I worked out a containment
system that can safely neutralize the virus,
if we can get
our hands on it.
Well, we need
four of them,
and a way to spread
the inoculant if this gets out of control.
I scrubbed through all the information
that Malcolm gave us
on the Hong Kong attack
five years ago.
The Alpha Omega virus
gave off a low level
emission from its RNA,
almost like radiation.
If you can hack
the keyhole hexagon satellite,
you can tune the quadband
to search for it...
Which you've been
doing for the last five minutes.
We need probable
locations
where he would
release the virus
as soon as you can get them.
Mm-hmm.
Maseo!
Where you going?
I don't know.
All I know...
is I wasn't strong enough
to save my son.
Or to do what Oliver did.
What Oliver did
was horrible.
He allowed himself
to become a monster.
No more of a monster
than I am.
I am...
without a soul, Tatsu.
Only if you
abandon your wife
when she needs you
the most.
Every time...
I look in your eyes...
I see my son's.
I see my failure.
I love you.
I'm not worthy of that love.
Where's he going?
Somewhere we
cannot follow.
I know I said I would never,
ever bring you coffee again,
but the city facing
a bioweapon attack
seemed like
a valid exception.
So your plan to take out
Ra's by dying...
We should talk about that.
Every night since
the mountain,
I've had the same dream.
You are pleading
with me not to go face Ra's,
and I listen to you.
Sometimes the dream
still ends badly;
I end up with this
sword in my chest.
But most of the time,
we escape.
And we're just driving.
And all this seems...
it seems so far away,
because it's just...
it's the two of us.
I know you think that
that's not possible,
that you dead and Ra's dead is
he only realistic best case scenario.
Felicity...
I can't defeat Ra's al Ghul.
Oliver Queen can't.
The Arrow can't.
Both those men tried and both
those men failed.
You remember what you said to me
during our night together
in Nanda Parbat?
You're no longer
either of those men.
You've become...
someone else.
Become something else.
This...
is different now.
Because despite
your best efforts,
you've allowed yourself
to feel something.
I know you think that
that's a weakness; It's not.
It's your key
to beating Ra's.
Don't fight to die.
Fight to live.
[Cell phone beeps
and vibrates]
Satellite trace is back.
I've got four locations.
Ok, let's go. Felicity...
Thank you.
All right, yeah, got 'em.
[Clears throat]
I don't know, we'll talk
about that later.
I need all units.
I need ESU, all squad cars
converging on these
four locations.
We got a potential
bioweapons attack.
I'm onsite.
Onsite.
John: I'm onsite,
but I have no idea what
I should be looking for around here.
Do you see anyone
in a League of Assassins outfit?
That would be
a dead giveaway.
I have no weapons.
And I have no virus.
Ra's al Ghul
awaits you
on the Starling City Dam.
He wishes to be
in your presence
as your city dies.
And what makes him think
that I won't just stay focused
on saving my city?
Because he knows
of your deluded belief
that you can
defeat him in battle.
And you know that as long
as the Demon's Head lives,
he will continue
to threaten your home.
Ok, I got a runner
carrying a metal briefcase.
Felicity: The bioweapon
is going to be in the briefcase.
Ok, I'm scrubbing footage
from traffic
and surveillance cameras
at the remaining three locations.
[Car horns honking,
cars crashing]
[John groaning]
Don't...move.
Nice threads.
Thanks.
Felicity,
the briefcase is empty.
It's empty!
Where's the virus?
Where's the virus?!
He is the weapon.
Ra's is using his own men
to disperse the virus!
And we will not
be stopped.
[Grunts]
The will of Ra's al Ghul
is our own!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Ra's: I knew
you couldn't resist.
The man who survives
the sword of Ra's al Ghul
shall become Ra's al Ghul.
So you brought me here
to kill you?
Either way,
I am victorious.
You either ascend to
Ra's as I have designed,
or you will die.
And the last thing
you will ever see
is your beloved city
succumbing
to disease and death.
Look out! Go! Go,
go, go, go, go, go!
Get back! Go! Go, run!
[All screaming]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Get back, go, go,
go, go, go, go!
Back!
[Siren]
You got to get out of here!
Thea: Malcolm inoculated me.
Oh, my God.
Starling City appears
to be in the throes
of a biological attack.
Outbreak at Nelson
Plaza. It's bad.
It looks the virus spreads when
infected blood is exposed to open air.
Even if we find Ra's men,
how are we supposed
to stop them
from spreading the virus?
Really bad
temporary solution--
get them off the streets in
a secured place as possible
and do not let them
cut themselves.
Wait. You're not inoculated.
This is
my father's doing.
I will see it undone.
You choose a sword that has already
defeated you in battle.
[Both grunting]
Miss Smoak, I've taken
out one of Ra's' men.
Don't take chances. Put that body
some place airtight,
and try not to kill anyone else,
while you're at it!
The virus is spreading.
Can you replicate the inoculant?
That is the easy part.
The hard part is disseminating
it over a three block radius.
Your nanotech.
Can you make them
airborne?
That is what
I'm trying to do.
[All screaming]
I have been a most
excellent trainer.
We need to get this guy somewhere
he can't infect anyone.
[Swords clanging]
What the hell's
going on here?
We're in the middle of a city-wide crisis.
I don't have time for this.
We've got two suspects up
on the dam.
Don't know why
they're fighting each other,
but the chief says they're responsible
for what's happening.
He's ordered me to take them out
as soon as I have a clean shot.
Something has changed
within you, boy.
Your will to live
burns brighter,
and yet you rejected my offer
of eternal life.
What you were offering
wasn't living!
[Both grunting]
Power serves you
no interest.
You'd rather love.
A man who condemns
his daughter to death
wouldn't understand.
[Cell phone rings]
Detective--Captain?
Quentin:
We got a problem.
You're going to have
to be a lot more specific.
I'm pretty sure your boy
is at the Starling City Dam,
and I got officers
not listening to me
getting ready
to shoot him.
Now, despite what
I think about your guy,
I don't want
to see him killed
while I think he is
trying to save the city.
But unless you order up
a miracle pretty quick,
that's exactly
what's going to happen.
John: Got number four.
Hold on a second, John.
We have a new problem.
Hey, you have to get
to Starling City Dam. You have to fly.
I'm still uploading the operating code
to the nanotech.
And I'm still
rewriting on the fly.
I--I can't leave
the station. Why?
Oliver's in trouble.
He needs your help.
Felicity, if I can't get
the nanotech to disperse
the inoculant,
thousands of people
in this city will die.
What? No! Ray, Oliver!
It's one life
against the city's.
What would Oliver do?
Unlike you,
thousands of honorable men
will mourn my death
when I leave
this earth.
No.
They will kneel
before the next
Ra's al Ghul.
[Speaking Arabic]
_
I knew I chose well
with you, boy.
[Gasping]
If I could
figure out how
to get this thing off,
I would be kissing you right now.
[Laughs]
The casualty count would
have been much higher
if not for
an airborne inoculant
that rumors credit
Palmer Technologies with developing.
You killed
my father.
I had to.
I wanted
to be the one.
You're lucky
you're still alive.
You wouldn't be had you not been
wearing league armor.
I like
to think I had
a little something
to do with that.
When I started this,
I wanted to keep you
as far away from it as possible,
because that has always
been my instinct--
to go it alone.
But the truth
is that we won tonight
because I wasn't alone.
I thought that this crusade
would only end with my death.
But even if I had
died tonight,
it would live on,
because of you...
and you.
Oh, and you.
It's true.
This city isn't lacking masks.
Heroes.
Which is why I no longer
need to be one.
What are you saying?
Ra's took the Arrow
identity from me.
I couldn't be that person
even if I wanted to be.
And I don't want to be.
I told you that...
I couldn't be the Arrow
and be with you.
I want to be with you.
You told me that I have
become someone else,
and I would like to...
maybe discover a little more
about that person.
If you'll come with me.
With you where?
Um...
Some place
far away from here.
Even without me,
Starling still has heroes
to watch over it.
John...
I'll talk to him.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's the word I've been
saying over and over in my head.
So, does that mean I'm going
to have to find
a new vice president?
I think so.
I hope that you find someone
who makes you happy, Ray.
You deserve that.
John?
I'm happy for you, Oliver.
Despite our issues,
you deserve to be happy.
You and Felicity.
And you're right,
the city's in good hands.
Including yours.
I'm no superhero.
You're a hero.
For three years,
you've been a rock.
The city's rock, my rock.
For three years,
you have been the person
I can count on.
I'm still counting on you.
Oliver, I don't know
if I can get past
what happened
between the two of us.
I'm not asking you to.
I'll think on it.
Ok.
[Elevator dings]
John.
[Clears throat] If you're going
to keep going,
you may want to find
a way to conceal your identity
when you're out there.
I'll think on that, too.
[Elevator dings]
You be well, Oliver.
You, too.
Oliver: Where will you go?
Tatsu: Kumamoto.
There's
a monastery there
near my childhood home.
I had always hoped
to show it to Akio
when we returned to
Japan as a family.
I'm so very sorry, Tatsu.
And where
will you go?
Back to
Starling City?
No, I...
I tortured Shrieve
for hours.
I don't want that darkness around
my mother or my sister.
What of your father?
You told me about
his message.
His hope that you would
save your city.
I'm not the man
my father thinks I am.
Even if I was, I...
I should be alone.
I need to be alone.
Be well, Tatsu.
He's upstairs,
packing.
I'll be leaving
Starling as well.
Try to imagine
my profound disappointment.
Thea, I love you.
I know my actions
always haven't shown that.
But I am your father.
And whatever you need,
I will always
be there for you.
Yeah, well, don't
wait by the phone.
But, a year ago,
you told me that you could
teach me to be strong.
You've made good
by that promise.
[Footsteps on stairs]
God, are you sure
you really want to do this?
As sure as I was
the last five times you asked me.
[Sighs]
Be safe out there, ok?
As safe as anybody
with a mask on can be.
But, actually,
I was thinking, um,
maybe I'll call myself
the Red Arrow?
Hmm.
I think I already told everyone
to call you Speedy.
[Chuckles]
As we agreed.
We've come a long way,
you and I.
I've always looked
at you as a son, Oliver.
And I'm glad we got
to work together
to trust as we did.
I will never
forgive you
for what you did
to Sara.
And my sister.
Ever.
Does that mean
we're enemies once more?
That depends on what you do
with your end of the bargain.
Open new file.
"Atom project
update gamma."
Had an interesting
breakthrough
while repurposing
nanotechnology
for anti-viral
dissemination.
With the proper
modifications,
the nanotech can be applied
to the miniaturization of key components
of the suit.
This will be miniaturization
test number one.
Execute.
Why can't anything
ever work the first try?
Hmm?
At least admit this was
your goal all along.
My only aspiration was to free myself
of your father's grasp.
A feat we both
managed to achieve.
I don't see how it was
possible in your case.
When I was your father's captive
three months ago,
he tortured me
with his blade.
And you survived because my father
chose to release you.
Funny thing,
prophecies.
Fate and my father
have shown you mercy.
I will not.
You took Sara from me,
and I will have justice.
You are
welcome to try.
Until then...
Kneel before
Ra's al Ghul.
Oliver: My name
is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
And I did.
I became a hero
who helped people.
But now it is time
for me to be someone else.
It is time for me
to be...something else.
So, where are we going?
I'm thinking a state
that can annul
a Nanda Parbat marriage.
[Chuckles]
Can I say
something strange?
I'm happy.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man