My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
That's why you won't tell me
who Prometheus is.
He calls himself Adrian Chase.
- Who's Simon Morrison?
- Adrian Chase.
Simon Morrison is his birth name.
That's his real identity.
Daddy's decided you're gonna
come home with me. I promise.
I spoke to Curtis's lawyer friend.
- I put things in motion.
- Good for you.
I am getting deeper and deeper
into the mud.
That doesn't mean that you have to quit.
I am broken, okay?
I need you to let me go.
Your resignation's accepted.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
I'm shutting everything down.
- Hey.
- Good morning.
Actually, it's a lousy one.
Tell me.
Last night,
Judge Balderrama granted retrials
on all the cases that Chase prosecuted.
Well, that's bad, but I mean, he didn't...
What, release them on bail?
Yep, that happened, too.
- Son of a bitch.
- That's what I said.
And now we've got 36 violent felons
walking around on the streets.
Well, put the most dangerous ones
under surveillance.
Yeah, it's already done. Listen, Oliver,
where are we on finding Chase?
Right where he is. We're nowhere.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor,
but I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave the building.
What? Why?
A suspicious package
was received by your office.
- When?
- Just now.
A large crate that set off the dogs.
Bomb squad's on the way.
Well, any indication
where it was delivered from?
No return address.
But the sender is a Simon Morrison.
Sir, I can't allow you to...
Then resign.
Look, I enjoy getting blown up
just as much as the next guy,
but am I missing something here?
It's Chase.
Simon Morrison's his real name.
Fine, but that's no reason
to get yourself, all of us, blown up.
- Step away.
- Sir, we can't...
I've got this. Step away.
Don't worry.
He was a bomb diffuser in a past life.
We don't believe
it's an incendiary device.
Snake-cam showed the presence
of concrete and building materials.
That could have set off the dogs.
Concrete?
Sir, protocol still requires
we wait for the bomb squad.
Mr. Mayor?
What the hell?
Who is he?
According to dental records,
Henry Goodwin.
- Ring any bells?
- No, not a note.
He was a Councilman in the Glades
back in'02.
Chase wouldn't have been old enough
to drink back then.
Right. And, so far,
there are no connections
between Goodwin and Chase
that we can find.
I mean, Goodwin was reported missing
in 2002, he was declared dead in '03.
Question is, why would Chase
send Oliver a 15-year-old body
that neither of them are connected to?
No idea. Then again, Chase is crazy.
Okay, pull all the forensics
that you can find.
Try and find a connection
between either Chase, or his father.
- Name's Justin Claybourne.
- Claybourne.
And if there is no connection?
There has to be a connection.
Chase does everything for a reason.
We need to know what it is.
It's gonna be a tall order, Oliver.
We're already spread thin
keeping an eye on the guys
that Chase was prosecuting who got kicked.
I have asked Quentin to task the SCPD
with monitoring the dangerous ones.
Which leaves us with the extremely
dangerous ones, I'm guessing.
Ooh, zombie "I can't feel pain"
Derek Sampson has my vote.
What's he been up to
since getting out of prison?
Partying like a guy
who just got out of prison.
Let's stay on him and whoever else
we think are the most dangerous.
What about your office's
newest art installation,
- the concrete councilman?
- Dinah's working the evidence.
She gets a lead, we make a move.
He'!-
How is it going with...
- William?
- Yep.
I'm actually having trouble finding him.
Samantha did a really good job
at hiding herself and William.
Well, if Felicity Smoak can't find him,
I feel better about Chase
not being able to, so, thank you.
Maybe drinking before flying
not such good idea.
Or not drink enough. I don't know.
Weather's getting worse.
Means we're close.
I pretend that is good thing.
All this time, you never mentioning
you know how to fly. Where you learn?
Yeah, my dad loved vintage planes.
He would take me up all the time.
One of my last happy memories.
I'm guessing this not one of them.
I'm not the man you think I am, Oliver.
I didn't save our city. I failed it.
I did a terrible thing.
You can right my wrongs.
You can save this city.
Why you want me watching this?
So you can understand
why I have to go back.
To Starling City,
or to this horrible place?
Ooh. That frown mean you struck out?
Mmm. Not exactly.
Concrete's a proprietary formula.
It's owned by
a specific construction company.
Killer's DNA
is underneath Goodwin's fingernails.
All right, so what's with the loser look?
You can't ID a suspect off all that?
The "loser look" is because
I did ID a suspect off all that.
Now, the bond offering
should pay for all the overtime
I'm asking the SCPD for
in order to keep track
of Chase's violent felons.
Clear the room for a second, please.
I missed you.
Yeah, well, once I heard
that Chase was Prometheus,
- I knew you'd drag me back to town.
- For your protection.
And say that. Ollie, I think you know
I can take care of myself.
It has nothing to do
with what you're capable of, Thea.
It has to do with
what Adrian Chase is capable of.
You mean an Oscar-worthy performance
of a decent human being?
As betrayals go,
it makes Isabel Rochev
look like a bad practical joke.
I'm sure. But I...
I know Chase is dangerous
and I know you're worried,
but I just...
I wasn't ready to come back yet.
Were you with Roy or...
Like I'd let him see me
in the state I'm in.
What state are you in?
Phrase "hot mess" comes to mind.
I don't know.
I'm figuring it out.
I'm glad. It's good to see you.
Oliver, I...
Thea. What are you doing here?
It's nice to see you, too.
No, sorry, I just...
It's great to see you, it's just...
Well, it's just bad timing is all.
Maybe we should do this in private.
This regarding Councilman Goodwin?
You know, yeah, I think maybe
we should come back later.
- What is going on?
- Chase sent a 15-year-old corpse
to my office this morning
as some kind of message.
Do we have a suspect?
Yeah, you could say that.
Okay.
Who is it?
It's your father.
This is Chase, obviously.
He's framing our father.
Yeah, but to what end?
The concrete came
from Wellward Construction,
which was a subsidiary
of Queen Consolidated.
And the skin
under the victim's fingernails
matches Mr. Queen's DNA.
And the problem is, all those forensics
passed through a whole lot of labs.
You can't keep this
from going public, can you?
Not for lack of trying, believe me.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
Dinah, I need you to get
DNA and concrete samples
to Felicity and Curtis.
Our father is being framed,
and we need to start to prove it.
Sure, a couple pieces of evidence
can go missing.
And what are you gonna be doing?
Holding a press conference.
I just weathered a scandal.
I need to get out in front of this one.
Okay, I think you should reconsider
doing this whole press conference.
- Why?
- Because this could be
what Chase is manipulating you into.
Just like he manipulated you
into the impeachment
by throwing Green Arrow under the bus.
But like with the impeachment,
I need to tell...
Lie to the press?
Because that's what you're gonna be doing
if we find out that Dad is guilty.
Thea, come on.
Look, I am just saying, what if?
It's not like our parents were saints.
Chase thinks I'm a killer.
What he's doing, this whole setup,
is him trying to convince me
that our father was the same way.
Our father was a lot of things.
He's not a cold-blooded murderer.
Can't believe you convinced me
to come back to this island.
Fly home any time you want, Anatoly.
You have irony back in America, yes?
To do what I have to do, no one
can know what I've been through.
You mean in Russia?
In Russia.
In Hong Kong.
How do I explain to my family
why I didn't come home sooner?
You know, it's easier
if I'm just a simple castaway.
There's no such thing as simple castaway.
You know what I mean. Just...
It will be easier to keep my cover
if no one is asking questions.
That's a bad omen.
He was my friend.
If that was true,
he would not have tried to kill us.
What are you doing?
Well, this just washed up on the shore
like some kind of sign.
Yeah, that you're crazy.
Come on.
Where are we going?
I'm taking you somewhere to explain
why I'm doing what I'm doing.
I spent a year on this island.
You never told me there was a bar.
Hey. You busy?
Uh. Yeah. I'm just going over
Councilman Goodwin's appointments.
I'm looking for an alibi
for Oliver's father.
I thought you were on freed felon patrol.
Just got some good news,
figured I'd share it.
Please.
Good news is in short supply around here.
Got a court date.
Ha! Finally. You're getting prosecuted.
That is good news.
Funny. It's for Zoe.
Lawyer thinks I can get expedited custody.
Oh, wow, that's terrific.
Huh, good for you, hoss.
I thought maybe, you know,
since you gave me the push, you...
You'd...
Show up for moral support?
It'd be an honor.
Now, get out of here.
- Got your 911 call.
- Gas chromatograph kicked back
something very interesting
on that concrete.
Traces of soil with high levels
of copper concentration.
Yeah, I think you and I
have very different ideas
of what "interesting" means.
Well, I cross-referenced
Queen Consolidated construction locations
with areas in the city
rich in copper, and...
And you think you know
where Goodwin was killed.
Well, nothing concrete.
But yeah.
If Chase is trying to send a message...
It might be saying, "Come find me."
Okay, send this address to Oliver.
I'll meet him there.
What about Curtis and Dinah?
They are staking out Derek Sampson.
Looks like
Sampson's not finished partying.
Except he's moved on from strippers
to M4 assault rifles.
Should we move on him?
For all we know,
those guns could be legal.
So, if we go in now, the SCPD
might not have enough evidence
to put him back behind bars.
Exactly.
- So, what do we do?
- We wait.
See what his plan is.
Trust me, when it comes to this guy
it's absolutely nothing good.
Anything?
Former Oliver Enterprises.
Used to be a Queen Consolidated
holding company back in the day.
I know, my father brought me here
when I was younger.
Said the building was named after me.
Felicity says it's been abandoned
for about a month
due to some "toxic gas leak."
Chase wanted everyone cleared out.
Seems that way.
Hell of a big building.
If he's in there,
we should get started.
If Chase wanted you here for some reason,
he could've been more specific
about which floor.
Overwatch, can you
narrow the search for us?
Well, normally, yes, but right now
the only heat signatures
I'm reading in there are you two.
- You all right?
- Yeah, wasn't much of a fall.
What's Chase playing at?
I had to ask.
It's concrete.
He's trying to bury us alive
just like Councilman Goodwin.
If you have one of those
smart ideas, I'm in the market.
After all these months,
I refuse to believe
this is Chase's endgame. Overwatch.
Okay. I'm dialing up a rescue,
but it's gonna take a few minutes.
I'm not sure how many more
of those minutes we've got!
Okay. Here we go.
Guys, we got a situation.
- Yeah, so do we.
- Sampson's on the move.
You're gonna have to
let him make it without you.
Oliver and Digg are in trouble.
Chase is going through
a lot of trouble to prove a point.
What the hell is his point?
He framed my father
for the same kind of murder.
Proves the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree, huh?
You both might be killers, Oliver,
but he's a psychopath.
Don't lose sight of that.
Were you assuming that
we're getting out of this?
Yes, lam.
It's Morse Code.
"Get clear."
You two all right?
So we had to move off
the Sampson stakeout?
Yes, because John and you
were re-enacting the paleo version
of my favorite scene from Witness.
Harrison Ford almost getting buried
under the corn in the barn silo.
- That's the one.
- Oh, right.
And for those of us who
haven't seen every movie ever,
they mean it was a trap.
- Who hasn't seen Witness?
- Or a distraction.
I'll bet real money
that Sampson's working with Chase.
Makes sense.
Chase is the reason
Sampson got out of prison.
What did Sampson pull down while
Curtis and Dinah were saving the day?
They broke into a nearby lab.
- To steal what?
- That's the thing.
The chemicals they stole,
torinium and lydracide,
they have absolutely zero street value.
Torinium and lydracide.
Where have I heard those two before?
It's two of the three components
that Justin Claybourne was using
to weaponize tuberculosis
in Lamb Valley five years ago.
You said Claybourne was Chase's father.
He's dredging up the past.
In the case
of Councilman Goodwin, literally.
For a reason.
- What was the third chemical?
- Cyclotrizane.
But it's highly unstable,
so it was banned
from all domestic manufacturing.
Which'll make it incredibly difficult
for Sampson to get his hands on
in case Chase is trying to live out
his dad's evil plan.
- Chase will find a way.
- To what end?
John's right.
I mean, if there's a connection
between Chase's father and framing yours,
I don't know what it is.
We might've found someone
that can help with that.
Darren Coffman.
Last dude Councilman Goodwin saw
before he disappeared.
SCPD interviewed him back in '02,
but we think
they didn't get the whole story.
Coffman was Goodwin's lawyer.
But not just his lawyer.
Coffman also represented Chase's old man.
Mr. Coffman, thank you for coming
on such short notice.
This is my sister, Thea.
DARREN". Pleasure.
Your office didn't mention
why you wanted to see me.
It's regarding the recent reports
about our father.
I never had the opportunity to meet him,
but your father did
some remarkable things for this city.
What's happening with his reputation
right now is simply terrible,
but I can't understand
what it could have to do with me.
Reportedly, you were the last person
seen with Councilman Goodwin.
I'm sympathetic to your desire
to identify a suspect
who isn't your father, but...
- What's this?
- I have no idea.
But I was asked to give it to you.
- By who?
- Adrian Chase.
Or, as I knew him, Simon Morrison.
You've been in contact with him?
Why didn't you alert the SCPD?
You've met him. You know why.
The man is terrifying, and smart.
He said you'd seek me out.
And that when you did,
I should give you that.
He said it proves the kind of man
your father truly was.
I know what kind of man our father was.
And he was nowhere close
to Chase's father.
You were Justin Claybourne's lawyer.
You must know something about him,
something about his son.
Attorney-client confidentiality.
I couldn't tell you anything
even if I wanted to.
Actually, I think you want to.
Thea, easy.
What do you know?
"Taiana."
ls that the one you killed Kovar for?
That's my father.
He's the reason I have to go back
the way I have to go back.
That video.
He wants you to save your home.
I do not think kapiushon
is what he had in mind.
Putting on the hood is the only way
I know how to save my city.
I told you, Oliver,
hood is just piece of cloth.
Not that you listen to me anyway.
The hood, Anatoly, is an identity.
One, you think,
channels monster inside you.
And protects the people
that are closest to me.
I do it this way,
my enemies will target the hood,
not the ones I care for.
You are many things, Oliver Queen,
but until today, I did not count
naive as one of them.
The people closest to you will always
pay the most for your sins.
You are paying for your father's.
Who will pay for yours?
I'm gonna destroy it.
Well, don't you wanna see
what's on it first?
- No.
- Why not?
Because Chase wants me to.
I've had my fill
of playing his mind games.
- Yeah.
- Dinah and Curtis
tracked Sampson to Fairbanks Chemical,
a military contractor who sold
a whole lot of cyclotrizane
to the US government.
Text me the address. I'll meet them there.
You want to come with,
for old times' sake?
I think old times should stay old times.
- Keep it going. We're halfway there.
- Hold it.
Pain's just another prison.
And I'm a free man.
To the next batch.
Hurry up, we've got more assigned.
Move out.
Sampson doesn't leave with the chemicals.
Gilmour, you guys coming back
for more of this stuff or what?
Gilmour.
They're here.
Where's your green friend?
I was really looking forward
to killing him.
We need to check to see
if this is cyclotrizane.
On it.
Ten'll get you 20,
that's exactly what this is.
One thing at a time.
- Go.
- Hey. Thea called.
She said she needs to talk to you.
Said it was important.
Thea, I thought that we agreed
not to look at whatever's on that drive.
Ollie, you have a habit of giving orders
and just assuming that they're agreements.
- But you have got to see this.
- No, I don't.
It's security footage
from the Oliver Enterprises
construction site back in 2002.
Dad must've confiscated it and...
Chase must've found it.
Thea, listen to me.
Ollie, I know what you are about to say,
and I don't...
I don't see how this could be fake.
Please.
Before he died, Dad said to me,
"Oliver, lam not the man you think I am."
And I should've believed him.
Are you okay?
Are you?
No.
But once you find out
Malcolm Merlyn's your biological father,
you can pretty much handle anything.
Between him and Mom,
and being raised by Dad,
it really is no surprise
I turned out to be such a monster.
You're not a monster, and neither was Dad.
Yeah, maybe you should
re-watch that video.
No. Once was enough. That was an accident.
Yeah, an accident
that he tried to cover up.
Ollie, our parents
may have loved us, but...
That love does not make up
for all the terrible things
that they have done.
And maybe the most terrible thing of all
was making us just like them.
I have to go.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I always am.
Okay, let's go over the plan.
Ugh, Oliver, we've been over, and over,
and over plan. I'm not that drunk.
Humor me.
I find boat.
Fishermen, most likely.
- Bribe them to sail here.
- In 48 hours.
Da, in two days.
You get their attention with bonfire,
then sail away home. A castaway.
Thank you, Anatoly.
Thank me for this.
What do we have here?
Proof that although I think
your plan is crazy,
I'm good enough friend to help.
It's from old friend of mine. Former KGB.
Man was chameleon.
This is... This is very smart, Anatoly.
I figured nobody would believe
there is barber shop on island.
Anatoly...
Last time we say goodbye, it took us years
before we see each other again.
How about, Ne dumay plokho obo mne.
How about prochnost.
Prochnost. Yeah.
You'll always be my brother, Oliver.
What's going on?
Curtis just finished his analysis
of the cyclotrizane.
Remember how we thought
Chase was following Daddy's footsteps
to recreate his TB epidemic?
Surprise, Chase's plan is worse.
The chemicals Sampson stole
are more refined
than the ones Justin Claybourne used,
and could produce a biological agent
- a thousand times more powerful.
- And without a cure.
How would Chase distribute it?
It's aerosolized,
so pretty much any way he wants.
We have to find out where
Chase is storing this thing,
and stop him before he releases it.
Cyclotrizane degrades pretty quickly.
Which means that it gives off
trackable emissions.
It might.
If they find a location we are gonna
need all hands on deck.
- Where is Rene?
- With Lance.
Said it was personal.
So, how long you known about this?
Lawyer called me this afternoon.
Right, so what's the big deal?
You already knew you had a court date.
But not a hearing.
I thought this was gonna be a cakewalk,
but the judge,
- she wants me to testify.
- So?
So it's gonna traumatize Zoe
all over again.
She's gonna have to listen to me
talk about her mother's drug addiction
and how she got shot?
And everything that
I put her through after that? No...
She shouldn't have to relive all that.
All right, but what's the answer?
You don't show
and she loses her father all over again.
- Hoss, you met her foster mom, right?
- Yeah?
She's giving Zoe a good life.
I show up to that courtroom,
I'm doing it for me, not for my daughter.
No, if you don't step into that courtroom,
that little girl spends the rest
of her life thinking you didn't want her.
Maybe it's better that way, right?
I mean, come on, we both know
I'm no prize, hoss.
- Come on, man.
- And this is way before
I put on that hockey mask
and started throwing down with human scum.
This is just the nerves talking,
all right?
You're just looking for a way out.
Listen to me, you go into that courtroom,
sure, Zoe's got to relive
some real bad times,
but for the rest of... Look at me.
For the rest of her life, the new memories
that she's gonna have...
You get to make sure they're great,
all right?
And you get to decide
how she remembers you.
Please, Rene.
I always told myself everything I did,
I did for my family.
That's a lie.
Because what good is a family
without a soul?
You can right my wrongs.
You can be better than I was.
You can save this city.
No pressure or anything.
Is this the video you said
your father left for you?
Yep.
He left one for Thea, too.
I never showed it to her.
Why not?
Because he asked her
to always watch over me,
and I didn't wanna burden her with that.
Hmm. Sounds like
typical Oliver Queen thinking.
Why are you re-watching it?
I wanna know how I missed it.
- Missed what?
- He's a murderer.
I mean, he helped Merlyn
start the Undertaking.
I've never deluded myself
into thinking that he was a saint,
but to take a man's life, cover it up...
It's like I didn't know him at all.
Has it occurred to you that
this is exactly what Chase wants?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Okay, the question was rhetorical.
Of course, it's occurred to you.
Of course this is what Chase wants.
Chase wants to destroy the basis
for everything that we're doing here.
And that crusade began with my father.
Everything that I've done, everything,
has, in some way, been about honoring him.
Your father inspired you
to save this city.
And you did.
Okay, at this point, who cares why?
You're not a killer.
The people you care about
are not suffering because of you.
Their life, my life is better because
you decided to become the Green Arrow.
Well, whenever you decide to become
the Green Arrow again.
I know you're right.
I believe that you're right,
but every time I take a step forward,
it feels like the past is pulling me back.
Probably because you're letting it.
Yeah.
Maybe it's time to stop
living for your father,
and start living for yourself.
Just leave the past in the past.
Cyclotrizane emissions trace came back.
Computer's been working on
a probable location...
What is it?
Nice.
What made you decide to put it back on?
Felicity has a way with words.
Dinah and Rene are also on site.
No sign of Chase or Sampson.
Actually, we found Sampson
and his buddies on the roof.
And they've got
their super-toxic gas with them.
Copy. Tell Wild Dog to sit tight
until we get there.
Why'd he say I had to sit tight?
Because he knows you.
Oh.
Go to the roof. Stop Sampson.
- What about him?
- He's mine!
And I'm the one that's gotta sit tight?
Terrific, disarm that thing.
We'll cover you.
Okay, please do.
'Cause I don't enjoy being shot.
Go!
Don't worry. I'll make it quick.
And thank you for making me the way I am.
How'd you think you were gonna
beat me, Oliver?
We were trained by the same teacher.
Just one of the many things
that we have in common.
You know, like both our fathers
being horrible men.
I am not my father.
I'm my own man!
Yeah, a man who's gonna die
knowing that my father's legacy
killed everyone in the city
he loves so much.
Your father's legacy?
That's almost funny.
What are you talking about?
What's so funny about my father's legacy?
If that son of a bitch even looks like
he's getting loose, light him up.
Copy that. I really want to know
what it takes to kill this son of a bitch.
- Terrific?
- Give me a minute.
Yeah, tell that to the city.
The pressure really isn't...
Helping.
Are we good?
We're terrific.
I've been waiting to use that.
What about Green Arrow?
Goodwin's lawyer,
he represented your father.
I knew that already.
You don't know
what your father asked him to do.
Adrian...
He was going to disown you.
Not because you were illegitimate,
because you're insane.
You're sick and your father knew it.
You've spent all this time trying to honor
the memory of a man
who was ashamed of you.
Now, my father wasn't perfect,
but at least I know he never
would have given up on me.
Go ahead.
- Do it.
- No.
I'm not gonna kill you.
But I am gonna watch you face justice.
Well, that's a lot
of satisfied-looking faces.
And Adrian Chase is warming up a cell
at A.R.G.U.S. as we speak.
Did you want to deliver that news?
- 'Cause I don't...
- That's fine.
Okay, so Oliver dropped
this truth bomb on him,
and then he was just like a marionette
with his strings cut off, so epic.
Great. But there are a lot of bad guys
left on the streets, okay?
Damn, girl, you know how to kill a mood.
Rene's right.
- Oh, say that again.
- You're right for tonight.
We should enjoy the win.
Agreed. So, first round's on me.
Yes-
FELICITY: Woo! Yeah-.
I have something for you.
Hm.
Oh. And here I thought
you could never top the Hozen.
It's a video from Dad.
He made it before he died and...
I should've given this to you sooner.
But I was worried that what he said on it
might feel like a burden for you.
You deserve to make that decision
on your own.
After today, I don't think I wanna see
any more videos with him in it.
That's totally up to you.
But I don't want you to think that you're
destined to be Dad, or Mom, or Merlyn.
You need to live your own life.
And the best way to do that
is to leave the past in the past.
Oliver Queen, I'm afraid you're going to
miss your boat home.
Any word from Mr. Ramirez?
Only that he swore
he would be here, Your Honor.
The only problem is, he's not.
Which is leaving me with very few options.
Please, Your Honor,
just give him a few more minutes.
And deprive the other people who got here
on time their right to a fair hearing?
Due to a failure to appear,
Mr. Ramirez's motion to restore
parental rights is hereby denied.
Hello, Thea. If you're seeing this,
then chances are that I'm...
Gone.
No matter what's happened,
no matter what you've heard,
I wanted you to know how much I love you.
You're my daughter. My special girl.
I've done some things in my life, Thea,
that I'm not proud of.
But I am proud of you. I always have been.
You are gonna grow up to be
a remarkable young woman.
Smart, generous, loving,
just like your mom.
But the day will come
when your mother and I are gone.
And then it'll just be
you and your brother.
And the truth is,
you're stronger than he is.
He is going to need to lean on you more
than you're going to need to lean on him.
Oliver, we know, can get through anything
if he has the love and support
of his sister.
I miss him.
I miss both of them.
Every day-
I don't know how to reconcile this...
This man with the one in the other video.
Maybe you don't have to.
Our parents were complex people, Thea.
They had complicated children.
What we have to do is
we have to leave the past in the past.
Live our own lives.
Doesn't mean that we love them any less.
And I have a feeling it's what
they would want for both of us.
Thank you for being here.
I'd like to talk with everyone
about my father.
Our father.
Based on further investigation,
I can now state definitively
that the allegations made
against Robert Queen are true.
My father is not hereto defend himself.
And I cannot find the words
to defend his actions.
What I can tell you
is that nearly ten years ago,
in a moment of immense courage,
Robert Queen chose to sacrifice himself
so that I might live.
So that I had the opportunity to
leave behind a better legacy than he did.
So that I might return
and one day serve this city.
Today, we took a step forward.
With help from the Green Arrow
and his team,
the Throwing Star Killer
is now behind bars,
and our streets are a little safer.
Tomorrow, we'll take another step forward.
And the day after,
we will take another one.
Because it is time, it truly is time
for us to leave the past in the past
so that our children might inherit
the Star City we have always dreamed of.
The way my father dreamt of a better life
for me and my sister.