My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal,
to save my city,
but my old approach
wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become
something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow..."
Who's Lonnie Machin?
He's kind of
an ex-boyfriend of Thea's.
Tell me where I can
find Damien Darhk.
You don't need another
man clouding your mind.
Alex, run!
No!
It's gone.
Darhk took it.
Lyla, you need to tell us
what Rubicon is.
Every NATO Ally--
Rubicon has control over
all their nuclear systems.
We have 12 hours
to stop it.
Darhk is powered
by death,
so if even one
of those nukes hits...
He will be unstoppable.
We lost one.
It's in the air.
Direct hit on Havenrock.
How many causalities?
Tens of thousands.
Hello, Oliver.
Nice timing.
I think you're going to need
much bigger arrows.
Cool.
You know, I didn't
even mean to do that.
I turn steel arrows
into dust,
and you thought lead
would do the trick?
He's not human anymore.
Oh, I'm still human.
Just better.
Doesn't give you the right
to remake the world.
Why not?
It's been done before.
Noah and the flood.
People even worship
the responsible party.
This might smart
a little.
I'm pulling the oxygen
out of your bodies,
molecule by molecule,
but here's the good news.
I'm not going
to kill you.
Well, not right now,
at least.
Instead, I'm going
to regain control of Rubicon.
That way,
when the whole world
goes all
"Dr. Strangelove,"
you can feel your skin
melt from Armageddon.
Oliver, let's go!
Come on!
We got to go now!
♪ Arrow 4x22 ♪
Lost in the Flood
Original Air Date on May 18, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Come on.
What happened here?
Too bad.
I liked him for you.
Where's Machin?
I-I don't know.
He--he disappeared, ok?
I wasn't paying attention.
Why do I have trouble
believing you?
Let go of me!
Not to sound too much
like your father,
but I really think
you need a timeout.
Government officials
couldn't confirm the death toll.
However, various reports
place the number
in the tens of thousands.
Evacuation efforts
of the surrounding areas
continue as--
What are you doing?
We can't afford
to get caught up
in grief right now.
Now, I've bought us
24 hours
by sending Rubicon's
launch algorithms
into an infinite loop,
but if we can't find
a more permanent--
God, what am I doing?
It's ok, sweetheart.
Don't "sweetheart" me.
You don't get
to do that,
but you're right.
I can't get wrapped up
in this.
Have you been
watching the news?
I can't stop.
Ironically, last week
my mom was giving me a hard time
about living
in Star City.
Between the earthquakes,
the viral attacks,
the homicidal
super soldiers,
why would anyone
want to live here?
It turns out
we live in only
the second worst
place in America.
Curtis.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
you had company.
This is my father--
Noah Kuttler.
Noah Kuttler, huh?
Curtis.
You know, it's funny
because there's
this super hacker
who's wanted by the FBI
whose name is also
Noah Kuttler.
He's kind of a big deal
on the Dark Web.
Honestly, I thought
they could have used
a more flattering photo
for the wanted poster.
Wait, you--you're
the Noah Kuttler?
And if you're
Felicity's dad,
you were married
to Donna,
and you make so much
more sense now.
Yep.
This is--
it was a big mystery.
I was trying to figure
out, like, how Felic--
- Yeah.
Ok. We have
work to do.
HIVE was behind
the Havenrock explosion.
They stole a cyber weapon
called Rubicon
and now are using it
to commandeer
the world's nukes,
so we have less than
24 hours to stop it,
or the world is
going to experience
the sequel
to "Wargames."
Actually, there was a direct-to-DVD
sequel in 2008,
but it was a bomb, too,
so that reference
still holds.
I have to go.
Don't worry.
Me and your fugitive
dad have got this.
He says, just realizing
he said that out loud.
Today was supposed
to be Christmas,
and I woke up
to a lump of coal.
Is it because I've been
naughty this year?
It's because Kuttler
and his daughter
are wrestling us
for Rubicon.
Which is why I felt
the need to up our game.
Mr. Seldon,
pleasure to see you.
Do you know what
the best part
about leading
a prison break is?
A long list of criminals
that owe you.
Amar, Brickwell,
and now Mr. Seldon.
It's like one-stop
shopping for thugs.
I'm a hacker,
not a thug.
Oh, turns out
he and miss Smoak have a history.
Just your typical
boy meets girl,
boy falls in love
with girl,
boy goes to jail
for girl...
Boy tries to kill girl
for money.
Speaking of thugs,
we have a new problem
at Tevat Noah.
Not this guy again.
Don't worry, darling.
I'm dealing with him.
Give Mr. Machin
my love, my love.
It's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas.
A long-range ballistic
KN-08 missile
was responsible
for the nuclear blast
at Havenrock.
The Pentagon has not
further commented.
FEMA and city emergency
services personnel
continue
their quarantine...
What's going on?
What the hell happened
in Havenrock?
Darhk happened.
This city is
starting to panic.
Are they right to?
Felicity's got it
under control,
but my wife and her top secret
government agency's
looking for a more
permanent solution.
I cannot get in touch
with Thea!
It's ok.
She got ahold of me.
Thanks for not being dead.
Um, aren't we
all going to be
if you're away
from your computer?
Curtis and Kuttler are
dealing with Rubicon.
What did Thea say?
Do you know
where she is?
It's not good news.
HIVE has her.
Do you have
a location?
I'm tracing a signal.
I should have taken
more processors
from Palmer Tech
on my way out.
They made a mistake
letting you go.
They'll see it.
And if they don't,
I'm taking revenge plan suggestions.
Got it.
Thea's message came
from the intersection
of Berkeley and Childress,
right in the heart
of the Glades.
I thought you said
Thea and her boyfriend
went out of town.
I thought they did.
Let's go.
I-I'm coming with you.
I want you to stay here.
If this gets worse,
the city is going to need
someone to listen to
that they can trust.
What is it?
Say something.
Your eyes were glowing.
Like Reiter?
My God.
Oliver, what's
happening to me?
It--it--it doesn't matter.
We will figure it out,
but for now we have to keep moving.
All right? Come on.
- Aah!
Oliver!
It's incredible.
I know now why Reiter
sought this power.
When you furrow
your brow like that,
you look just like Moira.
Don't you dare talk
about my mother.
Fine. Let's talk about
the future instead.
Genesis is coming.
With Machin
running around,
we can't have another
X-factor on the loose.
"We"?
Not the HIVE overlords?
Point being,
I need your word
that you won't
cause any trouble.
Or what?
Or I will have
to do something
to assure
your compliance
that I really don't
want to do.
Well, when there's
something I don't want to do,
I just get it over with.
This will make
everything better.
Overwatch, are you
sure this is the spot?
There's nothing here.
That's impossible.
Ok, not impossible,
but my back trace
on Thea's message
has a 99.9999%
accuracy rate,
so unless this is
part of the .0001 percentile...
It's just
an empty street.
Just look for anything
out of place, all right?
Whatever HIVE has built
is probably recent,
you know, new.
Is there supposed
to be sewer access on the street?
Not according
to city plans.
Stand by.
Help me with
something, Malcolm.
How is it again that
this juvenile annoyance
Lonnie Machin
is still a problem
for us?
Machin is exactly
what we--
Actually, I've
changed my mind.
I'm not interested
in excuses,
just results.
Yes?
Security, on radio:
Two hostiles have breached
the southeast entrance.
One in green,
the other in black.
Send a squad
and secure the entrance.
Green and black.
Oliver's come
for his baby sister, most likely.
And since she's only
here because of you,
I believe that makes
Mr. Queen your problem.
You have a lot on
your plate, Malcolm.
I suggest you
get started.
Come on, sweetie.
How did HIVE
build all this
without anyone knowing?
Well, doesn't hurt
having someone
controlling the city's
infrastructure.
Can't find any public
blueprints on file
for an underground lair
with a creepy
sewer entrance.
Believe me...
There are no public
blueprints for this.
Unbelievable.
Just like Mount Weather.
Continuity
of government facility
built by FEMA
during the cold war,
in case of
a nuclear attack.
I think that we
found the ark
that HIVE's been building.
What?
I lost their signal.
Well, get it back.
I have to get back
to Curtis and Kuttler.
All right.
I'll cover comms.
I hear anything,
I'll patch you in.
What's the emergency?
Is Rubicon still
stabilized?
Where is Kuttler?
Did he do something?
Did he--are you
drinking a beer?
I knew that being a child
of divorce was hard,
but what I did not
have any idea about
was all the yelling,
the name-calling,
the loudness.
- You poor thing, poor thing.
- Oh, oh.
What are you
talking about?
Oh, God,
do you even listen?
So I'm here to take
her away from you?
Get out--get out
of my brain.
Can we not
with her here?
She's here.
Just calm down.
This really is
the end of the world.
When you tell someone
to calm down...
It actually
does the opposite.
Baby, I've been
so worried about you.
Oh, my God.
Do you know
I have called?
I have called you
a million times, baby.
I have been calling
and calling.
- Are you ok?
- I am. I'm fine.
Just been a little
distracted.
With your father?
Thanks for telling me.
I don't know.
Everything just
happened so fast.
What has?
Sit down.
What? What?
I have to tell you
something.
Oh!
I'm going to be
a grandma!
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, you're not.
I knew you had more
than a bad burrito the other day.
I knew it was
more than that.
Ok. No.
Baby! Baby!
I am not pregnant.
Is that the only news
that a woman can have?
The world is under attack,
and I need my fa--I need
Noah to help me stop it.
Honey, what happened
in Havenrock is horrible,
but that doesn't
mean the world is going to end.
She's telling the truth.
You know, I know--
which she clearly
gets from my side
of the family,
thank you.
You know, I know
when my daughter is lying, ok?
There were
plenty of times
when she was
a teenager,
not that you
would know.
Here we go.
For once, this
isn't about you, Dee.
- Oh, you're calling me "Dee"?
- There are nuclear missiles...
- Are you calling me "Dee"?
- Targeted all across the globe.
Somebody stick
something sharp in my eye.
What happened in Havenrock is going to
happen to the entire world.
Unless we stop it,
which we will.
Sweetie, why do you
even think
this is something
that you can--
because I work with
the Green Arrow, Mom.
For how long?
3 years.
And you've been
keeping this from me?
Yes.
Wow, I guess
you and your father
are more alike
than I thought.
Mom.
We can talk about it
later, hon, after you...
Save the world.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
The world's two best
hackers side by side.
This is history.
I mean, it's--
it's no biggie.
It's crazy.
Take away the psychos
in the smocks...
And it might as well
be Ivy Town.
Everyone looks
so happy.
Happy's easy
when you're mindless
on some little
yellow pill.
Let's just assume we
weren't invited over for casserole.
What's our play?
We split up
and find Thea.
Scope the houses
on the north.
I'll head south.
Good afternoon.
Today is a brisk
and sunny 85 degrees.
It is a lovely day
to be outside.
As we all enjoy Tevat Noah,
I want to take this moment
to express my gratitude.
I want to thank
each and every one...
I've got eyes on Thea.
Fourth house down.
There are two
hostiles with her.
Speedy, let's get
you out of here.
Are you all right?
I have the intruder.
Move, and I will kill you.
Thea...
Don't move.
Listen to me.
You're not thinking clearly.
In her defense,
she's a little drugged
at the moment.
I should have
taken your head.
That's always been
your problem...
An inability to do
what is necessary.
Laurel is dead
because of you.
What are you going to do?
We've already established
you're not going
to kill me.
What the hell?
It's the yellow pills.
Son of a bitch.
They're there!
On the porch!
We got to go.
Let's move!
Not that it's not scintillating
to watch you type,
but when exactly will
I have Rubicon back?
Hacking isn't as easy
as waving your hand.
Oh, point taken.
So you and Felicity Smoak.
I just don't see it.
She used to be
a lot different.
All clear.
Looks like we bought
ourselves a few minutes.
John, this place
is enormous.
I don't know how we're
going to find Thea.
Just have to make sure
that the Ghosts
don't find us.
So much for "clear."
We're not going
to hurt you.
Then what are
the weapons for?
There's a woman being
held against her will.
We're just here
to bring her home.
Ruvé, on TV:
Citizens of Tevat Noah,
I have disturbing news.
We are under attack
from a man in a green hood
and another in a black helmet.
Do not let them
disrupt Genesis.
These individuals are not
an affront to our home
but to our future
and the futures of our children.
Find them and kill them.
Oh, no.
It's ok, Oliver.
I know what to do now.
I finally understand
what Reiter was after.
Taiana,
Reiter was insane.
Why?
He said after his village
was destroyed,
he would never be
powerless again.
I have a village, too,
Krasnoyarsk,
run by a government
strongman named Kovar.
Taiana...
Now I know why fate has
led me to this place--
to give me the strength
to free my home.
Ok. All right.
You'll go back
to Russia,
and--and you can
take on this Kovar,
but right now there
are people here
that need our help.
What would Vlad
want you to do?
What would your brother
expect you to do?
Find these hostiles
at once.
Nothing can be permitted
to stand in the way
of Genesis.
Thank you.
I'm not sure
murdering vigilantes
is what your
loyal supporters signed up for.
Well, you better hope
that they don't find
Mr. Queen and Mr. Diggle
before you do, Malcolm,
or I'll be forced
to seriously question
what your purpose here is.
Every time I knock down
a firewall,
5 more pop back up.
It would seem
that Mr. Darhk
has a counter-hacker
in his employ.
And he's good.
Yeah.
Ok.
I might have something.
Now, until the FBI
gets their way,
smartphones are protected
by encryption.
If you don't enter
your passcode
after enough times,
then the device
bricks itself, right?
Curtis, I don't even
have the time
to tell you that
I don't have the time.
You just did.
But here's the point.
Instead of trying
to break Rubicon's encryption...
We make it stop working
in the first place.
You're suggesting
as it is with a smartphone...
We overload Rubicon
with too many
access requests.
And it shuts itself down.
Unfortunately,
I doubt very much
that Argus would leave
Rubicon so vulnerable
to such a brute
force attack.
Let them try.
You're always such
a stick in the mud.
Yes!
Let's all take
hacking advice
from a woman whose only use
for her smartphone
is as a mirror.
Ho ho! Ha! So funny.
Ha ha!
Not.
Felicity may have gotten
her brains from you,
but she got her
creativity from moi.
Matching lipstick
to lip liner
isn't creativity,
and while I may not be
father of the year...
Oh, try the past
two decades.
I recently took a bullet
for our daughter.
Not metaphorically,
either.
By the way, a metaphor,
it's a--it's a--it's a--
Oh, I know what
a metaphor means,
just like I know what abandoning
your family looks like.
Really?
Because I remember not
having much of a choice
in the matter.
Uh, Felicity?
Cooper, on monitors:
Hello, Felicity.
- Remember me?
- Cooper.
Your system is now
under my control,
just like Rubicon will
be in the next 5 minutes.
Once again, you lose.
- Oh...Frak.
Who is this guy, again?
Cooper Seldon,
her ex-boyfriend.
How could I forget?
I thought he was dead,
and just came back evil.
Oliver, Dr. Palmer,
this guy.
You really have
a complicated romantic history.
Not the best
time, Curtis.
Be honest, Felicity,
hacker to hacker.
You prefer it this way,
don't you?
As it was meant to be?
Once more unto breach...
Is he seriously going full
"Star Trek VI" on you?
He shut our system
down with a virus.
It's an x-axis
binumeric algorithm.
I know. I created it
in college.
Wait. How did you know?
Just because I wasn't
in your life
doesn't mean I wasn't keeping tabs
on my daughter.
He's sending
electrical surges
- to all our previous IPs...
- Aah!
Whatever it is,
it's working.
It is, but it's pinging
back to his location.
You thinking what
I'm thinking?
We hitch our own code
on to the back trace.
Curtis, your Rubicon
lockout idea.
How long till you can
get me an executable?
Uh...20 seconds.
Great.
If this works,
it will send
the latest surge
back to its point
of origin,
triggering Rubicon
to lock itself out.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Just get the son of a bitch.
Locked and...
Loaded.
Got you.
Oh, no.
What is it?
To be, or not to be...
Did it work?
I think it worked.
It worked.
Well, the power's
still on.
That's--that's good,
right?
Rubicon's offline.
Ha ha ha!
He's going to need more than
some third-rate hacker
to get it
back up again,
all because of you,
sweetheart.
Thanks, Dad.
Mom?
Streets are filled.
Ruvé's mobilized
the entire ark
looking for us.
They're in here!
Oh!
Quiet.
You can't win.
You can't stop Genesis.
Well, what are you going
to do when you're not here
to enjoy your
brave new world?
Spartan.
Easy.
He almost got us killed.
They're like Thea.
They're not in
their right minds.
You mean the pills?
We haven't taken any.
Not even one.
None of us have.
We're here
because we believe,
because we know
the world is evil and darkness.
It's beyond saving.
How can you
believe that?
Because we've lived it.
Every day.
So many promises were
made to save the city,
but it all just
fell apart,
and we were the ones
left in the rubble.
Damien Darhk
has given us hope.
Can you with your
masks and your guns
actually say the same?
There's a plane
due east.
Stay here. We'll hold off
Reiter's men.
Taiana, help me
with this guy.
He's alive.
Hey. He's alive.
Help me with him.
He's too bad.
He'll only slow us,
keep us from
helping the others.
We're not just going
to leave him here.
You're right.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
His death
is inevitable.
Why waste his life when
it can make me stronger?
What are you doing
with my clothes?
When I get stressed,
I--I like to fold.
Yeah. I know.
When you two
were married,
it was like
living at the Gap.
Hey, what did Noah mean
when he said
that he didn't have much
choice in the matter
when he left?
I always just assumed
he disappeared.
He didn't disappear, hon.
I did.
We did.
I had a 7-year-old daughter,
and I know all
about gambling,
and I wasn't willing
to take the bet
that your father
could possibly change.
He let me believe
that he abandoned us.
Well, I don't...
I don't know what to say
about that, hon.
I mean, I think...
I think he just
didn't want you
to lose your mom, too.
Hey, look at me.
I didn't lose you.
Did I?
Never.
I'm sorry.
Do you ever think
that maybe Darhk has a point?
No, Darhk is psychotic.
Everyone down here is.
Are they?
He's not wrong.
The world is coming apart
just like Star City.
I mean, it is worse
than it has ever been.
That's because Darhk's
been spending the past year
trying to kill it.
Then why is he giving
these people more hope
than we ever could?
Go! Go in the bedroom!
Take cover!
Go! Move, move, move!
I'll hold them off.
Go find Thea.
Go, now!
Thea.
This isn't you, Thea.
They are trying
to control you,
but you are stronger
than that.
You can fight
through it.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
Every day we stand
side by side
to protect this city,
and no matter how dark
or how hopeless,
you always keep fighting.
You never give up!
I refuse to believe
that you're going
to give up now.
So fight!
Drug me again,
and I will kill you,
you son of a bitch.
Hi, everyone.
Uncle Lonnie here.
See, I just absolutely
adore your little
community.
It's so welcoming
to outsiders,
but it's so...structured.
Going to have
to fix that.
Mr. Darhk, remember me?
The loyal servant
you rejected, betrayed?
In 20 minutes,
I'm going to kill someone.
It can be your wife...
Oh, but, Damien,
you're my first choice.
Ball's in your court, buddy.
Oh, and be quick
about it,
because in 21 minutes,
I'm going to blow
your little underground world
into next week.
Ok?
So Machin is down here?
An ongoing pest we've
yet to exterminate.
He killed Alex,
who brought me here
because Ruvé
drugged him
just like
you did to me.
We can discuss my parenting
philosophy later.
Mr. Machin is
the immediate threat.
To Darhk and his wife,
and I still don't understand
why we should care.
Because he has
already tried once
to kill everyone
down here.
Malcolm's right.
We're not letting
anyone else die.
This place isn't safe.
I need you to get your
family out of here
in order
to protect them.
Please.
Now, you know the way out,
so if we can't stop Machin,
then you are going
to lead the evacuation.
I don't recall
volunteering.
And even if I did,
where exactly would
I evacuate them to?
Everything above our heads
is going to be under
a mushroom cloud.
I refuse to believe that.
Because you're a fool.
Because I have hope.
Let's go.
Taiana, I am not just
going to let you kill this man.
I'm the only one
who can stop Reiter.
This is how.
I need that man's power.
Listen to yourself!
This isn't you.
Whatever that idol is doing,
it is warping your mind.
No.
I've never been clearer.
Now get out of my way!
No, don't!
Deja vu all over again.
You as the bait,
me waiting to kill
your husband.
You know, I really hope
I get it right this time.
You have no idea the power
that you're up against.
Look at you.
No longer
the whimpering victim.
Mommy's so strong
and impressive.
Isn't she?
You do realize that
you're planning
to destroy
the last safe place
left on the entire
planet, right?
I'm sorry.
Did I leave you
with the impression
that I was
a rational guy?
Unh!
That's my mommy.
Isn't she pretty?
Oh, and she brought
her friends.
This is over.
More like under.
I tinkered with
the engineering here.
This whole place
is powered
by a dwarf star alloy.
Very powerful
but a little touchy,
so you might want
to be careful where you aim
because a stray shot
could blow this whole place.
We're not letting
you out of here.
Oh.
Well, in that case...
Unh!
Unless you want to die,
let's go!
Bye, mommy.
There's no time.
Save my daughter.
Please.
Promise me.
I promise.
We need to get out of here,
like, right now.
Finally,
electric boogaloo awakes.
Sir, there's something
happening at Tevat Noah.
Well, it looks like
the real estate value
of the Glades
just went up.
It's called
gallows humor.
What about
everybody else?
I saw Merlyn leading
some evacuations.
There must be
other access points.
Or Malcolm's
underneath all that.
What about her?
Is anyone there?
Green Arrow,
Spartan, Speedy?
Hell, I'd take
Malcolm Merlyn at this point.
We're all safe.
Where are you
with Rubicon?
HIVE's locked out.
We're good.
The city's safe...
You sound like there's
a "but" to that sentence.
People still
need saving.
They still need hope.
Give it back!
Taiana, if you
want it back,
you're going to have
to kill me,
and I'm betting
you won't.
What about me, Mr. Queen?
And after killing you...
I'll kill her.
Tell me.
It was Machin. He's--
Ruvé?
I'm sorry.
My daughter?
We're still getting
reports of survivors.
We're locked out
of Rubicon.
Momentarily.
I know someone who can
get us back online.
Damien.
Tevat Noah is gone.
It's buried
under miles of ash.
Even if you could regain
control of Rubicon,
there'd be no place
on earth that is safe.
If there's no place left
on earth that's safe...
Let it all burn.
All right, I'm listening.
Though, if you could
keep the lecture short,
- I'd appreciate it.
- No lecture.
Just a request.
Ah-ha.
Leave, and this time...
Don't come back.
- What?
- You helped Felicity tonight.
Maybe it was because
you'd be nuked, too.
Maybe it was a broken clock
being right for once.
Either way, we both
know it wasn't you.
- Dee...
- You know who you are.
Are you really going
to stand here--
Heh--and tell me
that you've changed?
You're every bit
as dangerous to our daughter
as the day
I took her from you.
If you care about her,
you will walk away.
After everything
that's happened,
she'll be crushed.
She'll survive.
She's strong.
She's my daughter.
You can lie to her,
but can you lie to yourself?
Can you really believe
that leaving
isn't the best
thing for her?
What do you
think your parents are talking about?
I'm trying not
to think about it.
Maybe they're
discussing that thing
that Noah said before
about not having
much of a choice.
That's exactly what I'm
trying not to think about.
- Felicity...
- Mm-hmm.
I helped you
save the world.
The least you can do is
give me a little gossip.
Ok, fine.
So apparently
my dad didn't leave.
My mom kicked him out.
Did she tell you why?
I think she didn't want
to risk him hurting me.
I mean, he could promise
whatever he wanted,
but he was a criminal--
is a criminal.
So he inevitably would have
gone back to his old habits.
Mm-hmm.
What does that mean?
It just sounds
familiar, that's all.
The criminal who you
don't think can change,
the slightly overactive
but understandable breakup.
Just saying,
you and Oliver,
Donna and Noah.
Where's Noah?
He's going away
for a little while.
That's what you
told me when I was 7.
Boo hoo.
Are you getting all weepy?
Do you need a moment?
No? Good.
Because I need you
to do me a favor.
Go to hell.
Why bother?
I'm going to
bring it to us.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.