My name is Oliver Queen.
For 7 years, I have fought
with only one goal...
to save my city,
but now a new threat
has emerged,
a danger so severe,
it has forced me
to leave my family
in order to face it,
and it won't be enough for me
to just be the Green Arrow.
To prevent the crisis
that's coming,
I am going to have to become
someone else.
I am going to have
to become... something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Earth-2 is... gone.
The destruction
of that Earth was
a necessary sacrifice.
Mar Novu is not trying to
prevent what's going to happen
because he's gonna be
what causes it.
John Diggle is
my adoptive father.
- Thanks, Mr. Diggles.
- Call me Dig.
We have to take out
the Deathstrokes.
Zoe!
Dad?
Oh, my God. Dad!
W-William? William?
Hey.
Mia.
Mia?
Dad!
Well, you're
so young.
Dad?
What is this?
How did they get here?
I... I don't know.
Those are my kids.
Your kids.
Are you... are you okay?
H-how is this real?
Good question.
The last time I checked,
you didn't have an adult
daughter or any daughter.
We had a daughter...
and we named her Mia.
Felicity gave birth a few
months after we left Star City.
How? I... I didn't even
know she was pregnant.
We didn't
tell anyone.
We wanted to keep her
off the grid
to protect her.
That was only
a few months ago.
This is Novu.
You called me Dad.
You adopted me.
Remember?
It's Connor.
No. No. I... I...
I haven't.
He hasn't because
he hasn't yet.
Look. What are you
talking about?
I think we're
in the past.
- That is insane.
- Look at this place.
It's new,
and them!
No gray hair,
no wrinkles,
and we are staring
at our dad alive
instead of
at his tombstone.
I'm sorry.
What year is this?
2-2... uh, it's 2019.
What year is it
supposed to be?
2040.
Wait. So an hour ago, I was
just with Ben Turner's 6-year-old child,
and now he's an adult,
and I'm his father?
At least you didn't throw up
like you usually do.
Just saying.
I'm genuinely sorry
that both of you
found out this way,
about Mia,
about the Monitor. I'm...
Felicity and I wanted
to tell you.
Oliver, as far
as excuses go,
a cosmic being asking you
to sacrifice your life
to save the entire universe
is a... pretty good one.
Look. Those kids have
20 years of stuff we don't know.
When are we gonna
be able to ask them what happens?
I think we should give
them their space,
and when they're ready,
they'll open up.
Okay. Laurel's on her
way to Star City.
I can't believe
her entire Earth is just gone.
I don't understand.
Why didn't the Monitor bring her here?
Or grown-up JJ
or Zoe?
What game is
he playing?
I don't know,
but we have
to stop him.
How do we stop
a god?
I'm working on it.
Okay. How did this happen?
This can't be real.
Well, it is.
Hey. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Yeah.
Just please tell me
that you were able
to get JJ.
I had him,
and I was gonna... kill him,
and the next thing I know,
I'm... I'm here.
So he's still
out there.
You mean, out there
20 years in the future
unless you're talking
about the current JJ,
who'd be, like, what, 5?
And you're not gonna
thwick him.
Mia?
No, I'm not, okay?
How does this
even work?
All right, 'cause my dad doesn't
even know who I am,
and if he finds out
about JJ, what he did,
what I... what I
almost did,
he won't want to.
So don't tell him.
Don't tell
anyone anything.
- Are you serious?
- She's right.
This is original Team Arrow
we're talking about.
They are gonna know
something's up.
Do you want to tell Rene
his daughter's dead
or tell John that
his son's the one who did it?
What's done
is done.
Wow. This place
looks exactly like it did
when I was 13,
which makes sense
because I guess I still am.
Sorry about
the boxes.
Felicity and I left
pretty suddenly
to get
to the cabin,
and we
had planned to
come back here
with both of you at some point.
Yeah. That, um,
didn't really work out.
Because I died?
We don't know exactly.
You just sort of
disappeared.
So did, uh... looks
like the two of you
got a chance to...
to grow up with each other.
Um... actually, um,
Mia and I
just found out
about each other recently.
I never saw Felicity
growing up,
and... and after
I left here, I...
I never saw you again.
Yeah. After you died,
it was, um,
just me and mom
at the cabin.
I'm sorry that I wasn't there
for the two of you.
However, we are
here now.
Um, why don't we
sit down,
and you guys can
catch me up to speed or...
On 20 years?
It doesn't really
work that way.
Even if it did,
I'm just... I'm tired.
I want to sleep,
and I... you know?
Yep. Well, the bedroom
is right there.
Just please make
yourself at home, okay?
Yeah. Sure.
Night.
This is gonna be...
interesting.
Who are you calling?
Felicity. She needs to know
that the two of you are back.
- You can't.
- Why?
Look. I'm not exactly sure how this
time travel thing works.
Maybe we shouldn't...
bring Mom into this
until we have
a better understanding
of what... this is.
That's a good point.
William, tell me
something good
about the future,
please.
Well... you know
those computer projects
that I would work on
in my room
when I wasn't
talking to you?
- Yeah.
- I turned that teen angst
into a multibillion-dollar
tech empire.
- What?
- Kind of a mogul.
That's phenomenal.
That's, um...
I get the feeling
I'm gonna be really...
really, really proud
of how you turned out.
Yeah. Well, um...
I didn't just turn out.
Um... there's something
I should tell you.
I'm gay.
Yeah, buddy.
I know.
- You know?
- Yeah.
Felicity and I knew,
and we just, um...
well, we hoped that
you were gonna
come out to us when
you were comfortable.
You clearly didn't
get that chance,
and that's on me,
so... I'm sorry.
Dad, we all have the chance
to get to know each other now.
If your sister
will let me.
Mia will come around.
You know, she can be
a little... a little bit stubborn
and... hard to reach
sometimes.
Shocker. Where'd she
get that from?
Mom, I guess.
My husband
needs help.
Um, did you check in
at the desk?
We're donors here.
Hold this.
I'm just gonna
have a look.
Run! Bomb!
Starling General
was attacked last night
after a bomb was found
inside Archroyal Capital CEO
Macmillan Fairfield.
Authorities believe
the infamous terrorist
Deathstroke orchestrated
the attack.
Please tell me the city's
better in the future.
Yeah, yeah,
definitely.
- You think this is Slade?
- No. No, no.
I have A.R.G.U.S.
Keeping tabs.
He's currently
in Buredunia,
which is nowhere
near Star City.
Neither is his son,
Kane Wolfman.
So this is
someone new?
Yep. Someone has co-opted
the Deathstroke mask,
and they're using it
to terrorize the city.
We need motive.
Well, the vic is some rich
Wall Street type,
and those guys
are easy to hate.
We're not all bad.
- He's a billionaire.
- Say what?!
Please tell me Zoe is, too.
How is Zoe?
I mean, are you guys
still friends?
Yeah. She's...
you'd be proud.
Hello, bunker!
Oh, it feels so good to
be back.
Wait. Are those
the kids from the future?
Those are definitely
the kids from the future!
Oh, my God, and excuse me.
When were you gonna tell me
about this, Councilman Ramirez?
This is so cool.
I may have had
coffee on the plane,
and by "may have,"
I mean I definitely did have it.
It's Candidate Ramirez.
We don't know if I win yet.
Uh, did you miss the part where
these kids are from the future?
Okay. Rene, if you really
want to know, you become mayor.
Seriously?
Hoo hoo hoo!
Oh, that's a text
from D.
I will let her know
about Slade
and gloat that I'm
gonna be her boss.
Uh, William, we should,
uh, go, let them work.
Wait.
But I just got here,
and I have
so many questions,
starting with why did nobody
say anything about my beard?
Good to see you, Curtis.
Your beard looks tremendous, okay?
I mean, work or otherwise,
I'd like you to stay.
Yeah. No. I just, um...
I'd rather see
the city than the bunker.
Let's go.
I can't believe
that's your son, that's William.
I can, however, definitely
believe that that is your daughter.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Uh, speaking of which,
I'm a little upset
you didn't tell me about her,
but that's okay.
I forgive you.
So why'd you call in the big guns?
- You know Earth-2?
- Yeah.
Well, yeah. It was destroyed
by a wave of energy.
This fabric was clipped by it,
and I would like you
to try and help me
figure out what it is.
I can... I can track down
some equipment.
It might...
take a bit.
The reason why
would help?
It's a wave of energy that's
powerful enough to destroy a planet,
so it's probably powerful
enough to stop a god,
which is... what we're
doing now.
God. You said god.
Um, so the
fate of the universe
is in my hands.
Cool, cool, cool.
Yeah. You guys... I got it. Ahem.
Hey. Lyla is still
off the grid,
but um, she'll be very
happy to see you.
You know, we always wanted
a brother for JJ.
- You and he close?
- Yeah. Best friends.
Glad to hear that.
I didn't know this was
bring your kid to work day.
Eh. Thought I might
be able to help.
Connor was an agent at an
organization called Knightwatch.
It makes A.R.G.U.S. look
like a kindergarten class.
The Canaries are
comparable, though.
Canaries?
Forget it.
What do you got?
Uh, found this
on the vic,
what was left of him.
May I?
Yeah.
I've seen
this before.
A, um, terrorist
organization,
they use these
to deliver messages.
Do you have
a black light?
Yeah, but we ran the inks on it already.
Nothing turned up.
That is because you
checked it dry.
Whoa. Okay.
So that's our motive.
That's good work, Connor.
Is there something else
you recognize?
No. Uh, that's it.
And that is Mia,
so I should probably...
Go. Go, go, go.
I'll catch up with you later.
It can't really
be JJ, can it?
This all started
the night we got here.
Maybe JJ came back, too.
What, and the first thing
he decides to do is blow something up?
It doesn't make
any sense.
It does if you
know my brother.
"Star City's cancer
is the rich"...
it's JJ's favorite
catchphrase.
Okay. We should tell Dad
and the team.
Not a chance.
This is our mess to clean up.
But we could use
their help.
I mean, maybe if JJ
sees John, then...
He won't care.
JJ will kill Dad
if he gets in his way.
This is on us.
It's on us to
avenge Zoe.
Well, then first,
we need to find him.
All right.
You know him best.
You know
the Deathstrokes.
Where would he go?
Where it all began.
Are you sure this
is the place?
20 years from now, this
place is galaxy one,
but 2019, it's where
the Deathstrokes started.
Oh. I am getting
a case of deja vu
in the worst
possible way.
You stay out
of sight.
Connor and I
got this.
Wait what?
He's dead.
Something's not right.
Don't move...
or we all go boom.
Frak!
JJ.
Oh, crap.
Why did you
do it, JJ?
Why did you kill her?
Damn it, JJ!
Answer me!
Who the hell is JJ?
Grant.
Incoming.
Evac now!
Oh, great. Looks like
we made it back
just in time to walk
into a bomb trap.
- How'd you find us?
- Later. We have to move.
Might be a bit
of a problem.
Buy us a few seconds.
On my mark.
Three... two... one...
Go!
Well, at least we
didn't die.
It's a good thing
we were tracking a victim,
or you would have been
in worse shape than that drive.
At least it's still
in one piece.
Maybe I can recover
the data.
Maybe you can explain to all of us
what you were doing there
with no backup.
We can take care
of ourselves.
That's not
the point, Mia.
What were you
looking for?
In the future,
that building is
the Deathstroke
home base.
The leader's
Grant Wilson.
Slade's other son.
Surprise, surprise.
Were you ever planning
on sharing that information
with the rest
of the class?
- No.
- Clearly your daughter.
So if you knew
it was Grant,
then why did you
call him JJ?
I heard you yell
his name.
What's going on here?
She doesn't know what
she's talking about.
Then you tell me,
Connor!
We came back,
so we thought maybe
JJ did, too.
That's why we didn't tell you
about the Deathstrokes.
Connor, I don't understand what
you're talking about.
In the future, Grant
trains a new leader,
someone who eventually
takes over the Deathstrokes.
It's JJ.
You told me
JJ was fine!
Dad, I'm sorry.
- There's something else.
- William.
Look. They have
a right to know,
and I'm done holding
onto this.
Future Star City
is a terrible place.
It's run by gangs,
the cops are corrupt,
politicians, too.
Does that include me?
We're
trying to save it,
but that meant
stopping JJ,
and that's what we were doing
right before we came here.
We... we thought
we could, but...
Zoe was
with Mia, and...
And what?
JJ killed her.
I'm so sorry, Rene.
Rene! Rene, stop, man.
Let's talk!
Talk about what, huh?
About how your son
killed my daughter?
Look, man. I know
you're angry, okay?
I'm shook, too.
My son's a murderer, Rene,
a murderer,
but, man, now that we
know what went on,
maybe we can do something
to change it.
Change it how?
What if what we do
today doesn't make
a damn difference
about tomorrow?
This is my fault.
I'm sorry. I should have
told you sooner.
Then tell me now,
Connor!
Everything.
When you took me in,
I was angry
and rebellious,
but you... you refused
to give up on me.
Man, you straightened
me out, made me who I am,
a soldier just like you...
JJ, he resented it.
You know, it was like
I had stole the love
that should have
been his.
Maybe if I had been
a better son
JJ would have never
broken bad
and Zoe would
still be alive.
Dad, please
say something.
Dad?
Connor, since the moment
you got here,
you have done nothing
but lie to me,
to all of us.
What do you want
me to say?
Zoe was fighting to fix exactly
what her dad helped cause.
That's why she was
a Canary like both of you.
You guys had a whole
network of them in the city.
And that's what Connor
was talking about earlier.
And yet we still
couldn't save the city.
After Rene walled
off the Glades,
the scope was
just too big,
and ever since the wall came down,
we've been fighting the Deathstrokes,
trying to make
things better, but...
I just still
don't understand.
I mean, JJ adores Zoe.
How could he do
something like this?
Seemed pretty easy
for him,
so how about we stop
mourning poor, innocent JJ
and accept who he
actually is?
Look, all that matters right now
is stopping Grant Wilson
before he screws up
everyone's future.
What else can you
tell me about him?
Just the broad strokes.
Grant made a name
for himself doing
pretty much exactly
what he's doing now,
targeting the rich,
appealing to
the disenfranchised.
They became cult heroes,
which is how he
seduced JJ.
Any more specifics?
Grant's home base
just got blown up.
That... that never
happened before.
We're in new territory now.
How long to
access the drive?
Uh, more than a few,
less than a year.
I'm gonna go check
on Rene.
We should be out there
doing something.
We will be
once we know
Grant Wilson's plan.
Are you crazy?
How can you not like mint chip?
It tastes like
toothpaste.
Aunt Dinah? I didn't know
you were gonna be here.
Hey, kiddo.
Give me a squeeze.
You want to talk
to my dad, huh?
- I'll go start scooping.
- Hey, hey.
Don't eat all
the ice cream.
How am I supposed to
wake up every morning
knowing how many days
we have left together?
By trying to change
what happens,
trying every single day.
- We should talk.
- Ha.
What are you doing?
I'm going to the hospital
bomb site.
Maybe Dinah
missed something.
- Mia.
- I'm not gonna stand around
and waste time.
Look. I know what's
driving you right now.
You lost a teammate.
I... I... I've been there.
I... I can help.
I'm here to help.
You know, I survived
my whole life without you.
I don't need you
to play dad now.
Hey. I'm not playing dad.
I am simply telling you
that it is not tactically
wise to go out there
- by yourself...
- Fine. I'll take Laurel.
When you are letting
your decisions
be driven
by your emotions.
Trust me. I've been there.
You don't get a say.
You gave up that right
when you left
me and Mom alone
in that cabin.
How could you just
abandon us?
Because I chose to keep you safe,
and I chose right.
You just wanted
to be a hero,
so you put your mission
above your family.
Don't worry. You'll learn
to live without me pretty easy,
just like I learned
to live without you.
Mmm.
I'm not letting you go
out there.
Nyssa Al Ghul
trained me.
You want to see
how well?
I'm not gonna fight you.
I'm your father.
Really? Because
from where I stand,
you're just some guy
in my way.
Mia...
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Uh... Dad, I know
this is bad timing,
but you should
see this.
It's live.
6 years ago, my father
rained terror down on this city.
He was short-sighted, foolish.
This city has a cancer,
the one percent
who control industry.
I will excise it.
Our siege of Star City
begins tonight.
This might be
how it starts.
This is the beginning
of the future.
Why would Grant give
us advanced warning?
It seems too easy.
That's because it is.
Look, Grant may be
planning an attack,
but it won't be
on the rich.
That video's a mislead.
This kind of deception is
a Deathstroke special.
How do you know
that?
I was undercover
with them for a while,
a last-ditch attempt
to get through to JJ.
Okay. So if this is a bait and switch,
what's the switch?
What do you think
Grant's planning?
Something
a whole lot bigger.
I just don't know
what exactly.
Everything happening
with the Deathstrokes is
different now.
Well, I've got some
good news.
I managed to extract
the data from the drive,
but, surprise, surprise,
it's encrypted,
and since I'm not
an expert
in early 21st-century
decryption algorithms,
I've called in
someone who is... Curtis.
Great. Now what about
Mia and Laurel?
We need to focus
on tracking down Grant.
Felicity's search algorithm should
still be on the computer.
Way ahead of you.
Wow. Mom really liked
playing fast and loose
with
the Fourth Amendment, huh?
Yeah.
Any chatter
from A.R.G.U.S.?
No. No, no, no.
They said they'll keep us posted.
Hey. I spoke
to Rene, by the way.
Well, I'm quite sure
he's not willing to talk to me.
No, but I do know
someone who is.
Are you avoiding him?
No.
Maybe.
I've never dealt with
anything like this before.
My head is still
spinning.
I... I... I want to blame someone.
I just don't know who.
John, we all failed
to save this city.
Yeah, Dinah,
but I'm his father,
so it's on me.
So you did pick
who to blame.
All this talk
about JJ got me
thinking about Andy,
how I failed him,
so yeah, the blame is
definitely on me.
I'm gonna tell you
the same thing I told Rene
because it's the same
thing I've been telling myself.
Knowing what's happened
can either destroy us
or save us.
We've seen our worst.
Now let's be our best.
In the future,
do they still use
the phrase
"wild goose chase"?
If you're bored,
you can go.
I don't need
a babysitter.
No, but you might
need backup
when you try and kill
Grant Wilson.
How did you know?
Oh. Well, clearly
no one has informed you
that I used to play
for team villain,
and I can spot a murderous
intent a million miles away.
So what, are you gonna try
and talk me out of it now,
tell me to listen
to my dad or...
Oh, God, no. I would never
tell anyone to listen to Oliver Queen.
No offense,
but I'm not exactly a very
big fan of your father's.
He's kind of a dick,
but you are a grown woman,
and if you want to
kill this guy, then have at it,
but I just want to
know why.
Because locking him up
isn't gonna change anything.
He escapes every time.
Why he's
such a cult hero
among all the worst
here in Star City.
- Including future JJ.
- Exactly.
Look, Grant has to die
so Zoe can live.
I don't know anything
about changing timelines,
but I am something
of an expert on vengeance,
and getting it,
it doesn't do anything
but cause you more pain.
So, what, you're an expert on
talking people out of murder?
Kind of.
I had to when Felicity
wanted to take down Ricardo Diaz.
My mom tried
to kill someone?
No, because I talked her
out of it.
And, look, I get it.
You and your mom,
you're both women
who won't allow themselves
to be talked out of anything,
and I appreciate that,
but Felicity, she never
regretted changing her approach,
so maybe you should try doing
things differently, too.
There you are.
Mia's back.
You crack the drive?
Curtis almost
has it.
God, you know, it's kind of
annoying how good he is.
Plus he's got this
perfect husband-slash-life,
not that I'm jealous
or anything.
Let me know when it's
done, okay?
You know, I have been told
by several ex-boyfriends
that I do this
moody, broody thing
when I'm problem-solving.
Guess it must be
genetic.
It's Mia, right?
I didn't want her
to go out there.
Well, then you should
have made her stay.
What, put her in timeout?
She's an adult.
Yeah, and like an adult,
she makes mistakes.
She's right.
I chose to go
with the Monitor.
I abandoned her.
I haven't earned
a say.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
she doesn't want you to have one.
Or... or that you shouldn't,
and I'm saying that
from experience.
You have kids
in the future?
Oh, God, no.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
Kids are a miracle
or... whatever,
but I was actually
referring to
when I left you to go
live with grandma and grandpa.
Yeah, that one's
still pretty fresh for me.
Right.
I... I... I...
I thought you
hated my guts.
I hated you
for abandoning me.
- I tried.
- True,
but I wanted you
to try harder,
push a little more.
I think that's all any child
wants from their parents.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Dad, I am glad that
you're in my life
then and now,
and Mia will be, too.
Um, I hate to interrupt father-son time,
but we got something.
So Grant is trying to
one-up his father.
The siege version 2.0
is tonight,
and this time,
Mirakuru is out,
and coordinated
bomb attacks are in.
- How many?
- Lots,
and Grant has them all
connected to a remote detonator,
probably a phone.
The good news is...
and I use that term very loosely...
is that he set up a relay device
underneath downtown.
So we disable the relay device,
we turn off the bomb.
Okay. What about Grant?
He's holed up
underground,
where the lines converge
at Water Street.
History repeats itself.
Well, maybe we can stop
the attack
by running the same play
we ran last time.
No. Someone told me
the only way
to change the future is to start doing
things differently now.
- Rene, look...
- John, we're good.
You, too, Connor.
I can't be mad
at either of you for something
I will never
let happen.
All right. We set up one team
to go after Grant,
one team to destroy
the relay device,
but we also need to
keep the public calm this time.
Last I checked,
the police are still good,
and I'm still captain,
future be damned.
I'll join you.
I got to do something
for the Glades
from there.
- What about the three of us?
- William, I think it would be
best if you stayed
and helped Curtis.
Mia and Connor, I'd like
for the two of you to come with us.
Rene said it. We have to do things
differently this time.
Agreed?
- All right.
- This is my favorite part.
Suit up.
Yes!
- Stay close, please.
- Where are we?
You're in the service
tunnels underneath the city.
Basically, you all are
in "The Shawshank Redemption."
"The Shawshank" what?
"The Shawshank Redemption."
It's... are there no movies in the future?
- Curtis!
- Oh, right. Staying on task.
Sorry. I'm a little bit
out of practice, guys.
Spartan, what's
your status?
We're at the east end.
Looks like someone
beat us here.
Tonight, we take
back this city
from the cancer
which has plagued it.
We will set
its citizens free.
We will save this city
from itself.
Stand beside me.
Take back what is rightfully yours.
Let's make Star City
great again.
Where are his men?
Mia, you should get
behind me.
I need three units
at the docks
and another two
in Pennytown, okay?
- Hey.
- Yup. Hey.
What's up?
Got a press conference
in the Glades in the works.
Great.
Brought you a new addition
to the drunk tank.
Watch him for a sec?
Hey. You got the time?
It's five to nine.
What the hell
is that?
Bomb!
We're almost
at the relay.
Well, that can't
be good.
Mia! Ohh!
Raise your hand
if you know how to disarm a bomb.
William, it's
an intervalometer.
Where'd you
learn that?
From you.
It's most likely
pulsating
in a consistently
synchronized pattern.
So it will have
a transfer switch embedded
into the mainframe.
Look at us...
Holt and Smoak 2.0.
There should be two wires
plugged into the console.
You're gonna disconnect
the red one.
Do not touch the blue one,
or else very bad things
will happen.
Unh!
What the hell?!
The device has been
neutralized.
I guess things have never
not been tense around here, huh?
Yeah. I like to cope
by stress eating.
- Gummy bear?
- Thanks.
This isn't over.
- Yes, it is.
- Mia!
Get out of my way.
No.
Hate me if you want.
I'm not letting you
do this.
Just got off the phone
with Gotham City PD.
Grant Wilson is being
prepped and transferred to Blackgate,
where he will spend
the next 20 to life.
We will keep an eye on him.
He's not going anywhere.
Takes the Deathstrokes off the board
for the foreseeable future.
Literally. Let's hope
it changes things somehow.
- For Zoe.
- And for JJ.
Here's hoping.
Or we make our own hope.
You guys really held
your own tonight.
Well, my keyboard
warrior skills are strong.
Uh, you know, Curtis went
right back to analyzing that fabric,
so I'm just gonna go
see if he needs help.
Thank you, William.
You okay?
- I would have killed him.
- I know,
and I know you
didn't want to.
Thank you.
Come on.
Hey.
You ready to go home?
You don't have to
do that.
I don't want to be a reminder
of everything bad
that happened to JJ
- and to your family.
- Connor.
You are my family, son.
Look. I'm sorry, Dad.
- I... I really am. I...
- It's okay.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, too.
We're gonna figure
this out.
Are you still
giving that speech tomorrow?
Yes. You really think
we changed things tonight?
In the future?
You mean in like
a baby Hitler kind of way?
"Butterfly Effect"?
- Come on.
- Hey.
If you want me to stop
training Zoe, I will.
Nah. I can't keep her
in a bubble
just like you can't
stop being a cop
and I can't stop
running for office.
So don't.
Not all of the future
was bad, right?
Just do
the good stuff.
I mean, the Canary network's
not a bad idea.
Could be useful.
Then why wait for a future
we can start making now?
So this is what you
wanted to show me,
Grandpa's grave?
Did your mother ever
mention him?
Not really.
I suppose she wouldn't
know what to say.
I barely do.
You weren't close?
I didn't really get
to know the real him
until after he died,
and, uh...
Look, I don't want
that to be us.
You've, um... you've
lost people, right?
Yeah. Too many.
Does the guilt
ever leave?
No.
You can learn to
live with it.
I can help you
with that, Mia,
if you'd like.
I've been a part
of the Glades my whole life.
Born and raised,
and if you're from here,
you know we've been
counted out a lot.
We've been told
we're low-income,
we're uneducated,
we're a lost cause.
And if you hear that
enough times,
all you can do is hope that
things will get better later.
Now, I don't know
about you guys,
but I'm tired of waiting.
I'm tired of waiting
for the day when
people stop being afraid
of the Glades
and start coming here
to raise their families,
to find opportunities
for growth and change,
to uplift our brothers
and sisters to be better
than we ever were before.
If we keep waiting,
we might run out of time.
That's why from here on out,
we don't wait
for our future in the Glades.
We make our future now.
Special delivery.
Ohh! Okay. This is the best late-night
snack you can ever have.
Want one?
Why not?
Yes, Curtis.
Do you want the long version
or the short version?
Please say the long one
because I would love to
geek out on this science.
- Did you know that...
- Curtis.
Short it is. Whatever it is
it is possible to replicate,
but there's a catch...
a couple catches, actually.
- Okay.
- One... I don't have the tools to do it.
Two... it is super illegal
because it requires
plutonium,
you know,
the bomb-making kind.
Luckily, there's a guy,
a military general.
Okay. Where is he?
Russia.
You must be
the Monitor.
How do you know?
Because no human
would actually wear
something
so ridiculous.
You ache for the world
you lost,
and I possess the power
to restore it.
You can bring
back my Earth?
The recovery
of your universe
will require
a single task.
What kind of task?
You must betray
Oliver Queen.
Greg, move your head!