My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years on a hellish island...
I have come home with only one goal:
To save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on Arrow:
Time to choose, Oliver.
Who lives and who dies?
In 30 seconds, I will shoot them both.
- You got what you came for!
- I guess you made your choice. Time's up.
No! No!
- Stick that in me, I'll kill you.
- No, brother Roy. You'll kill for me.
Where'd you get the Mirakuru?
It was a gift. A gift I will use
to save this city from itself.
The man in the skull mask.
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
You're the biggest street dealer
in Crescent Circle.
You know everything that goes
on over there. Who is he?
I ain't seen the guy before. I mean... a
skull mask? Are you freaking kidding me?
- Come on, man. I'm still on parole.
- Not anymore.
A spokesman
for the Central City Mayor's Office...
confirmed the lack of any damage
or radioactive fallout...
from the explosion that rocked
S.T.A.R. Labs five weeks ago.
Is Felicity not back yet?
She says she wanted to spend
a few more days with Barry.
Any improvement in his condition?
Still comatose.
How'd it go out there tonight?
Same as every other pointed conversation I
have with these lowlifes at Crescent Circle.
Nobody...
has seen a man in a skull mask.
He's still out there.
Oliver, for the past
five weeks, you've been
pushing yourself pretty
hard looking for this guy.
He has the Mirakuru, Diggle.
You saw what it took to kill one guy
that had been injected.
We practically had to drop a
building on him. Imagine, uh, 10.
Or a hundred. Imagine a thousand.
- You said Roy was injected.
- Yeah.
I've just never seen you
spooked like this before.
I should tell you something.
Shado always told me that
I wouldn't die here.
But looking back, I realize that
she never once said that about herself.
I just hope that she's with her father now.
Here, kid.
She'd want you to have that.
You're the one she cared for.
Slade.
Hey, Ollie. Just give him space.
I can't keep lying to him, Sara.
I need to tell him how Shado really died.
Ivo killed Shado.
- He pulled the trigger.
- Because I chose to save you.
- He needs to know the truth.
- Ollie, look.
He has the Mirakuru in his system.
What does that have to do
with anything?
Look the Japanese, they experimented on
hundreds of men working to develop Mirakuru...
and I read the research.
The people who died,
they were the lucky ones.
The ones who survived,
they were deformed.
Either their bones or their minds.
They became someone else.
You summon me here for a drink?
- You certainly look dressed for it.
- No, I have a date.
- What are you working on?
- Something to do with Sebastian Blood.
A.K.A. the next mayor of Starling City.
- Well, maybe he shouldn't be.
- What does that mean?
I've just been doing some investigating.
Blood had a connection
to the Langford Psychiatric Institute.
The one that burnt down
under very mysterious circumstances.
Did the police suspect arson?
No. They're saying
that it's inconclusive.
But Blood also knew Cyrus Gold...
the man that shot and killed
four police officers.
- Laurel, where are you going with this?
- I don't know. But I do have to go.
I'm gonna be late.
So who's the lucky guy?
Sebastian Blood.
He is the man we need to see
in the mayor's office.
So please join me in our efforts
to send Starling's favorite son there.
To Sebastian Blood.
Sebastian for Starling.
Thank you, Oliver.
And not just for your support...
but also for your friendship.
And thank all of you for coming.
You know, when Oliver calls me
a son to Starling City...
it feels like the literal truth.
I was a street orphan,
and this city raised me as one of its own.
I am the man that I am today
because of my Starling City family.
So it's time that I start to give back.
So thank you all for your support.
Nice speech, Ollie. I didn't know
you cared so much about politics.
Well, I care about the city...
and Sebastian has become
something of a friend.
He's got a way of doing that, apparently.
- That's very cute.
- Heh.
Speaking of which, how's Roy?
Oh, handsome, brooding, usual.
Why is my boyfriend
such a topic of interest?
Well, Thea, his idol
put an arrow in him.
I just wanted to make sure there
aren't any lingering issues.
Oh, my God.
Now that I think about it,
you know he did something
completely out of
character this morning.
- What?
- He showed up for work on time.
Heh.
Thea.
- It's just wonderful.
- Proud to do my civic duty.
No, I'm the one who's proud.
You've taken Oliver's hobby...
and turned it
into a successful business.
Hobby?
Oh, sweetheart.
- Oliver.
- Ah!
Thank you so much for your kind words.
I'm speaking the truth.
Forgive me, a friend just walked in.
- Hi.
Glad you could come.
Sebastian invited me.
Yes, I hear the two of you have been
spending a lot of time together.
We're just friends.
Does he know that?
Uh-oh. What's holding you back?
Sometimes I feel like
I don't know the real Sebastian.
He reminds me a little of you that way.
Hm.
Freedom.
Liberty.
Justice.
Long have the people...
of this city suffered
under the shackles of a corrupt government.
Slaves to self-interested politicians...
and their lobbyist puppeteers.
I declare war on them all.
Anyone in the building?
Cleaning crew and a group of bankers
working on a late-night deal.
- Can you patch me in to police and fire?
- I'm on it.
- Diggle.
- Hey, man, this is not my thing.
I can't get in there,
everything's locked.
We've still got people
on the fifth floor.
It's too hot. We're falling back.
Help! Gary's still back there.
Get to safety.
Give me your hand.
Thank you.
Hey.
You okay?
Where are you going?
To the plane. To get geared up.
For what?
Ivo is still out there.
I'm gonna find him, and when I do,
I'm gonna cut pieces off him.
You can't.
Ivo has a ship full of men, of killers.
I don't care what you did before.
You can't take them all out.
The only play here
is to find safe ground and wait him out.
Of course you would say that.
You were working for Ivo.
- You're probably still working for him.
- Hey. Hey!
- She's not.
- Get out of my way, kid.
You just need to take it easy.
- I said...
- Agh!
Get out of my way.
You okay? Long night.
Yeah. News reports say
the bomber didn't steal any money.
I think this guy just wants
to make a statement.
That went online an hour ago.
His manifesto. Three hundred
pages of anti-government hate.
You think this psycho is anyway connected
to our psycho in the skull mask?
This guy has
a completely separate agenda.
He's a lone wolf and we need to find him
before he finds his next target.
I'd start with the bomb.
Every one's unique.
Maybe we can get some
kind of signature on the guy.
But the bomb residue's with the SCPD.
Fortunately, we have an in
with one of the officers at the department.
I thought you were staying
in Central City for a few more days.
I got a newsletter about the bombing.
Caught the first train out this morning.
Good.
We need you here.
How's Barry?
He's still sleeping.
I prefer sleeping to coma
because coma sounds, you know...
not fun.
I'll reach out to Detective Lance.
Hey.
Did we have a lunch today?
No, I was just in the neighborhood.
- Thought I'd stop by.
- Ah.
But if this is a bad time,
I mean, I can always come back.
No, not at all.
They're still setting up out there.
Wow.
This is pretty impressive
for a street orphan.
Are you suggesting I spread it on
a bit too thick last night?
No, it's just...
Laurel, if there's something on your mind,
give it voice.
I don't bite. I promise.
- You know my father's with the department.
- Yes.
He said the suspect that
he was investigating
when he and his partner
were attacked was...
a man named Cyrus Gold.
Cyrus Gold...
was a preacher
at the orphanage where I was raised.
Cyrus was a very good friend to me,
like an older brother.
Or even a father figure,
to be honest.
He was the first person I said a word to...
and this was after a month
of not speaking at all.
You talk a lot about being an orphan.
But you don't talk about your parents.
Did you know them?
My father was a very unhappy man.
One night, he came home...
soaked in whiskey.
He lost his job again...
so he broke her arm.
I tried to stop him, but he threw me off.
The next thing I saw was my mother
holding my father's gun in her hand.
And I watched her shoot him.
She panicked.
Ran, and was gone
before the police even arrived.
That was the last time I saw my parents.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know...
why Cyrus' life took the turn
that it did, I'm sad to say.
All I know...
is that he helped a very young,
very frightened boy find his voice again.
Ahem. I'm sorry.
More later?
Didn't hear you come in.
Yeah, sorry, I got here early.
I just wanna get these crates unpacked
before lunch.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just haven't been sleeping much lately.
I got a lot on my mind.
You wanna talk about it?
- Talk about what?
- Whatever's been going on with you...
the last five weeks.
- I'm fine.
- Ever since the Arrow shot you...
you've been acting really weird, Roy,
with me, with everything.
This isn't about the Arrow.
- Is it me?
- Unh.
Is it us?
Look, I just really wanna
get through this, okay?
Okay. Let me know
if there's anything I can do to help.
Thea.
Heh.
You do help.
Every day.
Honestly, right now, you're the only thing
that's keeping me together.
I do what I can.
How did I get to be so lucky?
- You stole my purse.
- Mm.
Roy?
Thea. You okay?
Your arm.
That looks really deep.
It might need stitches. Um...
I'm gonna go downstairs and
get the first aid kit, okay?
Okay.
You know, most cops, they meet their
informants in the backseat of a cruiser...
or maybe a coffee shop
or something.
- What's with the mask?
- Gift from a friend.
- You got friends?
- Did you bring me what I asked for?
That's a sample of everything
the CSU collected from the blast.
There's melted glass,
multiple explosion fragments...
trace residue that looks like
nitroglycerine.
Which means that we're dealing with
more than just a basement nutjob.
Someone with training.
Thank you, detective.
I need a favor too.
The son of a bitch
who killed my men, my partner...
He's dead.
But whoever tipped him off and told him
we were coming, he's doing just fine.
What do you need?
Cell phone records for every cop
in my precinct.
You think there's a leak in the department?
I think those phone records are
the only way to know for sure,
and your blonde friend, she is
pretty good with computers.
I'll ask her...
DC-52 to Central, 10-80, downtown.
He's hit again.
- Starling City Municipal Building.
- Gimme a location.
I'll give you one better.
I'm checking the surrounding cell towers.
There was a GSM spike of 3800 megahertz
two seconds before the blast.
That frequency is way outside the
approved frequency for U.S. carriers.
Signal's moving.
I think he's mobile.
Give me an intersection.
Right in front of you, 400 meters.
I see him.
Turn left on 67th.
Felicity, I've lost him.
What?
Me too. Hold on.
Got him. Bank left on Gerrard Street.
You're almost on top of him.
It's not him, Felicity.
You picked up the wrong signal.
What? I thought...
He must have scrambled the signal.
It doesn't matter.
He's gone.
What happened?
He's using cellular technology
to detonate his bombs.
Clearly his expertise extends to
obscuring that signal.
Felicity, your expertise
was supposed to trump his.
Excuse me?
If you have something
to say to me, Oliver, say it.
People are dying. So I'd like you
to pull your head out of Central City...
and get back in the game.
Sure, right after you get
yours out of your ass.
- Excuse me?
- All right.
- Maybe we should just take a breath here.
- No, wait, I wanna know.
What exactly was that crack
about Central City meant to imply?
When the first bomb went off,
you weren't here.
And when the second bomb went off,
you sent me the wrong way.
After you didn't catch
him in the first place.
Don't blame me
because you didn't have it tonight.
I need some air.
At the risk of me getting
my head knocked off,
playing the blame game
is not gonna help us...
catch this son of a bitch.
Neither is doing things halfway.
Is that what you think's
going on here, Oliver?
You think she was distracted,
she wasn't giving it her all?
She almost ran me into a bus, Diggle.
What do you think?
I think you didn't have a
problem with Felicity's
performance until she
met Barry Allen.
I'm sorry.
You're not well, Slade.
It's the Mirakuru.
It's messing with your head.
It's gonna be dark soon.
We should make camp.
Yeah. What's going on? You okay?
Yeah, arm still hurts when it's cold, and
I lost the pain meds the doctor gave me.
- How's yours healing up?
- You know, good days and bad.
Yeah. That's gonna help.
I'll see you later.
- Hey.
- Pretty crazy.
Yeah, you doing all right?
I thought I could use your
help if you have a second.
You being at the D.A.'s
office now, it's almost
like you joined the
family business, come on.
I'm trying to find someone
named Maya Resik.
I've searched the internet, the D.M.V.
records, social security, nothing.
- Why are you looking for a ghost?
- Sebastian's paying her bills.
A woman who doesn't seem to exist,
I find that suspicious.
Thinking that your
boyfriend's up to no good,
that's typically more
my thing than yours.
He's not exactly my boyfriend.
Then that makes digging into his life
a little less fun then.
Hey, Laurel, I bring you something back,
you know I'm gonna wanna know why.
Of course you are.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are about to join
Sebastian Blood's press conference.
Oh, you're just in time to see the show.
- What's he doing?
- Bringing the city together.
And if I'm not mistaken, campaigning.
Tomorrow night, I am holding Starling's
first-ever unity rally at City Plaza.
We're going to show the world
that the people of this great city...
will not back down to terrorists.
He's committing suicide and he
just invited the city to join him.
Sebastian's your friend.
Can't you talk him out of this, Oliver?
- But that ends now.
- Well, he won't listen to me.
Sebastian Blood?
This rally tomorrow night...
you need to call it off.
The Starling City vigilante paying a visit
to wave me off.
I'm flattered.
This event, Mr. Blood, you might as well be
painting a giant bull's-eye on your chest.
This city needs to come together.
And I need to show them how.
You won't be able to show them anything
if you're dead.
Every night, you risk your life
for the people of this city.
How can you expect me to do any less?
And what about the lives of the people
coming to your rally?
This rally is about Starling
City standing up and
declaring with one voice that
living afraid isn't living.
I won't send a contrary message to people
telling them to stay home, to stay scared.
I've made my decision.
That's the thing, alderman.
Whatever happens tomorrow night...
it's not up to you.
Ah, Mrs. Fazekas.
A train set for your nephew just came in.
He's gonna love it.
Oh, you are a miracle worker, Mr.
Scheffer.
How much do I owe you?
Fifty dollars even.
Forget the sales tax.
Are you going to the Alderman's
unity rally tomorrow night?
Oh, I wouldn't miss it.
Gathered here despite the rash of
bombings that have plagued the city.
Some have called Sebastian Blood's unity
rally a cynical and dangerous P.R. stunt...
for his mayoral campaign,
but the crowd continues to grow.
I tried to get him to stand down.
He's as stubborn as you
when it comes to fighting back.
Or everything.
Is this how it's gonna be
with youn two from now on?
Maybe we should just
head down to the rally.
Maybe we won't have to.
I analyzed the bomb remnants
we got from Lance.
Design's identical to
the bombs used by an
anti-government militia
group called The Movement.
Lucky for us, they have a very active
and hackable message board.
One of their fans has an IP address
right here in Starling.
- Tell me.
- The Computer's in a local souvenir shop.
The wackadoo in question
goes by the username Shrapnel.
You want backup?
No, I need you at the rally.
Cover our bases.
Is this all for me?
No, for me, SCPD phone records.
Why are you going through
the department's phone records?
Um, so I checked up
on your not-exactly boyfriend.
And, did you find anything?
Yeah, it turns out he's a hell of a guy.
He covers the expenses of his dear aunt,
your Maya Resik.
If Sebastian has other family,
then why was he placed in an orphanage?
Well, maybe because aunt Maya is nuttier
than a Snickers bar.
She's a patient at St. Walker's Hospital.
That's a mental institution, it's
the kind you don't check out of.
Now listen, are you gonna tell me
what this is all about?
Something about him just seems off.
Laurel, there's nothing sinister
about a guy...
who's covering the expenses
of his only living relative.
The truth is it's kind of nice.
Listen, I've gotta get to City Plaza.
Pike wants all hands at this unity rally.
- You're not going, right?
- No, I need to look into this more.
Laurel, he seems like a good guy,
and you deserve good, okay?
So stop looking for reasons
to talk yourself out of it.
Please.
Alderman Blood, is this not dangerous?
Why are you gathering all these
people here to be targets?
I'll get to all of your
questions later, I promise.
Thank you all for coming.
Boom.
You're dead.
Or will be, if you take one more step
or move a single muscle.
And then you'll miss the show.
Candidate Blood's unity rally.
Already rigged with 50 pounds
of R.D.X. high explosives.
Not unlike what's packed
inside the drywall of my store.
This city thinks Sebastian Blood
can keep them safe.
Tonight, they'll learn the only thing politicians
care about protecting is their jobs.
- Felicity.
- Here.
- Did you get him?
- No.
He said he rigged the plaza
with an explosive device.
Oliver, it's crazy town here,
that bomb could be anywhere.
- I can narrow that down. Get me Diggle.
- Go.
Shrapnel said he rigged
the perimeter with R.D.X.
I'm on it.
- You're heading to the plaza too, right?
- Not yet.
I need you to pull me up anything you can
on the store.
Blueprints, permits, schematics, anything.
- What's going on?
- Shrapnel left behind a surprise.
He said he packed the drywall with
explosives, but the trigger needs to be...
Would need to be hooked
to some sort of a power supply.
That's assuming the detonator's
connected to the stores electricity...
and not something independent
like a car battery. I know.
Not helpful. You sure you want me doing this?
My head might not exactly be in the game.
- Felicity.
- That building was built in the '70s.
That's good news.
The wiring in a lot of construction
back then is defective.
So, if you sever one
wire, it'll blow fuses
in the building, shut
off power to the bomb.
Hold tight, I see a fuse box.
Oliver, be careful.
Oliver?
It's all right, I'm all right.
Get to the rally.
Help Diggle. I'm on my way.
Thea, I really don't think coming here
was a good idea.
It's gonna be fine, let's just go find Roy.
Please, please.
You're the ones who deserve an ovation.
Eight months ago,
this city survived a devastating attack.
But we rose up.
You rose up and banded together
just like we are tonight.
Dig, I'm on site.
I'm on the east side. I
think I found the trigger.
And proved to the world
that we cannot be broken.
That the people of this
city are too strong.
And that no bomb and no earthquake
is strong enough to tear us apart.
Oliver said that the
whole place was rigged
with explosives. It's
in the sound equipment.
This is the trigger.
Shrapnel activates it
by cellular transmission.
Listen, we don't have to disarm it,
just disable it.
I can do that.
I think. I hope.
Felicity, be careful.
He probably put in a safeguard.
Tampering with it will set
off a dead-man switch.
That is a thoroughly depressing term.
And a little bit sexist.
Step away.
Or we all know how this ends.
Dig!
Mom.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Drop the bow.
I've got charges planted all over Starling.
I drop this stick, they all blow.
- Did you just hear what I said?
- Yep.
Hey, how's your mom?
She's fine, just a little shaken up.
You saved her.
- I got lucky.
- That wasn't luck.
It was impossible.
You know those stories of moms lifting cars
to save their kids?
Things you can do when adrenaline hits?
It was one of those.
Your arm.
There's not even a mark.
- I heal fast. It's fine.
- Roy...
I'm kind of tired.
It's been a long night, you know?
I gotta go.
Roy.
With you dropping fewer bodies, Starling
City should probably build a bigger jail.
Another night of skull mask hunting?
Not exactly.
- How's your shoulder?
- Oh, just a through-and-through.
- Walk in the park.
- Still, Diggle.
You should go home and get some rest.
I'm sorry.
Were you apologizing to me,
or were you talking to your quiver?
I didn't snap at my quiver.
- You kind of more than snapped.
- I know.
And I'm sorry.
I understand that this Mirakuru thing
has you freaked out.
And I have been in Central City a lot.
Felicity, it's not that.
When you are there...
Well, it just made me realize
how much I need you here.
In the beginning, I was just gonna
do all of this by myself.
And now, with you and Diggle...
I rely on you.
Well, does that mean I have a shot
at employee of the month?
No.
Because you're not my employee.
You're my partner.
Barry's gonna wake up.
And when he does, you will be there.
I finally have a guy who's
interested in me...
and he's struck by lightning...
ends up in a coma, typical.
Well, maybe he's dreaming about you.
Actually, there's conflicting cases...
about whether coma
patients can in fact dream
normally, or they're
more like hallucinating.
Thank you.
Sara.
Sara, I know you're listening. Answer me.
This is very simple, Sara.
I know you and your new friends
have the Mirakuru.
You know I will lay waste
to this entire island to get it.
- Get Slade.
- But it doesn't have to be that way.
All I want is the serum.
In exchange, I'll promise you and your friends
safe passage off this island, I promise.
Within 10 days, you and your new friends
could be making port in Shanghai.
The alternative is I send my men
into the jungle to take the serum from you.
They'll be under orders
not to kill any of you.
Instead, you'll remain alive enough
for me to indulge my, um...
scientific curiosity.
Think about it, Sara.
He's gone.
What?
Slade's gone. And he took
the Mirakuru with him.
You can ask all the questions you want, but
I wouldn't count on getting anything back.
She probably won't even know you're there.
I'll be down the hall if you need anything.
Maya.
I'm here to talk about your nephew.
Maya, my name is Laurel Lance.
Maya, I'm here to talk about your nephew.
Maya?
Maya, Que chico?
Que chico, Sebastian?
Sebastian.
Yes, yes.
Sebastian Blood.
There will always be those who seek
to harm us, but it will not weaken us.
It will only make us stronger.
Well done, alderman.
Thanks to you.
It was still a very big risk to take.
Heh.
Tonight, we both stood
up for Starling City.
You and me...
we can save this city...
if we work together.
Maya, can you talk to me about Sebastian?
It's okay, you can trust me, it's okay.
Sebastian's my friend.
Sebastian is the devil.
He's the one who put me here.
He made everybody think I'm insane.
But why would he do that?
He killed his father.
And I was there.
I saw it.
What?
Oh, my God.
Sebastian isn't your nephew.
He's your son.
Don't trust what he says.
You can't trust Sebastian Blood.