This season on "Arrow"...
The only way I know
how to fight the darkness
is to be darkness,
and I don't want to be
that type of person anymore.
I'm running for mayor.
And I promise you
that I will never
stop fighting
to save this city.
You're all fretting
about this city dying.
I'm here on behalf
of an organization
that wants you
to let it die.
I'm Damien Darhk.
The type of magic
he's using,
I've seen it take
good people
and turn them dark.
If I don't
make it off this island,
you will go to Russia
and find my parents.
If Darhk wins,
Laurel died for nothing.
If you can channel
light and hope,
you will be able
to repel Darhk's magic.
Do you remember
what I promised you?
A new beginning.
Darhk plans
to burn the world
in a nuclear fire.
I'm assuming you know
what Rubicon is.
And I'm assuming it's
under Mr. Darhk's control.
Every NATO Ally--
Rubicon has control over
all their nuclear systems.
You mean
HIVE does.
If even one
of those nukes hits...
He will be
unstoppable.
- I think it worked.
- It worked.
Rubicon's offline.
Ha ha ha!
Do you need a moment?
No? Good.
Because I need you
to do me a favor.
Go to hell.
Why bother?
I'm going to bring it to us.
Get the hell
out of here.
Mom, stop.
- Oh, my God!
- Mom, get back!
This is your mother?
Oh, goodie.
Persuading you to help me
is going to be easier
than I thought.
Helping you
do what?
Your underground city's
already been destroyed.
I'm still going forward.
So, what,
you kill my mother
if I don't help you
destroy the world?
Newsflash--my mother
lives in the world.
Dying instantaneously
in nuclear fire,
rather painless,
and then there's
having your life force
slowly sucked out
like this.
Mom!
What's it going to be,
miss Smoak?
Look. I know you don't
live here anymore,
but those were
nice windows.
So unoriginal.
I am now powered
by the deaths
of tens of thousands
of souls.
There is nothing
you can do to stop me...
Or should I say, "us."
Stop!
You let them go,
or I kill
your daughter.
Do you think
I'm bluffing?
Let my daughter go.
It's ok, sweetheart.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Are you ok?
When did this
become your life?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God,
it's gone.
He took it.
It's gone.
What's gone?
The laptop with
the anti-Rubicon program.
If Darhk has that...
He can launch all of the world's
nuclear missiles.
♪ Arrow 4x23 ♪
Schism
Original Air Date on May 25, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Looks like
internal bleeding.
Possibly broken ribs.
Hemothorax.
We have to relieve
the pressure. Thea.
Felicity, we need you
at your station.
We have to stop Rubicon.
Is he going to be ok?
Put the gun down,
Reiter.
Aah!
Oh!
You think you can kill me,
miss Venediktov?
I am going to kill you.
You'll only kill
yourself in the attempt.
Without these runes,
the idol's power would
overwhelm my mind.
I don't care.
It's worth it to stop you.
See that, Reiter?
That plane filled
with all those people
you were keeping
prisoner?
They're getting away.
This is over!
That's not all of them,
Mr. Queen.
The plane's too small.
And it's not over.
Ohh!
All those deaths,
they give me power,
and her...Only madness.
Aah!
How is he?
Well, he's stable.
John said the next 30 minutes
should tell us...
Whether or not
he'll make it?
Yeah.
Hey, can I ask you
something?
I know it might not
be the best time.
Back at our place--
my place--
the--the place--
the loft...
Yeah.
Darhk's magic,
it worked on you.
I thought--
you thought I found
a way to stop it.
That was before
he grew so powerful.
It was the--
the hope you had in me
was able to counteract his magic.
And now my hope's
not enough.
So where are we?
Um, good news,
bad news time.
Good news is is that Darhk hasn't
launched the nukes yet.
I think his hacker's
still trying
to break our failsafes.
Ok, and the bad news?
Well, the bad news is
that with Rubicon offline,
there is nothing
for me to hack into.
Right, but your laptop
has to have a GPS--
- yeah.
- I'm sure that you've already
started to try and do it.
Yeah.
I thought you'd
shut Rubicon down.
Felicity is working
on locating the laptop.
Where's Sara?
She's fine.
She's in an Argus bunker
in Coast City.
With Darhk's anti-nuke
bunker destroyed,
why is he moving
forward with Genesis?
Machin killed his wife.
Well, his daughter still
lives in this world.
He must know that.
He knows, he just--
he doesn't care.
He's lost all hope.
Yeah, just like
all of us.
Wait. I thought he
was the cynic.
It's not like John doesn't have
a point, Thea.
We are not finished yet.
The key word
being "yet."
I got a 20
on the laptop.
Downtown, abandoned
office building.
Let's move.
Overwatch,
there's no one here.
That's impossible.
You're right on top
of the GPS signal.
She's right.
Oh, my God.
Overwatch.
I see it.
Just over 15,000
ballistic missiles,
and they all just launched.
How much time do we have?
Two hours.
Maybe less.
Confirmed.
15,434 birds in the air.
We need to set
defense condition one
and get the president
down to the PEOC.
Felicity.
He's got me
completely locked out.
Ok, how many
missiles are there?
DOD's
working on it,
but the targets
are worldwide.
You said that we
have two hours.
The world has two hours,
but I'm tracking
a Minuteman ICBM
heading straight
for Star City.
It just launched out
of Warren Air Force Base in Colorado.
Ok, well, that's close.
Which means we only
have 45 minutes.
Taiana.
I'm ok.
I think...I'm ok.
Taiana?
All right,
where's the fire?
What's this?
The safest place
within 100 miles
to survive a nuclear attack.
Based on wind patterns--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
What are you
talking about?
The world is going
to end in two hours.
I need you to take
my mother there.
Can you do that?
Yeah, I will.
Sara, on phone:
Bye, daddy. Bye, mama.
We'll see you
soon, sweetie.
I love you, baby girl.
Argus has a chopper waiting
to take us to Coast City,
so at least we'll
all be together.
If we can't stop the...
The end of the world.
In these situations,
you're usually the one
offering hope.
I'm fresh out, Lyla.
Because of what
happened with Andy?
It was self-defense, John.
It was a clean kill.
Lyla.
Are you having Argus
move on city hall?
John told me the source
of Darhk's power is there,
that he might be looking
to harness the deaths
from the nuclear attacks.
No, he's already
done that
with the first attack.
He will decimate
your team.
You should
pull them back.
And what if his hacker's
down there with him?
Cooper Seldon is not
going to be anywhere
that we think to look.
He'll be in a secure
location.
If your team
goes down there,
they will all die.
It's not your call,
Oliver.
It's mine.
I don't like
this place.
It's scary.
Hey...
It's just a little bit
longer, sweetheart.
I miss mommy.
I do, too.
But we're going
to see her soon.
Assault team sledgehammer
has engaged target.
Switching you
to their feed now.
Turn it off.
Those missiles hit,
and he's going to become
even stronger, isn't he?
He already is with the souls
of all of those Argus agents
that he just killed.
Wait.
I'm in. I'm through
Cooper's firewalls.
Well, shut it down.
That's what
I'm trying to--
Aah!
Look at me.
Listen to me.
Don't let it
control your mind.
Yaah!
You are a murderer.
You killed my brother.
You are darkness.
Yes...I am...
But you--you don't
have to be.
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
I can feel it
burning my mind.
Taiana, we will find a way
to work around this.
There is only one way.
You have to kill me,
Oliver.
With Mayor Adams
missing and presumed dead,
Deputy Mayor Remz
called for calm
in the wake
of unconfirmed reports
that a nuclear attack
on our city is imminent.
Newly assigned police captain
Frank Pike asks...
Just when things
couldn't get any worse.
Is everyone all right?
I think "all right"
is a relative term.
How much time
do we have?
I think 27 minutes.
It's kind of hard
to tell now.
I wonder what Laurel would
have thought of all this.
Well, she probably would
have said something
about finding a solution
no matter what.
Yeah. She's always
stubborn like that.
Too bad she would have
been wrong this time.
Hey, come on.
We can't just lose
all hope here.
You have.
I can see it
in your eyes.
I just can't believe
that I thought
that I'd be the one
to unite this city
while Damien Darhk
was trying to kill it.
That was arrogant.
It was the same arrogance
that made me feel like
I could be the Green Arrow
without descending
into darkness.
Bottom line,
it was foolish.
You don't believe that.
I didn't believe that...
Until Laurel died.
I thought you weren't
blaming yourself
for her death anymore.
We made a decision
to come back here.
I tried to do things
differently,
and for a time, I did.
And now I am left here
to wonder if I hadn't,
would Laurel
still be alive?
Curtis.
You shouldn't be up.
Tell me about it.
Someone's got to provide
a little optimism.
Doesn't seem like
anyone around here
is in the head-space
to do it.
Then you know we've
lost the city.
No.
I know that you're running
out of time to get it back.
Look.
Living in Star City
requires a special
kind of tenacity.
A sane person
wouldn't live here.
It's a fact that Paul likes
to remind me of weekly.
We were this close
to leaving Star City last October.
After 3 terrorist attacks,
we were done,
but then the night
before we were going to start packing,
the Green Arrow
popped up on our TV,
and he reminded me
that this city
is worth saving,
that my home--
that my home was
worth fighting for.
That guy gave me
inspiration.
He gave me hope.
And if he could
give me hope then,
why can't he give it
to others now?
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Please.
I know what you're
feeling right now.
I'm feeling it, too,
the sense of--
of helplessness,
of hopelessness.
I don't know
how we even begin
to process what might
happen to us right now,
but there are a few things
that I do know.
I know that this city
has been through
tough times before,
and we have pulled
through.
We survived
the Undertaking.
We survived the Siege.
We survived
the Outbreak,
and somehow, someway,
we will survive this.
A friend of mine told me
that living in Star City,
it takes a special kind
of tenacity,
but we do live here,
because this is our home.
This is our home!
It is our friend,
our family, our lives,
and we will not--
we will not
throw those precious
gifts away
by descending into chaos.
We will look
to each other for hope.
We will cling to each other
for strength,
and if we do that,
no matter what happens,
then we can all
stand here united.
Oh, my God. It's here.
That's terrifying...
And also kind of great.
I think you got hit
on the head harder
than you realize.
No, no, he's right.
I can't hack this system.
But if the nuke
gets close enough, which it is...
We could use
the line-of-sight attack
on the missile itself
and disarm it.
Still not getting a signal.
Are you sure you're pointing
that thing at the nuke?
It's pretty hard
to miss, Felicity.
Ok, ok, ok.
I'm just going--oh!
Whatever you changed,
don't change it again.
It's working.
I got a signal.
I didn't change anything!
Nukes are designed
to detonate
100 feet above
their actual target.
I'm uploading a GPS
spoof to disable it.
Great...
But, um, it's still
heading straight for us.
Just keep pointing
the IR receiver at the thingy.
You know, I have
perfect confidence in your abilities.
- Thank you.
- But just in case,
working with you
and the rest of the team
has been the highlight
of my professional career
and my entire life,
and--and I can't think
of any better way
for it to end than--
Curtis,
as sweet as this is,
the talking's
really not helping.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
it worked! Ohh!
Whatever you guys just
did was incredible.
We only took down
one nuke.
We still have 15,433
to go, give or take.
The code to
the line-of-sight hack,
can you distro
it to everybody?
I'm on it.
All right, that's one.
1 nuke in 15,000.
The chances of us
getting them all is--
1 in 375 million.
Well, we need to find
Darhk's hacker
and shut down Rubicon
at the source.
When we disarmed
the nuke,
we gained access
to its onboard computer
and cloned
its hard drive remotely.
Then we ran a back trace
to determine the source
of the initial
launch signal.
He's holed up
in a warehouse
on the corner
of Cheswold and Crombie.
Let's get after him.
That was quite
a speech, Oliver.
It made me long
for a voting booth.
You and Thea need
to back up Curtis and Felicity
while they deal
with Seldon.
Hey, what are you
going to do?
I'm going to city hall.
Oliver, you
yourself said
going after Darhk
is a suicide mission.
Well, John, I'm not
going to die tonight.
Well, let me go
with you, back you up.
If things go bad,
I need you
to back the city up.
Oliver, things aren't
going to go bad.
Your speech...
Inspired all of us, too.
Let's move.
Do it, Oliver.
Please, do it quickly.
Taiana.
I'm not going
to kill you--
Then I will kill you.
Don't you understand?
Please!
Before I kill whoever
is left on this island,
before I become worse
than Reiter, please.
Please don't ask
me to do this.
If you ever
cared for me,
then you would do this.
Don't forget
your promise.
I won't.
Taiana, I'm sorry.
It's ok, it's ok.
You killed her!
I thought you were
staying behind.
Yeah, it doesn't mean
I shouldn't be prepared.
I'm not going to ask
if you're all right.
I think I know
the answer.
Lyla, this isn't the right
time for this conversation.
When the Ghosts
attacked, you froze.
I've never seen you
do that before.
Lyla, I can't talk
about this.
Was it Andy?
- He was a Ghost.
- Lyla.
If the world's
going to end,
then let's
at least go out
being honest
with each other.
Yes, it was Andy.
But not like I said
and not like you think.
Earlier you said
it was a good kill.
It wasn't, Lyla.
I said it was
self-defense.
It wasn't.
You must think
I'm a monster.
Fog of war, Johnny.
You did what
you had to do.
It's that simple.
Lyla, there's nothing
simple about this.
Darhk!
What does a guy
have to do
to end the world
in peace?
Why is he here, Daddy?
Oh, he came here
to die, sweetheart.
Clearly.
Ha ha ha!
15 minutes till
the end of the world,
and you want
to spend them with me.
I am touched.
Yeah, it looks like
the hacker's here.
Thanks, unless you
were aiming at me.
At this point,
I honestly can't tell.
Even if you stop me,
even if you could,
those missiles are
finding their targets.
This is a mercy killing
on a global scale.
I'm sparing my daughter
the pain of growing up
without her mother.
Or Mr. Lance living
without Laurel.
And don't get me
started on your pain.
Let him go!
Get out.
For real?
- Get out of here.
- Get out!
Get out
of our town!
We don't want you here!
Get out of this town!
"Get out." Heh heh heh.
This heartwarming display
would mean
a whole lot more
had I not just
seen you all
tearing yourselves
and your city apart.
Aah!
That is why I did this.
Humanity is feckless,
and I wanted
to cleanse it
of a millennia
worth of rot
it has been infected by,
and I will do it!
No, you won't.
Ok, just for fun,
how are you going
to stop me?
Because it won't just be me
who's going to stop you.
It's not so easy
without the magic, is it?
Oh, I don't need magic.
I'm a former member
of the League of Assassins,
or have you
forgotten that?
Remind me.
Oh, my God.
Cooper.
Hey, Felicity.
How you doing?
Who shot you?
Guess.
He's moving the bullet
closer and closer
to my spine.
I said it hurt so bad,
I'd do anything
to make him stop.
Like blow up the planet?
Sorry, I'm
a selfish bastard,
but she knew that
already.
I need a moment
alone with him.
Felicity, I don't
think right--
Now.
I'm sorry, Felicity.
I know I should be
strong enough
to pull myself away
from this keyboard,
but I think we both
know that I'm not.
You are.
He's powerful.
He's so powerful,
and if I stop Rubicon,
he'll know,
and he'll kill me
in the most painful way possible.
You're better
than this, Cooper.
You're stronger than this.
You can still do
the right thing.
You can still be
the man that I loved.
I haven't been that guy
in a long time.
Remember what we wanted
to do 7 years ago
in that cockroach-infested
dorm room?
Save the world.
Now's your chance.
Mr. Seldon,
you weak-willed dust mite.
I'm sorry, Cooper.
Oh.
You brought friends.
That's ok.
So did I.
What the hell
happened?
Darhk.
We have 3 minutes
to take down 15,000 nukes.
Why isn't this
a simple matter
of flicking off a switch?
Rubicon has safeguards
for their safeguards.
I can't disarm a warhead.
Then don't.
I don't think
you understand how this works.
It's not the warheads.
It's just the missile.
If we invert
their horizons...
They'll explode
in space.
Agh!
Now you know how it feels.
Wait. I thought you
and Donna--
Don't worry, she's safe,
but I had to come back
to stand with my city,
because this
Oliver Queen guy
gives a hell
of a speech.
You two were supposed
to stay as backup.
I already lost one brother.
You two put down
the Ghosts.
You keep people safe.
What about Darhk?
Darhk's mine.
What are you going
to do now, Oliver?
Stop the posturing.
We both know that
you can't do it.
You spared the life
of the man who
killed your mother.
And you killed
a friend of mine.
You killed tens of thousands
of innocent people.
With Slade Wilson,
I had a choice.
This time, I don't.
It's going to take
forever to clean this place up.
Well, I wish you guys
the best of luck with that.
You going home
to my mama?
Uh, yeah, to pack.
We're leaving town
for a while.
Wait, why?
IAB reached out.
My suspension is
no longer a suspension,
but, uh, it's funny,
you know,
because, you know,
being a cop's all I ever wanted,
but when I got that call,
I didn't feel a thing.
All I could think
about was Laurel, you know?
But then you got
her justice, Oliver,
and you got me
some closure,
and I am never going
to forget that.
Well, this is going
to make me feel
like I'm piling on...
What do you mean?
Well, I...
I jumped straight out
of the Lazarus Pit
right into this,
into--to Speedy,
but, um, I've just
been wondering
if this is even
who I really am,
and then I threatened
to kill a little girl,
and I--I realized I'm
my father's daughter,
so I--I thought
about Laurel
and--and what she'd say
to me if she were here.
I think she'd tell me
to get out...
Before I lost
too much of myself.
I'm sorry, Ollie.
Hey. Come here.
You don't have
to apologize to me, ever.
Well, it looks like
it's just the 3 of us.
Team Arrow,
the original gangstas.
Up top.
You ok?
Not really.
I told Lyla the truth
about Andy.
What'd she say?
She's a soldier.
She understood.
But I don't, and I don't
think I ever will.
What are you
going to do?
Take some time
away from this team,
away from the city...
To figure out where
I went off track
and how to get back on.
John, I have never
done this without you.
You're the one
who keeps me in line.
Oliver, I don't know
if you've been watching lately,
but it's been
the other way around, man.
She begged me to do it.
Agh!
Listen, I know that this
is not going to make
a ton of sense,
but all of this
has to do with that.
It is darkness.
Taiana...
She was coming
to that darkness.
They destroyed the plane.
That was Reiter.
But there's another way
off the island.
And here
I thought
you'd never use
the comm gear I gave you
to radio
for a trip home.
Well, I lost it
for a while,
and the job wasn't done.
And now it is.
I sent you here to break
up Reiter's operation
and free his prisoners.
You did both.
You saved
a lot of lives.
I took some, too.
Do you remember
what I told you?
That the only way
out is through?
Well, I am not out,
Amanda.
I'm still filled
with darkness.
This was never
about expunging your darkness,
Mr. Queen.
That darkness will
always be part of you.
Then what was the point?
To show you
that sometimes killing
is the only path
to justice.
Director Waller,
what do you want to do
with the artifact?
Have it transported
to the SLAB.
Yes, ma'am.
So that's it.
Just going to bag
and tag everything
and pretend like
nothing ever happened?
You've seen what
that idol can do,
how large
the world truly is.
Speaking of...
What am I going
to do with this?
Our business here
is concluded, Mr. Queen.
Unless it's not.
As I said, justice
requires killing.
A man of your talents
could be useful
in hot spots
across the globe,
or you could just go back
to playing vigilante.
Neither.
I have a promise to keep.
I know you wouldn't
approve of what I did.
I mean, I know that
it's not what...
You would have wanted,
me killing Darhk,
but you were always
better than me, Laurel.
That is what I loved
most about you.
You ok?
No.
It's Thea and John.
Them leaving
has to be a blow.
And they're leaving
because of their own
personal darkness.
I just can't help
but think
that maybe they were
infected by mine.
Maybe.
Like you said, maybe you
can't become a hero
without succumbing
to the darkness
even a little bit,
but you were able
to defeat Darhk
by giving the city
its hope back.
You're saying it's
not black and white?
I'm saying that
there is a man
who killed Darhk
in cold blood,
and that same man
stood on top of a car
and gave the city
its hope back.
What you're feeling
isn't darkness.
It's a schism.
You're at war with two
sides of yourself.
Hello.
Mr. Queen,
this is Thomas Kemp.
I chair
the city council.
Yes, of course, councilman.
What can I help you with?
That impromptu speech
you gave
during the city's
latest crisis
got a lot of people's
attention,
and there's something
I'd like to talk to you about.
It's only an interim
appointment.
A proper election
will be held in August,
but given that you got
48% of the vote before
as a write-in candidate,
well, I think that's
just a formality.
I appreciate the optimism.
Are you sure
about this?
You look,
well, conflicted.
Well, someone
very close to me
recently told me
that I am...
But I am ready for this.
Good.
Shall we?
Put your left hand
on the Bible.
Raise your right hand
and recite the oath.
I, Oliver Queen,
do solemnly swear
to support the charter
and laws of Star City
and to faithfully
and impartially
perform and discharge
the duties
of the office of mayor
according to the law
and to the very best
of my ability.
Congratulations.
I didn't know
you'd be here.
You thought
I was leaving, too?
Not a chance.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.