Previously, on "Arrow"...
I'm going to run for mayor.
Mr. Palmer's last
recorded statement
could shed some light
on how he died.
Ahh!
What's happening to me?
We're going
to Nanda Parbat.
You need to feed this impulse.
Once you do, it will
subside for a time.
I want you
to bring my sister back to life.
Even if Sara
went into the Pit,
what came out of the Pit
would not be Sara.
Your daughter is alive.
The most loving act
you can commit
is to return Sara
to her final rest.
You are not going
to kill your own daughter.
She's not my daughter!
Sara?
Ohh, damn it!
Hey, honey.
Why don't you just
leave that right there?
Get off, bitch.
Oh, my God, thank you!
Hal Ha-tha An-tea?
SCPD! Stay where you are.
♪ Arrow 4x05 ♪
Haunted
Original Air Date on November 4, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I cannot thank you enough
for coming on board, Alex.
Well, then it is a good thing
you're paying me, also.
Sorry for the wait.
Ollie, this is Alex Davis,
the new political strategist
that Walter recommended.
Old enough
to vote, Alex?
I owned a bar and I wasn't
even old enough to drink.
I am old enough
to do both.
Well, I'm glad that
you're joining the team,
but I don't entirely know why I need
a political strategist.
Well... I guess
the question then is,
do you want to take office with
ten percent of the vote or 90?
After you win, you still need
to be able to govern.
Well, what
has you concerned?
My lack of experience?
No, we can spin that.
No, I'm talking about the kind
of closet skeletons
that could cripple you on
your first day in office.
Your personal
Chappaquiddick.
Wait, like that game
from Harry Potter?
Uh, Chappaquiddick
was a scandal
involving
a can't-lose candidate
whose campaign fell apart when
he was caught having an affair
after his vehicle
went underwater
and the girl
he was with drowned.
Does that sound
at all familiar?
Ah, referencing
the "Queen's Gambit" and Sara Lance.
Yeah, got it.
You're about to do
your first on-air sit down, right?
Yeah.
Bethany Snow?
Ten'll get you twenty,
she brings up Sara and her sister.
Alex, all due respect,
I don't think that people care
about my friendship
with Laurel Lance
and an eight-year-old scandal
when the city
is disintegrating
and there are masked
armed men helping it.
Not to mention,
there's a woman in Pennytown
that's just running
around killing people.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
For a moment,
I forgot how the electorate
always cares about the issues
and has zero appetite
for scandal.
You want this city united?
You can't do it as the rich kid playboy
from the tabloids.
And like it or not, Laurel Lance
is a constant reminder of that.
So from this day forward,
when anyone brings up Miss Lance,
you distance
yourself from her.
Hey, just in time.
I was looking for you.
Why?
I want to talk to you
about something you forgot.
What's that?
Is that how you want
to play this?
It's fine by me,
pal. Let's go.
I don't appreciate
the intrusion, gentlemen.
There's communications
gear in here.
We got ourselves a mole.
You believe
it's Mr. Queen.
Look, we've been
on this island eight months
without a single problem.
He shows up; Suddenly two guys
find landmines
and a bunch of drugs go missing.
Yeah, Conklin, you got me.
I didn't, uh, wash up on shore here after
a boating accident;
I parachuted in
on a secret spy mission.
You want to die a liar,
that's fine by me.
Man, that's enough.
Enough! There are more pressing
matters at hand.
Perhaps if you were focused more
on external threats
rather than witch hunts,
you would have caught this man
spying on us
in the fields.
Oh, I wasn't spying, mate.
Any of you squabblers
got a cigarette?
She mumbled something.
It sounded, I don't know,
middle eastern?
All right, um, I'm going to
have you sit down
with a sketch
artist, ok?
Take care of that.
Dad.
Hey.
What happened?
You tell me.
These two bodies,
dropped by a woman.
Probably the same woman
that's been linked
to the murders of three other skels
in the past few days.
A blonde woman.
Dad, I--
I didn't know what
to make of it until tonight,
and then this woman
here, she suspects,
speaks some kind of
middle eastern language,
just like Sara.
Is she still at your place?
I've been
looking for her.
Why didn't you tell me,
huh?! You tell Queen?
No!
Because he would just see this
the same way as you.
Oh, yeah, and how is
that, huh? How is that?!
That Sara is
just... a thing
that needs
to be stopped.
This is my daughter.
Then why
did I find you
with a gun
pointed at her head?
I'm not proud
of that, Laurel.
But people are dying.
And if I pulled
that trigger,
maybe they wouldn't be.
I'm going to go find
Sara, and hopefully
I do before
you or Oliver.
Curtis, I need you
to do something for me.
Felicity,
look at me.
Gym clothes, gym bag--
do either of those
suggest
anything to you?
Physical fitness, but then
I remembered you're a tech guy.
I'm also a bronze
metal decathlete.
Bronze medal, huh?
Beijing, 2008.
Beijing, as in the Olympics?
Mr. Palmer's recording.
Did you play it?
Yes. There's something
off about it.
You sure it's not the fact that
it's a dying declaration from your ex?
I mean, that is some serious
Nicholas Sparks-level stuff.
Don't judge. The man
can write emotion.
No, not that.
I mean, yes, there's that,
but there's still some
artifacts playing
that shouldn't
be there.
What about your work-out?
Didn't seem to concern you
20 seconds ago.
Ray, on recording:
I'm sorry, Felicity, this is my fault.
You hear that?
Like there's more
to the recording.
Something
overlapping with it.
I was hoping you could
clean it up for me.
I mean,
after your workout.
It can wait. I'm glad you
changed your mind
about hearing
Mr. Palmer's final words.
Thank you, Curtis.
Ah, thank you for coming.
I think we both know
I didn't have too much choice.
No. Well,
certainly not since
you literally doubled the number
of daughters
I have
to hold over you.
Or did you
take my advice
and return Sara
to the grave?
You didn't take
my advice. Pity.
What do you want?!
Oh, a new beginning
for the world,
a nice glass
of Merlot--
not necessarily
in that order.
Oh!
And for you
to do me a favor.
There's a federal server farm
30 miles outside of the city.
I want you to gain access and plug
this little baby into one of the computers.
And what's this
thing going to do?
Oh, it's of
no concern of yours.
But don't worry.
It's not like
it's going to destroy
the city or anything.
Whatever that spa weekend did
to clear your head,
it also improved
your technique.
You're effortless.
Yeah, well, you know
how I love my
hot stone massages.
By the way, that political strategist
was a good call.
But his advice
was a little harsh.
I mean, distancing
yourself from Laurel?
I wasn't expecting that, bu
he made a few good points.
What, like kicking
your friends to the curb?
Well, my friendship
with Laurel is... complicated.
We have been in each other's
lives for like forever.
I mean, you have been
in love with Laurel and Sara,
and Laurel, she--
she took me in at CNRI
when I was completely lost.
Even Captain Lance, ok,
he has been there for us
since mom died.
Ok, but your point?
My point is that...
Pretending that you don't
know who your friends are,
it... just doesn't
feel very united.
This is your overlord,
Felicity Smoak.
We have a P.A. system?
Yet another decision I might
live to regret.
Hi, what's going on?
Code 47 at
a nightclub on Ninth.
A blonde woman
going cray cray.
And since
I'm down here,
it's probably the blonde woman
we've been looking for.
The woman who's
killing people in Pennytown.
Suit up.
Yeah.
Help! Help!
Run!
You have got
to stop this!
Sara...
Your sister's alive,
she's out there,
and she's hurting people.
How is she alive?
The Lazarus Pit?
You two spent your spa weekend
at Nanda Parbat?
It was the only place
we could get a reservation.
The blood lust is worse
with Sara, isn't it?
Because you brought
her back from death.
Yeah, and that's not
the only problem.
Sara's not herself.
She's changed.
Why didn't you come
to me with this?
Come to you
for what?
Your expertise
with magical resurrection?
Or that judgmental
look on your face?
For help finding her, Laurel,
before she gets hurt,
or she hurts anyone else.
And if I have a judgmental
look on my face right now,
it's because you played with forces
that you do not understand,
and now people are dying
because of it.
Who's he?
John Constantine.
Says so right on the business card
your boss took from me.
He had this on his
person, as well.
Do you recognize
these landmarks?
Yeah.
Good.
Whatever it is Mr. Constantine
is looking for,
I want you to find it
and bring it back to me.
Oh, come on, I'm telling you,
you can't trust him!
Then you can follow him.
What are you doing?
Are you actually praying?
No.
No, these aren't
prayers, mate.
Ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah.
Unless you want
to redecorate
your lovely hut
with his brains,
I suggest you drop
your weapon.
On the floor.
You won't escape
this island.
Ah, I don't intend
on leaving just yet.
Come on, you.
You really know
the place on that map?
Yes.
You do?
Good.
You're going to show me.
Now drive!
We need to talk.
About Sara?
Laurel told you?
Not exactly.
You got to admire
her consistency.
Keeps her death secret from me,
her resurrection secret from you.
Are you ok?
Am I ok?
I think there are certain
situations in life
where the word
"ok" does not apply.
Well, we're working
on finding Sara.
Good. Because we got
other problems.
It's a rat.
A remote access Trojan.
Basically a computer virus.
A polymorphic code
designed to target and erase
certain pieces of data.
It's buried under
three levels of encryption.
By the time
I've cracked it--
Darhk could be wondering
why I haven't run his errand for him.
I'm not sending you
to break into
a federal facility
without back-up.
I don't want Laurel knowing
about me and Darhk.
I wasn't
suggesting Laurel.
Did Oliver tell you that Darhk works
for an organization?
Hive?
Yeah.
Hive had my brother killed.
I'm sorry.
And now, Detective,
you're telling me
that you were
working with them?
For them?
It's a long story.
I've got time.
This city's
been hurting.
This is nothing new.
Darhk comes to me,
he offers to help fix it.
He's got powerful friends,
he's got money--
and this was months
before the Ghosts, all right?
I didn't see him as anything other
than a concerned citizen.
Ok, and then?
Well, then he's doing
all of his good stuff,
and then he asks me where
the fire chief is going on his vacation.
So I give him the address
of his summer cabin.
Next day,
the cabin blows up.
You confront
Darhk about this?
Of course I did.
And that's when
he shows me
pictures of Laurel.
At work,
at home,
AA meetings.
So this thing
with your brother,
is it going to be a problem
for us working together?
No, Detective.
Because you being next to Darhk
is going to help us take down HIVE.
Any luck connecting
Sara's victims?
Just that she's only killed
muggers and street thugs.
I still can't believe
that it's Sara
we're talking about.
That she's alive.
I mean, I know how it's possible,
but how is it possible?
The world
is a much more...
Complicated place
than most people
are comfortable
believing.
I received an old message
from Ray,
in the moment
right before he died.
I almost didn't
listen to it,
because...
I didn't--I didn't
want to feel that grief again.
The threat of zombie
apocalypse aside,
isn't it kind of nice not
having to deal
with the pain
of saying good-bye?
Well, if it were that simple.
Not a day goes by
that I don't
miss my parents,
or Tommy.
And I think about
what I would...
give just to spend
another minute,
but what's happening
with Sara isn't
healing anyone's pain;
It's just--it's making it worse.
She almost killed
those two girls.
I mean, why would she
even go after them?
Her marble collection's
a little incomplete.
Just guessing.
Well, they have
something in common?
Well...
The waitress was
Stephanie Dangess,
and the girl at the club
was Lindsay Paulson.
Oh, my God,
both these girls--
they look like Thea.
♪ When you walk
in the room ♪
♪ it catches fire ♪
Last thing I want,
judgment for tonight.
Ho-wa An-tea!
I just can't believe that Sara
would do something like this.
She's not Sara.
No, that's not it.
Hey, hey.
How you feeling?
Ah, Sara, she--
Ah, I know, it's ok.
You're safe.
She tried to kill me.
She's not in her
right mind.
You have no idea.
This is the Pit.
She's going through
the same thing I am.
I--Thea, I thought that
you were better.
When I went
to Nanda Parbat, I...
Killed two guys.
Malcolm--
Malcolm served them up
on a platter for me,
and... helped keep
my blood lust at bay.
Oh, my God.
Thank God
you're all right.
Laurel, come with me.
Is Thea ok?
No.
Not only is
Thea hospitalized,
but she has Merlyn
influencing her to kill people.
What are you talking about?
Oh, just another
thing that happened
on your secret trip
to Nanda Parbat.
Hey! I didn't tell you
that I took my sister
to Nanda Parbat because I knew that
you wouldn't approve.
Why didn't you tell me
you took Thea?
What does that have
to do with anything?!
It's the hypocrisy
that I can't stand!
What?
It's ok for you to do
whatever you have to for your sister,
but it's not ok for me
to do the same to mine?
Sara was dead.
Thea wasn't.
Then why didn't you tell me
about Thea
seven months ago?
Because you don't see me
as an equal.
What? Oh, come on.
Laurel, of course
I see you as an equal.
No, you don't!
You never have.
You never told me
that you were the Arrow--
keep your voice down!
...becoming
the Black Canary,
and you never
would have told me
that there's a way
to save my sister.
My sister, she's out of her
mind right now.
Because of something
that I did.
A decision
that I made.
Did you ever just stop
and think for one second
about what I might
be going through?
I'm sorry about what
happened to Thea.
I really am.
I love your family--
I always have.
I just wish
that sometimes
you would give
a damn about mine.
Get out.
You're sure
this is the place?
It's the place.
What's going on,
who are you?
How much do you know
about what your boss
is really doing
on this island, mate?
He's making drugs.
If only.
Your friend Reiter,
he's the dangerous sort.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means there are
things on this island
that bad people
shouldn't have access to.
Says the guy with a gun
pointed at my head.
Ah. I'm not a bad guy.
A little hard
scrabble, sure,
but, uh, I'm on the side
of the angels, mate.
At least when they're busy
trying to screw me over.
You're right.
This is the spot.
Ahh.
De cruinne-ce
agus akasha
seall me do solas!
What? You've never
seen magic before?
Well, go on
then, Alice.
Down the rabbit
hole you go.
Nice job
getting us in.
You learn how to do that before
or after working for Queen?
Save that
for another story.
Yeah, I bet.
Is this the access point?
Yeah, yeah, looks like it.
All right, keep an eye out
for rent-a-cops,
'cause it wouldn't do
my career prospects too much good.
It working?
Yeah, I think so.
Looks like the virus
is erasing files on people.
Which people,
and why?
Both really good questions.
Hey.
What are you...
doing here?
Waiting for you
to wake up.
Thea, I owe you
an apology.
No, no, there's no need
for you to apologize
for anything.
Yes, I do.
I brought Sara back without
any idea of how to control her.
I'm the one who killed her
in the first place.
That--
that's why she's
after me, you know.
This blood lust
she's consumed by...
It's the same pain I feel
when I think about Ra's.
I don't understand.
Because the person
that I'm driven to kill,
the one who killed me
is already dead.
Thea, what are you
talking about?
As soon as she kills me,
she'll be ok.
If the only way
to save Sara is to kill you,
then that's
no cure at all.
How much longer?
Two minutes.
Wait, wait, what was that?
What is it?
I just saw my brother's name.
What is that all about?
What'd you do?
I didn't do anything!
I just have to get back
to whatever it is that's been erased.
No, no, no,
we don't have time.
Security's going to be
on their way now.
I'm not leaving.
Drop it! Drop it now!
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
it's all right, it's all right!
Captain Lance,
Star City police department.
I just tracked
this hacker here.
All right. Now, look,
go get some back-up,
all right?
Call this in,
come on, go, go!
It's a good story. I just
wish you would have told me
before you gave me
a concussion.
Come on. Then it wouldn't
have looked real.
I didn't know
you were still here.
Hey.
Yeah, I just came to make
sure Thea was ok.
I didn't have
a chance to before, so.
She's sleeping.
Trying to.
Look, I--
I know why
you're here.
Ok, I get it.
I want you--
I want you to know
that it's--
it's ok.
I want you to do it.
About what
I said before--
You said some things
that you meant.
Thea!
You sure you want
to be here?
I hated hospitals
before tonight.
Ah. It's just another
excuse to stay away.
At the hospital,
I looked Sara in the eyes.
She wasn't there.
What does that mean?
The Pit is not supposed to be
used on the dead.
It brought Sara's body back,
but all of this is happening--
Because it didn't
restore her soul.
We still need
to find her, ok?
Sara died long
before you moved in with Laurel,
and she knew exactly
which hospital room to look for you in.
What, you think Sara
can sense Thea somehow?
And here I was just wrapping
my mind around metahumans.
Wait, we've both
been in the Pit.
Maybe--maybe that
gives us some type of connection.
A connection we can use.
Thea, you just got
out of the hospital.
I don't want
to use you as bait.
Well, I guess
it's a good thing
you're not
in charge anymore.
We'll have her back,
Oliver. All of us.
I don't understand.
How did you...
Well, that's the great thing
about magic.
Can't be explained.
There are places in this world
as old as the world.
Places of Nexus,
draw bad people
to them.
This island
is such place.
It's no accident
that you're here.
Let me guess--
"Do not enter."
More like, only for
the pure of heart.
That's not
you, mate.
There you are,
my pretty girl.
How do you know
it's a girl?
I can do that
trick, too.
Clever boy.
I'd usually be
more artful,
but I'm on something
of a clock.
Get back!
I'm not a bad guy, either.
Mission accomplished.
Well done.
Are you sticking around for a cupcake
or something?
This thing you had me do,
I saw some of the names
you had erased.
All military.
And here I had you
pegged for a Luddite.
Fast learner.
One of those names--
Sergeant Andrew Diggle.
What is he to you?
He died 6 years ago.
Why are you erasing the record
of a dead man?
You know what,
I'm going to tell you.
And only because you completed
your task with such efficiency.
We hired an assassin
to murder
Sergeant Diggle.
Why?
Afghanistan's
an interesting place,
replete with
opportunities
for an enterprising
enlisted man to engage in.
What are you talking about?
Drugs, weapons, murder.
Your Sergeant Diggle
was an eager beaver.
Unfortunately for him,
our organization
weaved itself into
that part of the world,
and as you know,
we don't play well with others.
So you had him
killed?
What is this guy,
your best buddy?
I don't see you associating
yourself with crime lords.
Ha, present company excepted.
Now, are we done?
Set.
I have to say, it feels
really weird being back here right now.
Don't worry.
Everyone's in position.
It's nothing, ok?
I--I don't think
this is going
to actually work.
Oh, God,
I take that back.
Get her out of here!
Dad was right.
There's nothing left
inside of you, Sara!
Tranq arrow.
No.
No, you said it yourself,
she has no soul.
Laurel...
Let's get it back.
Oliver.
John.
It's been a dog's age, mate.
More than. Do you remember that
favor you owe me?
I hardly expect you
to let me forget about that.
How quickly can you get
to Star City?
I need your help.
So what, you're
going to perform
some kind of exorcism
on my sister?
No, an exorcism is a removal
of demonic possession.
What your sister needs
is a restitutionem,
the restoration
of her soul to her body.
And you've
done this before?
Ah, once. Maybe a year ago.
But don't worry,
it's just like riding a bike.
I'm sure we have a lot
of work to do to prepare.
I assume you brought a list?
Apologies. I didn't have
time to translate that
from its original Aramaic.
You know, if I knew you were
surrounded by so many pretty girls, Oliver,
I would have
stopped by sooner.
Where did Oliver find
this guy, the Luxor?
Oh, I'm just glad that the
latest person from Oliver's past
is not another
gorgeous woman.
I'm not even
going to ask.
You got my message.
I'm so happy you came.
I'm her father, too.
I hate to be the one to say this,
but what if something goes wrong?
Oh, don't worry.
If things go wrong,
then we'll all be
too dead to care.
Well, then.
Now we just need a--
I think I got everything
in here that you wanted,
although I am not
entirely sure
what you need a dead
peacock feather for.
Ah.
Ahh.
Oh, nice one.
That's been bugging
me for hours.
Now,
I've only got enough juice
to send myself and two of you
to the other realm
and back, so.
Oh, I think
it should be me.
Um, I'm the reason
why she's like this right now.
No offense, love,
but from what I hear,
you're not exactly
bringing out the best
in Sara right now,
are you?
Laurel.
Do you trust me?
Trust me when I tell you
this will work.
Oh, there's, uh,
one more thing.
Whatever's locked
her soul away,
it's not going to give
it over without a fight.
So be ready.
All right, then.
On with the show.
Pelako ameso yobe eleggua
imbone ukuchila panshita.
De domino vestro, aliquis.
Et stabit de domino vestro.
Audite vocem meam.
Ancor, anchor,
candones helosi
et vos eleutis phugori...
De cruinne-ce agus akasha
seall me do solas!
Oliver!
Ah, well,
I've had worse hangovers.
So what are we
supposed to do now?
Laurel!
Laurel, no!
This is new.
Well, new is why you
brought me along.
Help!
No, no, no, no.
Well, I'm not going
to just stand here!
We need a tour guide.
Axis mundi,
produco tuus vires.
This way.
Unless you want to be trapped here
for all eternity.
This is what locked away
Sara's soul?
How the human mind
perceives it, anyway.
Help!
Sara!
Get to the Pit. You need to work
together to get her out.
I'll take care
of our new friend.
No, Sara!
You want some of me?
You know, any time
today would be good.
Per júdicem vivórum
et mortuórum!
Qui habet potestatem
mittere in infernum!
Abire ex regno--
2, 3!
Whoo.
You're all right.
Everything's going
to be all right.
What happened?
What is she?
Did we...
Sara!
Thank you, John.
I owe you one.
I believe I owed
you one, mate.
Hows about we just
call it even, eh?
How about any time,
anywhere you need me,
I'll be there.
I'll take that.
You know, the hair
on the back of my neck
has been standing up
since the moment I got into town.
That is probably
our current problem--
Damian Darhk.
Ohh, you've heard of him.
You watch yourself
on that one, mate.
He'll make what you saw in the other realm
look like a bloody gnat.
Any helpful advice?
Yeah.
Leave town.
While you still can.
Well, he's a very specific
kind of yummy.
Oh! I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear you just say that.
Are--are we ok?
I mean, I just keep
waiting for you to blow up at me.
Because you lied to me
about Nanda Parbat?
Yeah.
Thea, I don't have
the right to be mad
at anyone for keeping secrets.
But I'm sorry that I made you
feel as though you had to.
Come here.
Thanks, mate.
I owe you one.
What the hell
is all this?
Oh, this is
the Orb of Horus.
It's actually
a grimoire.
An ancient
spell book.
You asked.
And, uh, what are you going
to do with it?
Same as I do with all
the other mystical objects I find--
I keep them in a safe place,
away from the Baron Reiters
of this world.
Remember what I told you
about this island, mate.
This Reiter bloke is not
only here for the narcotics.
But then again, it's not
your problem, is it?
Come back with me.
I've got a boat
on the southern shore.
You saw those
people at camp.
I can't
leave them behind.
Well, aren't you the hero?
I also can't come back
empty-handed.
Conklin suspects me
enough as it is.
Fair enough.
Here.
Goons like Reiter,
they're only interested
in the sparkly bits,
anyway. The real power
is in the spell.
Here. Here, I'll show you.
Yateeka masaha
la hasra laha
watahseen hayda
albaled almodeef...
Lift up your shirt, mate?
What?
Mah qoo-wat
min aldaw alzalam.
What the hell
did you just do?
I gave you some
insurance against Reiter.
And when the time comes,
you'll know how to use it.
Now, I believe,
that concludes our business.
I--i need you
to punch me in the face.
Right. My, uh,
escape attempt
left a bruise, right?
All right.
I must warn you,
I've got a hell
of a right hook.
I'm--I'm fine.
Thanks very much.
All right,
so just stay on message.
Unity, united
community.
United. Got it.
All right.
Hey, Laurel.
Ok, maybe we need
to work on your understanding
of the phrase
"distance yourself."
Only if you insist on continuing to use it
when it relates to my friends.
Ok.
It's your campaign.
You pay me whether
you win or lose.
Um, I am going to go
keep him from quitting.
But I'm very proud
of you right now.
How's Sara?
Resting.
It turns out that getting your soul
back is exhausting.
Yeah.
Ollie...
I don't know how I'm ever going
to be able to thank you.
Just like that.
Well, thank you.
And thank you
for inviting me here tonight.
After what I said to
you in the hospital,
I thought that I'd be the last person
you'd want to see.
Well, you were right. I--
I haven't always been
the best friend for you,
but I--I'd be grateful
for the opportunity
to try and start to be.
How can I say no
to the man
that helped me save
my sister's soul?
Mistakes that have
hurt people close to me.
But I'm not here
to run from the past.
Because the past has
contributed to making--
I thought you'd be out
celebrating with Sara.
Yeah, there's
enough time for that.
Please.
I figured
I owed you something.
I asked Darhk
about your brother.
He, uh, gave me something.
You don't have to read this.
You can remember
your brother how you knew him.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, it's legit.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you, Detective.
Gut punch doesn't
deserve a thank you.
I wanted to know why...
HIVE had my brother killed,
and now I do, so...
Felicity! Welcome back!
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
How many of these
have you drank?
It's "drunk," actually, and many.
But worth it.
You cleared up
the rest of Ray's message?
I think so. Uh,
the playback was rendering
when you came in.
So, propitious timing.
Ok, you're not even allowed to
say "energy drink"
while on company
time ever again.
That's ok; I think
I might be having
a cardiac incident, anyway.
So, the message, check it out.
I was just about to call you.
Wait, where's my phone.
Wait, did I call you already?
Curtis!
I'm sorry, Felicity,
this is my fault.
I--I got myself into this
mess screwing around
with my exosuit
and nanotechnology.
But recriminations probably aren't probably
the best use of this limited bandwidth.
What I need you to know is,
I'm alive,
and I'm in trouble.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.