My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city,
but my old approach
wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become
something else.
the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Those little
yellow pills you swallowed,
they do a few
interesting things,
including making
you cooperative.
Thanks to the algae
we engineered
from Star City bay,
the air down here
is now perfectly breathable.
Genesis is
almost ready.
We're much too close
to play games.
Do you remember
what I promised you?
A new beginning.
And you will have it
once we've brought
this world to its end.
Andy's working for Darhk,
has been the entire time.
Andy!
Your brother's way
beyond reach, Mr. Diggle.
If I'd listened
to you instead
of trusting
my brother,
Laurel would be
alive right now.
If Darhk wins,
Laurel died
for nothing.
He feels
unstoppable.
Because of his magic.
It's too strong.
You always find a way,
and you have to find
a way now.
Now is not the time
for panic.
We let him rot
in prison.
Clearly,
you overestimate
Damien Darhk's
capacity for forgiveness,
which is to say
that he has any.
Should Damien prove
to be unreasonable,
I have implemented
contingencies.
My buddies.
Long time, no see.
I brought my posse.
Hope you don't mind.
What happened
to Ian and Judy?
They come down
with that nasty, little flu
that's been
going around?
Some were wary
of this meeting given that--
You all abandoned me
to my imprisonment?
I visited.
Someone should teach
this evil organization
a lesson in helping
their fellow man.
I'm sure it's all just a simple
misunderstanding.
After all, why
would I rely solely
on the word
of Malcolm Merlyn?
He can be so
underhanded.
Cute.
And our
illustrious council
has worked together
for such a very long time.
I'm glad that
we still have your trust.
Of course.
I had a lot of time
to reflect while
I was in prison,
mostly about religion
and bundt cake,
but after much thought,
I realized that--
oh, almost forgot.
Did my little incarceration
delay Genesis at all?
Uh, of course not.
Genesis is much bigger
than just one person.
Heh heh heh heh.
Gold star for you.
Where was I?
Oh, that's right.
My jailhouse epiphany.
If I could escape prison
without your help,
what do I need
any of you for?
Milo, you really have not been
paying attention, have you?
Unh!
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Anyone else care to do
something stupid?
No takers?
Pity.
Ladies and gentlemen
and recently deceased,
it is time to begin
the final phase of Genesis.
Milo Armitage.
SCPD found him
in an alley
outside Ellendale,
and across town...
Phaedra Nixon.
Ok. So what
am I missing?
They were both HIVE.
You probably don't
recognize Phaedra and Milo
now that they're dead,
or maybe you were
too busy running
for your life, but--
They were with Darhk
when he held us hostage.
And now
they're dead.
What, so you think
crazy-pants Lonnie Machin's
back in town?
No. His grudge
is against Darhk, not HIVE.
You think Darhk
is cleaning house?
Well, HIVE didn't lift a finger
to break him out of Iron Heights.
That was all
Andy and Merlyn.
Ok. Well, if Darhk
is settling scores,
then now might be
the time to hit him.
We have seen how
powerful he is
I can't risk losing
anyone else.
We can't just sit on
our hands, Oliver.
We're not just sitting
on our hands,
but before we do
anything,
we need to know that
we can counteract his magic.
Well, is that
even possible?
I think it might be.
I was finally able
to get in touch with Constantine.
He put me on to
someone who he thinks
may be able to teach me how to defend
against Darhk's magic.
Ok. Well, I'm not
just saying this
because I love
"Harry Potter,"
but why are we not
all taking those lessons?
Well, it is easier
said than done
and apparently
quite dangerous.
So I have to go
to Hub City for a day or two.
Ok. In that case,
can I take the weekend
with Alex?
Kind of wants to go
away, clear our heads.
That sounds like
a good idea.
I think that--
actually, I think
everyone should take
a little time.
Lay low but stay
available,
and we will deal with Darhk
when I get back.
Ok.
Let him in.
Mind stepping out?
Hey, you.
How you holding up?
Mmm.
You've, um,
looked better.
Oh! Considering I've
spent two weeks
in a bomb-proof,
tungsten-encased bunker,
I think I look
pretty good.
Hmm.
You hungry?
Mmm. How long have
those been there?
That was lunch.
Might have even
been today's.
Yeah. I think
I'll pass.
Oliver is leaving tonight on some
magical mystery tour,
wants me to stay put
and do nothing
until he comes back.
Magical mystery tour?
Yeah. It's a long story,
but the point of it is
is that he thinks
it's too dangerous to go
after Darhk or Andy
until he gets the right
magical know-how.
I can see you're
thrilled about that.
If you think
you have it bad,
try remembering
you're not the one
being held prisoner
in a metal box.
Oh, sweetheart.
We've talked
about this.
Andy has been
inside of Argus,
he's been inside
of our home.
It's too dangerous
for you to be
either place
right now.
I don't want you
any other place either.
Oh, I got you, baby,
I got you. Mmm.
Let my agents see
what they can find.
- Yeah.
- And as much as you
don't want
to hear it,
Oliver has a point.
HIVE is too
dangerous for you
to go off
half-cocked, John.
Oh, it's always serious
when you call me John.
Well, John, why don't
you make yourself useful
by grabbing some
diapers while you're out?
We're running low and I hate asking
my people to get them.
You got it.
Back in a hour?
Or less.
Say, "bye, daddy."
Say, "bye-bye. Bye-bye."
You've been living
down here.
Ahem. It seemed to
make the most sense.
Where's all your stuff?
It's in storage.
You know me.
I don't need much.
Maybe, like, a plant,
like a...Fern
or something.
They thrive
in places like this.
How could I forget?
Come to see me off.
You were pretty stingy
on the details
about this "magic tutor"
Constantine referred you to.
It is sort of
my M.O.
Don't talk to me
like I'm other people.
What has you
so worried?
Darhk's idol, the type of magic
that he's using,
I've seen it take
good people
and turn them dark,
soulless,
almost inhuman.
And you're afraid
that's gonna happen to you?
There's an argument
to be made that I'm already there.
-That's not funny.
-I am not joking.
There is no length
that I will not go to
to avenge Laurel,
to stop Darhk from hurting anyone
ever again,
and I honestly don't
know where that path will lead.
I'm coming with you.
Felicity--
just because we're
not together
doesn't mean you have
to do this alone,
and I've already chartered
the company jet.
Mr. Dennis is furious,
and I booked us a room--
rooms...with points.
Should I even try
and talk you out of this?
No. You met
my mother.
Heh. Same DNA.
Did you see
anyone else here?
Which way?
Get out of here now.
What the hell?
Sorry, man...
But I'm not playing
anymore!
Hoo! You still got those
quick reflexes, John.
Too bad they couldn't
save your partner.
Don't you dare say
anything about her!
Well, you've got a gun.
Make me!
♪ Arrow 4x19 ♪
Genesis
Original Air Date on May 4, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, honey.
It's a little tough
for me to talk
right now!
You'll want to
hear this.
Satellite track
just picked up Andy.
Unh!
Let me guess.
He's somewhere south of Main
between Grammercy
and Addison, right?
How do you know that?
Because I'm trading
shots with him right now.
- Johnny.
- You can yell at me later.
Just send backup.
He's at the Grammercy
Power Plant.
How soon can
your men get here?
5 minutes, 10 tops.
That's too long.
Johnny, you need to wait.
You have no tactical
advantage in there.
Lyla, I can't wait.
If I do, he gets away.
I can't let that happen,
not again.
Your judgment
is compromised.
Maybe it is,
but it doesn't mean
I'm wrong. Get here!
Johnny!
So what exactly are
we looking for?
High roller room.
When you said that you'd found
someone  to teach you magic,
I was thinking, like,
a mountaintop
or a hidden temple,
not Hub City's
premier underground
casino.
Well, with Constantine,
I have learned to
expect the unexpected.
I'm betting on Fortuna.
Now he was a little bit
vague with the specifics.
He just said...
"Pitch game,
first base, mate.
See if you're worthy."
Wow. Ok. Pitch game,
Blackjack.
Uh, dealer using
up to two decks.
Mm-hmm.
First base, first seat
on the dealer's left.
I think we're
in the right place.
I'm not so sure that
finding this guy depends on gambling.
It's not gambling
when I play.
Alex?
Hello?
Hey. Morning.
And here I thought you were
gonna sleep past breakfast.
I--I almost did.
I'm so foggy.
Yeah. You were
exhausted.
You passed out 5 minutes after we
left the city.
Oh. Guess I was
really tired.
See? It just proves
how badly you needed this trip.
We both did.
You ready for some
famous eggs Benedict?
You poached eggs?
Hey. I'm not just
a cutthroat political operative.
I contain multitudes.
Mm-hmm, and you also
wear a very mean apron.
Well, you should see
what I have on underneath.
Mmm. Ha ha!
I forgot how good
you were at this.
Oh, like riding
a bike.
Rough beat.
Indeed. I should
probably head home soon
before they take
my shoes.
Oh. Well, you never know
when your luck's gonna change.
Trust me.
That's so kind.
Muchas gracias.
De nada.
Oh, boom!
Come to mama!
Ahem. I mean...What?
I'm starting to think
that this guy's
gonna be a no-show.
It's because he's
not a guy, amor.
Esrin Fortuna.
Tell John Constantine
he still owes me money.
Stay right where you
are, you son of a bitch.
It's funny.
I was gonna tell
you the same thing.
Unh!
Ugh.
Bravo, John.
You played the script
out perfectly.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Oh, don't worry
about it.
I'll explain
everything
after you wake up.
I'm sorry this place
isn't as fancy
as the cage you kept
me in for 3 months.
Where the hell am I?
You got
bigger worries.
Mr. Darhk is
on his way.
To do what?
Well, he's not coming
here to play gin rummy.
I'm supposed to
prep you.
Glad to see you're picking up your
psycho boss' old habits.
I'm sorry,
but is the man
that locked me up in a cage
and beat me half to death
questioning
my savior's orders?
Damien Darhk is
no one's savior.
He's a liar
and a monster.
The Romans said
the same thing about Jesus.
Just do whatever you're
gonna do, man.
Do it!
Wow. There's that
temper I remember.
You know, it's
a good thing that Sara's
not gonna have to grow up
with it like I did.
Keep my daughter's name
out of your mouth!
How could you do this
to everyone again for a second time?
Oh. Oh, I know
what you're doing.
You're referring
to my former wife and son.
I left that life
a long time ago, John.
You can't even say
their names.
Carly, Andy Jr.
They were your family.
They still are.
My family...
is HIVE.
Unh!
Argggh! Gaaah!
Ok. So since Oliver
doesn't seem to want to ask it, um--
Why is an immortal shaman
playing Blackjack
in Hub City's
premier underground casino?
Excuse me?
Immort--immortal?
You see any wrinkles
on my face?
And shaman.
A shaman is someone
who has influence
in the world of good
and evil spirits.
Blackjack is just
a hobby.
This way.
Planning on teaching
me magic
in the back room
of a casino?
You want to learn
the dark arts, Mr. Queen,
we cannot do that here.
Whoa! This is by far
the coolest high roller room
I have ever seen.
We've left the casino
behind, amor,
and that plane
of existence.
I've been
in a chamber like this before
on an island named
Lian Yu.
Yes. Lian Yu is
a place of Nexus
just like your home.
Star City?
Hmm. There's a Nexus
chamber there, as well.
Wait. You didn't think
it was a coincidence
that Damien Darhk chose
that city?
You know Darhk?
I wouldn't be much
of a shaman if I didn't.
Special brand
of nasty loco that one is.
Mmm.
So if you know
Darhk,
why haven't you
tried to end him?
That's not the way
of things.
We immortals tend to stay
out of the affairs of men.
Unless someone
owes you money.
Recognize this
handsome gent?
Darhk has a similar idol.
It gives him
his power.
Uh-uh. It only
channels it.
Darhk's power comes
from--
Death.
The more people he kills,
the more powerful
he becomes.
Not just a pretty
face this guy.
Yeah. Except Oliver's
not gonna go kill a bunch of people
just to be on the same
level playing field as Darhk.
All things have
their opposite.
Darhk draws
his power
from fear and death.
Its opposite is
light and hope,
la Luz Del Alma,
light of the soul.
If you can channel
la Luz Del Alma,
you will be able to
repel Darhk's magic.
Then that is what
I'm here to learn.
I wish it were
just that easy.
If the darkness
inside you
outweighs the light,
instead of repelling
Darhk's magic,
you will end up
fueling it.
You will only make
him more powerful.
Are you getting
a signal?
Nope. That's one of the benefits
of being on vacation.
Oh. I just wanted
to call my brother.
You ok? Seem to be
having trouble relaxing.
Yeah. No. I'm--
you're probably gonna
think it's stupid.
Oh, I can pretty much
guarantee that I won't.
It's--it's this place.
It just seems
too perfect.
Ha! Oh. It sounds like
it's been way too long
since you've left
the city.
Yeah, maybe.
Do you hear that?
Yeah. I think people
call that nature.
No. That's--
That's not it.
It...
I, uh...
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just tired,
but it--it sounds like everything is
on a loop right now.
Does that sound crazy?
That--that's crazy.
Only a little, yeah.
Look. I think this
is just the last bit
of you trying to
fight this vacation.
Yeah.
Hey. Let all
that go.
Just be happy, ok?
Ok.
I sure am.
- Ok.
- All right.
It's time.
I know this feels
personal, John,
but it isn't.
What's happening is just
what has to happen.
Rah!
Do it.
Do it for Laurel.
She'd be so
disappointed in you.
The only reason why
you're still breathing
is because one of us
is still human.
I'll hit you with a low dose
of Darhk's magic,
and then we'll take it
up from there.
Don't I need an idol
or a totem?
The tattoo Constantine
gave you does many things.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm--I'm sorry.
I just--I just thought that these
magic lessons
would have, you know, more
lessons.
Magic is a manipulation
of primordial energies,
primordial as
in prelinguistic.
You'll probably want
to take a few steps back, amor.
Hmm?
Two sides of you--
darkness, light.
Focus on the light.
Good, but that might
be, as they call, beginner's luck,
so let's kick it up
a notch or two, hmm?
The darkness
and light are within you.
In truth, you are only
fighting yourself.
The friends you've failed,
the people you've killed,
they have no place
in this.
Don't give in.
Cast aside your doubt,
resist your darkness.
Unh!
What happened?
He's not ready.
I'll get it,
I'll get it.
Now let's go again.
I could give you
an infinite number of tries.
It wouldn't change
a thing.
What? No.
I can do this.
I told you
if the darkness within you
is greater
than the light,
you will only make
your enemy stronger.
You've seen what's
inside of you, yeah?
Tell me, what could
I possibly teach you
that would change
what you saw?
Wait. So that's it?
It's over?
There's nothing
I can do for him.
It's not even getting
dark out.
What's that?
It's 8:00,
and it's raining outside,
but it's still
light out.
We're up north
and...
Seriously, what's
gotten into you?
You never even told me
where we were going...
And how can you not
hear that?
Thea, come on.
We've been
over this.
Seriously, listen.
There's 3 chirps...
Then a bark,
then 4 chirps,
and then it just keeps
repeating itself twice.
Ok. I think what's
happening here
is you're
beyond stressed.
No, ok, Alex.
I am not stressed out.
Just listen.
There's gonna be a bark
right...Now.
Since when did you start
taking vitamins--
Now you're worried
about my vitamins.
Where did you get
those?
Ruvé. She said
I needed to stay healthy.
Alex...Where are we?
Is--is the reason that
I don't remember anything
because you...
Did you drug me?
Thea, now you're
talking crazy, ok?
- No, I can't.
- Where are you going?
Thea!
What the hell,
Johnny?!
I told you
to stand down!
I know, I know,
but I couldn't.
You could have
been killed!
I couldn't stand down, not
after what he did.
Then you are going to
make an orphan of your daughter
because you are not
seeing straight.
That's why tonight
went south!
Shh.
Lyla, listen.
I know I--
I know I messed up.
I--I know my head
isn't on right,
but--but he's
my brother,
and Laurel, she--
she was like a sister.
I know,
and it's horrible,
but right now, Johnny, you are
not acting like the man I married.
You're the man
I divorced.
Lyla, look.
I just wanted to help him,
to bring
my brother back.
Then bring him
to justice,
but do it
the right way.
I will.
We'll find someone else
to teach you magic,
someone with more patience
and less smelly incense.
She was right,
you know?
It's not
about the magic.
It's about me.
If she didn't see
anything worthy inside you,
she never would
have dealt with us.
She didn't deal with us.
She dealt with you.
She didn't reveal
herself until you
offered her
your chips,
and that has always
been the way with us.
Felicity, you are
the one who brings the light.
You know, I told you
that I've seen
magic that's turned
good people dark,
but all Fortuna did was
show me who I really am.
Don't do this.
Every time you face
a setback,
you throw yourself
a pity party.
It's not a pity party.
It's acceptance.
You said it yourself.
No matter what I do,
I'm always gonna revert back
to the person I became on the island.
Yeah. When I said that,
I was hurt.
I was going through one of the most
painful experiences of my life.
No, Oliver,
you're not perfect.
None of us are.
The good is that
all of us can change.
Hmm.
Poowr widdle
Andy Diggle.
Did your big brother
knock your noggin?
Heh heh heh heh.
Bravo. Your performance
was pitch perfect.
Thank you, sir.
I assume the tracker's
in place.
We've already locked
in on his location.
Well, then I believe
it's time for one last family reunion.
Oh, come on.
You're a bigger baby
than Sara.
Ouch.
Is there anything else
you can tell me about their lockup?
Yeah. The place could
have really used some central heating.
No. It was strange.
Torture just doesn't seem like
the right play.
Why not just kill me?
What's that?
Proximity alarm.
Sweetheart, make sure
Sara's strapped in really tight.
- How's Sara?
- She's ok.
It's director Michaels.
We have a code black.
We have
two more bogeys.
How the hell
did they find us?
It's me. Andy let me go.
He probably tagged me
with a tracker.
You can blame yourself
after we get out of this.
You mean if we get
out of this.
Where's your backup?
HIVE has them engaged
elsewhere--
Argus headquarters.
- Where's your team?
- They're not answering.
So much for "stay
available."
We're on our own.
This rig was designed
to withstand just about anything.
Does that include magic?
It's me he's after.
I'll draw him out.
No!
If you were Darhk's objective,
he already had you.
He wanted you to
lead him to me.
What are you
talking about?
You need to get
out of here now.
Lyla, I'm not
leaving you.
Johnny, I am not
Amanda Waller.
If they use you
against me,
I will give them
whatever they want.
I need you both safe.
That was a fun bit
of business.
Get him.
You are a feisty
one, Ms. Michaels.
You had your fun.
It's time for me
to have mine.
Oh, it's been a while since I've
hit anybody with this thing.
I didn't think you
got my message.
Sorry we're late.
Oliver's on Lyla and Darhk.
Baby Sara?
- All right.
- Yeah.
- You got her?
- Yeah, yeah.
Ok.
Ok, ok.
All right.
Ok.
It's a small world,
isn't it?
Your bother-in-law being
my loyal servant.
Thanksgiving at your home
is gonna be
so interesting
this year.
Ha ha ha!
Agggghh!
Unh!
You seem like a likable guy,
Oliver.
I bet you've got
a lot of friends.
I'm gonna enjoy killing every
last one of them.
No. Never again.
Bet you regret not pulling that trigger
the first time around.
What are you gonna
do, John?
Agh! Unh!
After Laurel, I left
you alone to grieve.
I was being nice.
You have no idea how
much I hate being nice.
Unh!
Agghhh!
It isn't over.
You haven't been
paying attention, Andy.
Darhk got out,
I got out.
I'll get out again.
That mobile safe house you
got looked really homey.
Bet it will get cramped
when Sara gets older.
Shut up.
She's got to go
to school eventually,
and Lyla, well, you
can't watch her 24/7.
I said shut
your mouth, Andy.
Shut your damn mouth!
You're the one who's obviously not
paying attention
because this is war.
And women, children,
they're expendable
in your war?
Genesis is coming, John.
Lyla and Sara won't be the only women
and children who die.
Tell me, how's it feel
knowing that
you had no problem
pulling the trigger
to protect a bunch
of Afghanis that you never knew,
but you don't have
the guts
to do what's necessary
to protect your own
wife and child?
Uh...
How's Lyla?
Um...
She's fine.
She--she's, um--
she's unconscious,
but--but she's fine.
Felicity's taking
her and Sara back.
Darhk is--Darhk's
in the wind.
John, what happened?
He was never gonna
back off of us.
My family...
They were never
gonna be safe.
Hey.
Hi.
Did you get in touch
with Thea?
Not yet.
You ok?
Phew.
Earlier with Darhk,
it worked.
He tried to use
his magic on me,
and I was able
to repel it.
That's incredible.
How'd you do it?
I heard your voice
in my head,
and you were reminding me
of all of the good things
that I have
in my life.
I heard Thea,
I heard John.
I heard Laurel...
Just telling me
to keep fighting,
to never give up,
just telling me
to have hope.
Hey.
Sara? Where's Sara?
She's fine,
she's fine.
Felicity took her
to Donna's.
She--she's ok.
But something's
wrong.
I, um--I had to
put him down, Lyla.
Andy.
Oh.
I had to kill
my baby brother.
He wasn't a brother
to you, Johnny,
not in the ways
that really matter.
What happened?
He reached for my gun.
I didn't have a choice.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
What?
It's gone.
Darhk took it.
Took what?
Rubicon.
I thought Rubicon
was being stored at Argus.
It was until Shadowspire
tried to steal it.
After Waller's death,
I had it moved
for security reasons.
To where?
It was under your skin?
A subdermal implant.
Darhk ripped it out.
Lyla, you need to
tell us what Rubicon is.
A ballistic launch
override protocol
designed to prevent
any country, even our own,
from firing
a nuclear missile.
Something tells me
Darhk's plans aren't so benign.
With some work
and the right expertise,
Rubicon could be corrupted.
Instead of controlling nukes to
prevent them from being launched--
Oh, my God.
Darhk would control the world's
nuclear stockpile.
To what end?
I don't mean to apply
logic to a bad guy's plot here,
but Darhk destroys
the world, then what?
He'd be ruler
of nothing.
Unless he wants
to rebuild.
Andy told me that
Genesis was coming.
I don't think so.
Phil Collins said
they'd never tour again.
The old testament,
the book of "Genesis."
God wanted to give the world a do-over,
so he destroyed it.
He destroyed it
with a flood.
Rubicon is
Darhk's flood.
So nuclear
annihilation is Darhk's flood.
What's he planning
on building as his ark?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.