Last season on "Arrow"...
Star City's
seen better days.
They built a wall.
Star City is
a wall-free zone once again.
Restoring the Glades
won't be easy.
The four of you are
the heroes that this city needs.
We're stepping back.
We're leaving Star City.
What now?
A crisis
is imminent.
What does
the multiverse require?
We seek to prevent
the inevitable.
What are you not telling me?
I've seen your
future, Oliver,
inexorable
and unavoidable.
I have watched you die.
Among the many
misconceptions humanity holds dear
is the fallacy that all beings
are created equal.
In truth, there are
those who are greater.
They are called heroes.
But even among heroes,
there are different echelons.
The highest belong to those
known as the paragons.
And they are the only hope
of all creation.
Oliver?
Hi, Mom.
Ohh. Ohh.
I missed you so much.
Oh, my beautiful boy.
My beautiful boy.
Your room is exactly
as you left it.
I never had the heart
to change anything.
I can't tell you how great
it feels to be home.
Oliver, it's really you.
Hi, Malcolm.
Welcome home.
Ok, what... where's...
where's Walter?
He sold his shares of
the company
when the Gambit
went down.
Okay. Okay.
What'd I tell you?
Yachts suck.
I knew it. I knew you were
too stubborn to be dead.
Tommy.
Come on, man.
Why are you looking at me like
I'm the one who's
been gone a decade?
I just missed you.
Where's Thea?
Sweetheart, um, why
don't you settle in?
I mean, you
must be exhausted.
Yeah, but I'd like
to see Thea.
Oliver, when you and your
father disappeared...
it wasn't easy on her.
She took things
really hard.
And there is this new
drug called vertigo.
- I swear to you...
- Tommy.
I tried my best
to look...
Tommy,
it wasn't your fault.
What wasn't his fault?
Thea, on
her 18th birthday...
she overdosed.
Raisa's famous
chicken marsala?
I used to make this
for William all the time.
Who's William?
Oh, I know.
He was, like, your Wilson
on the island, right?
Something like that.
How did you manage
to survive by yourself all that time?
It's a long story.
So, uh,
things you missed
while you were gone.
I got married
and divorced twice.
Ah, let's see. What other
gossip did you miss?
Our parents getting married.
- It's, um...
- Complicated.
Oliver, I know
this must all be a lot.
Well, mom, my apologies,
but I actually am a little tired,
and I think I'm gonna head
up to my bedroom.
Thank you for dinner.
Hey.
Your bed has been made.
And there are fresh
towels in the bathroom.
Thank you.
I know the changes
must be overwhelming,
and you must feel
like you're
on a different planet
or something.
You could say that.
It couldn't have been easy
all those years on that island.
Sounds like it wasn't
that easy here.
Now, you're not the same
man as when you left.
And don't take this
the wrong way,
but I get the sense
that it's...
it's for the better.
I'm not so sure.
Mom, when we were
growing up,
if you had to leave me
and Thea to protect us...
would you have done it?
Oliver, whether
right or wrong,
everything I've ever done
was to protect my children.
It's all
a parent can do.
And someday, hmm,
when you have children,
you'll understand.
Mom, I'm so sorry.
Ohh. Ohh.
Everything's okay.
You're home.
You're safe.
Close your eyes,
sweetheart.
Get some rest, okay?
All right.
You have failed this city.
Hyah!
Stand down.
Oliver,
what the hell
are you doing on my Earth?
Showoff.
Jealous?
Nostalgic.
It seems Adrian and I
have the same design sense.
If by that you mean
Felicity, yeah.
But this is my bunker.
Chase?
He's one of the good
guys, literally.
And you're helping him
in Star City.
Starling City.
And he's helping me.
We make a pretty
good team, actually.
Not that kind
of a team.
So how much small talk
do I have to endure
before you tell me what
it is exactly you're doing on my Earth?
Yeah, it's
a long story.
Why don't you start
by telling me
what you were doing
on Lian Yu?
You know, if you wanted
to pretend to be back from the dead,
you could've just showed
up in town.
I wasn't given
a choice.
I was sent to your Earth,
and I arrived on Lian Yu.
Sent? Sent by who?
You get him to tell you
the truth yet, pretty bird?
And nothing but.
Seems Mr. Queen survived
the Gambit
and has spent the last
12 years on an island called Lian Yu.
That means
"purgatory" if I'm not mistaken.
It still doesn't explain
what you're doing
running around in my hood.
I needed an identity
to work under,
and yours seemed
convenient.
Sorry.
What were you doing
at Queen-Merlyn?
Not killing those
scientists,
if that's what
you are implying.
Well, I'm using Laurel's
equipment to compare
the metallurgy of your
arrows to the ones that we found
in those men and women,
so we'll see.
Speak of the devil.
Literally.
The Dark Archer?
Name's a bit on the nose,
but it's descriptive.
Dark costume,
jade pendant.
It's Malcolm Merlyn.
- Yeah, we thought so, too.
- Ruled him out months ago.
It's Malcolm Merlyn.
And he killed those
scientists for a reason.
Where are you
going?
I'm gonna have
a conversation with my stepdad.
It never ceases
to impress...
humanity's capacity
for invention.
Hmm. Infinite number
of worlds,
and not a single one
where man fails to emerge from caves
and hold dominion
over the Earth.
What are you doing here?
Reminding you what you
are doing here,
which does not
include interfering
in the events of this Earth.
I have no intention
of interfering.
Are you not here
to confront Malcolm Merlyn
with your suspicion that
he is the Dark Archer?
Well, I went to
Applied Sciences last night
to retrieve the
dwarf star particles
just like you
asked me to.
You make it sound
like a trifle.
Those specific particles
can only be found
on this Earth out of
a multitude.
My point is that when I arrived,
Malcolm had already stolen them.
You know what
might help?
If I actually knew why
I was after them.
That I have tasked you
should be reason enough.
Or have you come to doubt
your commitment to this mission?
No, I have not.
At Harris Consolidated, we see
the wall coming down as an opportunity.
For the criminals of Star City
to rob the Glades blind?
To reunite the city.
I don't think people
in the Glades got that memo
'cause last I checked,
crime's up 300%
since the wall
went down.
There's an old saying...
there are 3 kinds of liars:
liars, damn liars,
and statisticians.
You're focusing on the Glades
to the exclusion of Star City
while net, there's been
a citywide reduction in crime.
And we have the vigilantes who
brought down the wall in the first place
to thank for that.
Hear that, guys?
We're famous.
Really? 'Cause it sounds like
we got a long way to go.
Which is why we're
here, to make sure
nothing happens
to Mr. Vasquez.
Whoa. And where do
you think you're going?
Movement outside.
Gonna check it out.
Negative.
Don't break perimeter.
Relax. It'll take a sec.
Just like Pennytown.
What was that, Mr. Harris?
Uh... oh. I... I was just saying
that the unification money
put into Pennytown prevented
a potential disaster
because we listened
to each other.
Well, she is either
ignoring you, William...
For the second time
this month.
or the comm systems
are failing.
For the fifth time
this month.
It's a new era.
Growing pains are to be
expected. Heh!
Mia, do you copy?
Excuse me, miss.
Mr. Vasquez doesn't want
any guests wandering the property.
This neighborhood just...
just isn't safe anymore.
Sorry. I just, uh,
wanted a look around.
Mia...
Allow me to escort
you back in.
We recently completed
a total IT upgrade.
500 miles worth of
high-capacity fiber optics
married to an underground
server farm.
Is something like that
for Applied Sciences?
We had a small incident
there last night.
Very unfortunate.
The police
are investigating.
Oh, that's too bad.
I hope no one was hurt.
So do you think it had
anything to do with the, um,
the Dwarf... Dwarf
Star Project?
How do you know about that?
Oh, the internet. Heh!
I didn't know you had
wi-fi on Lian Yu.
No, no, no. I wish.
I stayed up late at the house last night,
doing my research,
catching up.
Well, the press coverage
hasn't been particularly kind.
Everyone wants to make
the Dwarf Star Project
out to be
something sinister,
but it's just an
alternative energy source project,
completely benign.
I suppose everything's
a matter of interpretation.
Now, do you think that
someone could show me
to the most important
room on this tour?
And, uh, what would
that be?
The bathroom.
It's supposed to be red.
Excuse me.
Nothing. Sorry. I'm
looking for Felicity Smoak.
Ha ha! Like Felicity Smoak
would slum it in IT
instead of running
Smoak tech.
Oh, good for her.
Sorry.
Who does run the IT
department?
There you are.
Malcolm Merlyn, you have
failed this city.
I... I... don't know what
you think I did, but I...
Aah!
- Oh, God.
- Get out of here!
Oh, no.
So that's your story.
An archer in black flew in
and attacked The Hood.
Hmm?
Well, who is he?
Why did he do that?
I don't know.
Find him, and you ask.
First there was an attack
on Applied Sciences.
Now there's a war between
two masks in your own office.
And your point, Sergeant?
My point is that I highly doubt
this is a coincidence.
Well,
obviously not.
Somebody is clearly targeting
my father's company.
Right. Except
from his statement,
your father claimed
The Hood
was targeting him.
It's funny. He doesn't
usually go after the good guys.
All right.
Interview's over.
Anything else you need,
Sergeant Drake,
you can either go through
me or Mr. Merlyn's attorney.
Perfect. I needed something
to look forward to.
She's got a point.
It's a lot of drama
for the past 24 hours.
Maybe we should reconsider
Oliver's welcome home party.
No, no, no, no.
It'll just look like
we're trying to
cover something up.
Yeah. And I missed tequila.
Oliver.
I want you to meet
John Diggle.
He'll be accompanying
you from now on.
Er... no. Sorry. No. I don't
need a babysitter, Mom.
No, this is something
that I need.
Yeah.
So what do I call you?
Diggle. Dig if you want.
Sorry, Oliver.
Fool me once.
- How did you find me?
- It wasn't easy.
It was like you disappeared
off the face of the Earth...
until Felicity figured out
that it was only our Earth.
Still, John, it's not like
you can just charter a jet.
Cisco let me borrow it.
And now if I'm done
answering your questions,
I have a few of my own.
- Can't talk about it.
- Can't or won't?
You know, Oliver,
it's interesting
that we're revisiting
when we first met.
You going at it all
alone is like deja vu.
I thought you and I
were past that.
This is new. It's bigger.
And I'm not going to ask you
to take the risk it involves.
Oliver, that's the thing
about being brothers.
You never, ever
have to ask.
Can you just believe me
when I tell you this is different?
Yeah. Felicity told me.
Some godlike being
talking about
the end of the universe?
What didn't she tell
me, Oliver?
A crisis is coming, John.
He's seen what happens.
He's watched me die.
Thank you for not making
a fuss about coming back in.
I wouldn't want you
and your friends
to miss out on the party.
Don't engage the Deathstrokes.
They're a distraction.
Guys! No one listens
to the tech guy.
Fine. I guess I'll do it.
William.
You okay?
Yeah. Mia, you okay?
They took Vasquez.
The Deathstroke gang.
Screw them.
Who's the one playing
security guard?
He knew who I was.
He knows
who we all are.
What? How?
He's my brother.
♪ Balla per me... ♪
♪ We learn to dance ♪
♪ But we're swimming
in a black hole ♪
♪ Pretty girl
in the red dress... ♪
Well, hello. You will
be pleased to hear
that I made sure the bar
was stocked with pinot noir.
I'll be right back.
♪ Balla per me
bimbo bianco ♪
You know, the party's
back that way.
I don't have time
for this, John.
Oliver...
has it occurred to you that
whatever happens in this crisis
happens because you push
the people closest to you away?
So you're in a forward area.
Somebody throws a grenade
right into the middle of your platoon.
What do you do?
I jump on it.
I contain the blast.
That's what I'm doing.
I can't prevent whatever
it is that's going to happen to me,
but I will be damned if I'm going to put
other people at risk.
And I will be damned
if I just let you
go gently into that good night.
Okay.
All right.
You always fall
for this move.
Wow. That Lian Yu
must have been one hell of a place...
Oliver.
So were you ever
really gone?
Because it looks like
you've been running around
in a certain green hood.
Like you've been running
around in a black one?
Heh. Ah, Ollie, you never should've
gotten yourself involved in this.
Hope I didn't hurt you.
Leave us.
So I've been
thinking it over,
and you really were
on Lian Yu,
because if you had been here,
you would've been
protecting our sister.
So the question is,
why are you running around
in The Hood's hood?
- Doesn't matter.
- Yes, it does!
The Hood is running around
this city, thinking that
he's saving it,
and nothing can save it.
You don't understand
the cancer
that has taken over
this city.
Oh, my God. This is
the Undertaking.
You stole the dwarf star
particles because you want...
to destroy the Glades
and get vengeance for Thea.
How could you know that?
And what happened
to you on that island?
What happened to you
while I was on the island?
While you were gone,
this city has been rotting.
It can't be saved!
That's not true, Tommy.
I have seen
Starling City come back
from darker moments
than this.
It can be redeemed.
You can be redeemed.
You don't understand
what I've seen.
You don't know
how I found our sister.
Every time I close my eyes,
I see her body lying there, cold,
on a dirty floor.
So I swore that I would get
vengeance on the Glades
for what it did to Thea,
and I am not going to let
her down. Not again!
That's not gonna make
you feel better, Tommy.
I don't care about
feeling better.
I just want the Glades
to suffer.
You're a better man
than this.
That was a different me.
Good-bye, Oliver.
Tonight was a disaster.
You mean you were.
JJ never would've gotten past us
if you hadn't abandoned your post.
Oh, you think this is
my fault?
What I think is that you need
to stop going rogue
and start acting like
you're part of this team.
Hey, guys, can we save it
for the Deathstrokes?
Speaking of your evil brother
and his masked maniacs,
we're gonna talk
about that, right?
Wrong. What do you got?
Nothing good. Ever since
we brought down the wall, your broth...
the Deathstroke gang has
really upped their game.
They've amassed more territory
and power than ever before.
Unintended
consequences.
Yeah. But that doesn't explain
why they went after Vasquez.
Vasquez is one of the Glades'
wealthiest citizens.
Maybe the Deathstrokes
plan to extort him.
Yeah, that or they're
planning to ransom him off.
Either way, this guy's screwed
if we don't find him soon.
Way ahead of you.
Satellite imaging indicates
that the Deathstrokes
have assumed control
of the old Galaxy One headquarters.
It could be where they're
holding Vasquez.
If he's even
still alive.
There's only one
way to find out. Suit up.
Let me guess. When Mom and
O.G. Team Arrow anointed us version 2.0,
you expected things to go
a little better, right?
I'm sure they had
their growing pains, too.
I know that working
and playing well
with others is still
a new concept for you,
but do you think
you could just follow
Connor's lead this one time?
I mean, the guy is
a Knightwatch agent.
He eats, sleeps,
and breathes tactical operations.
Yeah. And our target
is his own brother.
I believe that fate brought
the four of us together for a reason
just like it
did our parents
when they decided
to save this city.
Now it's our turn.
We don't want to mess
it up, do we?
How'd you find me?
- Tracking your shoe.
- Really?
Just kidding. That was
the way I found you
last time this
happened, remember?
Yeah. Yeah. It's not the only
history that's repeating itself.
Tommy's planning his
very own Undertaking.
Don't worry. We'll stop him.
John, I appreciate
the assist,
but I still have to
do this on my own.
Right, because you think
you have to die, right?
No. I know
I'm gonna die.
And I know that I don't
have to accept that.
If I let you help me,
you will get hurt or you will get killed.
And it will be
because of me.
- You don't know that.
- I do know that.
Because everyone else
in my life is either dead or alone.
Look at the Earth
that we're on.
I've been gone 12 years.
My mother's alive.
Tommy's alive.
Laurel's alive.
Thea is dead.
And, yes, Tommy's alive.
But he's trying another Undertaking
with Rene and Dinah helping,
who, if you haven't noticed,
are very bad people here.
Oliver, this world
isn't better.
It's much, much worse.
You know why?
Because you weren't in it.
I've known you long enough to know
I can't talk you out of this.
You better have
a good plan.
Oh, look who it is,
and you brought a friend
to my secret bunker.
I've been here before.
Oh, great.
You're here, too.
Uh, Adrian,
this is John Diggle.
He's my... bodyguard.
You need a bodyguard?
He's not a bodyguard.
And I thought you
didn't need our help.
I've been wrong before.
The Dark Archer stole dwarf star particles
and is planning to use them
to level the Glades tonight.
And you know that how?
Because I
was just with him.
Tommy Merlyn is
the Dark Archer.
Are you sure?
He blames the Glades for
what happened to Thea.
If you wanted to level
an entire neighborhood,
how would you do it?
I'd use
an Earthquake machine.
That sounds like
science fiction to me.
And Merlyn stole
dwarf star particles,
which would make for
a very real weapon.
Overlaying the blast radius
with a map of the Glades
should allow us to pinpoint
its optimal location.
He's like you, Curtis,
and Felicity all rolled up in one.
I could only narrow it
down to 4 square blocks.
So we split up,
find it on foot.
No, we don't. Thea
died in the Glades.
We find out where,
we find Tommy.
What are you,
some kind of psychic?
Maybe I'm just
10 steps ahead of you.
4587 Burke,
favorite hangout of
the Glades' worst drug dealers.
Good. That's where we head.
Suit up.
Tommy could be anywhere inside.
Start at the ground floor.
Work our way up.
Let's do this.
You should've stayed
on that island.
Back on my Earth,
you had a better teacher.
You don't
have to do this.
I was thinking
the same thing.
This is not what Thea
would have wanted.
That's funny. You know
what she used to say?
The dead don't want
anything.
It's one of the benefits
of being dead.
Tommy.
You can't. It's encrypted
by my personal code.
You can't break it in time.
You can.
I know how devastating
it must have been
to lose Thea because
we're only as good
as the people we have
in our lives.
I lost people, too,
Tommy.
I lost people
closer to me
than I could possibly
explain to you.
Every one of those losses
brings with it a choice
between darkness
and light.
Make the right
choice.
Are you gonna kill thousands
of innocent people,
or are you gonna be the man
I know you are?
That was
a pretty good speech.
As agreed. The dwarf star particles
that power Merlyn's weapon.
Thank you.
And now you're gonna tell me
what you're gonna do with them?
Not destroy a city.
Don't worry.
You're from a parallel universe,
aren't you?
The Hood from
another reality?
How did you know
that?
Bruce Wayne once told me
that if you eliminate the impossible,
whatever remains, however improbable,
must be the truth.
Well, as The Hood from
a parallel universe,
may I offer you
some advice?
Change "The Hood" to
Green Arrow.
Trust me.
Why do I get the sense
that you guys
won't be sticking around
for a victory drink?
We have to get
back home to our Earth.
This city's lucky to have
a hero like you in it.
Wow. That might be the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
Thank you.
You take care of yourself...
both of you.
You okay?
I'm alive.
You say that like it's
a bad thing.
Well, it's a temporary
thing, John.
Oliver, you
don't know that.
And I don't know this
Monitor, but what I do know,
that no one's fate
is sealed.
- He saw me die.
- In the future...
which means we can still
prevent this.
Oliver, you're not
alone in this.
Well, not anymore.
Thanks for having
my back.
Always.
Now, can we go home now?
Just one more thing
I got to do.
We'd better find
Vasquez fast.
Where to, William?
Top floor, southwest
corner office.
And JJ's got at least
4 friends.
The second I walk through
that door, JJ's gonna try
to run a sword
through my chest.
But that should keep him
occupied long enough
for you to rescue Vasquez.
Whoa. You're using
yourself as bait?
Yeah. And it'll work,
too. Trust me.
Whatever you want,
I'll give it to you.
Please stop.
The codes.
This better be everything.
It is. I swear.
Okay.
What's up, JJ?
- Miss me?
- Kill his ass.
Come on. Let's get you
out of here.
You think that you can
save this city?
I got news for you.
I own this city now.
Mia!
I am so sorry, okay?
I underestimated him.
It will never happen again.
No, it won't, because
from now on,
we're gonna do
things my way.
Hey.
You okay?
I don't know.
I haven't known anything
since Thea died.
I understand that.
I don't know, Ollie.
Just I... I can't shake
this feeling...
that our sister would
still be alive if you had...
if you'd just been here.
I've made my own mistakes.
Oh, God.
Tommy, are you ok?
Don't worry. We're gonna
get you out of here.
I am so sorry.
I have to go.
Mom?
Bye, mom.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hey.
I'll see you at the house.
Okay.
- All good?
- Let's go home.
What's going on?
My computer
went down!
Oh, good.
You're still here.
What's going on?
The city's under attack.
By who?
We have to get
the hell out of here.
- And go where?
- Home. Cisco's device.
- Oliver?
- Mom?
Dig, you got to
go. Go now!
What's happening?
Oliver? Oliver!
Laurel, come on.
Greg, move your head.