Oh, my God...
Oh, my God what? Who is that?
That's Tommy Merlyn.
He died over four years ago.
Oliver, who's Tommy Merlyn?
Thea's other brother.
And my best friend.
We're gonna need a moment alone.
He's a crony.
- Anachronism.
- That's what I said.
Lately, we've been dealing
with Anachronisms.
It's people and things
displaced throughout time.
Okay, but why would Nazis from 1945
want to crash my wedding?
Crab legs. They were delicious.
Well, Iris has a point though.
If they're out of time,
they would have targeted
the military or law enforcement.
Tommy was plucked from five years ago
and put in the Prometheus wardrobe.
That doesn't make any sense.
It does if we're not dealing
with an Anachronism.
Visitors from another Earth?
What, there are more than one?
There are 52, actually.
Though I'm hard-pressed to think
of one where Nazis are ascendant.
I can.
There's a 53rd Earth.
And it's called Earth-X.
It doesn't have a designation
because it's a place so awful,
so horrific,
no sane person
would ever travel there.
It's basically our Earth,
same history, same timeline with
one crucial and critical difference.
Let me hypothesize.
The Nazis developed the atomic bomb
before the United States did
and they were more than happy
to use it?
Yes. The Nazis won the war.
And New York, London, Paris
and Moscow were all obliterated.
The SS set up outposts not only
all throughout Europe
but also all throughout the Americas,
and Hitler continued his brutal reign,
aided by prime ministers
and presidents sympathetic to him,
until his death
in 1994.
Now they're not happy ruling
just one Earth.
God, this is making me
physically ill.
Yeah, line starts behind me.
We have to find them.
I mean, do you think they're using
the breach to hop between worlds?
That, or they're operating
from a staging area,
somewhere in Central City
or close by.
Well, good thing we have a metric ton
of smart people in this building.
And Rory.
Let's get to work on finding
our new friends from Earth-X.
- Earth-X.
- That's right.
And I'm dead on this Earth?
That's right.
I'd almost prefer that.
I was born into the Reich.
The whole world is the Fatherland.
We don't have elementary schools
and summer camps.
We have youth groups
and military training.
We all grow up without choice.
You have a choice now.
You can tell me where to find
the others from Earth-X.
On my Earth, you are my best friend.
I would die for you.
I would have died for you.
- "Would have"?
- You beat me to it.
I lost you. It was like...
It was like losing a limb and...
You weren't just my best friend.
Tommy, you were my brother
and you sacrificed yourself
for a woman that we both loved
and I was there
and I had you right here.
You were a good man here.
And I believe
that you still can be.
No, you don't understand.
If I talk...
If I break, the Führer will kill
my father. He'll kill my mother.
Everyone that I love...
I will not let that happen.
I will stop him.
Do you think you can do that?
I promise you that I can do that.
Then you really are
a special kind of idiot.
Your naivete would be charming
if your weakness wasn't so pathetic.
Is this how it is on your planet?
Everybody's swayed by sentiment?
Is everyone here really so weak?
The Reich will change that.
The weak will be eliminated.
Your entire world will be enslaved.
But you, you...
You won't be around
to witness it.
He is going to feel your skull crack
under the weight of his boot.
Everyone you care about,
everyone you love,
they're gonna die badly.
In ways that would give
even monsters nightmares.
I really wish that I
could live to see it.
No! Tommy, don't!
He's gone.
Who? Merlyn?
The biosensor in his suit indicates
his heart stopped.
He always seemed kinda soft to me.
- Oliver...
- He died for you.
And we will make
his death worthwhile.
That doesn't change the fact
that now we're down a man.
Keep your focus where it belongs.
And get to work on locating
that Prism.
Watch your tone.
Or I'll watch it for you.
Oliver!
Did you just tell me
to watch my tone?
You're angry...
- And I like it.
- Don't you mock me.
Don't threaten me.
Or have you forgotten...
I could end your life
before you birth your next thought.
Try it, once I break
every bone in your body.
Okay.
We're all a little emotional.
Here's what I suggest.
I will stop vibrating my hand,
you stop breaking my wrist,
and you...
Be 10% less brooding.
We accomplish nothing by arguing
amongst ourselves.
It's the accomplishing nothing
that has me concerned.
We came here to conquer this Earth,
or have you forgotten?
Locate the Prism.
Please.
Once we have identified
the location of the target,
I will devise a plan of attack.
I'm sorry about Merlyn.
He should've died in the church
before he allowed himself
to be captured.
Kara, we need that Prism.
We are running out of time.
You have to trust
in the plan, Oliver.
You should. It's yours.
And do you trust me?
Yes, with all of my heart.
You're kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
This feels like a really bad
wedding prank.
- No, I wish.
- Do you want us to come there?
I mean, Digg's on the mend
but Dinah, Rene, and I
can be up there in a...
What's another word for "flash"?
No, I need you guys in the bunker,
expanding our search
for the Earth-Xers.
I linked S.T.A.R. Labs' system
up with ours
so you can know what's going on
as we do.
Copy that.
I will get to work on hacking
Palmer Tech's spectrometers
to help the search for Nazis.
See you soon.
Hey, Caitlin and Wells are trying
to track down the Earth-Xers
using some sort of
dimensional something.
Vibrations.
I told Curtis to do the same thing
with quantum field analysis.
- I'm sorry about Tommy.
- That wasn't Tommy.
He said that they are trying
to mount some sort of invasion.
I guess the silver lining
to Black Siren
is that we have experience
with doppelgangers.
So, if it's not Tommy I'm reading
on your face, what's up?
You know what it is.
Well, maybe we should wait
until we repel invaders
from another Earth
to have this conversation.
Remember when we got back from Ivy Town?
Do you remember Ivy Town?
Mmm. So fondly.
When we got back,
you said that we could do this
and we could still have our lives.
- That was you.
- Yeah.
So, um...
This impending invasion
notwithstanding,
may we take two minutes
and talk about this?
Yeah.
So maybe what wasn't fair was me
saying I didn't want to marry you.
I mean, not the way I did.
Not with the most terrible timing
in the world.
Well, was it how I said it?
Because I know that it was really...
I mean, it was spontaneous.
It was so lovely.
It was so sweet.
I love you.
I just don't want to be married.
I don't...
Want to be married to anyone.
You didn't feel that way when we got
engaged two years ago.
Right, and then 10 minutes later,
I got shot and paralyzed.
Barry and Iris have a wedding
and Nazis crash it.
You didn't know that was going
to happen
when you said you didn't want
to marry me.
My point is...
We have something so good.
We have something so great going.
Let's not change that.
Let's just stand pat
with the cards that we're holding.
I want to move forward.
Felicity, I love you
and I want to marry you.
I love you.
I love you. I will always,
always, always love you.
Please respect me on this.
Okay.
Thank you.
Felicity's got her friend working
on Palmer Technologies'
spectrometry satellites...
Okay, but what about the Waverider?
I mean, a time traveling space ship
must have some sort of
tracking technology that we can use.
Yeah, not exactly.
It's in the Stone Age.
Like, literally in the Stone Age.
Okay, well, Parallel Earth jumping
is kind of Cisco's specialty.
Well, since he's so busy being
unconscious right now, I guess
we're on our own.
Oh, perfect timing, man.
We're trying to find the guys
from Earth-X and
we're coming up with nothing.
I'm sorry. Would you excuse us
for a moment?
Happily.
We don't wanna step on whatever...
- Come on, Harry. It's not about you.
- ...awkward, awkward thing that is.
Grey, we got Nazis
from a parallel Earth running around.
- We don't have time...
- Which is precisely why
we cannot afford to be at odds
with each other right now.
I hardly need a psychic connection
to know that you're upset with me.
- But I could stand to know why.
- Just forget about it, man.
It would make some sense if my
decision to be with my family
forced you to leave the Waverider.
But I accounted for that variable
and yet you're still upset.
- You just don't get it...
- No, I don't get it.
My retirement requires you
to give up nothing.
It requires me to give up you, Grey.
Look, I thought I made
my peace with it.
I thought, okay, fine,
I'll stay on the Waverider.
Maybe I can't be Firestorm,
but I can still be a Legend.
But then it hit me.
I still can't be Firestorm,
and I can't be a Legend with you.
I never knew my father.
But I got to know you.
You're the closest thing
I've got to a dad, and...
Now you're leaving.
Hey.
- Hey.
- How are you?
Well, punching Nazis.
That was definitely as satisfying
as I imagined it would be.
You okay?
Yeah. Oh, me?
No, I'm okay.
I'm completely okay.
- I'm okay, okay. Okay.
- Okay.
Okay.
This isn't going to be
a thing, right?
Yeah, no, no, no.
I'm okay, I'm good.
Hey, I was looking for you.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
Why is everybody asking me
that question?
Well, you sort of look like
you just killed someone's puppy.
Uh, no. I'm fine.
It's just this whole thing
with Sara.
God, it was a mistake.
A mistake? But...
You came here to have fun
at a wedding and...
Okay, Nazi invaders aside,
you had a good time, right?
No. I mean,
this was all kinds of wrong.
Waking up with a strange woman
in a strange bed?
I have never had
a one night stand before.
And this whole thing is just...
It's got me spinning.
Kara, I mean, what...
What if I made a huge mistake?
- No...
- Okay, no, no, no. I mean, look,
I know, I wanna have kids.
But Maggie was real.
I mean, what we had, that was real.
And now, with everything,
I just...
I chose to let her go.
I chose that.
I mean, what was I thinking?
Alex, Maggie was amazing.
And you two were amazing together
but the best part about her
was that she showed you
how to be true to yourself.
You want kids. She doesn't.
You just had to do
what was right for you.
What if I was wrong?
How long till you brainiacs
find these Nazis?
My answer hasn't changed in the two
minutes since you last asked me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dealing with some Oliver stuff.
Not "Nazis ruined the happiest day
of our life" stuff, but stuff.
Stuff like, "You don't want
to marry him" stuff?
You might've said it a little loudly
at the rehearsal dinner.
What happened?
I thought at the salon,
you said you guys were good.
We are good. We're great.
We're just as...
We're just as good as we were
the last time we got engaged
and I got shot.
That was the beginning
of the end for us.
I don't want to tempt fate again.
You know?
Break-in at Dayton Optical Systems.
I know this sounds terrible,
but maybe we should let the police
handle it.
I mean, we need our peeps
to focus on the Nazis.
- This is Nazis.
- How do you know?
I'll go get Barry.
Yeah, okay.
Just a quick reminder.
Super-speed.
I don't have it.
Noted.
So, what do we know about this place?
Why are the Earth-Xers targeting it?
Because...
They had something we need.
Whatever you stole...
We're gonna want it back.
Your confidence is predictable.
You've faced some of the greatest
evils known to man.
And you've defeated them.
But if you think so highly
of yourselves,
that you can defeat any threat
that comes your way...
How do you feel about us?
This is sick.
To be looking at your reflection
and seeing only weakness?
I agree.
- Thawne.
- Direct from Earth-1.
Do you like my face?
It's the face you were wearing
when I became the Flash.
I thought I'd put it on again.
You know, for old times' sake.
Plus, handsome.
- I watched you die.
- Or did you?
It's time travel, Barry.
So very confusing. I always seem
to be saying that to you, don't I?
Tommy killed himself.
I heard your Tommy died years ago.
That's what this Earth does.
Makes people soft.
We've been watching you.
We've been watching all of you.
And how you've squandered
the potential of two worlds.
On our Earth, we've developed
a meritocracy.
We've accomplished greatness.
You're perverse.
No, Kara, you're the perversion.
The most powerful being
on the planet
rendered weak by
saccharine Americana.
My pod was blessed to crash
in the Fatherland.
Then go back there.
This is not your Earth.
Leave.
I don't answer to the likes of you.
My allegiance is to the Fatherland
and to my wife.
His wife? Gross.
No offense.
Last chance.
Go home.
And stay there.
All of you.
And what do you think
that's going to do?
Bullets bounce off of me.
No, this arrow won't.
Is that a Kryptonite arrow?
Why do you have a Kryptonite arrow?
In case an evil you ever showed up.
Get the Prism out of here.
- Are you all right?
- I'm pissed.
Take it out on that.
It's gonna fall.
All right, get me over there.
Get the workers to safety!
We need to stabilize the building.
- Site's clear.
- And stabilized.
- Nice work.
- Let's not celebrate just yet.
We gave those doppelgangers
the window they needed to escape.
Escape with what?
Dayton Optical Systems
calls it "the Prism."
What on Earth do they need
a sub-light generator for?
It's basically a spectral emitter...
Which uses quantum entanglement.
They could also use it to create
a stable fusion reaction.
Okay, which all means what?
No, guys, really, I'd like to know
what you're talking about.
You got this.
Well, basically the device they stole
can be converted into a neutron bomb.
Boom...
I take it back.
The bottom line is
that we have to catch
these parallel Earth goose-steppers.
This might help.
Is that a Kryptonite arrow?
- Yup.
- I know I shouldn't have to ask
this question, but I have to ask
this question.
- Oliver didn't shoot Kara, did he?
- Sort of.
The other archer and flying woman
are Oliver and Kara of Earth-X.
When you said that Earth-X
was "horrible,"
you might've been under-sold it.
Wait a minute.
How could there be another Kara?
There are 53 Karas.
Just like there's 53 Kryptons
and 53 Earths.
And the Thawne from our Earth
is working with them.
He's an idiot.
If that arrow has Not-So-
Supergirl's blood on it...
We could track it using
quantum analysis.
- We could.
- Hey, guys.
I think I might have a quicker way.
These red blood cells are suffused
with short-wave radiation.
- Solar radiation?
- Yeah. Incredibly high amounts.
Like nothing I've ever seen.
Can you track it?
Well, I once caught a deranged serial
killer off his face cream, so...
- No joke.
- Let's just do it. Fast.
Okay.
Will it work?
It will.
With a few adjustments.
And a significant power source.
My husband's on his way
to handle that as we speak.
Your husband has a choice to make.
Me or the Reich?
That's right.
Because we have two goals.
And my worry is,
if we can't accomplish them both,
he's gonna choose you
over a second Earth flying
under our banner.
Oliver will not abandon our mission.
I've seen this before in 1945.
Hitler and his men
were equally short-sighted.
Hitler was driven by passion
and childish need.
Oliver is 10 times
the man Hitler ever was.
Not when he's blinded
by his love for you.
If it comes to Oliver choosing
between me and the Reich,
I'll make sure he chooses
the Fatherland.
- How?
- If it comes to it,
by taking the choice
out of his hands.
Maybe tracking her off of face cream
would have been easier.
Supergirl-X's blood
is filled with solar radiation,
more than it should be.
But if I can try to get that to act
as a kind of beacon...
Hey, um...
- How do you do it?
- Do what, Rory?
Bring the other you out of you.
- You don't wanna know.
- Sure I do.
It happens when I'm scared or angry.
So, if I were to, um... Boo!
Nice try.
Boom.
Whatever's going on
with Kara-X's blood,
- it's intensifying.
- Worse for her is better for us.
Better for us for tracking her,
at least.
We should have her location
any minute.
I can't believe he's back.
I don't know if I'll ever be
rid of him.
I know.
I know how much you're hurting.
I just keep looking for closure
but every time I see him,
all I see is...
Your mother dying.
You're going to stop him.
- How do you know?
- Because you always do.
And because we're not going
to let you do it alone.
Getting close on a location.
Look, guys. I'm sorry. This is not
how this week was supposed to go.
We can't think about that right now.
You should. We fight to protect
the people that we love,
so you guys, recognize what you have.
Recognize it and cherish it
and let it make you stronger.
'Cause if you do that,
you'll always find
your way back to one another.
It's the same for you
and Felicity, man.
I don't know, Barry. I...
She told me she doesn't believe
in marriage.
I'm not feeling sorry for myself,
I just...
I think that if she loved me
the way I loved her,
she would wanna marry me.
Oliver, I've known Felicity
for five years.
And I'm here to tell you,
as sure as I'm standing here,
- she loves you.
- Felicity...
- I appreciate that, guys.
- Just turn.
She's right there.
We got 'em.
They're at a shipping depot
outside Danville.
All right. We'll get the band
back together.
Yeah.
- Oliver...
- It's okay.
We can talk when I'm back.
Right now I need to have my head
in the game.
Get your head in the game.
Supergirl and Firestorm
are sweeping the perimeter.
It's done.
It's wall-to-wall Nazis in there.
Alex and I will take up breach
positions on the northwest corner.
If that's okay with you?
S.T.A.R. Labs thinks they converted
the sub-light generator,
the Prism that they've stolen,
into some kind of super-weapon.
Speaking of "super,"
theirs is our biggest threat.
Agreed. Let's take her out first.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
No.
- You know?
- Yeah.
It's gonna be okay.
Mustard. You people have breaches
but no mustard.
Um, what are you even doing here?
Yeah, why didn't you go with them?
Go where?
Halt!
Couldn't have left one for me?
I'm saving Nazi you for you.
There's no sign of the Prism.
Well, it's gotta be here somewhere.
We got incoming.
Stay where you are!
I see...
Their Flash, their Supergirl.
Yeah, I see them.
Where's their Arrow?
It was in the fridge.
- Did you check the fridge?
- Oh, thank you, sweetheart.
Any word from the team?
No, they're at the shipping depot
but it's just radio silence.
Oh, God.
There is no God.
You and you, hide.
What about Caitlin?
It's gonna get a lot colder in here.
Burn.
Afraid of a little heat?
No.
I'm afraid of nothing.
Bet you're pretty angry
and scared right now!
I told you. I don't fear anything.
Actually...
He was talking about me.
Didn't think this through, did you?
Just you. Against us.
I don't need to think to kill you.
Anyone else want to be a hero?
They wanted to wait,
but I don't think we'll ever get
a better entry line than that.
Thanks.
What the hell is that?
Metallo.
Hate to do this
to that handsome face but...
Is everyone all right?
We're gonna have to work on your
definition of "all right," Oliver.
Yo, Grey, you good?
It seems my "retirement"
was somewhat tardy.
Well...
Here we are.
This is fun for me.
Not so much for you.
All the times you've killed me,
and now here,
all I have to do is kill you once.
Enough, Eobard.
Enough.
Hey, you might wanna listen to her.
We know that if you wanted to kill us
you wouldn't have put
these dog collars on us first.
Now I know what it feels
like to hate myself.
Well done.
It wasn't a problem.
The pain... The pain.
I don't know how much longer
I can bear it.
It's all right. It's all right.
You're gonna be all right
because we found her.
We found her.
And now we have her.
I love you.
Now, very soon,
this nightmare will be over,
and I'll take you home.
So stand.
S.T.A.R. Labs is secure.
- If you hurt my friends...
- I did hurt your friends.
I really enjoyed hurting
your friends.
Are they alive?
Yes. Yes, for now.
We need your Kara's cooperation.
Well, we don't need it.
It would be preferable.
But for the time being,
you're more valuable as leverage.
- What do you want my sister for?
- To save my life.
That's your little mission statement,
isn't it?
Help people, save lives.
Well, now's your chance.
The General is dying.
Her blood. She's been exposed
to too much solar radiation.
Yes. Like Icarus,
I flew too close to the sun.
But we can save her.
We're going to save her.
All we need is a new heart.
And luckily,
on this planet we found
the perfect donor.
You stay the hell away
from my sister.
Hmm.
Such loyalty.
My sister tried to kill me.
That's why you stole the Prism?
So you can duplicate a red sun,
weaken Kara and cut into her?
You can't make an omelette
with invulnerable eggs.
Hey...
I'm going to kill you.
No, you won't.
You're weak.
And all of you choose the high road.
You're heroes.
I thought we were gonna die.
If I had a dime for every time
I thought that...
I'd have two dollars and forty cents.
I really thought I'd have
more than that.
It was Oliver. But it wasn't Oliver.
- Is Oliver in the High Castle?
- I just mean...
There's so much out there
for us to be afraid of.
Multiple Earths. Aliens.
Doppelgangers from the Third Reich.
I mean, what else is coming?
And that thought
wakes me up at night.
How do you ever
get back to sleep?
- Barry's by my side.
- Shut up.
- I'm sorry, I know you and Oliver...
- No.
Shut up.
We're not alone.
Stalag S.T.A.R. Labs.
What are we gonna do?
Kara... Where's Kara?
They're going to kill her.
It's okay. We're gonna get her back.
We need to figure out
where we are first.
Yeah. About that...
This is somewhat disconcerting.
I don't think this is our Earth.
We're on Earth-X.