My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its Mayor.
But by night, I am someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Former Police Captain, Quentin Lance.
Who'll be serving beside me
as Deputy Mayor.
Appreciate the vote of confidence,
Mr. Mayor.
- Are you not from Star City?
- No. Havenrock.
There's something
that I need you to know.
Havenrock was not the intended target.
Someone redirected the missile
to reduce the number of casualties.
That someone was me.
- Ever since I killed Andy...
- You think you need to be punished.
Stop fighting for me, Lyla.
We need to talk about John. He's back
in the country. And he's in prison.
And I need you to break him out.
Come on, Mr. Olympia. Hustle up.
Mr. Olympia is a bodybuilding competition.
I was... Am an Olympic athlete.
Yeah?
They give out gold medals for effort now?
Very funny.
And it was a bronze medal.
Why is that so hard to remember?
Quiet. Every time you're out in the field,
you could die.
Don't forget that. Don't lose focus.
Overwatch, do we have the target?
Headed towards the east exit,
closing fast.
- Do we know what he stole?
- Not yet.
But I have a feeling
we're about to find out.
Only if we snag him in the cordon.
Artemis, be ready.
Does this mean
I actually get to shoot someone?
I mean, not, you know, shoot someone,
shoot someone. I just meant more that...
We know what you meant.
You wait for him to reach the cordon,
- then engage. Do you copy?
- Copy.
- Copy. Still a lot of ground to cover.
Rag should be here.
Overwatch, do you have
a 20 on Ragman?
I texted him, like, 10 times,
and then 10 more, but nada.
Maybe he's sick.
I mean, the flu's been going around.
And by the looks of those rags,
he does not hit the dry cleaner
very often.
- Hola, muchacho.
- Wild Dog, that is Artemis' shot.
I got him. What the...
I got him.
What did I say? That was Artemis' shot!
- Dude was getting away.
- No, he wasn't.
And you missed.
You were in the Navy,
you should know better.
I was dishonorably discharged, actually.
Do you think that I don't know that?
Deliver that and the evidence
to the Anti-Crime Unit and then go home.
- What about tonight's training session?
- You're taking a few days off.
Nice going. Again.
How we supposed to get this guy
to the ACU? Call an Uber?
Oliver?
The op's over and you've been MIA
for days. It's not acceptable.
Get it together immediately,
or you're off the team.
That's why I'm here,
to tell you in person.
I'm off the team.
Feels pretty quick to throw in the towel.
I thought you were just getting started.
I was, and then Felicity told me the truth
about her role in Havenrock.
You didn't know she told me.
Did she also tell you that she was faced
with an impossible choice?
I completely realize that.
I get it wasn't her fault.
But that doesn't change
the fact that every time I look at her,
I see the faces of my family,
of everyone I ever loved.
Felicity is a constant reminder
of what I lost.
And as long as that's true, I'm sorry,
I can't be here.
What about your father?
I thought he was the reason
you were doing this.
I'll have to find another way
to honor him.
- I'm sorry to lose you.
- And I'm sorry to go.
Thank you. For everything.
Did my comms deceive me,
or did you actually let the recruits take
an SCPD victory lap?
It's never a victory lap.
They're rough around the edges,
but they're making progress.
Except Rory, who was waiting for me
upstairs to say that he quit.
He said you spoke with him
about Havenrock.
He'!-
- How you holding up?
- She doesn't know?
About John being in prison?
Oliver told me. I'm so sorry.
What Lyla means...
We are going to break him out.
- Of military prison?
- Yeah.
Wait, and then what? John is just
a fugitive for the rest of his life?
Better than being punished for something
he didn't do.
Well, I've been studying the schematics
that you hooked me up with.
This would be a lot easier
if we had John's cooperation.
You don't have what now?
Apparently prison
is more appealing to John
than coming home
to his own wife and child.
Okay, so wait a minute. Not only do you
want to commit multiple felonies,
and make John a wanted man for the rest of
his life, he doesn't actually want you to?
- Can I speak with you for a minute?
- Yeah.
- Is she going to be a problem?
- No.
But I was counting on her being a help.
Maybe I should pull
a few of my agents in on this.
Lyla, if this has your fingerprints on it,
then both of John, Jr.'s parents
will be fugitives.
There is something that might actually
make this not impossible.
I just read a briefing memo on a new piece
of tech, an anti-molecular compound.
I was kind of hoping Felicity
could help us get our hands on it...
Lyla. Whatever it is, I'll handle it.
Second test over.
Do not make any worse
by pulling out sutures.
Anatoly, if this is how the Bratva
treat their new members,
I'd hate to see
how they treat their enemies.
Pass third and final test, find out.
- What's the test?
- You keep asking about Kovar.
Our sources say this man
will get you one step closer.
You have to act fast though.
He will be arraigned in morning.
- Arraigned?
- Jail.
Yeah.
But what makes you think he'll talk to me?
You trust me. I trust you.
It's a little early for a drink,
don't you think?
Is not for drinking.
Anatoly, what the hell was that for?
I should probably just start pre-recording
apologies for being late.
Don't worry. Thea told us. I'm sorry, man.
Gout is a bitch.
Yes, it is.
I'm actually going to be taking some
time off to have it taken care of.
Well, fortunately, we now have
a Deputy Mayor to help pick up the slack.
It'll be great working with you. You've
had an impressive career, Mr. Lance.
Yeah. I mean, a lot of people out there
probably wouldn't share that opinion,
but thank you.
Public service isn't easy.
Sometimes you get a little dirty
clearing out the filth.
Speaking of which,
I heard there was an arrest last night
that may help
in our case against Tobias Church?
Sergio Espinosa. Long-time Los Halcones
member turned Church strong man.
The Green Arrow
and his merry band of vigilantes
left him giftwrapped for us at Anti-Crime.
The only thing that was missing was a bow.
- You don't sound too happy about that.
- Vigilantes are a superficial solution.
If we need their help
to get our streets clean...
It means we haven't done our jobs right.
Do you think that you can get Espinosa
to flip on Church?
I'll lean on him hard, see if he buckles.
Make sure he doesn't get any help
from crooked cops.
Not a chance.
I'm gonna walk every piece of evidence
in the custody chain through myself.
Good. Uh, if it's all right with you,
I'll have Quentin accompany you.
Be my eyes and ears while I'm out of town.
Sure. Give us a little bit of time
to get acquainted.
Hmm.
- Great.
- Yeah.
Um...
Sorry, when did, uh, babysitting evidence
become part of the job description?
Since I trust you.
You do?
I mean, all things considered...
If we didn't think you were right for the
job, we wouldn't have offered it to you.
Right?
I haven't had a drink in a week, okay?
Where the hell are you going, anyway?
Strange time for a vacation.
You should probably assume
that it's not a vacation.
Should I even ask?
No. I'm not gonna be gone long.
Just please make sure that no one
destroys the city while I'm away.
- Sure.
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Reviewing the SCPD evidence log
on what we kept from getting stolen from
Kord Industries last night.
- A 6800 processor.
- So?
Exactly. Kord manufactures bleeding-edge
tech, military-grade weapons.
I mean,
all kinds of city-threatening items.
Why would Church send a guy to steal
a computer chip
that you could buy
from any Tech Village store?
Well, who cares?
Everything's on its way to lock-up now.
Well, because knowing what
Church's endgame was is like...
It's like this thing that's
still out there. Lurking.
You all right over there?
Because I've been doing a lot of talking
and you haven't.
Which is very weird.
You know how you
told me to tell Rory about Havenrock?
Yeah? Oh, he's not sick
with the flu, is he?
No. He's just
sick of working with me.
Did you try talking to him?
There's not a lot I can say
that would make him feel okay
about his entire family being killed.
Incoming. Another robbery in progress at...
Palmer Tech. Gotta call Oliver.
Or maybe don't
and we just let them get robbed.
It'll serve Mr. Dennis right
for firing us.
- He fired me. You quit.
- Because he fired you. Same thing.
Hey, Sanchez,
you got anything?
Nada.
Okay, I'll kill the alarm.
What's up?
Hey, there's been a break-in
at Palmer Tech. Are you still in the area?
Uh, yeah. I can look into that.
How was Palmer Tech?
Before you answer, you should consider
that your phone has GPS.
And if you were thinking of lying,
I do admire your consistency.
I wasn't thinking of lying to you.
I wasn't looping you in after you made it
clear you didn't approve of the decision.
John is the one
who doesn't approve of the plan.
- John is not thinking clearly.
- Well, I bet Roy is.
And if he were here,
I think he would tell you
that life on the run is no life at all.
And I seem to remember you not being
on board with that plan.
Roy was making a bad choice.
Just like John is making a bad choice.
He is currently locked up in a military
prison for a crime he didn't commit.
To atone for a crime that he did commit.
And what does it matter?
John doesn't want to leave.
It is not your choice.
Why do you always have to go
and make decisions for him?
He already abandoned the team.
Lam not going to let him
abandon his family.
Is that what this is about?
John leaving the team?
This is simple.
Lam gonna stop John from making
a decision he will come to regret.
You should consider doing
the exact same thing with Rory.
You do realize that me having
a chat with Rory
is completely different than you
committing half a dozen felonies, right?
Did you ever think you'd be doing
this again? Handling evidence?
No. Didn't think I'd be
Deputy Mayor either, but here we are.
I was surprised you took the job,
to be honest.
From what I hear, you and Queen
have a, uh, complicated history.
Gotta be a lot of hatchets to bury there.
Yeah, well,
at least I know where they're buried.
That's something you can't buy or steal.
Package is here, boss.
D.A., Deputy Mayor too.
Ah, bonus. Get ready to move.
Let me guess. Felicity filled you in.
That you're going to break
into a military prison, yeah.
And you got the nerve to call me
"Wild Dog."
- I'm done debating this.
- Really?
Because this is the first we've heard
of it. I thought we were your team.
Running off to bust someone out of
prison sounds like team business.
And what happens to us
when you get caught?
You've made it clear that we can't do
this vigilante thing without you.
When I get caught?
I'm not gonna get caught.
Right.
Because we're not gonna let you do this.
I'm sorry.
Did you say that you're not gonna
"let" me?
Yes. I need to see you physically
deposit the item.
I've been on this job 15 years.
I've never lost a piece of evidence.
Now, relax, Sergeant. No one's doubting
your proficiency here. Okay?
Seems like.
This is it.
You gonna let me do my job now?
Have at it.
What the...
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Get out of here!
Whoo!
Find the weapons, boys.
Ah.
Sorry, gents. Load them up!
And burn this puppy down.
Let's go, let's go. Get out! Go!
Okay.
Last chance.
Get off the street.
Oh!
I didn't think he'd actually hit you guys.
You know what really sucks?
Realizing that
in all those training sessions
where he was kicking our respective asses,
the whole time
he was taking it easy on us.
Yeah, remind me to never,
ever get on his bad side.
I think that would imply
that he has a good side.
And you know, Felicity, could you please
explain to me again
how you thought
this was all gonna go down?
I thought if he saw you guys all united
against his crazy plan, he'd reconsider.
Right, because Oliver Queen is known
for thinking things through
and taking input from others.
Right.
Wow.
- The ever-expanding clubhouse.
- And who are you?
- I'm Thea. Oliver's chief of staff.
- And also his sister.
- Don't tell me, Oliver beat you up too.
- Wait, Ollie did this?
Object lesson. Long story. It's fine.
Don't ask. What happened to you?
Tobias Church happened.
That "evidence" that you guys recovered
from Kord Industries?
- Modified to go boom.
- He wanted it to be put into lockup.
He wanted to raid it.
That's one-stop shopping for weapons.
Including those RPGs that he took from
AmerTek, if this report's right.
We gotta find out what he's planning
to do with those weapons
'cause it ain't nothing good.
This is a really bad time for Oliver
to be out of town.
Yeah. Just tried him. He's gone dark.
Why don't you guys hit the streets?
We wanna figure out what Church is up to
before it's too late.
- You sure?
- Mmm-hmm.
I don't think Oliver would want us
out there without him.
Right. Well, Oliver forfeited his opinion
when he left.
Okay. But this is
an "all hands on deck" situation.
Rag-covered hands included. Just saying.
Where's Private Jesseman?
This is usually his delivery.
Flu's been tearing through the base, sir.
I drew the short straw.
I don't see you on the list.
Your C.O. should have submitted
a change of personnel form.
You sure he didn't?
It's an hour's drive back to the base.
Can't you refresh your WiFi or something?
There you are. As you were, Private.
Thank you, sir.
I'm in.
Twenty-five minutes till extraction.
Roger that.
Facility's cameras
are on a closed network.
If you can get me access to the mainframe,
I can open it up.
- I'm on my way.
- Oliver.
If you don't make it
to the extraction point...
I'll make it. And I won't be alone.
Hey, do you speak English?
Yes.
Your accent, you're American?
Yeah, maybe once upon a time.
But now I'm more just enjoying
everything that Russia has to offer.
Yes, I can smell that.
W W“ Midge me...
You're in this cell, too.
Yes.
A mistake my boss will correct very soon.
You mean Konstantin Kovar?
How do you know that name?
You know, the same that way that I know
you're name's Pyotr Friedkin.
Same way I know that
you launder money for Kovar.
- Same way that I know...
- That's what you're doing here.
How can you know that? Unless...
Are you Bratva?
Huh?
He's fine.
Hmm. Hmm.
I am Bratva.
And you are going to tell me
everything that I want to know.
Your turn to run systems check.
I'm gonna hit the hay.
Don't touch my ball.
Dude. What the hell?
Transponder's in place.
Roger that. I've got eyes now.
I'll walk you to Johnny's cell.
Hey! Hey, is this a bad time?
Do I want to even ask how you found me?
I feel like that's a trick question.
Sorry about the mess.
Wow.
These are amazing!
You spend enough time
with other people's castoffs,
you find ways
to make something useful out of them.
My father always used to say that.
- He owned a pawn shop.
- On Southmoor Road, right?
How did you know?
Last week, you told Oliver that you had
joined the team to honor your father.
When you quit,
I wanted to find out more
about what you were giving up.
Your father was a Gulf War veteran.
2nd Battalion, 1st Marines.
But that's not what made him a hero,
was it?
No.
He wore your rags.
Like his father before him,
whose name was also Rory.
That's a big legacy to live up to.
Mine is going to be
what happened to Havenrock.
I'm gonna have to live with that.
Every day for the rest of my life,
knowing that I cannot fix it.
And knowing that it's not the last mistake
that I'm ever gonna have to make.
- I still don't know if I can...
- Work side by side
with someone who's a reminder
of what you lost.
I understand.
Just like you're a reminder of what I did.
And I know they're not the same thing.
We both want the same thing,
to be able to live with what's happened
so that we can move forward.
It's Curtis.
I am so sorry.
And we could really use you.
I wish I could, Felicity. I just...
I can't right now. I'm sorry.
If you change your mind, well, we're here.
Cell 1138.
Right side, third from the left.
- Harbinger, he's not here.
- Give me a minute while I scan the feeds.
- Oh, no.
- What?
They moved him into Gen Pop.
You go in there,
neither of you are getting out.
Talk to me.
When's he coming back to his cell?
Outside our window.
Those MPs wake up, the first thing
they're gonna do is move John
and all the other prisoners to a more
secure location and we lose our shot.
Abort. We're blown.
Tell me where I can find Kovar.
- You think you scare me more than him?
- No.
But he's not locked up in here with you.
I am.
You wouldn't kill me
in front of all of them.
I'm not going to lay a finger on you.
Same can't be said for Alisa.
Or maybe I'll visit your wife, Maya,
when she's picking up Alisa from ballet.
Somebody is gonna die.
It could be Kovar, it can be your wife,
it can be your child,
but I need you to choose
and do it quickly.
Kovar is very paranoid. Careful.
We never meet in person, only remotely.
Remotely how?
- A digital dead drop. The dark web.
- What's the IP address?
What is the IP address?
108.166.7.161.
If this information is incorrect,
your family will suffer.
How does an American become this?
This...
- Bratva devil.
- I don't know.
About time, blondie. Can we go now?
First of all, not my name. Second, were
you able to locate Church on your recon?
No, but street cams actually picked
him up, so we know he's on the move.
We just don't know where he's moving to.
We can't go after Church
without knowing his endgame first.
Sounds like an excuse to sit around
and do nothing.
- What are you doing?
- Not nothing.
You're cross-plotting Church's prior
locations into a projection algorithm.
You probably got beat up
in grade school a lot.
- And junior high.
- Okay, based on Church's route,
I'm calculating an 86% likelihood
he's going to 18 Mill Road.
- Why does that sound so familiar?
- Because we were just there.
To hand over Sergio.
It's where the ACU is bunkered.
Church is going to take them out.
Montes, quit screwing around.
Station Chief, this is Gans in Cell
Block C. We have a code yellow situation.
Initiate immediate lockdown,
have all prisoners return to their cells.
I'm not rolling on Church.
You think you scare me more than him?
Hmm.
No.
But he's not here with you.
Lam.
You're not gonna put a beating on me.
You're a D.A.
Nah, haven't you heard?
All of the justice in this city
comes from vigilantes.
Word on the street is,
is that Church is planning something.
Something big.
You tell me what it is, then he'll be
the one in those cuffs instead of you.
You're talking about the Trust.
Oh, you can't stop it, man.
Can't even come close.
What the hell's going on? Church?
At least we definitely know
where Church is now.
D'Angelo is right. We gotta put him down.
Against that? Without Oliver?
No, we're short-handed as it is.
- You scared?
- No.
But I'm not stupid either.
Evie's right. I'm not sending you
out there just to get slaughtered.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
You saw what you're up against, okay?
This isn't some drill where you take down
a petty thug or a drug dealer.
This is real. And with real stakes.
The three of you could die out there.
That's something we get to decide
for ourselves, isn't it?
I mean, I don't know about everyone else,
but I didn't join this team to stay safe.
Okay, why don't we take a vote?
- All those in favor...
- We're all gonna say yes, blondie.
God. Not my name!
Good. Okay. Go. Do not die.
Code yellow.
Return all prisoners to their cells.
- Hey, John. What's new?
- I'm not doing this. I told Lyla.
Yeah. You can yell at us later,
but right now we're on a bit of a clock.
Are you even hearing me, right now?
I don't want anything to do with this.
The MPs going to do a count
in a few minutes. My guess
is there're only expecting
to find one person in here.
Really? So that's your plan? Blackmail?
Do what you say
or you get caught in here too?
You're my brother, John.
What happens to you happens to me.
Oliver, I killed my brother.
I went to the Army to change,
and I haven't changed.
I know, all right?
And I know that you think
this is your penance for that...
Oliver, it's not just that.
I trusted Andy.
Even when you told me not to.
I trusted him, and now Laurel's dead.
I need you. The team needs you.
The city needs you.
I'm not saying you shouldn't do
your penance. You probably should.
But do it as Spartan.
What's in the box?
It's an anti-molecular compound,
and theoretically,
it should eat through anything.
I'm not going to ask
how you got your hands on this.
Hey, you came back for me,
even against my wishes.
I guess I haven't changed
that much either.
Maybe that's what I have to do
my penance for.
That toy of yours is definitely coming
in handy.
Project that Lyla's been keeping
an eye on for A.R.G.U.S.
Should have known
that she'd be helping out.
Tell Johnny he can thank me later.
You've got to keep moving.
Follow the sublevel north for
200 meters...
...then climb up.
- What is it?
- Comms are being jammed.
Go! Go! Go!
Hey, is there another way out of here?
You mind uncuffing me
before they kill you?
Hey.
Hey. If that's for taking out the wall,
the blast will kill us
before we can get out. We're in too tight.
- Trust me.
- Yeah. Says the creepy-looking...
- What the hell are you, anyways?
- I'm in place. Blow it.
Sorry we blew up your building. Come on!
- We're goin' up.
- Then what?
Which way, Overwatch?
Take a right at the end of that hallway,
it should be a fire exit.
You through there, you're home free. Easy.
Not so easy.
Rag! Cover me.
Go, go: go'
Let's go!
- It's okay.
- Help me get him up.
Come on.
I probably should just shoot you, but...
But you've earned a little suffering.
- Get him to safety.
- But...
- Go!
- Come on.
Hey, don't kill him.
He may have his uses.
- We've to go back for Wild Dog
- Copy. Overwatch, Mr. Terrific is hurt.
- We could use some help.
- Inbound. Hold on.
Get in!
- Where's the Wild Dog kid?
- Still inside. Fighting Church.
We've gotta go back for him.
No, unless you all want to die,
we to go now. Now!
We can't just leave him!
- You have to. Go.
- Come on!
- Here.
- What's this?
Put it on.
Let's go.
Digg, your harness.
You two, freeze!
Down on the ground.
Lace your fingers behind your head!
Do it now or we will shoot.
John, don't move.
This place should keep you off the grid
for the time being.
- Until we find a permanent solution.
- Hey, first things first...
Mmm.
I can't believe you broke me
out of prison.
- For better or worse, Johnny.
- Told you I want to stay.
And I figured if you wanted
to make your own decisions,
then you wouldn't have gotten married.
Okay. How mad was Felicity
that you went along with this?
How do you know
she thought it was a bad idea?
I know Felicity.
What's wrong?
- I have to go.
- Hey.
When you said you haven't changed?
Don't.
How was first night in Russian prison?
Friedkin gave up the dead drop and now
he's dead. Mission accomplished.
- You are being sarcasm, yes?
- That man wasn't a threat, Anatoly.
He didn't deserve to die.
In Bratva, there is no death
without purpose.
If Friedkin living, he is warning Kovar.
If he is warning Kovar,
his information not so good.
You know, maybe you could have explained
that to me before you sent me in there.
I almost didn't kill him.
But you did. Why?
Because you told me to.
You trust us.
Now we trust you.
Third test over.
You get it?
You are Bratva now. Family.
Last handful of honest cops in the city
and Church nearly took 'em out.
- Along with me.
- We're just glad you're all right.
I've gotta be thinking
this is a PR nightmare,
something like this going down
and the Mayor's MIA.
Look, he called in this morning.
His health problems are almost over.
That's good news.
We're hearing that one of
the, uh, vigilantes
who was part of the rescue,
that he didn't make it out.
- Um, any word on him?
- CSU hasn't found a body, so...
So Church has him.
I've spent most of my life thinking
that men in masks
were only capable of doing
horrible things.
I may have to reevaluate that.
- Let me know when Queen gets in.
- Will do.
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean,
I barely knew the kid, Thea.
Well, doesn't make it sting any less.
Well, yeah, sure it does.
The year I've had, this is easy.
I mean, cold as that sounds.
Look, I know why you're asking, okay?
And I'm... I'm fine.
Okay.
I mean, I'm just saying.
If things ever get less easy,
you know I'm here for you, right?
Noted.
And appreciated.
Okay.
What is the point of having
keyhole satellite imagery
if you can't use it to find anybody?
Feel like I don't understand half
the sentences you say.
What I'm saying is that no matter how
hard I try, I cannot find Rene anywhere.
I was the one who told you guys
to leave him behind.
Sounds like another impossible decision.
Does that mean I'm supposed to get better
at making them?
I'm saying you were right.
If we're going to do this,
we can't let guilt swallow us up.
I'll keep you from doing it if you promise
the same for me.
Deal.
Ow.
Ow. Ow.
So, "Ow," then?
Things have really fallen apart
without Oliver, haven't they?
It's a good thing I'm back, then.
Was he waiting for an entrance line?
Nope. He's just that cool.
I got your text.
Have we found Rene?
You get John?
Yeah. He's fine. He's holed up at HIVE.
I couldn't write him off.
And we are not gonna write off Rene.
We're gonna find him.
We're gonna bring him back.
Wherever he is.
Ah.
Wakey, wakey.
Hey, hell. Man.
Been a long time
since I've been tagged like this.
- Respect.
- Oh, my pleasure.
But I promise you, if you untie me,
I'll show you a hell of a lot
more than respect.
Ooh, man, you've got spirit
and I am duly impressed.
But I'm gonna break that spirit.
I'm gonna break your soul.
And when we're finished,
assuming that you're still alive...
Now, I wouldn't bet
no money on that, though,
there's gonna be very little of you left
for the Green Arrow to work with.
Light him up.