My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years on a hellish island...
I have come home with only one goal:
To save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on Arrow
I'm Barry Allen.
From the Central City Police Department
I'm with the Crime Scene
Investigation Unit.
I have friends that can help.
This Miracle could kill you.
It was a serum designed
to create human weapons.
You think someone found the recipe?
A centrifuge and a large supply of blood.
I think someone wants to make more of it.
- Oliver!
- Is he alive?
- We can't save him.
- Right, we can't.
Please save my friend.
- Hold him.
- He's not gonna make it.
He will. We just have find out
what's in his system.
I... I usually only work on dead people.
Barry.
Alright, I can think of
four possible diagnoses...
for what's causing his body
to react this way.
Make that three possible diagnoses.
Two.
Start chest compressions.
I need to get to his arm.
Got it. He's suffering from
intravenous coagulation.
- What?
- His blood is unnaturally clotting.
It's like maple syrup.
You can save him, right?
All right.
Lucky you guys have a rat problem.
- Are you kidding? That'll kill him.
- He dies if I don't.
- Felicity...
- Do it.
Ok, just the right amount
of this stuff will thin
his blood enough to get
it circulating again.
Let go, Oliver.
He's crashing.
Don't fight anymore.
Oliver, stay with me.
Stay with me.
- Oliver, let him go.
- Oliver.
What the hell's going on?
You were injected with a strong-acting
blood coagulant.
You would've stroked out. Ahem.
But fortunately, you had a very effective
blood thinner handy.
Warfarin, better known as rat poison.
Kid saved your life, Oliver.
This is the point in a
life-saving emergency...
where you thank the person
that did the life saving.
- You told him who I am.
- Yeah, I did.
That's not your secret to tell, Felicity.
I decide who finds out my identity.
Well, we didn't have time to get your vote
what with you unconscious and dying.
What happens if he leaves here
and goes right to the police?
- He wouldn't do that.
- I wouldn't do that.
- I trust him.
- I don't.
What are you gonna do,
put an arrow in him?
I'm considering it.
Don't worry, he's kidding. How is this any
different from when your mother shot you...
- and you came to me for help?
- Your mother shot you?
Or when you brought Dig here
when he was poisoned with Curare?
Well, the difference is that
I did my homework on both of you!
I don't just tell people easily.
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
And you don't have to
thank me, but you should
thank her instead of
being kind of a jerk.
Mr. Queen.
I have to go home.
The man that I fought in the bunker...
he has what he needs to mass-produce
the serum from the island.
And we have to stop him.
Yeah.
He touched your skin
when he grabbed your neck.
I was able to absorb the residual oils
from his skin, which...
when added to a gel-based polymer,
might be able to re-create his fingerprint.
Never meet your heroes, right?
Mom?
Thank you for coming home, sweetheart.
- Is everything all right?
- I don't know.
Your sister has locked herself in her room
and she won't talk to me.
- Don't worry, I'll talk to her.
- Okay.
It's Christmas.
Yes.
But given the last gala that we threw...
I think we're gonna skip
this year's Christmas party.
Thea, it's Ollie. Open the door.
Not now, Ollie.
- Speedy, open the door.
- Is Mom with you?
No.
- What's going on?
- I didn't want Mom to see.
See what?
What happened to him?
The vigilante decided to use him
as target practice.
You're right, the guy's a psycho.
Why didn't you go to the hospital?
In this city, an arrow's the same as
a bullet if you want the cops involved.
Mom actually likes Roy,
but something tells me
she'd revoke his
tree-trimming invitation...
if she found out
he was messing around with the Hood.
Uh-huh.
Hi.
Roy...
this is gonna hurt.
My anger is dulling the pain.
This'll dull it better.
Put pressure on it right there.
Diggle, I need you to come
to the Queen mansion.
Roy's been shot...
with an arrow.
It's a long story.
Look, just bring the first-aid kit
to Thea's room.
Thank you.
Roy, my driver, Mr. Diggle...
...he has medical training from his time
in the army. He's gonna patch you up.
- Thank you.
- It's the least I can do.
Look, I don't know
what the three of you are up to...
but maybe the vigilante was
just trying to keep you safe.
By shooting Roy?
I...
I'm just saying...
maybe you should let this go.
So are we gonna let this go?
No.
But now we're gonna do things my way.
Mom?
Hello?
Shado?
You can't be here.
I had to see you.
- Had to warn you.
- Warn me?
You can't fight what's coming.
Put down your bow.
- Take off my father's hood.
- I wear that hood to honor your father.
- To honor you.
- If you want to honor me...
stop fighting and live.
Or everyone you love will die.
Ollie?
Who were you talking to?
Drop your weapons!
Get over there.
Mirakuru.
Take them.
Anthony...
you got what you wanted.
You can let them go.
If you ever cared about me...
But I do care about you, Sara.
Which is why I won't choose to kill you.
But he might.
What are you talking about?
Time to choose, Oliver.
Who lives and who dies.
But pick quickly,
because in 30 seconds...
I will shoot them both.
The incubation process has begun.
The serum will be ready for distribution
in 48 hours.
Two days.
And we will be able to create
a hundred more like you.
And the people who run this city
will see what real power looks like.
- I knew the vigilante had partners.
- He likes to be called the Arrow now.
You three have messed
with some really nasty people.
I mean, the Dollmaker,
Count Vertigo, Dodger...
- the Huntress.
- We weren't keeping score.
- I was.
- Barry.
The rat poison that you gave me,
are there any side effects?
Um, yeah, I think hallucinations, maybe.
And excessive sweating.
Are you sweating excessively?
You're hallucinating? What are you seeing?
A girl named Shado
that was with me on the island.
Shado. Sara.
How many women were you marooned with?
Sure this wasn't Fantasy Island?
You did train in a jungle or forest
environment. Hence the green.
Hey, let me draw some blood, see what's up.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Why no mask?
Not to tell you how to
do your vigilante-ing...
but the grease paint thing...
it's a poor identity concealer.
So find me a mask that conforms
perfectly to my face and
doesn't affect my ability to
aim while I'm on the run.
You should look into
a compressible micro fabric.
- It could be great.
- I found Cyrus Gold.
Who's Cyrus Gold?
The human weapon that left
you nearly dead the other night.
The kid did manage to pull his print
off your neck.
I've had facial recognition software scanning
close circuit cameras all over town.
He's at the corner of Delgado and 25th right
now, but we're just about to lose him.
- What else is at that intersection?
- A parking lot, a market, a motel...
Could be where he's holed up.
- I got this.
- Oliver.
Why don't you let me handle this one?
- It's just recon.
- Fine.
But I'm going as your backup.
Don't worry...
- I'll figure out what's wrong with Oliver.
- You'd be the first.
Heh.
Secret admirer?
No, actually, they're from my father.
- What brings you by?
- We need your help.
Cindy's friend was murdered,
but the police aren't going to investigate.
They said that he OD'd, end of story.
Check this out.
He earned extra money donating blood.
We found it in Max's apartment.
They wouldn't accept his blood
if he was using, right?
Max went missing the same day
as the blood drive.
If he did donate blood there, maybe they at
least know something that happened to him.
- I'll ask around.
- Thank you, Laurel.
You get bored, I keep a book of
crossword puzzles in the glove box.
That's not funny.
Okay, what do you see?
It's clean. Really clean.
- Solomon Grundy, born on a Monday
Christened on Tuesday
I know the poem.
It symbolizes the seven stages of life...
- from birth to death.
- What stage is this guy in?
Go, go, go!
He picked me up like I was nothing.
- Felicity, call for backup.
- On it.
This about Sara?
You heard from her?
No. I'm sorry, this is...
This is something else.
Cyrus Gold.
He robbed the Applied Science division
of Queen Consolidated last week.
Detective...
he's extremely dangerous.
The CSI kid from Central City...
...he said this guy was
like some kind of monster.
He is.
- What is it, steroids?
- Worse, it's...
it's...
Look, assuming I believe you,
why come to me?
I've been compromised.
- What does that mean?
- It means I'd be a liability.
You have to take my word
on this, detective.
Gather as many men as you can.
And do not hesitate to kill Cyrus Gold...
because if given the opportunity,
he'll do the same to you.
You don't have to do this.
You got what you came for.
Just take it and go!
- Ten seconds.
- You fricking psychopath!
History will make that judgment.
Five seconds.
Time's up.
Wait, no, no!
I guess you made your choice.
No!
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I came by to see Thea.
Oh. Come on in.
She's upstairs in her room.
I noticed on the drive up that your house
wasn't festooned with Christmas decorations.
Well, we didn't feel very much
like festooning this year.
I know what you mean.
I remember last Christmas...
Tommy and I came here for your party.
It was one of the best holidays
I'd had in a really long time.
Anyway, I should probably go talk to Thea.
I checked into the blood drive
and it's all legitimate.
In fact, what Sebastian's done
has helped save a lot of lives.
So if the blood drive
is on the up and up,
then how are we supposed
to find Max's killer?
There is one other thing.
All of the blood donors at the drive...
were subjected to a psych evaluation
by the Langford Institute.
Is that, like, legal?
It's not entirely out of the norm.
And while someone at the institute
might know if Max was on drugs...
there's no way of finding out
without a warrant.
Which we're certainly not going to get.
I'm sorry I couldn't be more help.
What are you doing?
Uh, just messing around with something.
Shouldn't you be trying to figure out
what's causing Oliver's hallucinations?
The sample's still being scanned.
Shouldn't be too much longer.
Good.
You're really worried about him, huh?
He takes crazy chances...
even when he's not hallucinating
about beautiful island girls.
Mm. Heh.
The other night I asked you
if you liked Oliver.
I told you, I don't.
I remember.
But if you did...
I could see why.
I mean, Oliver Queen...
he is a billionaire by day...
and saves the city by night.
Sounds like you wanna date him.
I just have a little experience...
with liking someone
who doesn't see you the same way.
Protests continue into the final countdown
for tonight's ignition...
of S.T.A.R. Labs' controversial
particle accelerator.
S.T.A.R. Labs' founder, Harrison Wells...
promises a new era
of scientific advancement is at hand.
Guess I won't be back in time
to see them turn it on.
Look, I know it sounds crazy.
Human weapons?
Look, his name is Cyrus Gold.
He's the one
that broke into Queen
Consolidated last week.
He's the one that robbed the blood bank,
and he killed all those people.
Wait, hold on a second.
Where are you getting all this intel?
Aw, man, what's the matter with you?
Talking to the vigilante
is what got you demoted in the first place.
Look, we take a small squad.
McCarthy and Evans from SWAT, Jones.
We could bring this guy down.
I promised Jeannie I'd
take her christmas shopping.
Lucas, please.
Fine, but you get to call Jeannie
and tell her I'm not taking her shopping.
Hey, sir.
I don't mean to overstep,
but could you guys use an extra man?
Grab a vest, Officer Daily.
The police
are onto Gold. They're looking for him.
I made sure I'm in the loop.
We are too close to let
the police interfere.
Brother Cyrus...
the police are eager to meet you.
Introduce yourself.
So any plans for Christmas?
Lighting my menorah.
Hey.
Hey. How are you feeling?
Fine, just...
It's a little bit crowded
at my house and I wanted
to come down here and
get a little privacy.
Yeah.
Come on, Barry. We can watch
the countdown at Big Belly Burger.
- Your blood analysis is almost done.
- Thank you.
What's the matter, kid?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
- Are you sure he's in there?
- Yes Sir.
Sector car spotted Cyrus Gold entering.
He hasn't left.
Safety's off.
Open and surround him.
This is a nice place.
It's a bit more comfortable
than the fuselage on the island.
- You're not real.
- Neither are you.
You told everyone
when you started this crusade...
that it was about making up
for your father's sins.
That was a lie.
This charade is to atone for your sins.
- You're dead.
- You are not a hero.
Or a friend.
Or a brother.
You are nothing.
Do not turn your back on me. Not again.
You're gone.
Wherever I am, it's time you joined me.
They say a coward dies a thousand deaths.
- But even that wouldn't be enough for you.
- I tried to save you.
- And her.
- But you couldn't.
Just like you couldn't save this city.
The island didn't make you strong, kid.
It revealed you to be weak.
Thank you for being my shopping guide.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just, um...
Can I ask you a question?
- It's about the blood drive you sponsored.
- Of course. It's a wonderful cause.
Especially with the underfunded hospitals
we're dealing with. What about it?
Hello?
What?
Okay, I'll be right over.
- What happened?
- My father.
He's in the ICU. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I have to go.
I'm sorry.
What happened in here?
- Did someone break in?
- No.
Uh, your blood analysis is done.
- Good news.
- So you know what's in my system?
That's the thing, your blood's clean.
- There's nothing wrong with you.
- Then why am I hallucinating?
I don't know. I mean,
whatever your problem is,
it's not pharmacological,
it's psychological.
- It's in your head.
- It's in my head.
Oh, my God.
Oliver.
- Dad.
- Honey.
Honey.
I can wiggle my toes.
That must be a good sign.
I'm all right, honey. I'm fine.
How's Lucas? Is he all right?
Uh...
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
I gotta call Jeannie.
I gotta call his wife.
No, Dad, I'll do it.
You just stay here.
Get some rest.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to make sure
your father was okay.
He is.
Wanted to make sure you were too.
How are you, detective?
I'm alive.
Unlike most everyone else in my unit.
I'm sorry about your partner.
I took him in there.
Because of me.
I hate to disappoint you,
but not every death in this city is on you.
I got this off Gold.
Hopefully you can do something with it.
I didn't believe it at first, but this guy,
I mean, it's like he's not human.
He's human.
Well, then you can kill him.
For Hilton and me.
Think those are sharp enough.
Apparently I'm not.
Diggle, do you think I'm losing my mind?
No more than the rest of us.
I saw...
Slade Wilson.
Slade was my friend on the island...
and like Shado,
he is dead because of me.
Mr. Lance just told me that not every death
in this city is my fault. Fine.
But there are plenty that are.
When I got home from Afghanistan,
I saw a ghost too.
Survivor's guilt. Why us and not them?
See, I know why.
Then the why is not your problem.
How'd you make your ghost go away?
I figured out what they
were trying to tell me.
Which was?
That's for me to hear, Oliver.
You have to figure out what
yours are trying to tell you.
Guys, we got something here.
I scanned the key Lance gave you and
traced its serial code to the manufacturer.
This particular key fits a locked gate
somewhere on Crescent Circle in the Glades.
Where are you going?
You can't go out there in your condition.
I have to stop this.
Oliver, Gold left you
half dead, which is 50
percent better than how
he left Detective Hilton.
Felicity...
I don't have a choice.
I'll come back.
Promise me?
Stanton. Stanton.
Max.
It's ready.
Is this where you killed Max Stanton? Hmm?
What are you doing?
Stick that in me, I'll kill you.
No, Brother Roy, you'll kill for me.
Brother Cyrus told me he killed you.
Guess he's not as strong as you hoped.
Where'd you get the Mirakuru?
Who gave you the formula?
It was a gift.
A gift I will use to save
this city from itself.
Another failure.
Get up, Oliver.
Tommy?
You're not gonna die down here.
Tommy, I'm sorry.
I let you die.
You didn't let me die, Ollie.
You fought to save me.
Because that's what you do,
what you have always done.
You fight to survive.
I know I called you a murderer,
but you are not. You are a hero.
You beat the island.
You beat my father.
So fight, Oliver.
Get up and fight back.
Kill him.
Come on, Roy.
Right here.
I am not leaving anyone else to die.
You're a strong kid. Hey, come on, come on.
Come on, Roy.
Fight. Come on, fight!
Roy?
Roy.
Where have you been?
I've been looking all over for you.
I was...
I was running down another lead.
It didn't pan out.
I thought you were chasing after
the vigilante again.
I got so scared. I thought
something happened to you.
Hey, hey, don't worry.
I'm alive.
I wanna serve the people of Starling, not
the men and women who think they own it.
Together we can help rebuild our city...
into a place where there are no elites
and no oppressed.
Where we are all brothers and sisters.
So your campaign begins.
The city needs a leader.
And putting the copycat Hoods up to assassinating
the mayor was just the first step.
The vigilante...
he destroyed the centrifuge
and the serum along with it.
I will arrange for you
to receive another sample of my blood.
And then you can begin
to mass-produce the serum again.
When I ask you not to confront
the vigilante, you will listen.
Remember,
your mask can be worn by another.
You know who he is under that hood,
don't you?
I know exactly who he is.
He's my friend.
That's why you don't want him dead.
Death would be a release from this life,
and his sentence is yet to be carried out.
I am going to tear everything
he cares about away from him.
Destroy those who choose to follow him.
Corrupt those he loves.
Once he has lost everyone
and everything he values...
I will drive an arrow through his eye.
Shado.
Shado!
No.
Why?
- Ivo just shot her.
He didn't say why.
Whoever did this to her is going to suffer.
Still have a ghost problem?
No, I got the message.
But we...
we have other problems.
Wouldn't be us if we didn't.
- Roy was injected with the serum.
- Oh, my God. Is he okay?
He's alive, but we are gonna have
to keep an eye on him.
And Cyrus Gold?
Died on Saturday, buried on Sunday.
But he was working with someone.
I saw him.
He work a mask in the image of a skull.
He's trying to mass-produce the serum
to build an army.
For what?
You're a soldier.
- What's the primary purpose of an army?
- War.
- Where's Barry?
- He went back to Central City.
Wanted to get home in time to see them
turn on the particle accelerator.
I should take this.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Did you make it?
Yeah, I made it back to
Central City in time...
but I missed the cutoff in line
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I was late as usual. Ahem.
But in the spirit of not
being late again...
uh, if you ever decide
that Oliver Queen isn't the guy for you...
if you decide that you wanna go
on a date with someone else, urn...
you should know that, that guy,
he'll be on time.
Good to know.
Oh, hey, and I left something for Oliver.
I hope he likes it.
- Bye, Barry.
- Bye, Felicity.
I'm Linda Park.
We're live outside S.T.A.R. Labs...
despite the inclement weather,
which is only going to get worse.
The torrential downpour has driven away
almost all the protesters...
but S.T.A.R. Labs CEO Harrison Wells
has assured us...
that the storms will in no way
effect the particle accelerator...
which is up and running smoothly.
We are now being told to
evacuate the facility.
The storm may have caused a malfunction
to the primary cooling system.
Officials are now trying to shut down
the particle accelerator...
but so far have been unable
to regain control of the system.
Even the Arrow
deserves a Christmas present.
Here.
How do I look?
Like a hero.