What is the cost of lies?
It's not that we'll
mistake them for the truth.
The real danger is that
if we hear enough lies
then we no longer
recognise the truth at all.
What can we do then?
What else is left but to
abandon even the hope of truth
and content ourselves
instead with stories?
In these stories, it doesn't
matter who the heroes are.
All we want to know
is "who is to blame?"
In this story it was Anatoly
Dyatlov. He was the best choice.
An arrogant, unpleasant man.
He ran the room that night.
He gave the orders.
And no friends.
At least, not important ones.
And now, Dyatlov
will spend the next ten years
in a prison labour camp.
Of course,
that sentence is doubly unfair.
There were far greater
criminals than him at work.
And as for what Dyatlov did do,
the man doesn't deserve prison.
He deserves death.
But instead, ten years
for criminal mismanagement.
What does that mean?
No one knows. It doesn't matter.
What does matter is,
that to them, justice was done.
Because, you see, to them...
..a just world is a sane world.
There was nothing sane
about Chernobyl.
What happened there,
what happened after,
even the good we did,
all of it...
..all of it.
Madness.
Well, I've given you
everything I know.
They'll deny it, of course.
They always do.
I know you'll try your best.
Lyudmilla?
Comrade Dyatlov?
Comrade Dyatlov!
- What just happened?
- I don't know.
There's a fire
in the turbine hall.
The turbine hall.
The control-system tank.
Hydrogen.
You and Toptunov,
you morons blew the tank.
- No, that's not...
- It's an emergency. Stay calm.
- Our first priority...
- It's exploded.
We know. Akimov,
are we cooling the reactor core?
We shut it down but
the control rods are still...
They're not all the way in...
I'll disconnect the servos
from the standby console.
Get the backup pumps running.
Get water moving through the
core. That is all that matters.
There is no core!
It exploded. The core exploded.
He's in shock.
Get him out of here.
The lid is off.
- The stack's burning. I saw it.
- You're confused.
RBMK reactor cores
don't explode. Akimov.
Don't worry.
We did everything right.
Something strange
has happened.
- Do you taste metal?
- Akimov!
Comrade Perevozchenko, what
you're saying is impossible.
A core can't explode.
It has to be the tank.
We're wasting time. Let's go.
Get hydrogen out the generators,
pump water into the core.
- What about the fire?
- Call the fire brigade.
- You're not on call tonight.
- They're bringing in everybody.
Military and civil.
Pripyat. Polesskoe. Kiev.
This is a big one.
But it doesn't look right.
The colour.
Pravik thinks they're shining
floodlights or something.
What if there are chemicals?
Chemicals?
The problem's the roof.
It's covered in tar,
so it's gonna burn all night
and will stink like hell.
That's it,
that's the worst of it.
Go back to bed.
- Is it war?
- Where's the dosimeter?
Here. Here.
Are they bombing?
What the fuck is this?
- 3.6 roentgen.
- That's as high as it goes.
The good one's locked
in the safe. I don't have a key.
Valera...
..your face.
Come on.
I'm going to find Khodemchuk
in the pump room. You, here.
Get Shashenok. He's in 604.
Go. We need to get everyone out!
- Shit.
- Hey!
We need to get into the reactor
hall. The lift's destroyed.
Up two flights and across.
All right.
Why are you going there?
- Have you seen Khodemchuk?
- No. Where's Viktor?
Still in the pump room.
Stay here. I'll come back.
Viktor!
Viktor.
Viktor. Oh, Viktor.
I'm gonna get you
out of here.
Can you stand?
Khodemchuk.
Get Khodemchuk.
I dropped the control rods
from the other panel.
- They're still up.
- What?
They're still only a third of
the way in. I don't know why.
I sent trainees to the reactor
hall to lower them by hand.
- What about the pumps?
- I can't contact Khodemchuk.
Fuck the phones
and fuck Khodemchuk.
- Are the pumps on or not?
- Control panel's not working.
I called for the electricians.
I don't give a shit
about the panel.
I need water in my reactor core.
Get down there and make
sure those pumps are on.
Now.
What does the dosimeter say?
3.6 roentgen. But that's
as high as the meter...
3.6. Not great, not terrible.
We did everything right.
Get the pumps going.
- Over here.
- I'm going with you.
Vasily.
Hey, Vasily.
What's this?
I don't know, Misha.
Don't fuck around with it.
Hook these up.
Come on.
- You taste metal?
- Yeah, what is that?
I don't know.
The valves, Misha.
The valves.
The valves. Come on.
What do you need?
We need to get into the reactor
hall to lower the control rods
but the door's jammed.
I don't think there are control
rods. Or that there's a core.
No, you're mistaken.
Akimov said...
Let's go.
Ignatenko, get on his hose.
It's all right.
All right. All right. Easy.
Are you sure?
Akimov...
OK, move.
Go, go! Go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey!
Lyudmilla, do you
want to come with us?
Come where?
We're going to the railroad
bridge to get a better look.
It's not like anyone can
sleep with all the sirens.
I don't think you should go.
Could be dangerous.
What do you mean, dangerous?
It's a fire. It's over there.
- Mikhail.
- What?
Oh. Sorry.
- It's Vasily?
- Yeah.
- Did he say it was bad?
- No, no.
He said it was just the roof.
Well, he's never gotten hurt
before. None of the boys have.
He'll be fine.
Get some rest.
The tank, it's big enough,
this kind of explosion.
The control tank on 71,
it's 100 cubic metres.
110.
110? Could do this, definitely.
It's gone.
I looked right into it.
Looked into the core.
Did you lower
the control rods or not?
Take him to the infirmary.
Toptunov, take him.
- Where's Kudryavtsev?
- He fell.
- I need a medic.
- He's delusional.
- His face.
- Ruptured condenser lines.
The feed water is mildly
contaminated. He'll be fine.
Do we still have
a phone line to the outside?
- Akimov?
- Yeah.
Call in the day shift.
But if...
We have to keep water
flowing into the core.
We need electricians, mechanics.
We need bodies.
How many times
do I have to say it?
I'm going to
the administration building now
to call Bryukhanov and Fomin.
They're gonna want
a full report.
I don't know if I can
make things better for you.
But I can certainly
make them worse.
Call in the day shift,
Comrade Akimov.
Yes, Comrade Dyatlov.
You're doing fine.
Raise her up.
That one may be an hour,
this one, not until morning.
How's it downstairs, Doctor?
- Quiet.
- Always is.
Nothing at this hour but babies.
You know, I once went
two days without sleep.
Ten women went into labour
at the same time.
- Did I tell you that story?
- Yes.
Well, I won't need you
in here for a while.
If you want, get some rest
in the break room.
They haven't brought
anyone in from the fire.
- What fire?
- The power plant.
Oh. It mustn't be too bad.
Do we stock iodine?
- Hm?
- Iodine.
- You mean disinfectant?
- No, pills.
Does the hospital
stock iodine pills?
Iodine pills?
Why would we have iodine pills?
Hello.
Who else knows this?
Have you called Fomin?
Of course I want you to
call him. If I'm up, he's up.
Whatever the cause, it's
important neither you nor...
I take it the safety test
was a failure.
We have the situation
under control.
Under control? It doesn't look
like it's under control.
Shut up, Fomin.
I have to tell the Central
Committee about this.
I have to get on the phone
and tell Maryin
or, God forbid, Frolyshev
that my power plant is on fire.
No one can blame you for this,
Director Bryukhanov.
Of course
no one can blame me for this.
How can I be responsible?
I was sleeping.
Tell me what happened. Quickly.
We ran the test exactly as Chief
Engineer Fomin approved.
Unit Shift Chief Akimov
and Engineer Toptunov
had technical difficulties
leading to an accumulation
of hydrogen
in the control system tank.
It regrettably ignited,
damaging the plant,
setting the roof on fire.
The tank is quite large. It's
the only logical explanation.
Of course, Deputy Chief
Engineer Dyatlov
was directly supervising tests,
so he would know best.
The hydrogen tank, fire.
Reactor?
We're taking measures to ensure
a flow of water to the core.
What about radiation?
Down here it's nothing,
but in the reactor building
I'm being told
3.6 roentgen per hour.
- Not great, but not horrifying.
- Not at all.
- From the feedwater, I assume?
- Mm-hm.
We'll limit shifts to six hours
at a time but otherwise...
The dosimetrists should
be checking regularly.
Have them use the good meter
from the safe.
Oh, right.
I'll call Maryin.
Have them wake up the
local Executive Committee.
There'll be orders coming down.
Here. Sure?
What do you think
makes the colours?
It's the fuel, for sure.
Oh, it's the fuel, for sure.
What do you know about it?
You clean floors
at a train station.
My friend, Yuri, works at the
power plant. Says it runs cold.
No gas, no fire, just atoms.
Yuri says you can't
walk right up to the fuel.
If you do, a glass of vodka
an hour for four hours.
- Isn't Yuri a plumber?
- At the nuclear power plant.
Well, it is beautiful.
Yeah.
Do you have a cigarette?
Do you need help?
It's over.
We've done all we can
from the perimeter.
We need to start
making our way to the roof.
Vasily! You gotta put it out.
Come on, boys.
Vasily, it's this path,
straight up.
All the way up, all the way in.
Come on.
Yeah. Going in now.
- What about the auxiliary?
- The pumps are gone.
The electrical's gone.
The core?
I didn't go in there
and I won't.
I think it's time we...
We have to get water into the
core, or there'll be a meltdown.
- We have to work on the valves.
- Sasha.
What do you want, Boris?
If it's true, we're dead,
a million people are dead.
Is that what you need to hear?
We have to open the valves
by hand.
By hand?
The number of valves, time to
turn them - it's hours in there.
- Then help us.
- Help you do what?
Pump water into a ditch?
There's nothing there.
Leonid, I'm begging you.
Watch the panel
while we're gone.
It's not working.
Just watch it.
I guess we know why
they called us in early.
Is anyone saying what happened?
They were running
the safety test in the turbines
through the control-system tank.
It doesn't make sense
to me either.
What about sabotage?
A bomb?
Sitnikov.
Bryukhanov said to use the good
dosimeter but it's in the safe.
- We can't find the key.
- It's in building two. Has...?
Follow me.
Gentlemen, welcome.
Please find a seat.
Plenty of room.
I apologise for the lateness
of the hour.
Rest assured, we are
all very safe down here.
We built this shelter to
withstand a nuclear attack
by the Americans,
so I think we'll be fine.
Erm... as you can see
we have experienced an accident.
A large control tank
malfunctioned,
damaging reactor building four
and starting a fire.
Now, I have spoken directly
to Deputy Secretary Maryin.
Maryin spoke to
Deputy Chief Frolyshev,
Frolyshev to Central Committee
member Dolghikh,
and Dolghikh to
General Secretary Gorbachev.
Now...
..because the Central Committee
has the greatest respect
for the work of the
Pripyat Executive Committee,
they've asked me to brief
you on matters as they stand.
So...
first, the accident
is well under control.
Second, because the efforts
of the Soviet nuclear industry
are considered key state
secrets, it is important
that we ensure
that this incident
has no adverse consequences.
Now, to prevent a panic, the
Central Committee have ordered
a detachment of
military police to Pripyat.
How large of a detachment?
Between 2,000 and 4,000 men.
What's really going on here?
How dangerous is this?
There's mild radiation but it's
limited to the plant itself.
- No, it isn't.
- Excuse me?
You saw men outside vomiting.
You saw men with burns.
There's more radiation
than they're saying.
We have wives here,
we have children.
I say we evacuate the town.
Gentlemen, please.
Please, my wife is here.
Do you think I would keep her
in Pripyat if it wasn't safe?
Bryukhanov, the air is glowing.
The Cherenkov effect.
Completely normal phenomenon.
Can happen
with minimal radiation.
I wonder how many of you know
the name of this place.
We all call it Chernobyl,
of course.
What is its real name?
The Vladimir I Lenin
Nuclear Power Station.
Exactly.
Vladimir I Lenin.
And how proud he would be
of you all tonight.
Especially you, young man.
And the passion
you have for the people.
For is that not the sole purpose
of the apparatus of the state?
Sometimes we forget.
Sometimes we fall prey to fear.
But our faith
in Soviet socialism...
..will always be rewarded.
Now, the state tells us the
situation here is not dangerous.
Have faith, comrades.
The state tells us
it wants to prevent a panic.
Listen well.
It's true when the people see
the police they will be afraid.
But it is my experience...
..that when the people
ask questions
that are not
in their own best interest,
they should simply be told
to keep their minds
on their labour
and leave matters of
the state to the state.
We seal off the city.
No one leaves.
And cut the phone lines. Contain
the spread of misinformation.
That is how
we keep the people
from undermining
the fruits of their own labour.
Yes, comrades.
We will all be rewarded for
what we do here tonight.
This is our moment to shine.
Thank you.
Comrade Sitnikov,
the chief engineer.
Well?
I sent my dosimetrists
into the reactor building.
The large dosimeter
from the safe,
the one with the thousand
roentgen capacity...
What was the number?
There was none.
The meter burned out
the second it was turned on.
- It's typical.
- This is what Moscow does:
sends us shit equipment,
- wonders why things go wrong.
- We found another dosimeter.
From the military fire
department.
It only goes to 200 roentgen,
but it's better than small ones.
And?
It maxed out. 200 roentgen.
- What game are you playing?
- No, I-I...
I asked and he took
multiple measurements.
- He's my best man.
- It's another faulty meter.
You're wasting our time.
I checked the meter
against the control.
What's wrong with you?
How did you get that number
from feedwater leaking
from a blown tank?
You don't.
Then what the fuck
are you talking about?
I...
I walked around the exterior
of building four.
I think there's graphite
on the ground in the rubble.
You didn't see graphite.
- I did.
- You didn't.
You didn't!
Because it's not there.
What?
Are you suggesting the core...
What? Exploded?
Yes.
Sitnikov, you're a nuclear
engineer, so am I.
Now, please tell me how
an RBMK reactor core explodes.
Not a meltdown, an explosion.
- I'd love to know.
- I can't.
Are you stupid?
No.
Then why can't you?
I...
I don't see
how it could explode.
- But it did.
- Enough.
I'll go up
to the vent-block roof.
From there, you can look right
down into reactor building four.
I'll see it with my own...
my own eyes.
I apologise.
Guards! Guards!
Get him to a medic or
a hospital. Whatever he needs.
It's the feedwater.
Been around it all night.
You go, then.
What?
Go to the vent-block roof
and report back what you see.
No.
No, I won't do that.
Of course you will.
You'll be fine.
You'll see. Come on.
OK.
Let's begin.
Leonid.
Oh.
All the way, OK?
All the way open.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
I told you,
we did nothing wrong.
But we did.
- Hello.
- Valery Legasov?
- Yes.
- You're the Legasov
who's the First Deputy Director
of the Kurchatov Institute
of Atomic Energy?
I am. Who am I...
This is Boris Shcherbina,
Deputy Chairman
of the Council of Ministers
and Head of the Bureau
for Fuel and Energy.
There's been an accident at the
Chernobyl nuclear power plant.
- How bad is it?
- No, no need to panic.
There was a fire.
It's mostly put out.
The system-control tank
exploded.
Control-system tank.
And the core?
We've ordered them to
continuously pump water.
- Yes, I see. Any contamination?
- It's mild.
The plant manager, Bryukhanov,
reports 3. 6 roentgen per hour.
That's significant. You should
evacuate surrounding...
You're an expert
on RBMK reactors, correct?
Yes, I've studied...
General Secretary Gorbachev
has appointed a committee
to manage the accident.
You're on it. We'll convene
at two this afternoon.
That late? Forgive me,
don't you think, given the
amount of radiation, it'd be...
Legasov,
you are on this committee
to answer direct questions
about the function
of an RBMK reactor,
if they should
happen to arise.
Nothing else.
Certainly not policy.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, of course.
I didn't mean...