It's time to go.
Did you hear me? This is
an evacuation. You understand?
- You have to come with me.
- Why?
Because they told me,
so now I'm telling you.
Everyone in this village,
everyone.
It's not safe here.
There's radiation in the air.
What's wrong with you?
Do you know how old I am?
I don't know. Old.
I'm 82.
I've lived here my whole life,
right here,
that house, this place.
What do I care about safe?
I have a job.
Don't cause trouble.
Trouble?
You're not the first soldier
to stand here with a gun.
When I was 12,
the Revolution came.
The Tsar's men,
then Bolsheviks.
Boys like you marching in lines.
They told us to leave.
No. Then there was Stalin
and his famine.
The Holodomor.
My parents died.
Two of my sisters died.
They told the rest of us
to leave.
No. Then the Great War.
German boys, Russian boys.
More soldiers, more famine,
more bodies.
My brothers never came home.
But I stayed and I'm still here,
after all that I have seen.
So I should leave now,
because of something
I cannot see at all?
No.
Just one moment!
It's time to go.
Please stand up now.
This is your last warning.
It's time to go.
0.4.
0.6.
15.
Legasov.
I'll meet him there.
The atom is a humbling thing.
It's not humbling,
it's humiliating.
Why is the core still exposed
to the air?
Why have we not
already covered it up?
We want to,
but we can't get close enough.
The debris on the roof is
graphite from the core itself.
Until we can push it off
the roof, back into the reactor,
it'll kill anyone
who gets near it.
You can see,
the roof is in three levels.
We've named them.
The small one here is Katya.
1,000 roentgen per hour.
Presume two hours
of exposure is fatal.
The one on the side, Nina.
2,000 roentgen. One hour, fatal.
We used remote-controlled
bulldozers in Afghanistan.
Too heavy.
They'd fall right through.
- So, then...
- Moon rovers.
Lunokhod STR-1s.
They're light,
and if we line them with lead,
they can withstand
the radiation.
We couldn't put a man
on the moon.
At least we can keep a man
off a roof.
That is the most important
thing, General.
Under no circumstances
can men go up there.
Robots only.
What about
this large section here?
Masha.
12,000 roentgen.
If you were to stand there
in full protective gear,
head to toe, for two minutes,
your life expectancy
would be halved.
By three minutes,
you're dead within months.
Even our lunar rovers
won't work on Masha.
An amount of gamma radiation
penetrates everything.
The particles literally shred
the circuits
in microchips apart.
If it's more complicated
than a light switch,
Masha will destroy it.
It would be fair to say that
that piece of roof
is the most
dangerous place on earth.
So... what do we do?
That's what
we wanted to ask you.
Tent 181?
Hey.
It's all right, it's free.
It's a little early.
- Bacho.
- Pavel.
- Yeah?
- Hm.
What unit were you in?
Er... they had me in motor pool
in Kiev, but then they...
Not this bullshit.
In Afghanistan.
Oh, I erm...
I wasn't in Afghanistan.
I'm not in the military.
They're running out of men.
Showers, food.
Those guys,
they dig up the ground.
Those guys, they cut down trees.
Those guys, they evacuate
people, I think, like villages.
- What about them?
- I don't know them. Fuck them.
Janek.
- What do you want?
- Give me an egg basket.
- No, I've only got the one.
- Give me the fucking basket.
He's with me. You understand?
Nobody fucks with him.
We make these from lead scrap.
- Put it on under your balls.
- Now?
No, no, you can wait until
the radiation gives you a cunt.
Yes, now.
Over your clothes! Fucking shit!
- You ever go hunting?
- No.
Well, today's your lucky day.
You, me, that ugly Armenian
in the tent, Garo,
we do animal control.
Animal control?
Yeah, they're radioactive,
so they have to go.
But it's not hard.
They're mostly pets.
They're happy to see you.
They run right up to you. Bang.
We load the bodies on the truck,
dump them in a pit,
bury them in concrete,
and then we drink.
As much vodka as you want.
Plus 1,000 roubles.
Let's go get you a gun.
Yes?
I need to see
the following documents.
They're listed
as permission only.
I'm working for
the Central Committee.
Comrade.
She can have that one.
Thank you, comrade.
- All clear.
- Bring up the cameras.
- Signal?
- Acceptable.
Running on-board diagnostics.
Tell me when
we're ready to move it.
To think,
that's what we put on the moon.
Not that one.
I know not that one.
This rover was in storage.
They can build two more.
That should cover
Nina and Katya.
And Masha?
The Central Committee
have informed me
that they may have
found something
that could work up there
from the outside.
- American?
- Of course not.
It's a German police robot.
But West German,
so, as you can imagine,
that wasn't
an easy conversation to have.
Diagnostics complete. Ready to
engage main power and motor.
Begin.
Can we move it?
Valery, was that... a smile?
I see your condition has
improved, Comrade Dyatlov.
No. Leave.
I need your help.
Akimov initiated AZ-5.
- When you gave the order...
- Order? What order?
Toptunov called it out,
Akimov pressed it.
It was the only good decision
they made, incompetent morons.
Can you confirm
that the reactor exploded
after they attempted
to shut it down?
How do I even know it exploded,
huh?
I found this
in the state archive.
Written in 1976.
It's about the operation
of RBMK reactors
under extreme conditions.
So?
The names of the authors
have been redacted
and two pages have been removed.
Well, the state must protect
its secrets, comrade.
Do you dare suggest otherwise?
They made a mistake.
They didn't redact
the table of contents.
The missing pages
apparently refer to
a positive void coefficient
and AZ-5.
Does that mean anything to you?
What are you after?
Why are you asking me this?
You worked with this reactor,
you know it more than I.
So everything's my fault, then?
- Is that what this is?
- I'm not here to blame you.
I'm here to find out
what happened.
And whether
you realise it or not,
I'm your best chance
to avoid a bullet.
Can you help me or not?
I have no idea
what would have gone here.
Void coefficients
have nothing to do with AZ-5.
There, now you can go.
- You're not even curious?
- What for?
What, you think the right
question will get you the truth?
There is no truth.
Ask the bosses whatever
you want, you'll get the lie.
And I will get the bullet.
I only have two rules.
One, don't point this gun at me.
That's easy, right?
You can point it at this piece
of shit, I don't give a fuck.
Never me.
Two, if you hit an animal
and it doesn't die,
keep shooting until it does.
Don't let them suffer.
Or I'll kill you. Understand?
I mean it.
I've killed a lot of people.
Good. Then we're ready.
Once we start, they'll run
inside where they feel safe.
So we go door to door.
OK?
Good.
Hey. Do your job. Door to door.
Go. Go.
Go away. Go!
- Don't let them suffer.
- Sorry.
Sorry.
You're dragging that
to the truck.
You gonna eat?
Drink.
Again.
Look...
..this happens to everyone
their first time.
Normally, when you kill a man.
But for you, a dog.
So what? There's no shame in it.
You remember your first time,
Garo?
My first time, Afghanistan.
We were moving through a house
and... suddenly a man was there
and I shot him in the stomach.
Yeah, that's a real war story.
They're never any good stories,
like in the movies.
They're shit.
A man was there - boom, stomach.
I was so scared,
I didn't pull the trigger again
for the rest of the day.
I thought,
"Well, that's it, Bacho.
You put a bullet in someone.
You're not you any more.
You'll never be you again."
But then you wake up the next
morning and you're still you.
And you realise...
that was you all along.
You just didn't know.
The happiness of all mankind.
What?
"Our goal is the happiness
of all mankind."
Yeah.
I'm happy. I'm happy every day.
All right. Back to work.
Come on.
It's here.
Push it over.
Hang on, hang on.
Easy now. Careful.
Pull it.
Joker.
What the Germans named them.
"Joker".
- Is it ready?
- It's ready.
Good signal.
Cameras? Motors?
Motor's good. Signal's good.
All right, let's take this easy.
Forward one metre,
reverse one metre.
Forward one.
Germans.
Reverse one.
Did you lose the signal?
It's not the signal,
it's the vehicle.
It's dead.
Of course
I know they're listening!
I want them to hear!
I want them to hear it all!
Do you know what
what we're doing here?
Tell those idiots
what they have done!
I don't give a fuck!
Tell them, don't tell
Ryzhkov! Tell Ligachev!
Tell fucking Gorbachev!
Tell them!
The official position
of the state
is that a global
nuclear catastrophe
is not possible
in the Soviet Union.
They told the Germans
that the highest detected
level of radiation
was 2,000 roentgen.
They gave them
the propaganda number.
That robot
was never going to work.
We need a new phone.
What if we don't clear it?
We have to clear it.
If we don't clear the roof,
we can't build a cover over it.
If we can't cover it,
that's 12,000 roentgen.
Nearly twice the radiation
from the Hiroshima bomb.
- Every hour, hour after hour.
- I know, I know, I know.
What about lead?
We could... I don't know,
we could melt it
and pour it from above,
like a coating.
First, we've already used most
of the lead we had to line...
There's lead sheeting
around the instruments
in the other reactor buildings.
The soldiers are stripping it
for their armour.
Are you serious?
Even if,
we're still talking about...
boiling metal in a helicopter.
And it's lead, Boris.
It'll weigh a ton.
What if we shoot the graphite
into the hole?
We've got high-calibre bullets,
exploding bullets.
They wouldn't just ricochet,
they'd push.
You wanna shoot
exploding bullets
at an exposed nuclear reactor?
- Well...
- No, no, no.
Let's go light that roof
back on fire.
It was so easy
to put out the first time.
What are we talking about here?
We need another robot.
One that can withstand
the radiation.
I've asked. There is nothing.
The Americans?
If the Americans
had that kind of technology,
do you really think
they'd give it to us?
And the Central Committee
would never stoop to ask.
You know it, I know it.
There are no robots.
Bio-robots.
What's that?
We use... bio-robots.
Men.
A lot today.
Where do they get their food?
They eat the chickens.
Then they eat each other.
Door to door.
Pavel!
Did you not hear me?
I'm talking to you.
Fuck.
Just go outside.
Go.
Comrade soldiers,
the Soviet people have
had enough of this accident.
They want us to clean it up
and we have entrusted you
with this serious task.
Because of the nature
of the working area,
you will each have
no more than 90 seconds
to solve this problem.
Listen carefully
to each of my instructions
and do exactly
as you have been told.
This is for your own safety
and the safety of your comrades.
You will enter reactor
building 3, climb the stairs,
but do not immediately
proceed to the roof.
When you get to the top,
wait inside,
behind the entrance to the roof,
and catch your breath.
You will need it
for what comes next.
This is the working area.
We must clear the graphite.
Some of it is in blocks weighing
approximately 40 to 50kg.
They all must be
thrown over the edge here.
Watch your comrades,
moving fast from this opening,
then turning to the left
and entering the workspace here.
Take care not to stumble.
There's a hole in the roof.
Take care not to fall.
You will need to move quickly
and you will need
to move carefully.
Do you understand your mission
as I have described it?
Yes, Comrade General.
These are the most important
90 seconds of your lives.
Commit your task to memory,
then do your job.
It's time to go. After
90 seconds, I will ring a bell.
When you hear it,
return immediately,
drop your shovels in the bin
and proceed to decontamination.
Above all, while on the roof,
throw your debris over the rail.
Do not look over the rail.
Is that clear?
Very well.
On my mark: ready, go.
Comrade soldier.
You're done.
Time to go.
Oh. Your glove.
Mummy! Mummy!
Sorry for all this.
We needed to speak to you
somewhere without...
They're going to put
Dyatlov on trial.
And Bryukhanov and Fomin.
We're going to be asked to...
give expert testimony.
All three of us.
But before that happens...
The Central Committee's
sending Legasov to Vienna.
It's the headquarters
of the International...
Atomic Energy Agency.
I know what's in Vienna.
What are they asking you to do?
Tell the world what happened.
Well, then,
you'd better know what happened.
I've constructed a timeline,
minute by minute,
second by second in some places.
Every decision,
every button push,
every turn of a switch.
- And? Are they guilty?
- Yes.
Of gross incompetence,
violation of safety regulations,
recklessness beyond belief.
But the explosion...
I'm not sure.
What do you mean
you're not sure?
I've analysed the data.
Toptunov was telling the truth.
They shut the reactor down
and then it exploded.
I think this article
may have the answer.
But two pages have been removed.
You've seen this before.
Please believe me
when I tell you
that I had no idea
it could cause an explosion.
- None of us knew...
- None of you knew what?
In 1975,
at an RBMK reactor at Leningrad,
a fuel channel ruptured.
The operators pressed AZ-5,
but instead of the power
going down immediately,
for a brief moment, it went up.
How is that possible?
This is the question posed
by my colleague named Volkhov.
He's the one
who wrote this article.
When an RBMK reactor
runs at low power,
it's notoriously unstable,
prone to swings in reactivity.
Under normal circumstances,
the control rods
can compensate for that.
Under normal circumstances.
The Chernobyl staff stalled
the reactor during a test.
They pulled almost
all the control rods out
to bring the power back up.
This is what Volkhov learned
from Leningrad.
If the boron control rods
are completely withdrawn
from the reactor,
when they're put back in,
the first thing that enters
the core isn't boron.
It's graphite.
The control rods
have graphite tips
that displace water and steam.
So the reactivity doesn't go
down, it goes up dramatically.
Why on earth
would they press that button?
They didn't know.
Volkhov warned the Kremlin.
Ten years ago.
But there could be no doubt
about the supremacy
of the Soviet nuclear industry.
Oh.
The KGB classified it.
It's a state secret.
When I saw the reactor
blown open,
I still didn't think
it could be this flaw in AZ-5.
Because the flaw
will not lead to an explosion
unless the operators
have pushed the reactor
to the edge of disaster.
- So it is their fault?
- Yes.
But not only their fault.
No.
Is that what you're
going to say in Vienna?
You can't possibly be
that naive.
There are 16 RBMK reactors
running in the Soviet Union
right now.
We have to fix them.
The only way to do that
is to go public.
Force the Central Committee
to take action.
What you're proposing is that
Legasov humiliate a nation
that is obsessed
with not being humiliated.
We can make a deal with the KGB.
You'll leave this information
out in Vienna
and they quietly let us fix
the remaining reactors.
A deal with the KGB?
And I'm naive.
They'll go after your family,
they'll go after your friends.
You have a chance
to talk to the world, Valery.
If that chance was mine...
But it isn't, is it?
I've known braver souls
than you, Khomyuk.
Men who had their moment
and did nothing.
Because when it's your life
and the lives
of everyone you love,
your moral conviction
doesn't mean anything.
It leaves you.
And all you want at that moment
is not to be shot.
Do you know the name
Vasily Ignatenko?
No.
He was a fireman.
He died two weeks
after the accident.
I've been looking in
on his widow.
She gave birth. A girl.
The baby lived for four hours.
The radiation
would have killed the mother
but the baby absorbed it
instead.
Her baby.
We live in a country
where children have to die
to save their mothers.
To hell with your deal.
And to hell with our lives.
Someone has to start
telling the truth.
Congratulations, comrades.
You are the last of 3,828 men.
You have performed
your duties perfectly.
I wish you good health
and long life.
All of you are awarded
a bonus of 800 roubles.
- Thank you.
- I serve the Soviet Union.