TOKYO: Gandía was an animal.
After almost killing two of his prey,
he could've retreated to his den
and rested.
But that would have been
against his nature.
He was a predator.
And he wasn't going to stop
until he finished off the entire flock.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [NAIROBI GRUNTS]
- [SHOTS FIRED]
Nairobi.
Fuck!
PALERMO: RÍO, Denver, with me. Let's go.
This vent goes to
the bathrooms downstairs.
Denver, you okay?
You'll climb through there?
- DENVER: Sure.
- I'll go too.
PALERMO: Go, kill that son of a bitch.
DENVER: Let's go.
[GANDÍA GRUNTS]
[NAIROBI GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- GANDÍA: Don't move or I'll kill her!
[GROANING]
[NAIROBI MOANS]
[SCREAMS]
- PALERMO: Don't move! Nobody move!
- Where are you shot?
[SOBS] In my hand.
The next bullet
goes straight into her head!
["MY LIFE IS GOING ON" BY CECILIA KRULL]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
- NAIROBI: Merry Christmas! [LAUGHS]
- [PROFESSOR LAUGHS] What do you mean?
It feels like Christmas Eve.
Don't you think?
We're here with all this food,
setting the table,
- waiting for the rest of the family.
- Not just family,
don't forget there's Manila
and the welders.
- It's good for you to get to know them.
- Of course.
They're like distant cousins.
You know why I came back for this heist?
Before you scattered us all across
the world,
this gang...
was the closest thing to a family
I've had in my whole life.
I've never had a Christmas
like the kind you see on TV
with Grandma, Santa, cookies,
all that shit.
- And Axel's father? Didn't you celebrate...
- No.
You know, I...
I had already given up on the idea...
of having a family.
Completely given it up.
But now I think
there's another way of doing this thing.
I have this urge to be a mother.
But a different one.
I wanna have a bunch of kids,
and a dog and whatever else I want.
What you're saying is beautiful, Nairobi.
Very beautiful.
Y-you...
Would you be the father of my child?
- I mean...
- Pardon?
I need to get good genes
to combine with mine. It's very important.
I look at you in class,
and I think...
"This man is brilliant,
and he's honorable,
and so sensitive. Even handsome.
He's a man with ideals."
And I believe in what you do.
Your perception of me
is very, very flattering.
And honorable...
Well, that's one way to look at it, but...
that's impossible.
Why? Impossible is pulling off a heist
at the Bank of Spain.
I'm not asking you to be a father
if you don't want to.
What I'm asking is a donation
so I can do things differently.
- No strings attached.
- Nairobi...
Listen, I set up the heist
at the Royal Mint
in memory of my father.
And this one, for my brother. I'm...
I'm not one
who doesn't develop attachments.
I would not ignore, even for a second,
the fact that I have a child out there
somewhere in the world.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
You were the one that built this family.
And you...
you taught us to look out for each other.
You said, "Whatever it takes."
- But what you're asking for is...
- What I'm asking you is the same.
Because a family is there for you,
no questions asked.
That's what binds us.
They will risk their lives for you.
You've got your plan,
but I also have a plan.
You've taught me
that we have to help each other
because that's who we are.
Ágata...
I guess I've asked you
to do more complicated things.
A little bit more, yeah.
And...
I've done fucked up shit for you
without asking.
I know. I've asked you...
to take big risks.
SeRÍOus risks.
In fact, much more
than what you're asking me now.
Are you saying that's a yes?
You're saying that's a yes.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Come here!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you! I swear to you,
you're never going to regret this.
We will find the best in vitro
fertilization clinics in the world.
Or, if you want,
we could do it the traditional way.
The traditional way is for sure
off the table.
We'll leave in the hands of professionals.
Okay?
Okay.
We'll do it once we've finished the heist.
Right.
This is gonna be amazing.
[PANTING]
GANDÍA: You're doing very well, mutt.
You look like Jesus Christ. [CHUCKLES]
How's your hand? You okay?
I am loaded with morphine.
- NAIROBI: Have you found Tokyo?
- She's still locked in the panic room.
[BANGING]
DENVER: Ssh!
[WHISPERS] We're making too much noise.
We have to take off our boots.
What was that?
[MOUTHING]
[DENVER WHISPERS] Look.
Stay still. Don't!
What the fuck?
- DENVER: Move! Move!
- [SHOTS FIRED]
RÍO, Denver, you okay?
We got to cover. [PANTING]
PALERMO: You can't escape!
And who the fuck said I wanna escape,
you one-eyed queer?
This is where all the fun happens.
How many clips you have left,
little soldier?
Why don't you come in here and count them?
[SHOT FIRED]
Bring the drills!
Make some fucking holes in the walls.
- [NAIROBI GRUNTS]
- GANDÍA: For each wall hole,
I'll make another in you.
NAIROBI: He won't kill me.
If he kills me, you kill him.
And he knows it.
Palermo, she's right.
We have to take this opportunity.
No. He's gonna keep shooting her.
It's way too risky.
Gandía!
You know what's gonna happen?
When this is over,
you're gonna get killed by two queers.
[NAIROBI LAUGHS] What do you think
is worse?
Getting killed by a one-eyed sudaca
or a Serbian?
Helsinki, promise me
you'll rip this fucker apart.
I fuckin' swear it, Nairobi. I swear it.
What are all your buddies at the gun club
gonna say, Gandía, huh?
You'll end up
getting slaughtered by a teddy bear!
Nairobi, save your strength.
You're making my hostage nervous,
and I want her to stay calm,
so we're going to start singing now.
I want to hear everyone
so I can know where you are.
And for every person I don't hear singing,
one bullet.
Huh, Nairobi? Come on.
You're gonna start.
Do you know the song "The Fisher of Men"?
- [NAIROBI GRUNTS]
- [GANDÍA GROANS]
You'd better stop kicking me,
you goddamn stupid bitch. Sing!
Let's sing!
♪ You ♪
♪ Have come to the shore ♪
Come on!
[PANTING]
[BOTH SINGING] ♪ You were not searching ♪
♪ For wise ♪
♪ Nor rich men ♪
I told you to sing, and anyone
who doesn't know it, just hum along!
[ALL SINGING] ♪ You only want me ♪
♪ To follow you ♪
♪ My Lord ♪
♪ You looked me in the eyes ♪
[SHOT FIRED]
Where's the choir?
♪ I left my boat ♪
♪ On the shore ♪
♪ With you by my side ♪
♪ I will search for another sea ♪
TOKYO: That song sounded like a requiem.
A requiem for our own funeral.
And that bitter reality...
woke the Professor up.
PROFESSOR: We're up against the ropes.
Nairobi is knocked out.
Tokyo is knocked out.
Lisbon is knocked out.
Professor.
Marseille, I can't think clearly.
I have too many emotional attachments.
Before, I had a gang of people
with city names. Now...
now I could be having a child,
not with one,
but with two members of the gang.
MARSEILLE: Mixing professional
and personal doesn't work.
Tokyo is stuck in the panic room.
And that is precisely the place...
where Gandía... intends... to hide.
We need to find that room
and give him no way to escape.
So where would you put a panic room?
In a place you need to protect.
Where the gold is.
No.
These rooms are used to protect lives,
not gold.
Whose life is most important
in the Bank of Spain?
- The governor's.
- Exactly.
It must be close to the governor's office.
But why doesn't it show up in the plans?
- Perhaps there was a renovation.
- No.
Palermo, don't respond.
The panic room
is behind the governor's bathroom.
It's not in the official blueprints.
I bet they falsified the measurements
of the adjoining rooms, but trust me
it's there.
- [WHISPERS] They're singing church music.
- Huh?
That's a bad omen, yeah?
These assholes sing all the time.
They like doing that kind of shit.
On the other hand,
those shots we heard... Yeah.
That could be a sign these bastards
aren't doing so well.
- Don't you think so, Governor?
- How could we know?
MAN: Ssh!
I know. The shouting, the grenades,
and that random guy watching us.
I have no damn clue who he is,
but he's the tiniest piece of shit
in the gang, and that's a fact.
We should take advantage of our moment.
We should tip the scales in our favor.
A push, a simple tiny push,
could bring us a little closer to victory.
- MATÍAS: Ssh!
- ARTURO: If you permit me, Governor,
I think that that tiny little push
is our responsibility. Yours and mine.
The two of us have to be the ones that...
save the people in this room.
GOVERNOR: What we have to do
- is remain calm and wait.
- ARTURO: Fuck!
MATÍAS: Shut up back there!
I hear you again, I'll start shooting!
ARTURO: I'll have to disagree with you,
Mr. Governor.
See, it is your responsibility.
You just happen to be
the governor of the Bank of Spain!
It's your responsibility as a man. Fuck!
Make your own decisions,
face your problems,
and like I always say,
sometimes it's better to get up
and die on your feet than to live...
forever and eternally kneeling.
- You want me to tell you what I think?
- Please do.
I think you're a clown.
You put everyone at risk
with your little adventures
and with your stupid
asinine infomercial speeches.
Leave us in peace.
And if you want to die on your feet,
then stand up and do it.
SIERRA: Grenades,
shooting.
All in six minutes.
And look at you so relaxed.
What am I missing, Tamayo?
- I know just as much as you, Alicia.
- SIERRA: Liar.
- What's going on in there?
- I said I didn't know.
Then why aren't we intervening?
When there's shots, the protocol says
we should intervene immediately.
It's Gandía,
- the head of security.
- Oh, fuck.
He's inside, free and armed.
He's acting alone on his own accord.
Wait a minute.
Did you talk to him, or what?
Mm-hmm.
You gave him the green light
to start a war in there and kill everyone?
My official command
was he remain inactive.
He said he didn't give a shit
and plans to defend himself.
And if he wants to defend himself,
I'm not going to stop him.
You piece of shit, Tamayo.
Out there, you look like a saint.
Worried about your image in the eyes
of the public, calling a pointless truce.
In the meantime, you send some crazy fuck
to do all the dirty work.
If it goes well, you'll get a medal.
If it goes wrong, you'll say,
"Shit. I told him, no,
but you know he was fucking loco."
It's always us, the fucking crazy ones,
doing the dirty work...
Wait. Do you have anything against Gandía
starting a war in there?
Do you have anything against him
hurting them or killing them?
No, right?
It's better we keep our mouths shut.
- Are you thinking, Professor?
- Um, Yes. I'm thinking, yes.
- MARSEILLE: What about...
- When was...
the first moment that we lost control?
When Denver went out with the red boxes
instead of Gandía.
- And the second time?
- LISBON: We have a problem.
When Lisbon wasn't able to climb...
the tree.
Those were the two mistakes
that put us against the ropes.
We need to take a step back...
and reverse them.
I'm gonna exercise
to get my brain working.
Palermo.
Hang in there. Got it?
Hang in there.
Motherfucker!
[BANGING]
[HOSTAGES WHISPERING]
[PAQUITA WHISPERS] Arturo!
I have something to help with
that push you were talking about.
ARTURO: What?
- It's a cellphone.
- No! Hide it. Holy fuck!
It's Nairobi's.
The one sent in by the police.
I found it while cleaning.
You'll know what to do with it.
What the fuck is going on back there?
If I hear one more fuckin' breath,
I'll shoot you.
Sir, I need to go to the bathroom. Now.
Now is not the time.
No one's gonna leave here,
so you're gonna sit down and stay calm.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You go first.
- Thanks very much.
- No problem.
[JULIA SCOFFS]
What's up, Daniel?
- I was in the middle of my meal...
- No, no. Not Daniel.
Not Daniel. Here... Here, I'm Denver.
Okay? Denver.
I'm sorry. It's hard to get used
to your new identity. I'm sorry.
Hmm. Well, that, uh...
- Look, there's just a couple of things...
- Mm-hmm.
...that I'd like to understand,
and it's not easy for me.
[JULIA LAUGHS SOFTLY]
Ask away.
I'm the same person I've always been.
Well, not exactly the same person
because now you've got tits.
- Hmm, well...
- Yeah, you've got tits.
- I got tits. Mm-hmm.
- You're a woman.
That part is already clear for me.
Are you gay too?
Or how does that stuff work?
So, what you're worried about right now
is knowing whether I'm into guys or not?
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
Hmm. Well, I like men. It's true, yeah.
- I like them a lot, actually.
- Right. Okay.
But hang on.
I don't like just any kind of man.
Um, I like them strong, you know?
I like gym rats.
Punks, but they have to read
a little bit too so I can learn from them.
Um... They have to watch football.
I like that.
But they have to watch like a true macho,
you know,
with a beer in their hand
and their legs spread wide open...
Okay, okay. I got it already.
I got it. It's crystal clear.
Have you...
Have you always liked men,
or did this happen
after you became a woman?
First of all,
I've always been a woman.
No.
You haven't always been a woman.
I saw you rob gas stations.
- You weren't a woman.
- How does a woman rob?
Do they scratch people
and pull their hair?
I'm not a Neanderthal.
What I'm talking about, it's just that,
usually you can tell it's a woman.
You can tell.
I went on all these robberies
with Juanito, not a woman.
Right?
Maybe this thing about being a woman...
happened later.
Let me tell you something.
When Juanito
got out of a robbery with you,
- he'd go back home into his room.
- Yeah.
He'd put on a little music.
- He'd roll a little joint...
- [LAUGHS]
...and put on some red lipstick.
Italian lipstick. It looked wonderful.
Ferrari red.
And he'd take his little joint,
and he'd lie down on the bed...
and right there in that moment...
alone, relaxed, looking gorgeous...
[LAUGHS]
...that was the moment I was me, for real.
You've always been a woman.
Always.
And I never realized.
Do you know
who made me really horny back then?
[LAUGHS] Of course I know.
- Yeah?
- Of course I do.
David Beckham.
You talked about him all day.
- Fucking David Beckham.
- Beckham, too. I mean, he's sexy, but no.
Um, you.
You turn me on so much.
I didn't turn you on at all.
- I was in love with you.
- What are you saying?
- You don't mess around with love.
- Think about it.
Why do you think I was with you
all day long, doing jobs or whatever?
To be close to you.
- Are you being seRÍOus?
- Of course. What do you mean?
I'd grope you all the time on the bike.
I touched you all day, you never noticed.
- I'd touch your leg, your back...
- Stop.
- And your smell!
- Wait a second! Okay, hold on.
Do you even realize what you're saying?
This is really seRÍOus.
You were taking advantage of me.
I'm screwing with you, moron.
- JULIA: It's just...
- Mother...
Motherfucker!
Come on. Give me a hug.
I'm sorry, sir,
but I'm not gonna piss myself.
Nobody move!
I don't wanna hear a fuckin' sound! Hey!
MATÍAS: Hey!
ARTURO: Miguel... Miguel, listen.
We need to figure out a way
to communicate safely with the outside.
You get it?
Take it. Hide it.
Keep it. They'll always
be suspicious of me, but not you.
- What are you doing here?
- JULIA: What the fuck?
What's happening? Where's Denver?
- Denver's fine.
- GANDÍA: Who's there?
- HELSINKI: It's a hostage.
- Get her out now, Matías!
- Let's go.
- Fuck, no. I'm staying. Give me a gun.
That's not why you're here, Manila.
Get going.
You guys are in trouble. Give me a pistol.
Get out of here right now.
Let's fucking go.
It's okay.
Look, from this moment on,
you and I are gonna be
the main part of the resistance.
I'm gonna have a heart attack
just listening to you.
RÍO: Denver.
It'll take four seconds at most.
One goes for it.
The other stays and covers.
And we save Nairobi.
PALERMO: Gandía. What do you want?
- Let's negotiate.
- GANDÍA: Negotiate?
Look, let me explain the situation.
Option one:
I come out of this room with the gun
pointed at Nairobi's head.
All of you stay back
against the wall on the right.
I let her go, and nobody dies.
It's a good deal for both sides.
Zero-zero. A tie.
Option number two:
instead of me going out, you come in.
I blow Nairobi's head off her neck.
You shoot me.
I'd still have another hand left
to shoot at you,
and I swear to God, I'm gonna take
more than one of you with me.
You forgot option three.
You come out on your knees, unarmed,
and surrender and give us Nairobi.
That's also a tie. What do you think?
I wouldn't kneel down,
not even before God Almighty.
I'll give you one minute.
After that, I'll start shooting.
- And I'll score at least six-zero.
- [LAUGHING]
NAIROBI: You fucking moron!
Gandía,
you're not getting out of this alive.
[LAUGHING] You're a fucking clown.
The other day...
when Tokyo and I broke in,
we made you look like such an idiot.
- Shut up.
- [NAIROBI LAUGHS]
And Tokyo... [LAUGHS]
...used the dumbest fucking trick
with the water.
Shut your fucking mouth right now.
NAIROBI: You fucking ate
- the door handle.
- GANDÍA: Shut up!
You got knocked out so hard...
- [NAIROBI LAUGHS]
- What is she doing?
What happened
to your little macho balls then, huh?
- [NAIROBI LAUGHS] So amateur.
- She wants to save Tokyo.
You're useless! [LAUGHS]
She knows that if he kills her,
we'll kill him.
NAIROBI: You've been training for this
your whole fucking life, right?
You had all your little soldier friends,
then two girls show up and make a fool
of you like that.
- Want me to shoot you right now?
- Surprise me.
How about I put a bullet up your asshole?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
We have to get her out.
We have to get her out now.
If we let him get out of there,
he's gonna do whatever he wants.
I don't trust his word,
- we have to be patient.
- BOGOTÁ: Fuck your patience.
She's in there because of you.
You helped him get free.
We have to get her out.
Everyone agree?
Okay, Gandía.
We're gonna let you out.
Okay. Very good.
This is how it's gonna go...
You'll be seeing Nairobi the entire time.
We're gonna walk forward together
as I point my gun against her head,
until she confirms everyone's standing
against the wall in the corridor,
starting with
those two little fucking kids up there!
Denver, RÍO, hear that?
- You have to come down here.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Earlier, you asked me if my husband
was too disgusted to sleep with me,
and I didn't answer.
Well, no.
I didn't disgust him. [CHUCKLES]
Because I wasn't a bitch back then.
But now I guess I am.
And yeah, we had sex.
We did it everywhere.
And it's fascinating how creative we were.
I imagine you and the Professor are more
like a once a month kind of couple, right?
And always missionary.
Money can't buy it all.
All that poison inside of you
is eating you away, Alicia.
I can see it in your face.
What's wrong? My face?
You're not yourself.
All this talk about sex. What's wrong?
Is it the hormones?
I don't know. Download an app.
There's a million perverts
who'd like to fuck a pregnant lady.
I prefer getting to know the other person.
I don't date the first geek
that I meet at a bar
that gives me his phone and says...
[PANTING]
"Hey, gorgeous. Why don't you come with me
to my warehouse
and taste my cider?
It's really tasty."
You know what your problem is?
- Tell me.
- If your mask crumbles,
everything else does.
You're a step away from a breakdown.
And I get it. I get...
I'm not the one with a mask on.
Let's see. Earlier, hmm,
the two of us had a deal.
You were holding the phone,
then you changed your mind.
What happened?
I made you waste your time
while you were questioning me.
I pretended you were breaking me
little by little
and that I was about to give in.
In the meantime, he slipped
through your fingers. He escaped.
It's called diversion tactics,
and it worked well.
You know what I think?
Your little shepherd somehow found a way
to make it here in time.
I'll find out how.
You'll see.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
- BERLIN: Think.
- RÍO: I knew we weren't in Spain.
I heard the prayer call from a mosque.
BERLIN: Think. You know how.
Fly with me.
Shakir.
PROFESSOR: Shakir, do you hear me?
Yes. This is Shakir. Go ahead, Professor.
I need you to track
RÍO's airplane to Spain.
It's a Beechcraft Air King 250.
Property of the Spanish Air Force.
The flight landed at exactly 4:30 p.m.
on April 4th.
Look for that plane
in every navigation satellite.
I need you to find
the exact point of origin.
ARTURO: Does it have battery?
- It does.
- And reception?
MIGUEL: Yes, sir.
Okay. Go to outgoing calls.
Miguel, for fuck's sake.
You need to keep a cool head
You understand me?
You are never going to be suspicious.
- But my fingers are really sweaty.
- Then calm down!
MIGUEL: There's one call.
A private number.
- Go to contacts.
- [MIGUEL BREATHES HEAVY]
MIGUEL: There's a number.
Call it.
Oh, God. Please don't answer.
INCOMING CALL
It's the phone we gave to Nairobi.
[BEEPING]
- ARTURO: What are you doing?
- I'm not talking.
- ARTURO: Fuck!
- They called and hung up.
I'm leaving my fingerprints.
I don't wanna call the police!
Listen.
All you have to do
is leave the phone connected.
Then you talk to me casual.
A normal conversation between hostages.
When they hear it,
they'll know what to do.
You got it?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
They're calling again.
MIGUEL: Speak.
ARTURO: So...
here we are...
in the library.
All together, and we're just being
watched by one of them.
Random guy. I think his name's Matías.
- Turn the volume all the way up.
- I think it's Arturo Román.
No one's in the hall, right, Miguel?
[LOUDLY] There's nobody.
- [WHISPERS] I can't use my voice, sir.
- Ssh!
And now since that guy escaped, Gandía,
I think it'd be the perfect time
for the police to come in
because, I repeat,
there's no one in the main hall.
Thank God we're okay. We're scared.
There was a shooting, a grenade,
screaming, even religious chants.
It's nuts. Right, Miguel?
- [LOUDLY] That's right.
- [MIGUEL COUGHS]
I'm sorry. [COUGHS]
[MIGUEL COUGHS AND PANTS]
We need to go in. Fuck!
The President doesn't want any
armored vans to approach the bank.
For fuck's sake! They're not looking.
We'll catch them off guard.
I can't do it!
What are you guys doing?
It's this kid.
He's lost it. He's really nervous.
Poor little guy. He was praying.
- I think so. What do I know?
- Come here.
Sit over here and be quiet,
nice and close to me.
Raise your hands where I can see them.
If you lower them an inch, I'll shoot you.
If you move an inch, I'll shoot you.
And if you say even one fucking word...
- You'll shoot me.
- Yes, I'll shoot you.
- I'm thinking about shooting you anyway.
- Copy.
Ssh. Quiet.
Suarez, get an intervention unit ready.
We're going in through the main hall.
And Call Gandía in the panic room
so we can coordinate.
Fucking finally.
I didn't think you had any balls.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC INTESIFIES]
SHAKIR: Professor.
The Beechcraft Air King 250,
the one that flew RÍO to Spain,
took off from Algeria at 3:03 p.m...
from a village named Timimoun.
It's located in the Atlas Mountains.
PROFESSOR: Good.
That's minutes before
the car with RÍO got there.
It's right by the plane.
I need you to find that car.
I can see the whole area is a desert.
There's no trees,
so we should be able to trace it
through the satellite
- and find where the car came from.
- Okay.
We'll start with the weather satellites.
Very good.
You're going to Algeria.
In four hours, I want you in Timimoun.
I can't fly with weapons.
I know. Once you get there,
everything will be ready.
- The plan was not to leave you alone.
- The plan has just changed, Marseille.
I need all the Serbs
and Benjamin's team
to go on the offensive.
We're gonna hit them so much,
so fast and so hard
that they won't even know
where the hits are coming from.
How are you doing?
My stitches...
are coming out.
DENVER: Where is he?
NAIROBI: I don't know.
Where is he?
PALERMO: Denver...
I don't know.
Here we are, you son of a fucking bitch.
GANDÍA: And the other one?
I'm right here.
Good.
Then I'm gonna start releasing Nairobi.
Mutt, would you like to say something
before we begin to dance?
[GULPS]
GANDÍA: Well? Well...
- Party time?
- Party time.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[PANTING]
Nairobi.
NAIROBI: Hey, sleepyhead!
[LAUGHS] You've gotta be a real badass
to sleep like this
while everyone's waiting for you
at the table.
You staying in bed all day?
- TOKYO: Hm? So sleepy.
- Hey!
TOKYO: What?
He said yes.
The Professor.
He said yes. [BOTH LAUGH]
- You're going to be an aunt!
- An aunt!
[BOTH SCREAM AND LAUGH]
- TOKYO: I'm so happy for you.
- I can't believe it!
- TOKYO: Hey...
- What?
You'll have a little nerd in the house.
NAIROBI: Yeah. What are we gonna name it?
NAIROBI: Hmm?
Ibiza.
[NAIROBI GASPS]
Oh, my God. I love it. Ibiza.
- NAIROBI: I love it!
- TOKYO: You call the baby Ibiza,
and you're gonna have
so much fucking fun together.
Fuck. It's gonna be so popular
in high school.
TOKYO: It's not a city.
It's an island.
NAIROBI: Fuck it, you know
what other rule we're gonna break?
Not seeing each other again.
You're gonna be an aunt.
NAIROBI: You know what?
You're gonna be a godmother.
That's right, baby.
- [NAIROBI LAUGHS]
- TOKYO: I can't wait.
NAIROBI: Me neither!
[NAIROBI SIGHS] Me neither.
I can't believe it.
- TOKYO: Mm.
- What? What?
- Ibiza, right?
- Yes! I'll tell you one thing.
I'm not spending any more Christmases
alone with Helsinki.
He doesn't know any Christmas carols.
From now on,
every Christmas is for family.
- What's going on here?
- What are you doing?
Single mother bachelorette party.
- NAIROBI: Whoo!
- Are you pregnant?
Yeah! No, no, no, no. After the heist.
I will be after the heist.
- I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
- Me neither.
LISBON: What?
A friend with benefits.
- LISBON: Awesome.
- Okay.
- TOKYO: Wanna know the baby's name?
- TOGETHER: Ibiza!
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
[SCREAMS]
GANDÍA: Okay, mutt.
[NAIROBI MOANS]
GANDÍA: I want everyone against the wall.
Lower your guns.
I'd ask you to throw them on the floor,
but I know myself,
and if I saw you unarmed,
I'd get too excited.
So we should show a little mutual respect.
Right?
PALERMO: Down.
GANDÍA: Come on. Yeah.
I'm aiming my gun at her head.
I'm wearing a bulletproof vest,
and she's tied up,
so I wouldn't try anything crazy
if I were you. Come on. Let's go.
Lower your fucking gun, asshole!
Aren't you listening?
There.
Slowly. Slowly.
Shall we dance a little bit?
Come on. Let's dance.
[GANDÍA HUMS A SILLY TUNE]
- Darling, you're falling.
- [GROANING]
GANDÍA: I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Look at your fatty.
Hello, fatty! [LAUGHS]
That's enough.
Let her go now.
GANDÍA: Easy. Easy.
Take it easy.
I'll let her go.
Hey, don't worry.
Here we go.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Here.
There. See?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, mutt.
I told you I was gonna kill you.
ALL SHOUTING: No!
["DELICATE" BY DAMIEN RICE PLAYING]
♪ We might live ♪
♪ Like never before ♪
♪ When there's nothing to give ♪
♪ Well, how can we ask for more? ♪
♪ We might make love ♪
♪ In some sacred place ♪
♪ The look on your face ♪
♪ Is delicate ♪
♪ So why do you fill ♪
♪ My sorrow ♪
♪ With the words ♪
♪ You've borrowed ♪
♪ From the only... ♪
♪ Why do you fill ♪
♪ My sorrow ♪
♪ With the words ♪
♪ You've borrowed ♪
♪ From the only ♪
♪ Place that you've known ♪
♪ Why do you sing ♪
♪ Hallelujah
♪ If it means ♪
♪ Nothing to you ♪
♪ Why do you sing ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ At all? ♪
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
[CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44