PROFESSOR: Palermo,
this is a war.
Act accordingly.
Denver!
Fire!
[SIREN WAILING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
TOKYO: Everything can to go hell
in less than a second.
[SOBS]
In moments like this,
you feel death creeping in,
and you know nothing
will ever be the same.
But you need to do
whatever it takes to survive.
TOKYO: Nairobi, hold on!
Hang in there.
Hang in there, Nairobi.
- It's gonna be okay.
- HELSINKI: Come on!
Come on!
TOKYO: Everyone has a sniper
aiming at their heart.
TOKYO: Let's go!
But true terror...
- isn't when the bullet hits you.
- We're almost there!
It's when it takes away
someone you love.
Come on! Come on!
HELSINKI: RÍO, Saline.
Come on!
[NAIROBI GASPING]
TOKYO: Okay. Exhale.
That's it.
TOKYO: The Professor was feeling
that true terror more than any of us.
His heart held two words
that should never be together:
love and death.
And that fucked with his head.
While running through the forest,
he could only think...
"They've killed the love of my life."
But there was Lisbon.
Very much alive.
The two gunshots of her fake execution
were pointed directly
at the Professor's mind.
The Professor was drowning
in his own grief.
And with him,
- we were sinking too.
- [PANTING]
[SLOW BEEPS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[RAPID BEEPING]
Pulse is 155 and going up.
HELSINKI: Blood pressure, 85/40.
It's dropping.
Okay, we need two units
of blood and saline.
HELSINKI: Nairobi,
stay strong. I'm here with you.
[SIREN WAILING]
TOKYO: In the tent,
Tamayo felt the same way I did.
Horror from being face to face with death.
A dry mouth with the taste of metal.
Shortness of breath, anxiety,
and lots of pain.
But as long as the game was on,
we all had to keep standing.
[PANTING]
Blood's at 30 degrees.
Ready for transfusion.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
HELSINKI: It's right here, the bullet.
Behind the seventh rib.
It's in the lower part of the lung.
- My love, that's good news.
- [BEEPING]
[WHEEZING]
She can't breathe.
It's a pneumothorax.
- STOCKHOLM: Make a puncture.
- She's choking.
Tokyo. Surgical kit six.
Okay. I'm going. Surgical kit six.
Her air is between the lungs
and chest wall.
STOCKHOLM: Hurry, Helsinki!
- HELSINKI: Tokyo!
- I got it.
[WHEEZING]
[GASPS]
That's it.
[MACHINE BEEPING STEADILY]
You have to get me out of here.
I'd rather be in jail, alive.
I don't wanna die in here.
Tokyo...
[NAIROBI SOBS]
Just give me up to the police, please.
Please.
[CRIES]
Get me out.
[SAD MUSIC]
["MY LIFE IS GOING ON" BY CECILIA KRULL]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
STAGE 3
RESISTANCE
Once RÍO's been released,
we'll begin phase three of the plan...
resistance.
No one can get out
of the Bank of Spain alive.
It's impossible.
But I will get you out of there.
Once we have begun phase three,
the only thing that matters is the gold,
and our only goal is...
to melt it.
Because the gold is our only key.
If we don’t get the gold,
I can't get you out of there.
The police...
will strike back at us with everything,
but no matter what...
whatever happens,
whatever it is they do,
we need to be able to keep... control.
Otherwise,
all our lives will be in danger.
[DOGS BARKING]
Did we kill any police?
PALERMO: I don't know,
we sent one up in flames.
When they come back, they'll bring
everything they've got,
and we're not in a position
to defend ourselves, Sergio.
And Nairobi needs a surgeon.
We fired an antitank at them.
They’re not going to give us a surgeon.
She's got a fucking bullet
inside her lung.
We can't do it ourselves.
You have to try, Sergio.
We need to get
the surgeon in Pakistan.
How much time do I have?
She's dying.
ÁNGEL: He has climbing equipment,
dog deterrent and camouflage clothes.
He could be in the treetops.
Shoot up,
and aim at the crowns of the trees.
[SHOTS FIRED]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Raquel, don't let them get you alone.
Tell them I surrender.
Raquel!
Get out of there!
- Just get out!
- [SHOT FIRED]
I'm gonna try.
[BULL GROWLS AND SNORTS]
[SNORTS]
Ssh. Easy now.
Easy.
- Easy.
- [GROWL AND SNORTS]
Easy.
Good little bull.
- [SHOTS FIRED IN DISTANCE]
- Easy.
Easy.
[BULL BELLOWS]
The Professor attacked the police,
but nobody is moving
from the Bank of Spain.
The protesters are in a state of shock,
and the big question is: what'll happen
with the support from the Dalís?
For the moment, nobody can say,
but we could be witnessing
the first big problem
for supporters of the Professor's cause.
It's like a movie.
Best thing to happen to us.
Those men out there have
second and third-degree burns.
That's normal.
Now what we need is another armored van.
Don’t you care about anything?
I'm not sending more men
to have their faces disfigured
for the rest of their lives.
They fired two rockets at us,
and all of Spain saw it.
I am not starting a war
in the center of Madrid.
The war has started!
Tamayo. Tamayo, don't fuck this up.
Don't make the worst mistake of your life.
The mistake was you torturing that kid.
If we'd just taken him to court,
we wouldn't be here.
We made them stronger and gave them
an argument. I'm not doing that again.
You're scared.
[SCOFFS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You’re just like Prieto...
a Viagra box on the bedside table
for your limp erection. Ugh!
And you think that the law will save you.
Hm!
The law can't help us now.
I am the law.
And limp erection, my ass!
We need to keep our composure.
I want to de-escalate the situation.
Everyone understand?
Dialogue and truce. Truce and dialogue.
Is that clear?
Crystal clear, boss.
Antoñanzas?
Antoñanzas!
Yes, Inspector?
You heard him, no?
That guy is the law. Like John Wayne.
I want a surgical ambulance and a surgeon.
Now!
Let's get out there and make them
hand over their wounded.
The Governor took three medical courses
in the army.
He's gonna help with the operation.
I didn't finish my studies,
and I didn't pursue it as a career,
but I remember some principles.
Great. Put your scrubs on.
I'll get 'em.
So where's the surgeon?
I'm trying to make contact,
but they have to allow access.
Bogotá, anesthetic.
Nairobi, we're putting you to sleep.
You're not putting me to sleep! Tokyo!
Tokyo...
Tell him it's my life,
and I decide.
Please!
It is your life. That's why we're doing
the surgery here, so relax.
Tokyo, please.
Please.
[NAIROBI COUGHS]
She decides.
That's final.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Helsinki, put her to sleep.
That’s a fucking order.
You don't give me orders.
You're not my boss.
You let her get the phone.
You're supposed to protect us.
She can make mistakes, but you can't!
Shut your mouth, fat ass,
or I'll kill you right now,
you son of a bitch!
You're my little whore, not my mama.
It's her fault she's like that
because she chose to be a fucking idiot.
If Nairobi says she's leaving,
I'm walking her to the door.
And you, you piece of shit,
you're gonna shut your mouth
because from now on,
you're no longer my boss.
- Tokyo, lower the fucking pistol.
- Denver...
If Nairobi talks, they'll kill us all.
We're doing the operation in here.
What do you know about operations,
you idiot?
Nairobi needs a surgeon.
Are you all fucking crazy or what?
I swear on my son...
I won't tell them anything.
That’s what you think, but when they
start torturing you, it changes.
Go fuck yourself.
Nairobi's leaving.
[COCKS GUN]
I don't think so.
[LAUGHS]
Do you really think that now is a good
moment to play the rebel leader? Hmm?
One of us is dying,
so just stop fucking around!
Another one of us.
What do you mean, "another"?
They executed Lisbon half an hour ago.
[EXHALES]
If I could show you all
my magnificent democratic side,
we could vote and get her out,
but I'd be killing her.
Lisbon was executed on her knees, unarmed.
They brought Nairobi's son with his teddy
bear so they could shoot her in the head.
Do you think a couple of nuns
from the Red Cross are waiting outside?
Stop fucking around!
[SIGHS]
[PALERMO SIGHS]
Palermo is right.
You're gonna have to cut me open...
and take the bullet out.
[SOBS] Maybe...
cut out part of my lung.
And all that without me bleeding to death.
You're gonna kill me!
You're gonna kill me.
Helsinki... [CRYING]
It's too complicated.
Helsinki, it's too complicated.
Take me to the door.
- Take me...
- HELSINKI: Stay calm.
- Take me to the door!
- Stay calm.
- HELSINKI: It's gonna be okay.
- Thank you.
- It's gonna be okay.
- NAIROBI: No!
No! I don't want to! No!
No, no, no, no!
- HELSINKI: Ssh.
- NAIROBI: No!
No!
No! No! No! [CRYING]
No, no, no, no!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Forgive us, Professor,
uh, we just had an argument tonight.
I'm going to sleep with Tokyo.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Is this okay with you, Tokyo?
Do you mind that I'm sleeping here?
It's totally fine.
So you know, when someone in my bed,
I get really horny.
You don't care, do you?
- Uh, I don't care about what?
- You and I getting rid of our stress.
Rubbing our clams together.
[GROWLS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
I knew that was a joke.
Can somebody please explain to me
why the fuck Palermo...
is leading this?
Because it was his idea?
- And he's the genius.
- He's the genius?
The same guy that was fondling
his balls in the hallway
like a fucking creep?
Oh, come on!
You know who should be
in charge of this?
You!
Yeah, you.
I think so too.
If there's anyone who cares
about this heist going well, it's you.
Don't put ideas in my head, huh.
Don't put ideas in my head.
I'm going to bed.
Good evening.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
I'm gonna talk with the Professor.
Don't wait up!
[DOOR OPENS]
TOKYO: Professor,
I wanna take charge...
of the heist. I'll be better than Palermo.
Tokyo, can we talk about it
in the morning?
The morning? No, now.
Why does he have to be in charge?
- Let's see, Tokyo. He...
is in charge because this heist has been
in development for a long time, and...
he's been on it since the beginning.
He has the plan in his head.
TOKYO: So?
I can learn the plan.
I'm a quick learner.
"Platero is a small, soft, hairy donkey.
So soft, one would say
he's made of cotton with no bones."
Platero and I by Juan Ramón Jiménez.
We know.
I don’t know if you noticed,
but you're ruining an intimate moment.
LISBON: Hmm?
[LISBON SIGHS]
What's wrong?
Are you horny?
I was. I was, yeah.
- Oh, yeah?
- Hm-mmm.
You don't seem very imaginative.
You might be a little shocked.
- Please! For God's sake...
- Oh, wow! Is that right?
Hm-mmm.
Oh! [CHUCKLES]
Do you want me to stay?
No.
And you?
Why are we talking about this?
Because I'm proposing a threesome.
Palermo, you and me.
He handles the numbers and calculations.
You handle our strategy,
but I'm the best fucking captain
you can have in there.
Because when things
start getting fucked up,
I react.
That's not something you learn
by studying. You're born with it.
Gentlemen,
I'm assuming command.
Let's operate.
Assuming command. The brains.
The intelligent and temperate one.
The crazy bitch that got us in here
is who you'll lose your lives for. Great.
I'm gonna let you all
play little doctors...
while I think about my next move.
Careful, huh?
[DOGS BARKING]
TOKYO: That half hour was our darkest time.
In 30 minutes,
the police covered lots of ground
shooting at the trees.
They kept us isolated and desperate.
And the Professor,
inside the drinking trough,
was thinking about those 30 minutes
and how if he could've made this call
half an hour earlier...
[COUGHS]
...Lisbon would be alive.
[PANTING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
It's time to begin phase two of Hamelin.
MARSEILLE: Copy that.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
PRIVATE NUMBER
Alicia, empathy, dialogue and truce.
[LINE RINGING]
Professor.
Five minutes as a widower,
and you're calling other women.
Naughty boy.
You're a real horn dog, aren't ya?
- Did you order her execution?
- I didn’t have time. She executed herself.
Raquel Murillo
violently resisted her arrest,
firing against her ex-colleagues,
- just like a traitor.
- MARTÍNEZ: Colonel.
The signal isn't in Madrid.
Looks like a highway.
Close to Huelva.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
TAMAYO: Ángel, he's getting away from us.
That bastard is on the move 42 kilometers
away from your position.
You sure? What if it's another trap?
I'm completely sure.
The signal bounced off three repeaters.
He's on National 435, north. Go after him.
Okay.
[DOGS BARKING]
Inspector Rubio to all units.
We're leaving.
The target is escaping
along National route 435, northbound.
[DOGS BARKING]
Listen to me, Sierra.
Before we get out of the Bank of Spain,
I will burn you to the ground.
SIERRA: You're so boring.
Weren't you a professor of ethics?
Oh, no. You fired two rockets
in the center of Madrid,
and now you're the same as al-Qaeda. Huh.
Bing, bang, boom. Made a joke out of you!
I'm going to fix my mistakes,
and now I’m giving you the chance
to do the same.
- Nairobi...
- No.
I'm not sending a surgeon in.
But I can give you an easy solution.
Send Nairobi out,
and I'll have an ambulance waiting here.
I'm not going to leave Nairobi
in the hands of the one
who tried to kill her.
- You'll face the consequences.
- Oh, yes. I'm trembling with fear.
Okay, fine. I will show off my goodwill
by offering you a truce.
For 48 hours.
This way, you can assess
how seRÍOus the wound is.
- Or just let her die in there.
- I accept the truce.
But listen to me.
Nairobi is going to survive...
with or without your help.
Good.
Let's go catch that motherfucker!
[PANTING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
LISBON: How do we get out of the epicenter?
By following Plan Hamelin.
[CHUCKLES] Let's hear it.
Marseille will play on his flute,
and all of the mice
will start to chase him.
LISBON: We'll make them believe
Operation Cage failed?
- Exactly.
- Hm.
PROFESSOR: We’re going to leave false tracks, but...
we'll make it believable
by supporting it with evidence.
And the trees where we were hiding
will be empty.
LISBON: And when the predators are gone,
we'll climb down from the trees
like monkeys. [CHUCKLES]
Won't it be the greatest reunion
of your entire life?
[LAUGHS]
[ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Why'd you call me Mr. Potato Head?
- I don't know. Your walk?
- My walk? What does that mean?
Maybe because you're... tender.
So, are you calling me tender,
or calling me fat?
Okay, okay.
I prefer you don't answer that.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
You really crossed a line
with Potato Head.
See, now everybody knows about it...
homicide, internal affairs,
even the judiciary.
I didn't know what a meme was
until I got a bunch of memes
of Potato Head.
I'm really sorry, Ángel.
[BOTH LAUGH]
You're not gonna ask me...
why I did all this?
No.
No. I know you did it for love.
When we get to Madrid, they're gonna
offer you a deal for your cooperation.
Yeah.
Strong-arm robbery,
breach of the public peace,
resistance to authority,
possession of weapons,
disclosure of secrets,
collaboration with armed groups
and abduction...
of the hostages...
and of my own daughter.
So, no matter what the deal is,
even if the judge and the system
is empathetic,
I won't be out for 30 years.
So I'm really fucked,
Mr. Potato.
TOKYO: Try to be clear and very concise
with your instructions.
Okay? Good.
How many units of blood do we need?
Have three ready
at the proper temperature.
Denver, how many do we have?
- Three units.
- TOKYO: Go get more.
O negative and A negative.
Draw blood for three operations,
and ask if anyone's a doctor.
Bogotá, downstairs.
It's our only way out of here.
Keep melting gold.
Being in charge suits you.
Nobody trusts you anymore.
Do you know what your only way out
is gonna be when I'm not here?
To walk out with your hands
on the back of your head,
and pray they don't shoot you because
of all the cameras and people outside.
Messieurs...
au revoir.
Hasta luego.
Go ahead, doctor.
Make an incision 15 centimeters
between the sixth and the seventh rib.
TOKYO: Scalpel.
Should anyone get injured,
we'll be more than ready
to save their life.
We'll learn the protocols for the most
common cases of gunshot wounds.
And in the military truck with all
the equipment we need for the heist,
we'll include medical equipment in case
any type of surgery is necessary.
Dr. Ahmed will be the brains,
but he'll be 7,000 kilometers away,
so you will be his hands.
It won't be easy.
You can't hesitate.
You can't fail.
Because it's not gonna be
a dead pig on the table.
It'll be one of you.
- Aspirator. I can't see well.
- TOKYO: Bring the camera closer.
DR. AHMED: Always keep the surgical area clear.
- Better.
- So what's next?
We need to separate the ribs.
It's possible
you will have to remove part of the lung.
RÍO: Separate the ribs?
Are you kidding?
TOKYO: Go get me the rib spreader.
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Is this it?
- Yes. Bring it here.
Those with blood type O negative
and A negative, put your hands up now.
Are you gonna make us
check your medical records, or what?
Paquita.
You were a nurse, weren't you?
Yes, sir, and a midwife.
Then follow me.
Everyone who raised their hands
come with me now!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
MAN: Hey...
Hey, Professor!
PROFESSOR: Marseille?
Yeah, it's me. Keep calm.
[PROFESSOR GRUNTS]
- Come on. There's no police.
- And the bull?
- What bull?
- Help me get up. My body's numb.
MARSEILLE: That bull?
- [GROWLS]
- That bull.
Oh!
PROFESSOR: Step back
really slowly, Marseille.
Don’t stop staring him in the eye.
Backwards.
- Doesn't this remind you of something?
- [BULL BELLOWS]
San Fermín?
MARSEILLE: No.
Italy.
The time we met... at the wedding.
TATIANA: Come on. Farther back!
This bouquet thing,
don't single women catch it?
Martín, do you see any single woman here?
- The closest thing we have is you.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
TATIANA: It's tradition!
The bride throws the bouquet,
so just move a little further back.
BERLIN: Come on! Let's go!
BOGOTÁ: A welder, a gay,
a mute, and even a librarian.
The fun never stops. Gotta love Italians.
[LAUGHS]
I'm not mute. I just keep quiet.
And I'm not... I am not a librarian.
Please limit yourself
to calling me Sergio.
Ladies, stay focused!
- The bride is about to throw the bouquet!
- Girls, a little farther back!
BERLIN: Farther back!
Farther back!
[BULL BELLOWS]
[SNORTS]
[BELLOWS]
[BULL BELLOWS]
[BOTH PANTING]
- [BULL RETREATING]
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
TATIANA: Ready?
Whoo!
[CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
BERLIN: Little brother!
[LAUGHS] Bravissimo, little brother!
I'm so happy for you.
Well, Mrs. Fonollosa, we must begin
the wedding dance, but first...
- I have a surprise.
- What?
BERLIN: Ooh!
[SINGING IN ITALIAN]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Come on! Everybody sing! Come on!
[SONG CONTINUES]
TOKYO: Like people
with no sense of rhythm that can't dance,
the Professor just sat at the table,
and he asked himself,
what weighs more?
Love or death?
BERLIN: Life weighs more, little brother.
Life.
Then there’s me. Even though I'm dying,
I'm getting married.
[LAUGHS]
Isn't it a beautiful contradiction?
[TATIANA LAUGHS]
Does she know you're sick?
BERLIN: Ah, of course she knows. Hmm.
She's very smart.
And if you look on the bright side,
it's good luck.
People have no idea
when their time's gonna come.
But we get to stay
in the honeymoon peRÍOd forever.
People buy a bottle of champagne
for a special celebration,
but go back to their mundane days.
Tatiana and I are gonna live our lives
burning through barrels of champagne
from France!
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
Death can be the greatest opportunity
of your life, Sergio.
You're sad, Professor?
If you want,
you can talk to me about feelings.
Do you want to listen to some music?
Music tends to cheer people up.
["TE ESTOY AMANDO LOCAMENTE" PLAYING]
This is a stolen car.
This music is not mine!
It doesn’t matter, Marseille.
Just keep driving.
[SONG CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
WOMAN: Excuse me.
Um, who's the blood for?
Why do you care who the blood's for?
I saw two people going upstairs
with the teddy bear,
but there's only one of them now.
Well, now you know who it's for.
So let's stay quiet.
- Denver.
- What?
Thanks, man.
- For what?
- I wanted to get in here
so I could talk to you in person.
I know we didn't exactly start off
on the right foot,
but at the end of the day,
the only thing that's important
is that you raise my son.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing, you moron?
It's fine, Paquita. That's enough.
That's enough. Thank you.
I know at your age
with all the money you've got...
Pft! [LAUGHS SOFTLY]
I’m pretty sure changing shitty diapers
wasn't in the cards.
That’s why you've got my respect.
Because you've gotta be a real man
to take care of a kid that was born
from the sperm of another guy.
Listen, you motherfucker.
Shut up, and don't fuck with me,
or I'll beat the teeth out of your face.
STOCKHOLM: He's not...
He's not A negative.
Arturo is A positive.
Arturo, what have you done?
What have you done?
What if I didn't check these?
This could have killed Nairobi.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry. I was wrong.
I swear I'd never do that on purpose.
I knew I was A something,
but I didn’t know what,
positive or negative.
Who knows these things?
It's not something you use every day.
Oh, okay. So you're confused now.
Is that it?
[ARTURO GROANS]
- What the fuck, Denver?
- What do you mean?
What are you doing?
Maybe he was actually confused. Fuck.
[COUGHING]
- Help him, for Christ's sake!
- Get up. You’re okay.
Get up!
You can't go around
punching people like that. Jesus!
It's enough
that they're already trapped in here.
Now it's over.
He's okay. It’s over. I'm sorry.
It's no problem.
You see...
[PANTING]
I know why you're so pissed at me, buddy.
- Why? Why?
- It's okay. I get it.
Monica told you
what happened in the bathroom, didn't she?
What bathroom?
What bathroom? What is he talking about?
I really apologize.
I'm sorry. God, I don't know
what was going through my head, really.
It was so long since I'd seen her.
She was so close.
I don't know.
I guess I didn't read the signs right.
She told me that we would meet somewhere
after this so I could see my son.
One thing led to another, and I jumped.
You jumped?
He jumped for what?
Denver, nothing happened.
Just let it go. Let it go.
You were gonna meet this piece of shit
to show him our son?
He tricked me. He said he was his father.
He was emotional.
Yeah, but what did he jump for?
I don't understand this.
ARTURO: She didn't do anything.
Leave Monica out of it.
The person at fault is me.
We hugged, I got aroused,
- things got heated.
- Shut up!
Is this true?
This dumb motherfucker
rubbed himself against you with a hard-on?
I pushed him away
in a second with the gun, Denver.
Listen to me.
I defended myself, Denver.
So it is true.
[HOSTAGES GASP]
- [ARTURO GROANS]
- STOCKHOLM: Stop! Please stop!
Stop! You're gonna kill him!
- Stop! You're gonna kill him!
- [DENVER YELLS]
STOCKHOLM: Stop! Stop!
[GROANS]
[ARTURO COUGHS]
[SOBS]
What the fuck is this?
What the fuck do you have inside of you?
So much rage.
So much violence.
You shot a hostage.
And now you beat him up.
Like a maniac.
[SOBS] I can't do this.
I don't know what your trauma is.
I don't know what your trauma is
or where it comes from, but...
I can't, Denver.
I can't, and I don’t want to.
I don’t want to.
I don’t want my son...
to feel that irrational violence
you carry inside of you.
I don't want that.
MAN: That's right. Go on.
- Good morning.
- Is it him?
- The car rolled several times.
There's traces of blood, we can't find
the driver. It's gotta be him.
Or a drug dealer,
or a random criminal, no?
The car was stolen
two and a half hours ago in Salvatierra,
the closest village
to the place where we found Murillo.
And he climbs trees.
ÁNGEL: Right.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me.
[CELL PHONE RINGING AND BUZZING]
- Yes, Colonel.
- Was it him?
I think so. He can't be far.
Looks like he lost a lot of blood.
We'll leave it to Suarez.
I need you here with Murillo.
Bring her to Madrid.
That's what's most important. Got it?
- Yeah, copy that.
- And make sure Suarez
sends units to all the area hospitals,
every veterinarian,
even the fucking monasteries.
I want everyone on high alert.
The only way he's getting away from us
is if he's dead.
Pamuk.
What?
My dog's name was Pamuk.
It was with me during the whole war.
I know what you feel.
Marseille, are you trying to create
a metaphor
or something between your dead dog
and my wife?
She was a female dog.
After the war,
all of my friends were dead.
And I...
spent my nights in a bar.
One day, another day.
Pamuk was always outside waiting. Always.
So you two were also in love,
and was she executed in front of you?
Yes.
What happened to Pamuk?
The boys from the village...
liked to play war.
So after a while,
without an enemy,
they got all bored of playing war.
One day,
they found some rocks.
They broke bottles...
and said my Pamuk
was the enemy.
I'm sorry.
She was a good dog.
Marseille, can you stop for a moment?
I need to... urinate.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
[SOBBING]
[WAILING]
Good piss?
Mmm-hm.
Pissing is a relief sometimes.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
TOKYO: Even though we were all in pain,
we couldn't lose sight of one fact:
our lives depended on what was happening
48 meters below the ground.
The plan had a very simple rule:
either we got the gold out,
or we were all dead.
No matter what was going on above,
the gold had to be taken out.
DR. AHMED: Move the lung.
I want to see the lower part.
Lift it up.
Colonel!
There's been an increase
in the flow of the electromagnetic signals
coming in and out of the bank.
Martínez, in clear terms, please.
They're communicating
with someone outside.
DR. AHMED: Move the image closer. Good.
Okay. We need to remove
the lower part of the lung.
There's a risk of infection and necrosis.
It could cost her life.
RÍO: How are we gonna cut
part of her lung?
- Do you have an electric scalpel?
- TOKYO: Yes.
From the bandwidth,
it looks like a video call.
TAMAYO: Can we see it?
The signal is encrypted.
I'd say
it’s going through a Kazakh satellite.
And from there, probably through
the deep web, but I'm not sure.
So let's take it down.
DR. AHMED: Let's do it.
There's no time to waste.
Listen and follow my instructions
very closely.
- We're going to move slowly. Understood?
- TOKYO: Understood.
Colonel...
If the satellite belonged
to a phone company in Spain,
- we'd have to request a temporary jam...
- I don't need you to tell me
what we can't do.
I told you to cut off
their little phone call.
DR. AHMED: If a vessel gets cut,
we remove the scalpel
- and close with Kocher forceps.
- TOKYO: Understood.
We'd have to jam every signal in the area,
take down the Internet and anything
going through satellites.
Like in Egypt in 2011.
Do it.
DR. AHMED: Let's make the first incision.
- Can you see the lingula?
- What's a lingula?
It's the lower part of the lung...
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What happened?
RÍO: You've gotta be kidding!
What happened?
- There's no return signal.
- What?
RÍO: Oh, fuck!
- We can't reach the doctor! It's down!
- [SPEAKING SERBIAN]
What do we do?
Her blood pressure's dropping.
We're about to lose her!
- TOKYO: No, no, no, no. Fuck!
- [BEEPING]
[CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44