A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
TOKYO: There's always happier days to remember.
And the more fucked up things are,
the happier those days seem to be.
While waiting for a miracle and listening
to the beeps of Nairobi's vital signs,
I remembered one of those days.
The soccer match at the monastery.
- Defense! One minute!
- PALERMO: Let's go!
- NAIROBI: Go!
- PALERMO: Hey, Nairobi!
I'm open here! Got it!
Hey! There!
TOKYO: I'd never imagine
that the seconds before a throw-in
could be so much fun.
Hey! Hold on!
- DENVER: What are you doing?
- Wait!
You think 'cause I'm gay
you can put your hands on my balls?
PROFESSOR: For God's sake! Shut up!
There's one minute left,
- and you're arguing?
- DENVER: He hit me in the back.
You rubbed your hands all over his balls!
Okay, that's enough! From now on, no one's
touching anyone. You understand?
- Come on! Go! Let's go!
- Come on. Let's go!
PALERMO: Hey!
DENVER: Oh! So close, man.
Penalty!
Hey, that's enough!
- NAIROBI: They're gonna have a fight!
- [SPEAKS SERBIAN]
TOKYO: Ooh! There he goes!
PROFESSOR: Get up.
Get out of here. Let's go.
- Good luck with this.
- Come on.
DENVER: Let's go!
- [BEEPING]
- RÍO: There's no return signal.
- They took everything down.
- TOKYO: What do we do?
- GOVERNOR: We're about to lose her.
- TOKYO: No, no, no! Fuck!
[STEADY BEEPING]
[UNEASY MUSIC]
GOVERNOR: Be careful.
Slowly.
TOKYO: Okay. I got it.
GOVERNOR: A little bit higher.
You're doing really well.
Now get the bullet out.
Go ahead.
Yeah, that’s it.
Good, good.
Careful. That’s it.
Yes! There it is.
["DAYS LIKE THIS" BY VAN MORRISON PLAYING]
♪ When it's not always raining ♪
♪ There'll be days like this... ♪
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
TOKYO: But I guess that's nostalgia.
Finding out that moments from the past,
even if we didn't realize it at the time,
were true happiness.
♪ Well, my mama told me ♪
♪ There'll be days like this ♪
- ♪ When you don't need to worry ♪
- TOKYO: Fuck, yeah!
♪ There'll be days like this ♪
♪ When no one's in a hurry... ♪
TOKYO: We still hadn't reached
the end of the first half,
and Lisbon was already three kilometers
away from the tent,
- forced to switch jerseys.
- [SIREN WAILING]
A goal by Sierra
from the edge of the field.
♪ There'll be days like this... ♪
TOKYO: Meanwhile, like robots,
we removed a piece of Nairobi's lung.
We didn't even know
if we were saving her life or ending it.
The second loss for our team.
A second goal against us.
And the third goal was coming.
Palermo was gonna score it,
and it would be on our side.
♪ There'll be days like this ♪
♪ When everyone is up front... ♪
TOKYO: He was a good captain,
but he was a terrible team player.
♪ When it's nobody's business ♪
♪ The way that you want to live ♪
♪ I just have to remember ♪
♪ There'll be days like this ♪
♪ When no one steps on my dreams ♪
♪ When people understand what I mean... ♪
TOKYO: The Professor's arrival in Madrid
was the only thing happening
according to the plan.
But not even that was right.
Because a rider was missing.
Professor, we have to go.
TOKYO: On a motorbike through forest
trails, dirt roads and cattle farms,
they crossed La Mancha without being seen.
The knight and his squire,
defeat after defeat,
advancing towards a crazy battle
in this insane war.
Meanwhile,
everything was about to explode.
♪ There'll be days like this ♪
[SIREN WAILING]
[SIRENS CONTINUE]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
SIERRA: Can you believe it?
Me, pregnant?
Who would've thought, huh?
How great.
SIERRA: Thank you.
["MY LIFE IS GOING ON" BY CECILIA KRULL]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
- [MAN BLOWING AIR]
- AMANDA: Okay. Just a little more.
AMANDA: You're very brave, huh?
I only did what I had to do.
If we don't stand up to them,
they'll walk over us like in Auschwitz.
- If it stings too much, let me know, okay?
- Use all the alcohol you want.
I can handle pain. It's nothing.
Uh, let's see.
Ooh!
[ARTURO GRUNTS]
[WHISPERS] Did you lose your fucking mind?
You almost killed him.
- You can't lose your shit like that!
- How can I not?
- We're in a nightmare.
- Exactly!
Exactly. You can't keep getting
into fights like a fucking teenager.
[MUSIC STING]
- You have blood all over your T-shirt.
- Oh!
Pretend I'm not even here.
I can't see a thing, not in this eye.
Listen, Amanda...
have you had any anxiety attacks
because of this whole heist thing?
Well, yeah. I think so.
ARTURO: Of course.
And also, I can’t seem to sleep for more
than 30 minutes straight, you know?
- No.
- I feel a lump in here that doesn't...
That's...
That's normal in these cases
because, see,
there is so much tension in here.
Too much tension, but don't worry.
I’m gonna get you something
for that anxiety.
'Cause the thing is,
we really don't want you to suffer
from post-traumatic stress
because it's hard to get over.
And, well, in some cases,
it could even last forever.
Hey.
Come here. Let me help you.
You have blood on you.
Don't worry, honey,
because as long as I'm around,
I'll make sure
you have everything you need.
ARTURO: Hmm?
You'll be my personal project.
DENVER: We're in a heist
inside the Bank of Spain.
Maybe you forgot how this works,
I didn't.
- We never acted like assholes.
- Maybe I have some trauma.
Maybe that's what's going on.
Maybe we all have trauma.
What are you saying?
What trauma do I have?
- Maybe I shouldn't say it.
- Tell...
You broke up with Tokyo.
How many guys, other than you,
would break up with Tokyo?
Nobody. Nobody would break up with that.
What do you know about Tokyo?
Tokyo's a fucking Maserati,
and everyone wants a Maserati.
And if you take a Maserati,
leave it on the street,
doors open and keys in the ignition,
you've gotta be really fucked up.
Look, RÍO...
I'm gonna make this really clear.
Maybe you're traumatized
'cause they screwed with your manhood.
Maybe they changed you
with the... the torture.
But you need to let it go.
That's why you broke up with Tokyo, huh?
If you were hurt by one person
or a group, the trauma is no different,
so let it go!
You can count on me.
I'm here to help with anything you need.
Anything.
Well, ladies and gentlemen...
I'm sorry to inform you
that I must say au revoir.
I'm leaving.
Keep up the good work. You're doing great.
What the fuck you think your doing?
Matías...
I'm leaving.
It's been a pleasure working with you,
as always.
And I would even say...
that I love you dearly, Matías.
As for you all,
I hope my leadership
hasn't been too traumatic.
But at least it'll be a fun story
for your loved ones,
your kids, your grandchildren, whatever.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's been a pleasure.
- [SHOT FIRED]
- [HOSTAGES SCREAM]
What the fuck?
[HOSTAGES WHIMPERING]
Calm down.
Palermo, calm down.
We can talk.
Calmly.
But as for leaving, that's not happening.
PALERMO: Motherfucker!
You staged a coup d'état,
you fucking bitch!
What do you want?
I am in charge of the military,
you the technical.
PALERMO: The technical?
Do I strike you as some sort of
geeky engineer with glasses?
What kind of orders
would I be giving down there? Let's see...
Now melt! Now don't!
Bathyscaphe in! Bathyscaphe out!
Immersion! Emersion!
[IMITATES HORN BLARING]
Who the fuck do you think I am?
I didn't come in here for that bullshit!
I'm not in the mood for this. I'm leaving.
I'm activating...
the manual door,
and I'm doing you a favor.
If I stay, I'll rain down bullets on you,
you fucking bitch, and everyone else.
I'm not in your gang anymore.
[EXHALES]
I'm the one that's doing you a favor here.
Because, I swear,
the next thing I’m gonna do...
is blow your fuckin' head off.
I don't think so.
I do think so.
Claymore mines.
As you can see,
they're pointed in your direction.
I'll be fine over here.
You know that I don't give a shit
if I have to kill you.
PALERMO: Relax.
TOKYO: You won't betray us like that.
Wanna bet on it?
HELSINKI: Palermo!
Calm down!
PALERMO: Ah, yes!
The bearded princess just arrived to wave
her prince goodbye at the train station.
For God's sake,
have some dignity, Helsinki.
Where are you going?
To jail?
To be shot in the forehead?
To betray your friends?
I'm not selling anyone out.
My safe passage is right here.
State secrets.
I'm not gonna betray you.
Leaving is treason.
Leaving us alone in here is treason.
- PALERMO: No!
- [SCREAMING]
I don't wanna kill you today, fatty.
You don't wanna kill me?
Well, you're gonna have to kill me.
PALERMO: Don't be an idiot, Helsinki.
Because if you go outside,
I swear...
I'll go boom,
boom,
ciao.
I'm telling the truth, Palermo.
I'll do it.
That's the truth.
[WHISPERS] I got you.
[KISSES]
Can you please tell me
what you said to RÍO?
- About what?
- Did you tell him he's traumatized?
DENVER: Call it trauma or whatever you want.
- Something is wrong with him.
- Something's wrong?
Why? Because he left Tokyo, no?
And she's a Maserati.
Okay, hang on.
The Maserati thing
was just the way guys talk.
What really matters
is that after the torture,
something happened to him.
I think they changed him.
They did what?
DENVER: Forty sweaty guys opened his back door.
- [SIGHS]
- They combed him inside.
RÍO is dealing with being tortured,
and you feed him all that bullshit?
All that bullshit is true. I asked him
if they forced him to do things.
Know what he did? He was quiet.
He was quiet because it's true.
A textbook case.
I can't.
You can’t what?
You know, all of a sudden,
I feel like there's...
a balloon that burst.
- What balloon?
- [STOCKHOLM SIGHS]
What balloon?
Monica, no! I wanna know what balloon.
What balloon are we talking about?
What balloon?
It's as if suddenly
my blindfold came off, Denver.
I look at you, and I don't recognize you.
I don’t know what we're doing together,
you and I.
I don't know who you are.
Monica, don't get me wrong.
I said Tokyo was a Maserati,
that doesn't mean you're a used car.
I'm sorry, Denver.
I can't be with you.
[DRAMATIC EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Look...
When you see her coming at you
as angry as a hydra, well, you shut up.
A hydra.
Um, no? Well, forget it.
Just keep your mouth shut.
- And I don't defend myself?
- No.
Because you don't even know
what she's angry about.
You shut up,
and the less you know
what she's talking about,
the more sorry you look.
All you say is,
"yes" and "I am sorry, my love."
Now, that's a textbook case.
- Sounds like a textbook for pussies.
- A textbook for survivors.
You wait for the storm to pass,
and then, when you figure out
where the wind is coming from,
and when she seems to be calmed down,
well, then and only then...
you make a move.
Understand what I'm saying?
She's been mad at me since the monastery.
That's what's going on.
- Well...
- Yeah.
We dragged it all here.
And because of the pressure
from the heist, it all explodes.
That's what's going on.
TOKYO: Professor.
It's Tokyo.
- Tokyo, you just staged a coup d'état.
- Palermo's gone crazy.
He was about to explode
the main operation room,
- but I have it under control.
- No, you don't.
You can't control Palermo
because he's unpredictable.
He's tied up
and under 24-hour surveillance.
Tokyo, the whole plan is falling apart!
I'm still here... Professor.
So what if you’re still there, Tokyo?
Without Palermo, we are incapable
of getting the gold out,
or do you know how to do it, huh?
And without Nairobi!
And without Lisbon!
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
PROFESSOR: Palermo was escaping
because it's the only smart move left.
Professor...
you've always been my guardian angel.
Now it's my turn.
How did it happen?
She died so she could protect me.
I'm really so sorry.
I...
was camouflaged in a tree,
and there were...
There were soldiers,
and police were everywhere.
And she was in a farm.
That’s where they found her.
They made her kneel down,
unarmed, and they asked about me.
And I ran and ran, and...
They asked her, "Where's the Professor?"
I said, "Tell them, Raquel.
Tell them where I am.
Tell them I'll surrender. Please."
"I don't know."
She repeated, "I don't know."
And they shot her two times.
She was unarmed,
and they shot her two times.
I couldn't make it on time.
But did you see it?
No.
You only heard it?
Professor, did you see them move the body?
I had to run.
Listen to me.
I also heard my mother
telling me to come home,
that I'd be safe there, but there were
20 cops waiting for me in her kitchen.
And in the tent,
they also heard us escaping from the bank.
But we're still here.
The only one that got out
was the little ferret with a jumpsuit.
Did they publish anything?
Nothing.
Just like with RÍO.
If they really killed her, we'd know.
She's being interrogated.
- Where you going, Professor?
- To the Bank of Spain.
No, no, no.
It's not a good idea. It’s too risky.
I appreciate your concern,
but it's the only place
where I can find out
if my wife is still alive. Move.
- No!
- I'm asking you nicely.
- Step aside, Marseille...
I won't allow you
to get on the motorbike.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
SIERRA: Seventy.
With what we have in those files,
you'll be 70 years old
when you get out of jail.
And Paula 40.
And your mother
will have been dead so long
- you won't even be able to find her grave.
- Just stop.
You don't have to do that.
The years are up to the prosecution,
not you,
and the conviction by the judge.
You know very well
that the prosecutor and the judge
are gonna work...
based on what I write in these reports.
And I can write whatever I want.
What would you like me to write?
Are you going to force me
to resort to violence?
- I’m only protecting the plan.
- I decide the plan!
That's not the plan.
That's an improvisation.
And like you always said,
no improvisation.
I won't give in.
I want you to understand
that I need to be there.
The only place I can get answers
is the Bank of Spain.
Very well.
SeRÍOusly, Professor? Huh?
I don't know where the Professor is,
or what he'll do.
You have no ideas?
Has love made you dim or something?
The plan has different types of firewalls.
This is nothing to do with our love.
SIERRA: Of course it does.
Think about it.
In jail, love drains like sewer water.
It happens very fast.
In two months, it's already dry.
Two months of suffering,
or your whole life in jail?
Hmm?
If you were reincarnated seven times,
you'd never understand
the nature of our love.
To protect the plan,
we need to know
if she is there and under interrogation
because if she is, that means
Alicia Sierra is interrogating my wife,
and that is taking place
at the Bank of Spain!
But you can't go!
Allow me to tell you
about the real nature of your love.
One in Soto del Real,
and the other in Cádiz,
waiting for a conjugal visit once a year.
And that's if you’re lucky
because if we don't catch your sweetheart,
then you'll never see him again
in your fucking life.
The choice is yours.
Either that or actually have the time
to raise to your daughter.
You're not trying
to fuck with my emotions, Alicia.
I'm just telling you the truth.
Like I always do.
We need to go to the Bank of Spain.
And how are you gonna get to the tent
if your face is all over the news, huh?
Just like everyone else.
Dressed in red with a face of Dalí.
Good. Good.
She... She won't betray us.
Give me your hand.
How many of your old relationships
feel completely meaningless now?
The same thing will happen with this one,
and you know it.
Everyone could betray me, Marseille.
Everyone.
- It's just a matter of...
- [PROFESSOR GROANS]
What the hell? You hit me!
Weren't we finished?
We were?
I didn't know.
[SIGHS]
[SINGING IN ITALIAN]
Sergio, come on.
- Just drink a little bit more.
- I had two already.
- This is a strange wedding, Andrés.
- This is so great!
- I don’t think so.
- Little brother!
I feel sorry for her because she's young
and she's in love,
and if you remember, you have a disease.
Didn't you hear the priest, hmm?
"Till death do you part."
Andrés, fine. Maybe for you,
this is the grand finale, but for her,
it's the beginning, and this beginning
is not fair. It just isn’t.
My God! She knows about my illness.
Everyone knows about my illness.
You are betraying her feelings.
[LAUGHS]
I’m gonna give her the best
two or three years of her entire life.
Yes, yes, and after that...
Yes, I guess I'll somehow betray her.
Anyway,
betrayal is an inherent part of love.
Since we're on the subject, look at him!
Martín.
So loyal! My best friend. Happy.
Would he betray me?
BERLIN: Hmm?
Of course, he would.
He just needs the right circumstances.
Tatiana?
[SIGHS] Tatiana, as well.
No. You say your life is about
love and feelings
more than anyone else,
but all you see are traitors.
- No, no, no, no!
- Everywhere.
That's not what I'm saying.
No. What I'm saying is that
betrayal doesn't depend on how much
or deeply you love someone.
It depends on the magnitude
of the dilemma put in front of you.
Would you... Would you betray
your loved one? At first, no.
But what would happen
if someone told you if you did
you'd be given a medicine
that could cure your beloved brother?
[BERLIN LAUGHS]
Now, that's a good dilemma. [LAUGHS]
Come! Come!
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[GLASS SMASHES]
SIERRA: Sergio Marquina.
Emotional coldness.
Compulsive narcissism.
Socially inept.
Psychopathic traits.
[CHEERING]
- In short, a real gem.
- LISBON: Well...
a report made without interviewing
the subject by your mindless dogs.
I can assure you,
he's a lot more fun than that.
[SCOFFS]
Charming.
I know. A psychopath can be a lot of fun.
Then there's your profile.
Huh?
What's in my profile?
That you're the type that gets
hooked by bastards like this guy.
You idealize them.
And little by little,
you get smaller and smaller by their side.
Then they use you. Manipulate you.
When did you lose your instincts,
inspector?
Was it before the Professor
entered into your life?
Because Alberto used to beat you up.
How does this one humiliate you?
First, you use my mother's Alzheimer's,
and now domestic violence.
Tell me you don't see a pattern here.
Tell me you never heard your mind
going "click"
and thought, "Watch out.
This guy could be a real piece of shit."
Tell me it's not true.
PROFESSOR: You know the protocols,
how they negotiate, but so do I.
I got you last time, Raquel.
I must be an idiot...
because I thought
that we'd fallen in love.
I never asked you to come with me.
She's just bluffing.
She hung up,
and we didn't even play our hand!
He went after you
because you're the weakest link.
SIERRA: What would he do for you?
Would he follow you to an island
with his mother and daughter?
Would he follow one of your plans?
How many times
has he listened to your ideas?
Once.
Or did you always follow him
like a little puppy?
I warned you about Alberto.
Complete motherfucker.
And I’m warning you about this one.
I'm gonna ask you
a very simple question, Raquel.
Do you deserve to spend
30 years of your life in jail
for that little fuck in a mask?
Colonel.
I've been taking a look
at the arrest reports,
and it could be my mistake,
but I can't find any records
from the arrest of Murillo.
You were looking at what?
I don't want a technical issue
like that to... Oh, you know...
- It's a question of human rights.
- What's the matter with you?
Did volunteers outside the supermarket
get you to join an NGO?
Did you join Amnesty International?
Get the fuck out.
If you were to obey the law, Colonel...
Look, Antoñanzas. Do you know
when we fully obey the law here?
Can you take a guess? Hmm?
Come on. Answer me.
- Well, whenever, uh...
- I feel like it.
The feeling usually comes from
the back part of my balls, the dark side,
and usually arrest reports and procedural
guarantees don't reach that far.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
TAMAYO: Hmm.
So until then...
Until then, that bitch
will be sitting over there
in a chair with no sleep
and pissing in a bucket.
Do we have a problem?
No, no, no. No, sir.
Better, Antoñanzas. Better.
[CHANTING]
TRANSPARENCY
GIVE ME A RAISE
LONG LIVE EVIL
LONG LIVE CAPITAL
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
TOKYO: The Professor wished
he'd had X-ray vision
to see if Lisbon was in the tent.
But he wasn't Superman,
so he had to settle
with being Sherlock Holmes.
He made it to the outside of the bank
in search of a thread to pull,
and he found three.
The van. What was it doing there?
And why did it have mud on it?
PROFESSOR: CNP85600N.
TOKYO: Pakistan answered those questions.
The vehicle belonged
to the national police of Huelva,
close to the place
where Lisbon had supposedly been executed.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Ángel.
If someone had to be following
the tracks of plan Hamelin, it'd be him.
Unless he had
something more important to do.
Like transporting Lisbon to Madrid.
And if someone had to be crying
over a friend's death,
it also would be him.
And Alicia Sierra.
It had been a few hours since the truce,
but there she was.
As much of a workaholic as she was,
she should still be home, resting
and taking care of her swollen ankles.
Unless she was itching to interrogate
one of the most wanted criminals
in the country.
Lisbon might be alive,
but he needed to be sure
and to reach out
and let her know he wouldn't let her down.
They just brought us the ambulance
you used as a communication center.
You know who's examining it?
- [SCOFFS]
- [SIERRA CHUCKLES]
Alberto, your ex.
He's not just the best at what he does.
He also really wants
to fuck up your life a little more.
But there's another option.
I could get in the ambulance before him,
before anyone else,
and get rid of all the evidence.
You'll find nothing.
Fuck, Raquel.
It's like you're new at this.
There's always something.
You'll see. Something in there will lead
us to your mother and your daughter.
You'll see.
[STEADY BEEPING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
The next five, get ready
to go to the restroom with my colleague.
[BLOWS AIR]
Hey, Gandía,
now that we're both on the same side,
may I ask you a question?
I'm a little confused.
Are we...
the good guys or the bad guys?
I'm gonna make a little cut
in your scrotum, pull out your balls,
and then stuff them both in your mouth.
That sounds fun.
But your hands are still tied up, Che.
Did you know
that the reliability of handcuffs
is based upon
one single anatomical concept?
The metacarpus doesn't let them through.
But actually, it's a joint
that's very easy to dislocate.
Is that right?
PALERMO: Well, just some ideas
for liberty.
[PALERMO SINGING IN SPANISH]
♪ Free ♪
♪ Like the sun is free at dawn ♪
♪ I am free ♪
♪ Like the sea ♪
♪ Free ♪
♪ Like the bird
that got out its silent cage ♪
♪ And it can fly at last ♪
♪ I'm free ♪
♪ Like the wind that takes away
all my wailing and my pain ♪
♪ Endless roads and paths ♪
♪ In endless search of truth
And I'll know at last ♪
♪ What freedom is ♪
Time for bed.
[HIGH-PITCHED]
Four little corners to my bed.
Four little angels around my head.
Matthew, Mark, José and John,
bless this bed I lie upon.
[URINATING]
- PROFESSOR: Antoñanzas.
- [PANTING]
What are you doing here? [PANTING]
You're... [BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're under arrest.
On your knees.
I was just giving that a shot.
[COCKS GUN]
Get on your knees.
Please! My wife and my daughters
are asleep in bed.
Nothing's going to happen to them.
All you have to do is follow
my instructions and answer my questions.
I won't say anything
while a gun is pointed at my head.
[ANTOÑANZAS PANTING]
You're gonna speak.
SIERRA: We've got... one:
the ambulance.
[IMITATES AMBULANCE SIREN]
Two:
the crazy grandma.
"Where am I?
Where am I? Oh, my back! I can't."
Three:
the motherless child.
"Mama!
Mama! Mama!"
Four:
El amour du Professor...
which won't last past the second
conjugal visit when you're in jail.
And now...
the final scenaRÍO.
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
You're assaulting an officer of the law.
You don't know
what you're getting yourself into.
We called a truce.
Sometimes a truce
is the most important part of a war.
[PANTING]
ANTOÑANZAS: I can't.
I can't breathe...
[GASPING FOR AIR]
Control yourself, Antoñanzas.
Control yourself.
[WHEEZING]
ANTOÑANZAS: I can't breathe.
Marseille.
[BREATHING SLOWS]
[WATER STOPS]
PROFESSOR: Better?
[ANTOÑANZAS GASPS]
Argh!
If you cooperate,
the prosecutor will request 12 years,
which will turn into ten.
You'll be out in five.
That's what your life could be.
If you don't cooperate, 30 years.
That's what your life will be.
You decide, inspector.
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
[CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Original SUB by hadilan.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44