At the moment you don't know each other
and I want to keep it that way,
I don't want any names.
no personal questions
or, of course, personal relationships.
Profesor.
Miss Tokio.
What are we gonna steal?
La Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre.
What happened?
How many hostages?
- Confirmed, 35 workers,
11 security guards
and 17 kids from the British school.
- I'm Raquel Murillo, Inspector in charge
of the management of the heist.
What do you want?
Time.
We're locked up and we don't know how long.
Let's assign some chores so
you don't get depressed.
- It's 48 m down to the collector.
The shifts will be 3 hours.
We'll go out through another tunnel.
Just take it from vault number three.
I frisked you, almost stopped you,
and you still cares about me.
If you need any kind of help that I can...
Thank you.
- And you have the workshop?
Yes, right next door.
Sorry to intrude, but I can't wait
to try that cider
that you promised me.
Of course you did. Right now.
Did you find anything?
- There was a fingerprint,
but there's no match.
- Check it with the fingerprints of this spoon.
Retroxyl.
Used to palliate tremors from degenerative disease
very infrequent neuronal.
Since it has to be ordered on demand,
they have the patients
very localized.
There was an unusual order in Toledo.
- Just three days before entering the factory.
Go to that pharmacy by yourself.
Please don't talk about this with anyone.
Help, please, we just got mugged.
- Raquel, I don't know,
the pharmacy's been robbed,
the records have been taken.
- You and I knew about the pharmacy.
- You haven't told anyone?
Didn't you say anything to the
weird guy in the cafeteria?
- How much do they pay you?
- Go fuck yourself.
Come on, Salva, look at me under the table.
I have suspicions that you're hiding
something in that workshop
where you make cider.
I'm sorry, Salva, this place is wonderful.
I got you the results of what you asked for.
Raquel, it's me again.
We've got the guy who helps them
from the outside, it's Salva, Salva.
Arturo, can you hear me?
We're in the basement of the boilers.
Have them bring you back. Two hours, two hours.
You take the tools and stick
them under the toilet seat,
on the inside.
Okay.
Give me one fucking reason not to open
your head right now!
They're getting away.
What?
And hostages, he's got six hostages now.
Come here! Come here!
- Aah! Aah!
Listen to me, all of you.
I need you to look for all the farms
with hunting grounds.
within a 100-kilometre radius of the pharmacy.
If they bought the drugs there,
it means they were very close.
- Inspector, we have the house.
- This house has to be search thoroughly.
Every corner.
- I'll only go in there if you promise me,
if it goes to hell,
you won't get caught.
I won't promise you that.
We've won the lottery.
It's all on the walls, schedules, photos, plans,
the whole damn plan.
We got 'em, fellas.
Searching the upper floor.
This room looks like a classroom.
Stools, slate...
There is no human presence.
Inspector, we found something else.
- Don't let anyone into the classroom
other than the CSI.
- Count on it.
- Inspector,
the kitchen and bathroom are
full of debris.
Come with me.
- What's that?
- It looks like anchovies.
- Anchovies.
- Inspector, the purchasing records
that was stolen from the pharmacy.
They're in a drawer.
- Fucking hell.
The person helping them from the outside
has been here
and less than 30 hours ago.
Put surveillance on the adjoining roads.
- Attention, cut the roads in 10 km around.
Suspect may be close, repeat,
the suspect may be close.
- Acknowledged.
"The inspector started secreting
adrenaline and cortisol.
His rhythm and blood pressure went up,
just like a lioness seconds before she
hunts her gazelle.
She was excited and felt the breath
of her prey very close."
We have up to eight different types of prints.
One of them has already been collated.
It belongs to Silene Oliveira, aka Tokio.
"Raquel couldn't stop asking herself questions.
Were those tests a thread to pull
or again a dead end to get stuck in?"
This doesn't make any sense.
"And Raquel were right,
because the Profesor had meticulously planned
to take the police all the way to Toledo,
so they'd left a fantastic crime scene
worthy of an Oscar and full of people's DNA.
that had nothing to do with the heist.
What the Profesor didn't count on was going back
and leave the fingerprints of those the police
already had identified,
Berlín, Río
and me.
And by the way, baffle them with some anchovies
and the pharmacy papers.
All he wanted was to take Murillo to a dead end.
in which he would lose at least three days.
Three very productive days for us,
because they give for a lot when you print bills
at eight million an hour; mostly,
with the help of the hostages."
Come on, girls, I need this counted
in half an hour.
What's the matter with you?
Get a move on, girl.
Look at the smile people work with.
To work, to work, that work means power.
"Become accomplices and with the illusion
of one day receiving
by post one million euros."
You with me.
- Uoh!
"Something didn't fit.
Between those walls there was nothing
they didn't already know.
What the Profesor had calculated
would take three days,
the inspector took 50 minutes."
Suárez, call Alberto, have him come
as soon as he can.
- Alberto, your ex-husband.
- Isn't he the best of the CSI?
Well, let him come.
- Attention, communication with headquarters.
Operational service 315 Toledo estate.
Inspector Murillo requests Vicuña's presence,
of the CSI.
"Raquel, I'm Julia, Paula's teacher.
I just wanted to let you know that
Paula's father was here.
and took her out to eat.
He said it was a family event.
I'd like to meet with you.
No, it's not about Paula, Paula's doing fine,
but her father
wants to buy me a coffee after class and...
And I don't quite know how to approach it."
You can't come in.
Sorry, I know the inspector.
Raquel.
- Salva.
Excuse me, I just wanted to say goodbye.
I'm sorry about all this mess.
No, no. You're working.
Don't worry about a thing. It's all right.
I'll take that road, I'll get to town
and some bus I'll find for Madrid.
Wait. Suárez, is there a car going
to Madrid now?
- The first batch of evidence comes out
in half an hour.
I really don't want to bother you.
I take a bus and nothing happens.
- Pulling along the road and then all to the right
you get to the road.
I thought I saw a stop.
Yes.
- Salva, no problem
a companion takes you to Madrid.
Thank you.
- It's about time.
- There's still a minute till 6:00.
- Well, given the circumstances,
you know where I'm going to get your fucking
British punctuality.
Third unanswered call.
That's 18 hours without news of The Profesor.
We already know what that means.
We'll make a control call every six hours.
What if you don't call us?
- Or if you don't pick up the phone.
If for any reason something
unforeseen comes up,
you'll have to wait for the next call.
and so on to complete a cycle of four calls,
24 hours.
What if in 24 hours we've lost
contact with you?
Then, almost certainly,
they'll have stopped me and they'll
be interrogating me.
- We don't know anything about the police either.
I'm sure there's something going on outside.
What do we do?
- All right, then,
there's still one call left to complete
the cycle,
at 00:00.
- What cycle?
The fucking mousetrap cycle?
- Denver, relax.
The Profesor will be tying up some loose ends.
There's nothing to worry about yet.
At the moment we're still watching the hostages
and printing money.
I'm gonna get some rest.
Are you kidding me?
With the problem we have on top of us,
are you going to go fuck now?
Tokio, please.
What?
There's no need for you to get all ordinary.
You don't need it. It doesn't suit you.
That's the first thing.
And second, if I had to look
for some ally here,
in this band, on hedonistic terms,
that would be you.
What happened to carpe diem?
It happened that the plan fell to
fucking pieces.
and maybe you don't care because
you're hopeless,
but not me.
I'm going.
- Son of a bitch.
- Another one.
- Are you really fucking a hostage?
Who, that poor thing you got here and there.
like I'm a fucking secretary?
- Not poor, her name is Ariadna.
And, yes, we've bonded.
The day we came in here
Ariadna trembled in a way I recognize.
That fragility, that delicacy
awakened something in me.
- What a shitty speech, 'cause there's
nothing more crawling
in this life than fucking a hostage.
- Ah...
- It's not that bad to be with
a hostage either, is it?
What's going on?
I can be accused
of good fucking or bad fucking,
but not from fucking at gunpoint.
- Denver, no.
- What's up? Yes, I have a relationship too
with Mónica Gaztambide.
- What are you saying, son?
- Hell, I saved her life and she hugged
me and kissed me.
I didn't make her do anything.
There was love.
- Ay...
- But what love, you little asshole?
Don't you know what Stockholm syndrome is?
- Well, no, Nairobi,
I don't know what that syndrome is;
but if he's got a syndrome or a fucking disease,
we'll get through it together.
- You're not going to get through it together
because you're provoking her.
Stockholm syndrome
is when the hostage ends up having feelings
for the kidnapper.
This girl is scared,
but you're a fucking illiterate and
you think it's love.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- That's enough.
All right.
None of us here are Nobel Prize winners,
but we have to stop
throwing shit at each other.
We're in a critical situation.
- No.
In a critical situation we'll be
if the Profesor doesn't call in six hours.
And then we would activate the Chernobyl plan.
- The Profesor didn't say anything about that.
What is the Chernobyl plan?
- If all goes well, you'll never know.
So, please, let's have a little patience.
All right?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to empty my mind.
- Salva, do you think I should drop the case?
I don't know, say I'm not well,
take a medical leave,
to give up.
Well, it's a very intimate question.
That's why I make it for you.
We slept together and you know my mother.
I mean, it's a question that only you can answer.
Only you know how you feel.
Well, I feel like all this is too big for me.
If they had put someone else in my place...
No, not that, Raquel, no.
If you're in charge
of such a crisis is
because no one better than you
knows how to manage it.
I don't know.
Still in the tent, talking to that guy,
The Profesor, with whom I do business,
I feel useful there.
And I'm confronted with questions like:
"What are you wearing?"
"What are you wearing?
Yes, it is.
But, I don't know, here, in the open field,
I feel he's stronger than me.
I can't deal with him.
I don't know. Look at all those people working.
30 guys from the CSI and I don't even know
which way to go.
I feel lost.
Ay... Sorry, Salva. You're getting late,
aren't you?
No, no, not at all.
- Inspector Murillo,
the inspector Vicuña, of the CSI,
is entering the perimeter.
- Will you come with me?
Oh, sure.
- Hello, Raquel. Thank you for calling me.
That was a very professional gesture on your part.
How's Ángel?
- He's still in a coma.
There is nothing new.
This is Salva, a friend.
Well, my current partner.
Salva, Inspector Alberto Vicuña.
Salvador...
Martín. Salvador Martín.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
I'm glad you're with Raquel.
I'm not bothering you.
I get inside and it's like I'm not there,
but you have to tell me the background.
What's that?
460 000 euros.
A little pinch, in case we get busted.
To start from scratch you and me when
we get out of prison.
I'm gonna hide it here, behind our tile.
I'm gonna make a hole with a radial.
and I'm going to reseal it.
In a few years we come
and we bought a little flat in La Manga.
That's if the euro still exists, isn't it?
Fuck, it's true.
You listen to me.
No, don't start that shit again that
you want to leave me.
Wait till we get arrested and you leave me
with a letter or something.
You listen to me.
Things are gonna get really ugly.
and I'm not one to stand still.
I'm more of a shooter.
I know.
But you're not.
I need to ask you a favor.
When the action starts,
you have to turn yourself in.
You get a white flag and turn yourself in.
That'll serve as a mitigating factor
when things get complicated.
When things get complicated,
I'll be with you.
When the action starts,
I'll be with you in an open grave.
And I'll tell you something else:
I only take out the white flag
when Madrid wins.
Okay.
So, what, we fuck a little?
Okay, now's not the time.
Action then?
Action.
Hey, come on.
- Did you know about that syndrome?
- Stockholm syndrome?
Yes, I had heard something.
- I didn't make her do anything, Dad, I swear.
I brought her food and
she hugged me around the neck,
she was looking for my mouth and
you don't know how, she wouldn't let go.
That it was real, that I swear we really kissed.
I started dancing in front of her and everything.
- Look at her.
When have you ever had a girlfriend like that?
- Well, La Vane.
- La Vane?
- La Vane was beautiful.
- La Vane wasn't pretty, she wasn't smart
and she wasn't good.
Because he was from your world and you had
your little things in common.
- What's my world supposed to be?
It's a shitty world, isn't it?
- Take a good look at her. Look at her!
First, she's an opposition official,
has studied and studied a lot;
Second, her last boyfriend was the CEO
of the factory and, third, she's very pretty
and elegant.
That woman is from another league, son.
He's from the Champions League and we're more about
whether we go down or not.
- That's enough. That's enough.
I heard about that!
That I'm a piece of shit, that I
have to think like a piece of shit.
and I have to dream like shit.
I heard about it.
Freeze!
He said freeze, damn it!
Hands on your head!
Hey, hey, hey!
May I ask what's going on?
It happens that this is very rare
and no one's calling here.
And if they're gonna shoot us and
we're gonna fuck off,
unless we find out on TV.
It's all right. Mónica Gaztambide,
it's your turn to heal the wound
In the first recognition,
we found the fingerprints of eight people.
There's DNA in cigarette butts, chewing gum,
chopsticks, even a yogurt.
More than 100 classified tests and
we have a lot more.
Looks like they also wrote the plan on the board.
We're trying to rebuild it.
- Have they left the plan written down?
- Yeah. Well, that's the question,
if this is a contaminated scene.
or if he responds to a lack of professionalism
for destroying evidence.
- They're inside the Fábrica Nacional,
I don't think they lack professionalism
or intelligence.
None of this is worth a shit.
Ángel went further than you with the prints he found.
- What prints?
- He didn't say anything to you?
He got a personal item, a spoon.
That's where we isolated the same
fingerprints we found in the zeta
Ángel hit on someone in the band or at least
he was very close.
If there's anything useful here,
I know where it might be. Come.
Everything they really wanted to erase
they must have burned it in there.
It's the safest way to destroy something
and that's what we'd all do.
- But there are only ashes there, and few of them.
- And those ashes before were firewood, charcoal,
but also documents, photos,
a paper that when burned
loses most of its matter.
Fire creates scrolls of hot air
that elevate those paper
particles through the chimney flue.
Sometimes these particles
stick to the rough brick
from the wall.
If there's anything worthwhile, it's in there.
Let us work.
Gandía, bring the glasses and the infrared camera.
Come on, girl, I'm in a hurry. Come on.
Let's get to work.
Turn around.
You're serious, aren't you?
No.
Can you stop?
I will spill the Betadine.
Now, now, the Betadine.
Mónica, I'm telling you seriously.
What's the matter, our 60 hours
of love are over?
You happen to be a hostage and
I've kidnapped you,
so when this is over and
we get out of here, we'll see.
What? What's going on?
Come on.
Something happened and I didn't find out?
Maybe you don't realize why you're here
against your will, Mónica,
but you have a syndrome.
What? What syndrome?
Stockholm.
That you fall in love with the son of a bitch
who's holding you hostage.
Since you're crazy about it, you treat
me like I'm your boyfriend.
It's a psychiatric thing,
it's treated by doctors.
Listen to me.
What if I tell you it's the biggest
nonsense I've ever heard in my life?
What are you gonna tell me
if you're with the syndrome?
No, listen to me.
What if we'd crossed the street?
And if I'd asked you for change at a slot bar,
what would you have thought of me?
Would you have noticed more than two seconds?
Really, tell me. Don't you?
Well, that's it.
You go on your way,
I follow mine
and forward.
Wait.
Do you feel anything?
Anything for me?
I don't have any syndrome, Mónica.
Tell me, do you feel anything?
Yeah, but mine's real,
it's not from Stockholm.
And yours, I can't make it
go away from your head.
I can't.
I can't do that to you.
What are you thinking, green eyes?
I look at you and I want to know
everything about you,
every day you've lived,
every smile, every tear,
every moment of happiness.
You're a charming mystery to me, Ariadna.
For example, let's see, the first kiss.
Do you remember who gave it to you?
What was his name?
- Raúl.
- Raúl had to really feel like a lucky man.
and, like Neil Armstrong, walking on the moon.
First times are special,
unique
but the last few times are incomparable,
are priceless.
What happens is that people don't usually
know what they are.
You see, I've got six months to live.
or four,
maybe even less,
and one of the few things I really
care about right now,
You know what that is?
To know that I'm going to live here,
in here,
forever and ever,
inside this beautiful little head.
Berlín, something serious has happened.
Excuse me, the agents who were going to Madrid?
At the moment it looks like no one's leaving.
Wow. Well, then I'll take the road.
May I come in and say goodbye to the inspector?
Come with me.
Are you sure you want to do that?
You should take it all with you.
Since tomorrow they are no longer memories,
they are simply
evidence against someone who's on a
search and seizure..
Nostalgia is seductive,
it's hard for us to get rid of the memories
because we think the memories
are really those happy moments, but...
But they're not.
And what we're going to do tomorrow requires us
to think about the present.
Not in the past.
That was your father.
And that's all that matters.
And we're gonna do it for him.
"So far more than 50 troops have moved here
among which is the inspecting officer in charge,
the head of the operational unit GEOS
and officers of the CSI,
who continue to work on the house that,
according to nearby sources,
could be the place where the muggers organized
the assault..."
The Profesor has been arrested.
If he's being interrogated at the
door of the house in Toledo.
"The judge has decreed the secret of summary.
CSI could have found evidence
that confirm the presence in that
house of at least three..."
Fucking hell.
Shit!
They've cut off the terrestrial digital signal.
Fucking hell.
They don't want us to find out.
And if they don't want us to find out,
it's because they're coming in.
We can stand idly by for five hours
or start the fucking Chernobyl plan,
that sounds better to me every time.
The Chernobyl plan is for desperate situations.
And I don't know if this is the situation
more desperate than we can bear.
Is it?
Warning, it's a plan in which you'd lose
all your loot.
I personally don't have any desire
to quit, do you?
Are you now going to give up everything
you've fought for
so harshly, Tokio?
Guys, they've got the Profesor.
There's not gonna be a tunnel in the hangar,
cause the damn GEOS are gonna be waiting for us.
We're in a fucking mousetrap.
In five hours, the Profesor will call,
I still believe in him.
In fact, I'm not passionate about democracy,
but I'm getting a crazy urge to vote.
Who still believes in the Profesor?
Helsinki?
- I still believe in the Profesor.
- Río.
- I believe in what I see.
And what I see is that we can no
longer count on the Profesor.
So I'm with Tokio.
- Moscú?
- I came in accepting a few rules.
The rules haven't been broken.
I still trust the Profesor.
- Denver?
- I vote to get out of here, now.
Me being a multimillionaire
it kind of gets a little big.
- Perfect, Denver, three, three.
Nairobi, it's up to you.
The tiebreak.
- I have a very good reason to be with the Profesor,
and if he doesn't jump to pieces,
I'm gonna believe in him to the end.
I'm with Berlín.
Raquel.
Forgive me, I don't want to bother you,
but it's just...
Now I'm getting a little late...
I'm taking this to Canillas.
I was just going to Madrid,
I was going to catch the bus.
If you want, I'll bring him in.
- What?
Well, I could use it.
Let's go.
The truth is, I've seen Raquel very well,
and that's good.
You know, in a separation, until the
two of them remake,
well it's complicated.
I'm glad too, the truth is that Raquel
is an extraordinary woman.
Yes, yes, of course.
I want what's best for her.
If she's okay, the girl's okay,
we're all okay.
Are you hot? Shall I put the air in?
No, no, the temperature's fine.
It's me, I'm a little...
A little stirred up.
You haven't had the coffee from the caterer,
that shit should be banned.
Well, yes, I made that mistake,
because I had three cups
and besides, I have a problem...
A colon problem, it's nothing serious,
but I have a bacterium that...
Well, which forces me to evacuate
more regularly than usual.
It's kind of embarrassing,
but I didn't want to poop at the
crime scene either.
Do you want me to stop?
Well, if you don't mind,
I'd really appreciate it.
No problem, the first gas station stopped.
Well, I think the best thing for both of us
would be to stop as soon as possible.
Look, right here.
Right there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure, no problem.
Thank you.
Salva!
Salva.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yeah, yeah, much better.
Let's see what people are like.
Alberto, anytime, huh?
Suárez, come here a minute.
Pilar.
Listen, I want you to analyze Ángel's car.
- We've already done it, it's procedure.
- So? Did you find anything anomalous?
- He had the brake fluid conduit plugged,
but it doesn't mean anything.
- What do you mean, no?
He could have been manipulated, couldn't he?
- It could, but it's usually not.
Sealing of ducts, breakage of parts...
That's what happens when you do two
overturns at 170 km/h.
I'm sorry.
- Wait, wait.
Did he tell you where he got the spoon
that he sent you to analyze?
- No, no.
I have to keep working.
Suárez, when did Ángel come to Toledo?
Yesterday, right?
- Yesterday, yes, but...
- It's possible he took her from here.
To get to this house before we did.
Or... I don't know, maybe he took it
from the village bar
or the pharmacy.
Maybe he suspected someone...
- Raquel, Raquel, calm down.
That way you won't solve anything,
only Ángel knows where it came from.
- Ángel and the guy who helps them from the outside.
The same guy who was listening to us through the mic.
The same guy who tried to kill Ángel
manipulating your car's brakes.
- They just told you that's not proven.
- Ángel followed a lead and someone tried to kill him.
And he's gonna do it again if he comes out of the coma.
- What are you up to?
- This time we'll set him up.
"Don't judge him.
Helsinki did what it had to do,
what soldiers do in war,
what we do with animals when we don't
want them to suffer;
without hatred, as an act of humanity.
And I did what I had to do, too.
Not out of hatred,
as an act of humanity.
After all,
what's more human than trying to survive?"
I was just thinking about what you said earlier,
that you want what's best for Raquel.
What?
Well, I don't think that's true.
If it were true,
you wouldn't be fucking his sister.
Look, that's none of your business.
I'm sorry, but I am interested.
When I heard about your story, I thought:
"This guy's got to be really in love
to get into a mess like this."
Falling in love or fucking your wife's sister,
but when I found out that you were flirting
With your daughter's teacher...
Your daughter's teacher.
I thought, "This is one of these guys
that shares intelligence with the
cock and the muscles,
a perturbed man who has to disguise
himself in society."
The thing that pisses me off the most is
that it's Raquel who ended up going to the psychiatrist
when it should have been you.
What are you going to the psychiatrist for?
You have no idea what a piece of crap you are.
You bastard.
Bastard? Me?
You garbage
Get out of the car.
Alberto, if I get out of the car,
I'm going to give you a punch that you're
not even going to stand on.
Get the fuck out of the car.
Do you know what this is?
My meds.
Days of life.
It seems unbelievable that such a
valuable thing
is stored inside something so fragile,
right?
It didn't do you any good to lose the election,
Tokio.
You should do a little more personal work.
I'm not going to stand still.
while they go in and kill me for a shitty vote.
You stay if you want,
but you don't decide about us.
Is that it? You can go in peace.
No problem, I'll bring you present
in my prayers.
I've lived with you really beautiful days.
- Tokio, please, come on,
they'll come and get us.
Berlín, tell us about the Chernobyl plan
or I'll blow up your whole arsenal.
No, I'm not.
Are you really going to torture me
by breaking little glass jars?
Oh, Tokio, Tokio.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
So mature for some things and so young for others.
You should consider doing something more forceful;
severing a limb, for example.
Of course, I'm so high on opiates
and I may not know anything about it.
Denver, give me the gun.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Yes, it is.
Tell us what the Chernobyl plan is.
You don't have what it takes.
You don't.
Three, two,
one.
What? What do you have to tell me now?
You'll find out.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
There goes the second one.
Son of a bitch.
Oh! Oh!
The fifth.
What the fuck are you doing?
- We're playing Russian roulette, Nairobi!
Come back later!
- Shit, Tokio!
Tokio, you're losing it.
What the fuck are you doing?
You want us all to go fuck ourselves
because of you?
You're gonna fuck up the plan.
- That's clear.
All by yourself.
Me?.
I'm fucking up the plan?
It's just that you can't stop and
think for a second for once
fucking brainless.
I'm a brainless?
and the plan to go find
your son is bullshit.
What the fuck are you saying?
When was the last time he saw you?
Were you three years old?
He doesn't have a bloody memory of you.
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up.
He won't recognize you
because he already has a mother and a father,
that to him they are the real thing.
You don't know shit.
What?
All I know is that you were the aunt
who carried him in the gut
and left him to go get some fucking pills.
Do you know what's going on?
I'm not listening very well.
No?
Why don't you come a little closer
to the door or why don't you open the door
and you say this to my face, friend?
What I'm telling you is that you missed
the opportunity
of being a mother, face it.
Knock it off!
- Hey, Tokio,
Maybe all this it's getting a little out of,
Isn't it?
You didn't want to go to the open grave with me?
Well, welcome to the slide.
Son, listen to me.
Get out of there immediately.
You're getting yourself into a very big problem.
- In a very big problem?
What difference does it make?
It's all gone to shit.
- Let's see, forget that Stockholm,
we're rushing, there's no one
here who's a doctor,
but please don't fuck it up.
- Are we going out or what?
No, I'm not.
Maybe we're just in time to...
No!
We've already voted.
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
That's enough.
Here we go. If it is true
my time has come, shoot.
Come on, Tokio, I'm terminally ill.
No one you're going
to cut off dreams and worries,
but if you're playing at scaring him,
think of something.
When you bust my head, you're gonna be scared.
I'm the only one here who knows the plan.
You won't fucking know how to get
out of this mousetrap!
It is you who are playing Russian roulette.
Do it!
Alberto, forgive me, I've let myself
be carried away by passion.
I apologize... Alberto
You're under arrest for assault on authority.
Don't even move.
Hold it right there.
Romero, I have a detainee.
Attacking authority.
Take his prints and lock him up.
Sit down here. I'll be right back.
Rest in peace.
Helsinki. Anytime.
Rest in peace, Oslo.
The quietest guy in the band and the one
with the worst luck.
Then the next one was me.
I earned it.
Berlín took advantage
of my teammates' break time
to give me what I deserve.
By all means irreversible.
You look like a birthday present.
All you need is the ribbon.
What are you gonna do to me?
You should dose your energy.
You're not gonna kill me?
No... I'm not going to kill you.
Nor am I going to torture you.
Son of a bitch. I hate you.
Let me ask you something.
because this has to be the end
of something, right?
Couldn't it be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship?
No!
"And that's how it all started.
All that would be the end of the robbery,
of the days of confinement,
of my love with Río.
Everyone's dreams.
Of my freedom.
Sergio.
Shall I tell you I've got a date and you
don't have time to hit on him?
- The one who knocked me unconscious
is fucking Chuck Norris with glasses.
Fucking hell.
Man, Mr. Prieto.
Tokio lost its head, but I had to deliver it.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm sick of hearing this guy complain.
- If you're so bad, why don't you do something?
This is patriarchy.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means I'm in charge here.
It's a lie. It's a lie!
Isn't that right?
About Andrés.
You want to know how it all started?
Who's the profesor?
What you've done is high treason.
- What are you going to do?
- Execute you.
Don't move!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Reduce it.
- Tokio!