I have made the decision to enter.
Sub-inspector Rubio will accompany
the two surgeons and enter
as a nurse.
One of the restrooms is
an undercover cop.
You know what to do.
Perfectly, let's do it.
Welcome.
Thank you.
We know that those inside
were there before.
I want you to check the
camera footage.
Release channel 8 for
the hostage crisis.
No one should broadcast
on channel 8.
- I have breached the first
rule of the plan.
I killed a hostage.
Who was she? Mónica Gaztambide.
You're gonna have to punish me.
Come on, let's see that wound.
Let's get her out now.
- What are you doing?
- A bullet wound.
- Here, let me do it.
Bring, throw here.
Throw, throw well.
It's the recording of the
day Cortés and Oliveira
visited the museum.
- Get as close as you can.
There, stop it. Enlarge.
They are the keys of a car.
A 92 Ibiza.
Search scrapyards, car cemeteries
and the like.
Tell me what, at least,
if they didn't make the junk car,
wiped the fingerprints.
I didn't do this.
Hey!
You!
I got in because my car
is here and...
I count five and let go of dog.
Do you understand?
If you want to negotiate with me,
release eight hostages.
I'll propose something to you.
I will give you Alison Parker
and no one else.
This is a matter of state.
I will take responsibility.
- Alison Parker.
Yes, it is.
Tokio.
"He ordered me to filter
the conversation."
You'd rather save Alison Parker's
life than eight?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Hey! Hey!
See who that is and what
he's doing here.
- Stop, police! What are you doing here?
Circle.
It was him!
"That Sunday, Raquel Murillo
was just seconds away from
seeing the Profesor.
That image was one of the ones
missing to complete the puzzle.
of the kidnappers and enter the final phase.
I already had Río's.
Mine.
And I was about to have Berlín.
The Profesor had foreseen that
Raquel would get these photos.
Like a deck of cards that was
slowly coming loose.
to entertain himself by playing cards.
His image was the only one
I should ever find.
But it was no longer so
anonymous or unknown.
His image was going to start drawing.
as a hologram in police protocols.
The loose end had put him at great risk.
And now, if the inspector played
her cards right.
and got the Profesor's face,
the game would be over.
Checkmate would be irreversible.
"Alison Parker.
Would you rather save Alison Parker's
life than eight?
Yeah, I'm sure.
- That's cold, you didn't hesitate.
When one is able to make such
a decision without hesitation,
one is left speechless.
That the lives of eight Spanish boys
is worth less than an English
girl's cry to heaven.
- Alison Parker is Spanish,
has dual nationality.
- Bearing in mind that the main
thing is the hostages,
we must reflect on the role of
Inspector Murillo.
I don't know if he's up to a
negotiation of this caliber.
- He has an extensive career
within the police force.
Psychologist, criminologist.
What more do you want?
- Curriculum is surplus to requirements.
The problem is that right now,
Inspector Raquel Murillo
has just filed a complaint of ill-treatment."
- Paula!
"You have to see how mentally
affected she is.
Probably medicated, unstable..."
- He just spoke to his father.
Paula, honey, why don't you tell Mommy
What did your daddy tell you?
Let's go.
- Do I want to live with him and his aunt?
- And what did you say to him, darling?
- That's right.
- Daughter, but you know that if
you're going to live with Dad,
we're gonna see a lot less of each other.
- Same as now. You are never home.
- Look, Paula.
Mom doesn't want you to live
with Dad because...
Because Dad's no good and he's done me
a lot of harm. Understand?
- Dad is good.
- No, daughter, Dad is no good.
- It's not true, Dad told me.
- He told you it's a lie.
You're talking nonsense out there.
- I want to live with the aunt.
- But, darling...
Your aunt Marta is a knucklehead.
It's wrong for me to tell you because
I'm his mother too.
But he's got the brains of a rag,
like your rabbit Eugenio.
- Mama.
Don't turn her against her aunt.
- It's all right.
- Look, honey, you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna go get a burger.
You want some?
- With ketchup?
- With ketchup and potatoes.
And when I finish this job,
we are going to the Canary Islands.
To the beach, girl's plan.
What do you think?
- Well, if it's a girl's plan, I'm in.
- Come on, let's go.
- And also chocolate ice cream.
- Chocolate ice cream, okay.
"Questions about this heist that keeps us
in suspense are piling up.
Who are the kidnappers?
Were you planning to stay inside?
Do they want money or is it a protest
against the financial system?
How long can they hold out
without the police deciding to come in?"
Why won't the police come in?
Because we're going to lock the door inside.
How to itch.
They're not coming in.
because no one in Spain
is going to want me to come in.
- What's the matter, you're going to
have a referendum?
Cri, cri.
Okay. Let's see.
Year 2011.
A group of kids
begins to squat the Puerta del Sol,
the most emblematic square.
More than 20 000 people gather there.
- The 15-M, right?
That's it.
If they get to tell any of us
that 20 000 people were going to camp
in Sol for a month without
the police entering,
we would never have believed it.
We would have said it's impossible.
- But it was.
And the police didn't come in.
Why is that?
Because all of Spain was with those kids.
But those kids wore tents.
and we carry guns.
A little different.
- That's true.
- Politics is politics.
Money is money.
Sangría is sangría.
No, no, in Serbia, that's why police come in.
Yibeli, my friends.
- Don't do that!
- What a filth!
We're gonna be the resilient ones
trapped in that mousetrap.
in the same way they were the Sun's resistors.
And resistance always falls well.
And if that doesn't work...
You have your audience, don't you?
No, sorry, go on, go on.
Thank you.
If that doesn't work,
the police will know we have assault weapons, explosives.
No elite unit is going to know how to differentiate
hostages of robbers.
No Minister of the Interior
is going to give the order to enter, none.
Why is that?
Because there are minors.
Choosing Alison Parker's life
over eight was her decision.
He told me that intelligence
would assume the consequences.
Get out there and tell the press it was you.
and his friends at CNI.
- Intelligence cannot make such statements.
But don't worry.
The Presidency is aware and has
the support of the government.
- It is brought to me
by the government's support.
I care what my daughter and my mother believe.
Not what the president thinks.
- Inspector, those people never thought of
letting Alison Parker go.
or the eight minors.
It was a trap.
But if you'll allow me,
I'll tell you something.
When it's all over,
no one will remember this.
It is...
It's like the Spanish national team.
It doesn't matter how the World Cup starts.
If it finally achieves a happy ending,
will be the heroine of the country.
But if you leave a rosary of corpses,
we'll all be fucked.
I am very sorry for my mistakes.
And I am at your entire disposal.
But if you want me to go...
- Suárez, I want everyone up and running.
I want the evidence from
the Seat Ibiza scientist now.
And the underground unit report.
What about it?
And above all, Mr. Prieto,
I want intelligence to tell me how the muggers
are going to get out.
I have a question, Profesor.
How are we gonna get out of there?
Through a tunnel.
- Is that the master plan?
The police get that in two minutes.
- Yes, I do.
Look.
This is the National Mint.
view from above.
Just come in,
you're gonna put the hostages to bite right here.
In the basement of boilers.
It's exactly 13 meters from the sewer.
At 13 meters? Uh-huh.
At that distance, we'd be detected
by any georadar.
Isn't it?
True.
A georadar has a range of about 15 meters.
And if not, they'll do it with a seismograph
capturing the vibration.
That's why they're gonna think we're
gonna elope around here.
But we're not going that way, are we?
No.
We'll go out through another tunnel.
A tunnel...
that they won't be able to see.
Because it's 26 meters
from any other conduit.
of sanitation and, above all,
because it is already done.
Just take it from vault number three.
¿Who made that tunnel?
I had it built five years ago.
Once you enter the tunnel from the factory,
you will find 486 meters...
already dug up to...
a hangar...
which I have already planned.
No.
I take off my hat.
- And the panties.
- But all cameras...
also have armored floor.
That's right.
There's a first layer of steel
and a second, reinforced concrete.
Besides, there can't be any air hammer in there.
It must be done by hand, thermal and radial lance.
How many meters?
16 centimeters of steel.
80 centimetres of reinforced concrete.
Finally, land.
Six meters and 70, in total.
- Fuck.
- Good hole.
- And how long does it take
you to make this hole?
- 10, 12 days.
- The time we'll be inside.
A few...
200 million euros printed per day.
2400 million.
- Yes, sir!
- Come on! Profesor!
Scientific confirms the presence
of ammonia and alcohol
in dashboard, upholstery, glass.
Come on, in the whole car.
The report reveals that those
products were applied
a few minutes before we arrived.
Which suggests that someone related to the gang
was there at about the same time as us.
What about the beggar?
No trace.
We've checked the traffic cams
and nearby shops, but nothing.
There is good news, though.
They've managed to isolate
a fingerprint on the button.
The owner has a record.
They are sending us the file.
- Attention, listen to me, all of you.
I need you to step out of the tent
for a few minutes.
All except the sub-inspector Rubio.
- It's gonna be a few minutes,
fellas, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Least of all the CNI.
Do you think it was a coincidence that this guy,
the beggar, get to the junkyard before we do?
No, it wasn't by chance.
- There is a mole among us.
- And what are we going to do?
- Find him.
The police file has arrived.
Take it easy.
It's all right.
You rest.
Freeze.
Take it easy.
Joke.
Joke. 310.
It's all right.
Joke.
- Ah!
- I'll be right back.
It's all right.
No infection. All right.
All right, all right.
37,6.
No problem.
40, problem.
37.6, no problem.
I, in war, take care of many men.
Man look after man.
No problem.
It's all right.
Mónica.
Mónica, uh.
How's it going?
It's better.
What are you doing here?
It's my hour of sleep, but I wanted to know how you were.
It's hot in here.
Yeah. Ugh!
Looks like the oxygen's missing.
Ugh!
You can rest here, I don't care.
Sitting on a racket is enough.
All right.
Yes, yes.
Andrés de Fonollosa.
Currently in search and seizure.
Jewelry stores, vans, auction houses.
White glove robberies.
You do not have exit visas
in your e-passport.
- He's probably got a fake one.
- No family or friends
are known to him either.
The usual confidants don't know who he is.
There is no address,
no census or registration.
All I can think of is
talking to your cellmate.
They shared seven months in Soto del Real.
- OK.
Order the paperwork to be brought to the tent.
- Wait, that's not all.
The most important thing is forensic psychiatry.
Shall I read you?
We're looking at a self-centered narcissist.
with delusions of grandeur.
I have gathered you here to tell you
a little how things are going.
And to silence rumors.
- Shows an absolute lack of empathy.
- I know it floats in the atmosphere
that Miss Mónica Gaztambide
is dead and that's not good.
Rumors generate...
uncertainty,
anxiety.
That's why I want to silence this.
Indeed, Mónica, his companion, has been executed.
- An eccentric with
tendencies to megalomania
which prevents him from
distinguishing evil from good.
- But I also love them
to share other news.
Good news.
Because the truth...
is that this heist...
it's going downwind.
It goes like a shot.
- He has a great sense of honor.
and a pathological need
to make a good impression.
Especially among strangers.
- That's why I want...
thank you, I have to thank you
to all those who are p
utting forth their efforts
and collaboration. Especially one person.
Mr. Torres.
Paco.
Paquito.
- Don Francisco Torres.
This gentleman has been
printing banknotes for 27 years.
And today, he broke his own record.
After 40 hours, you have printed...
Say how much you printed.
- 311 million euros.
- Say it loudly, proudly, let everyone know.
- 311 million.
- 311 million euros!
- EUR 311 million,
pimpam, pimpam.
All by himself!
- Well, with the help of my classmates.
- On top of that, he's humble.
Thank you, Mr. Torres, thank you.
Thank you all very much.
Mr. Torres, do you know what you are?
You're the kidnapped fuck of the month.
- That's right, let's give him the
applause he deserves...
Mr. Torres!
Let's go!
Come on, let him notice
all the love we have for him!
- You're a monster.
- Let love be noticed.
- Thank you!
- Joke.
But like good news never comes alone,
I would like us to receive...
as he deserves,
that we give him an unforgettable ovation...
Don Arturo.
The director general, who has finally
come out of danger!
Joke.
Thank you, Paco.
- May I speak to you privately, please?
I want you to leak everything about this
guy to the press, everything.
- What for?
- For what?
- Yes.
- That guy's doing a hell of a show.
Like in a movie.
Let's see what Spain thinks now
when he sees that
an eccentric is holding back
a lot of teenagers.
- Raquel.
I don't think the public will be won over.
saying the boss of the
kidnappers is an eccentric.
This country loves eccentrics.
You'll need something else.
Trafficking in women.
An almost unresolved one of pimping.
Something the citizenry won't forgive.
Don't do it.
Raquel, don't do it, don't fall so low,
don't do that.
Filter it. Pimp.
With a case open for trafficking in women
from the east.
Some of them, minors.
Released for collaborating with the police.
- Above, a snitch.
I like your style.
I'm going to the agency to
prepare everything.
- Listen to me, Raquel.
No, listen to me, Raquel.
You have it clear. Let's slander a person.
- To defame a person?
- Yes.
- Look, Ángel, I'm in the TV talk shows,
in the international press as the
biggest son of a bitch.
And, coincidentally, my ex-husband has taken
advantage of this moment
to ask my daughter if she wants to live with him.
Do you know what that means?
That he's going to take
custody of my daughter.
He's going to go to a judge to tell him:
"Your Honor, that son of a bitch
can't raise my daughter.
And besides, the girl
wants to live with me.
- A judge will not give you custody
to a guy who mistreated you.
- If my mother doesn't believe me.
Do you think a judge will believe me?
- I believe you, Raquel.
I believe you.
I can testify.
- Testify?
- Yes.
- What are you going to testify?
You didn't see anything.
- What the hell!
Aren't we going to defame Fonollosa?
Here all God is defamed.
Fuck! Your husband, the first.
That's it, I say I saw your cardinals.
Below the miniskirt, though.
- If I don't wear a miniskirt ever.
- It doesn't matter, dammit.
And, by the way, I declare the night
we spent in the mountains.
It wasn't in Cercedilla, it was in Miraflores.
- Excuse me, Inspector.
Can we?
- What's going on?
- We have come from the scrap yard.
We have interrogated the Russian.
Nikolai Dimitrevich, the watchman.
A man asked for a car an hour
before you arrived.
He spoke to him in Russian.
According to the subject's description,
could be the same person who talked to Almansa.
The beggar.
- Bring that Russian.
Have him check the Eastern criminal files.
And have him do the robot portrait.
- I want all the chips
of all the Russians he's ever questioned,
arrested or charged.
There is a software aid to make a portrait rob
"The Profesor's image was so anonymous
as a puzzle of 1000 pieces.
But a witness was going to put all
those pieces together.
And Raquel, who had never believed
in robot portraits,
was going to have the key
to the whole operation.
Fucking hell.
Jessica.
Elena.
Denise.
Paula.
Elisabeth.
Aurora.
And Alison.
I'm sorry I tied you so tight.
But you also pointed a rifle at my head.
What did you want me to do?
For the ambassador's daughter,
you're a bit of a rebel.
- Don't believe it, it's the second madness
I've done in my life.
- Oh, yeah, and what's the first one?
- Secretly signing up for dance.
- Fucking crazy!
You start with the dance and end up
in something nasty,
like the violin.
And then, chunda, chunda.
- My father has chosen everything in my life.
The school, the race...
To the house where I'm going
to graduate school.
Alison, this cutlery is fishing.
Alison, not that glass.
Alison, you're going into chess.
And so on.
- Sure.
And to touch his balls, you sign up for ballet.
- I got into dance because my father hates dance.
And volleyball was on Saturdays.
And on Saturdays I can't do anything without him knowing.
- All right.
Take the toilet bag and we'll go up in single file.
Boo.
What were you talking about?
You're welcome.
Something from Oxford.
I heard you.
No, my life.
That my father is a bossy man.
Are you going to invite him to the embassy?
Who?
To Río.
No.
You don't like my boyfriend?
I love his smile.
Don't you?
No, I don't.
If I've seen you look at him,
why are you lying to me?
Ouch!
Isn't Río a monkey?
Yeah, well.
See how you like it?
It's all right, admit it.
Yes, I do.
Yes, he's with me.
But I'm not some rabid bitch.
that bites when she feels insecure.
If you like to play,
we'll all have to play.
Pull.
How long have you been in there?
Look...
I'm very worried about my student Silvia.
Because she's a girl...
particularly fragile.
And I think she'd feel a lot more protected
with the group, with their companions.
- What kind of classes
do you teach at the school?
- Me? Uh...
- Yes.
- Well...
Philosophy, ethics.
- Philosophy?
- Yes.
- That's good.
- History of religions.
And...
Well, also some workshops.
- Workshops of what?
- Environment, sex education.
- What an important job.
And since you're an expert,
maybe you can help me solve a problem
I have with this sexuality thing.
Actually, I'd like to explain a theory to you.
May I?
- Yes, of course.
Hello.
- I came up with the jokes.
- The jokes.
You know that for a joke to work,
it has to have a part of truth...
and another of pain.
- Is that so? Well, I didn't...
I didn't know.
That's funny.
- Yes, it is.
That's right.
Do you know the one with the headache?
- No, no, no, no.
- A husband comes home.
"Honey,
I brought you an aspirin."
And the woman says,
"But I don't have a headache."
Then let's fuck.
Have you noticed
of the amount of jokes that portray the male
bent on bending the female
to get sex?
And the woman, always obliged,
as if she didn't like it.
What do you think is true about all this?
Don't you have the same appetites, profesor?
- I understand you do.
Perhaps not with the same frequency.
- Could be.
- But tell me, Silvia, can you take her...?
- Oh, of course, Silvia.
Stand up for a moment, please.
Come with me.
Come on.
Look, there's Silvia.
- Mmmm!
- See how quiet?
Hello!
Hello.
Say hello, profesor.
I'm sure the little girl is
looking forward to it.
- What is it, Nairobi?
- You're on TV.
- Oslo.
It's been a pleasure, Profesor.
Come back when you want,
we'll talk about ethics.
Take her away.
- Let's go.
Three sexual assaults,
six narcotic poisonings,
exhibitionism.
In total, 38 years in prison
and there's still a trial pending.
- Why did you bring me here?
- He shared a cell with that man.
Do you remember who you were related to?
- With no one.
- Well, he'll have a family.
Bride.
Couple.
- I don't know.
- Friends.
- He didn't mention.
- Are you telling me that in seven months,
you didn't mention anyone?
Is something wrong?
- What if something happens.
- Did he tell you about his house?
- No, I don't.
- From his neighbourhood, a village.
Somewhere I'd plan to go back.
- I don't know, he didn't say anything.
- I don't think you understand
very well how this works.
I need you to give me something.
Do you understand?
A thread to pull.
Please think.
- There is one thing.
- What's that?
- I'm not just going to say it like that.
I've been in jail for four years.
I need something in return.
- Sure.
- Don't touch my balls.
- Ángel.
- This is not a movie.
You talk and then, we'll see,
we come to an agreement.
You sing and I'll give you a sugar.
Did you hear me?
- Ángel!
Take it easy.
Look.
I'm going to sign a paper requesting
to the board of Soto the third degree.
But on two conditions.
The first is that you give us the
information now.
If the information is good,
I will give you the second condition.
You have my word that I will get you
the third grade.
- He was injecting a drug every day.
- I have your infirmary report here.
It says nothing about any disease.
- Yeah, I know.
It was something he was wearing in secret.
Something degenerative.
- Do you remember the
name of the medication?
- Retroxil.
- How did you get it?
- I don't know if you know how easy it is
to put anything in jail.
Through the rectal cavity.
And now, tell me what the second condition is.
- That you voluntarily submit
to a chemical castration treatment.
As soon as you ask, I'll sign the third degree.
No?
- No.
- Suárez, take him away.
- Come on.
- He gave me his word.
Son of a bitch!
- Find out what the Retroxil is for.
Track any anomalous shopping patterns
in the last six months.
If that guy injects that every day,
has had to come up with a good arsenal.
All by yourself.
We can't trust anyone before we find the mole.
- All right, all right.
- I brought you the Russian, Inspector.
- Nikolai.
I sent for him.
to recognize this morning's man,
that of the scrap yard.
Do you think he'll recognize your face?
Can you do a robot portrait?
- Perfectly.
- Ángel.
Tell the others they can come in.
I think this nose.
- Almansa.
How's the robot portrait going?
- Well, he and I agree on the traits.
Soon we'll have his face.
- All right.
"Those words threw the Profesor
to do something he'd never imagined before.
Find the police to save your skin.
Fuck, what a bitch.
Is it still like this?
Can I help you?
The sooner we finish, the sooner we get out,
right?
Are you tired of being here already?
You see.
If this bores anyone.
You're bored with 67 hostages,
firing bursts with your M-16.
and with the police on the door.
Is that it?
Is that why you threw yourself
at that little lamb's neck?
You've started snoring at her,
scared to death.
What the hell was that for?
To provoke you.
Make very quiet poop...
What now?
Is Río boring you already?
Why do you say that?
Because you're that kind of person.
Is that so?
What kind of person?
The kind you don't want for your child.
Remember in Toledo, the day of the paella?
It was St. John's night.
You escaped to the verbena.
Yes, it is.
Whoa!
What's going on?
What is it? What?
What?
Did you know there are over 2,000
billion stars?
What's the matter, you've counted them? Of course.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Here, I need a little party.
And I know, Tokio,
that in your room you have something like this.
Something. From lost, to the river.
Oh, Río!
Río, how drunk I was.
Very drunk.
Can I have a puff?
Hey.
Why did you tell me about the stars before?
I don't know, man, 'cause it's pretty.
All the stars in there, like...
In the middle of the mountain.
I don't know, man.
That's it?
Nothing more than what?
I don't know what...
Maybe you wanted to say something else.
Like you wanted to fuck me or something?
But would you like it?
Get off, man. Fuck it!
Dad...
Dad, what are you doing there?
- Nothing, I was there and you weren't...
Where do you come from at this hour and so on?
Joke.
We come from the verbena.
Come on, the other one.
The verbena.
- Did you get out of here?
- What are we going to get out!
Don't lie.
We have remained of botellón.
Go to the bed.
- I've already revealed myself.
And since I've been awake,
I'm going to have a little drink.
- You take the dream with nothing.
Dad, look at me.
Go to the bed.
Go to the bed. Listen to me.
- Do you have a cigarette?
- Fucking hell!
Here, smoke. While we're at it.
Take this one. Come on.
I go to the bathroom. When I get back,
each of you, to your little room.
Come on.
Let's see if we sleep a little bit.
See you later, gorgeous.
- Man!
Can't you see I'm doing this to you with my eyes...
for you to leave?
- Why?
- Because you cut me off.
- Tokio and you...?
- Yes, there.
- Man, it's good.
- Good?
She's hot, Dad.
- But you'll have time.
You have to concentrate.
- I haven't been more focused on my life.
- What you have to concentrate on.
Let's go to bed.
- Fuck I'm going to sleep with you now
after I almost lay with that goddess.
I'm going to sleep in the damn car.
- How are you going to get to the car?
- Shut up, shut up.
You're always doing the same fucking thing to me,
you're always doing the same thing to me.
What's the matter, I'm too little for your son?
I think you're too much.
Because you live life like a video game.
Muggings, shootings, lovers.
Adventures.
Well, yeah, I like to live.
No.
You like to jump from stone to stone in puddles.
Every step of your way, a stone sinks.
You're leaving corpses on the verges.
That's what you like.
Who came up with the armored car heist?
You, right?
Well, now, your boyfriend's a corpse.
And so is your mother.
I'm sure you were aware of the damage
you were doing to your mother.
And now it's Río's turn.
You're bored already.
And on top of that,
you reach for a girl at gunpoint.
Unconscious.
Capricious, superficial, selfish.
How do you define yourself?
If we all do our jobs and it goes wrong,
is part of the job.
But if it goes wrong because
a capricious little girl
wants to rush out of here, I won't allow it.
So get to work. We only have 10 days left.
Let's see if you'll ever
finish what you started.
"Known to perpetrate numerous robberies
to jewelry stores and luxury establishments,
Fonollosa is also attributed with other
crimes of a sexual nature."
- What a résumé!
Andrés de Fonollosa.
Who'd have thought?
With that finesse you have.
And that stick that looks like you've
been shoved up your ass.
And in the end, what you're into are whores.
"Belonging to a trafficking network of women
that they brought from Albania and Bulgaria
to be subsequently sold..."
- Did you also taste Bulgarians before you sold them?
"Crimes of pimping, extortion of minors,
deprivation of liberty..."
- Minors?
Minors?
Minors.
"Among them, the attempted assault on a
well-known jewelry store."
- You're a pig.
What's the point of having that little
girl tied up in your office?
Huh?
What are you trying to do,
you piece of scum?
"Andrés de Fonollosa would have eluded
this last charge thanks to his collaboration
as a confidant."
On top of that, you're a snitch.
"Identified by the police next to..."
- Ah!
- I would never sell to women.
And much less, I'd be his pimp.
My code of ethics prevents me from doing so.
How does it prevent me from betraying a companion,
even if it is a spoil.
And that has nothing to do with my
tastes and hobbies.
- If you say so.
Ah!
"Fonollosa's footprint has been found
on a button that the agents found
in a Seat Ibiza linked to the investigation.
Special units..."
- I've never been in that car before.
But I do know someone who did.
What's going on?
- What the fuck are you doing with my jacket,
mamarracho?
- Fucking hell, man.
Holy shit.
Tell me, Nairobi, do you know where Denver is?
- No. No.
I've sobered up, man, fuck.
Yeah, I was gonna wake you up now.
Have I been here long?
I don't know.
The first time I've ever slept with a girl
and when I wake up, she's still there.
I don't know where you wanted me to go.
Huh?
Shot in the leg and in the middle
of a kidnapping.
I don't have many options.
What's the matter with you?
You don't have to be so rude,
I saved your life.
You saved my life? How?
Like the Jews of Auschwitz?
A Nazi took him out of line and he
didn't go to the gas chamber.
I'm not a fucking Nazi,
I'm not a fucking Nazi.
I remind you that you put a cell
phone in your panties,
that I was sent to kill you.
And what did you do?
Hey, what did you do?
Did you tell him no,
did you stop him? No.
You shot me in the leg.
You humiliated me in front of everyone.
And now, you've got me locked up here,
I can't breathe or go to the bathroom.
I do my needs in a bucket.
So don't get confused.
You may be the best of the Nazis.
But you're still one of them.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry, no...
I didn't mean to humiliate you.
I don't know what to do with all this either.
I'm gonna take you to the bathroom.
Is that okay?
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Denver!
My friend!
Come here!
- Ouch!
Wait!
Stop it!
Wait, damn it, Berlín!
Wait, stop, stop, you're right!
You're right.
Maybe Denver lost a button on your jacket.
because he put on your jacket, but so what?
You can't change it.
- But I can punish him.
- Berlín.
He's not resting. Not in museum.
Not even in a tunnel.
Not even in print.
- Has he gone to the verbena again?
Don't worry, guys, I'll get it.
- Berlín, please, come to your senses.
Come to your senses.
You can't shoot him because he stole
your jacket.
It's a botched job.
You're a classy guy and that's a mess.
- And what about my dignity?
- Huh?
- I have a reputation to uphold.
My friends from the Côte d'Azur
have seen...
my name associated with those infamies.
Denver screwed up my honor.
And if anyone fucks up my honor,
I crush him.
We're talking about integrity.
Huh?
Ethics is important, Nairobi.
But also, aesthetics.
- I'm asking you please.
Please don't fuck with our plan, Berlín.
You fucking bastard!
- Hey, hey, hey.
Nairobi.
It's here.
- Helsinki.
Are you going to shoot me?
- Stay here.
- It was a fucking joke about the jacket.
It was a fucking joke about the jacket!
It was a joke!
I don't know if I'm overdoing it a little
bit with my lip.
I'm a bit of a whore anyway.
What do you think?
I, on the other hand, I'm going supersimple.
Yeah, that's why I'm telling you.
Where are we going? To the verbena.
Then you'll have to go as a whore verbenero.
What is it? Let's party.
Shhh.
The Profesor's keys? Here.
Holy shit!
Mmm!
- Where is Denver?
- I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
- Yes, sir, now, yes.
Shut up.
- But what is this?
Pure and hard elegance.
The Berlín jacket?
Yes, sir.
We're going, we're going.
Silence, silence, silence.
Silence, it comes to me...
What do you say?
Did I ever tell you about my five women?
- Shhh.
They just want us to fertilize them, but later,
what comes out of there...
is a nuclear warhead.
- I'm getting nervous!
Meow.
You look very pretty.
I've put on manga for you.
I like manga.
What's the matter with you?
You cried.
How do you think I am?
Fucking awesome.
I think I'm a weather vane
that ends up fucking everybody.
It's like I'm in a movie.
As if he didn't recognize me.
Because I thought I was...
different,
but actually, I'm a crazy bitch who hurts.
And who gets tired of everything.
And it doesn't make people happy.
I don't like the way I am.
And I don't like this shitty book I found either.
He says I'm a toxic woman.
If you're trying to leave me,
walk away or something,
don't even try.
Río, man,
I am scorched earth.
Worse.
I'm a fucking gas can and a match.
Well, I love bonfires.
And if you're toxic, I get dizzy.
Like with a joint and I enjoy it.
Look.
When I see you on the other side of the museum,
I feel like crying
for the simple fact of being with you.
And we fuck and I float around the room.
I already know you'll leave me.
But why don't we hold out a little longer?
Does it have to be now?
No, it doesn't have to be now.
Record.
And this hair.
- Perfect.
Z-75, all units.
We have an armed robbery in Alcántara, 33.
Any units nearby?
Z-32, we're right at the door,
we're on our way.
That's him.
Yes.
I'm sure.
- Why doesn't he pick up the phone?
Where the hell is he?
I'm in front of your daughter's school, Karina.
And people from my organization are in Krostoma.
watching your wife leave the supermarket.
If the portrait you're making
it looks like me,
you'll never see
either one of them.
Who the fuck is broadcasting from channel 8?
The police can't protect you, Nikolai
Drop that, drop that!
Let go...!
- Fuck!
- Drop it!
What the fuck did he say?
- I didn't hear anything.
- What did he say?
- Where did you get that
message in Russian?
- From Z-32.
- Z-32, do you copy?
- Z-32, leaving a hardware store.
False notice of theft.
- Someone is in your car.
Go running to the unit.
- Dispatch, someone has entered our car,
but there's no one there anymore.
- He's still got to be around.
Look for a suspect.
Male, 40 years old, with a beard.
- There's no one around.
We get moving.
Denver!
Denver?
Denver.
I was looking for you.
- Here I am.
- It turns out that...
my face doesn't stop appearing on the news.
Do you know what they say about me?
- No.
- That I'm a thief.
So far, so good, but they also say
I'm a bitch lover,
a pimp who abused children.
And all at because of a button.
A button on my jacket.
Do you remember? The one you wore.
Apparently, you left it abandoned
in Toledo's car.
A car to which I, I'm sure,
I never got on it.
Do you know what that means?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
- That you just fucked up my life.
- Come on.
- What do I do with you?
- Berlín.
- I'm sorry, I didn't notice the
fucking button.
I'll make it up to you with 10 or
15 million of mine.
You think so?
- 15 million?
- 15 million, don't fuck with me.
We're going to go fuck ourselves.
15 million.
- 15 million euros.
- I'll sign it, if you want.
- For a button?
- For a button.
- Leave him, Berlín.
- What's going on here?
- Nothing's going on.
- It's funny.
It came with the idea
to put a shot in his foot to compensate
and I'm getting the urge to put a bullet
in your head.
and I don't know why.
- Berlín.
- Shhh.
Thank you.
- Retroxil. It is a rare medicine,
ordered on request.
Used to palliate tremors
of a rare degenerative neuronal disease.
- How?
- Herbert's myopathy.
The Russians took this drug four years
ago and it was successful.
They've managed to make Fonollosa's disease
pass from kill to those who suffer it
that they only palm nine out of ten.
So if Fonollosa is not that one,
in less than 24 months, he'll be dead.
- That man has nothing to lose.
- No need to...
Denver.
Denver, is that you?
I sent you to kill her on a Friday.
And today is Sunday.
Resurrection Sunday!
Praise the Lord.
Proceed!
I'm Alison Parker and I'm fucking awesome.
Don't fuck with me!
I have a good surprise for you.
Hello, son.
- Everything can be reversed, sweetheart.
Think about it.
- If Hannibal gives himself up, it means
our plan works.
I can help you solve your problems.
You can change your destiny.
You don't want to be the big heroine
of the paper house.
You mother fucker!
Alison!
The Valencia plan is activated.
Now.
Quite a beach bar you've got here.
I have scissors.
Give them to me.
I have to get out to avoid a massacre.
Sit down!
Alison!
Assault units, stand by.
Four minutes.
Fire!