Inspector, we have the estate.
- The person helping them from the
outside has been here
less than 30 hours ago.
Call Alberto.
- Whatever they really wanted to erase,
they'll have burned it inside.
Look, I was just going to Madrid, I
was going to catch the bus.
Get out of the car.
Son of a bitch.
Aah! Aah!
You're under arrest for assault on authority.
I'm calling from the police station,
I'm under arrest.
I don't know how he got these wounds,
I swear I didn't touch him.
- Have the handcuffs removed.
What are you gonna do to me?
On your feet!
Who's the Profesor?
All right, take her away.
Sergio! The Profesor's name
is Sergio Marquina.
We're going to request unconditional
incommunicated prison.
Let's go. Let's go.
I ditch this from the cider in a few days
and we're going to a Caribbean
Look at her, she's very pretty.
And elegant.
That woman is from another league, son.
- I heard!
That I'm a piece of shit and that I
have to dream like a piece of shit.
You have a syndrome.
What syndrome?
Stockholm. You go your way,
I go mine and forward.
Sub-inspector Rubio is coming
out of the coma,
He is the only person who knows who I am.
You're gonna have to go and see
if it's a trap.
And if it isn't, finish him off.
- Let's get that motherfucker
a fucking red carpet
to the foot of Ángel's bed,
where Lobo will wait for him.
- It's very difficult for him to escape.
It's the office where they keep the fake guns.
And who's going to take his gun?
Mónica will have to do it
when Denver's going to cure her.
Where the fuck are you going?
You've got a toy gun and I've
got a bad motherfucker.
I can't stand it.
Why don't we check it out?
Turn around.
Come on, quick.
Mónica, open the door!
I'm gonna count to five and then
I'm gonna shoot him.
Mónica, don't open the door!
Raquel, sooner or later,
this will all be over.
And then you and I will meet at the beach.
But you have to pick a place.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
It's just that I haven't had time.
Let's see.
What do you say we pick it out
between the two of us?
I'm fine with that.
Pick one.
What a responsibility.
Let's see, ah...
Palawan.
Let me see.
That's wonderful.
And where is this?
Palawan, yes. It is an island
of the Philippines.
It's southwest of the archipelago,
it's a little above
the island of Borneo.
It has 849 000 inhabitants,
more or less, and the capital
is Puerto Princesa.
Ángel must have gotten very close
to get the evidence.
It's possible they were even face-to-face.
- Have you looked into it? Because I do.
Have you done your damn job?
The best fine sandy beaches in the tropics.
You don't like the Philippines.
Yes, I do.
Do you mind if I go to the bathroom
for a minute?
Oh, sure.
Suárez, one question.
What colour was the wig of the
clown who spoke
with the kid from the hospital?
Orange?
You sure about that?
"For your life to fall apart in pieces
it doesn't matter if you're in a bathroom..."
Three, two, one...
"... in a robbery
or at the entrance to a penal institution.
You see, that afternoon we were
going to be synchronized
the misfortunes of three women.
Raquel suddenly realized that
she had fallen in love
With the Spain's biggest robber."
She's one of them.
She's with them, you've all seen her!
She's with them!
"Mónica Gaztambide realized that
she had just become
an accomplice to the muggers,
that there'd be no turning back.
And I walked according to the instructions
that the Profesor had given us in Toledo,
but without any certainty.
Like anesthetized,
like a bottle someone threw into the sea.
With no idea if they were going to pick it up.
on the other side."
If you're caught, within 24 hours
of being arrested
you say you want to make a pact,
you want to declare,
but before a judge.
And they will have no choice
to take you to the National High Court.
And it's possible that in that transfer
I can do something for you.
"Well, there I was on my way
to the courthouse,
in the hope that my guardian angel
knew the itinerary that
van was going to follow
and save my life for the second time.
It was hard to hope for a van,
imprisoned and handcuffed,
but it would have been worse
to know in that moment,
20 km from there, my guardian angel
had just been discovered."
Raquel?
- Hello, Alberto.
Have you already analyzed the
evidence you found
in Toledo's chimney?
- Yes, yes, but nothing conclusive.
- What do you mean nothing conclusive?
- Because they were the remains
of a sports paper
from a couple of days ago,
so I don't know
if the evidence is contaminated or
is that the guy with the anchovies
reads the diary on Sundays.
- Ok.
Hey, how exactly was
the fight with Salva?
- Fuck, Raquel, I told you
it wasn't a fight.
The guy grabbed me by the neck,
made me a ninja movement
and I lost consciousness.
I didn't touch him.
He's a fucking ninja with glasses.
Why do you ask me that?
- For nothing.
And... Are you saying that he provoked you?
- Yes.
He told me he shared my intelligence
with my dick and fists,
among other beauties.
I wanted a fight, but for what?
- I don't know.
Good-bye.
Alberto
No one touches those trays,
they're sealed
until further notice.
I want you to take out all the fingerprints
and check them with the spoon
of sub-inspector Rubio.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I'm not.
And then you go to my car and
you get the fingerprints
of the copilot's inner handle.
- But...
- Do it.
And remember, we're looking
for a middle-aged male
with a beard and glasses.
Hey, hey, hey!
See who that man is and
what he's doing here.
"It was him, of course it was him."
Sorry, you won't have a phone
charger out there.
- No, I'm not.
Do you want to use mine?
"It had been him from the beginning.
Always kind, always with a smile,
always in the right place.
The only civilian who had set
foot in the tent."
You see, I think there's something
wrong with your daughter.
"The stranger who had managed to get through
one by one all her defenses.
And not just as a cop."
Salva.
I don't have such a wonderful gift
like these postcards,
but I'm going to improvise a surprise.
In the ladies' room.
First you go and then I go.
Raquel.
That we're on children's schedule
and in this bar they know both of us.
Salva.
It's the first time I'm going
without a parachute
and throw myself in the pool.
Don't tell me there's no water.
Yes, it is.
Then go and wait for me there.
Hands against the wall.
Raquel, I don't know...
Oh, what are you doing?
Do you carry a gun?
How can I carry a gun, Raquel?
Turn around.
Put it on.
Raquel, is this...?
Put it on, put it on!
You're being arrested for collaboration
in the hostage assault
to the Fábrica Nacional de Moneda
"You see."
You have the right to remain silent.
"Finally, the third time was the charm."
Not to testify against you and
to be brought before a judge.
"And this time she had something much bigger
than a suspicion,
he had a grudge, he had anger.
She was poisoned.
Helsinki felt something similar,
but not by deception,
but for lack of sleep,
had slept four hours in the last
five days.
Do you know what happens to a
person when they stop sleeping?
That their neural connections
merge like a short circuit,
stops secreting dopamine,
stops metabolizing glucose
and the only information left
in the brain
is to survive.
So if there's something you can't ask
a guy who hasn't slept in five days
is patience."
Let's go.
Take off your clothes.
T-shirt too.
I have a shoulder injury...
Take off your shirt!
- And on top of that you steal from us.
Ole.
This for not killing when
you had to kill.
What are you going to do?
If I shoot you, you just die.
You don't suffer.
Now you're gonna go with two
kilos of explosives
glued to your body.
I detonate, but you don't know when.
- Helsinki, that's a lot of explosive,
Be careful, you can make a mess
that you freak out.
- This worm fuck us more than the police.
Oslo dies because of him.
Denver almost died because of him.
This is the end of trouble.
Eh, Arturito?
Don't remove wires, this explodes.
Don't move fast.
Don't sweat it.
Don't touch yourself.
Detonator.
If I touch this button, boom!
Not even your wife to recognize.
Mince of Arturito.
Do you have a cigarette?
Mónica, you are pregnant.
Pregnant, kidnapped, shot...
And in a moment accused of collaboration
with an armed band.
Don't get into the worst.
Arturo can help you,
he's your son's father, isn't he?
What father, what father?
The one who just pointed
me out as one kidnapper?
What father?
The one I banged his head on
with an iron stick?
Maybe all my colleagues will help me,
I just screwed up their whole escape plan.
I'm sure they'll say it in court.
God! Why have I been so foolish,
where the hell is my head?
Come on, give me a cigarette.
Give me a cigarette,
my fetus needs a cigarette.
You're not going to sit on any bench,
because I'd rather blow up Arturo.
- You're not going to destroy anybody, okay?
It's okay.
- But she's right,
That if we run away
and the police catch us, she goes to jail.
If we stay and they come in, too.
He's going to jail, yes or yes.
Fucking hell.
I always make the wrong choice.
I mess with a married guy.
I got pregnant with him.
And then there's another guy,
shoots me in the leg.
and I go and I fall in love.
You know what we're gonna do?
What?
You're coming with us.
If you crossed the line,
you crossed the line,
I'm not gonna leave you lying
in the road, okay?
- We can still...
- Yes, she's coming with us.
Let her take the place of Tokio
or Oslo and that's it.
No, no, listen. I'm just a secretary,
I don't see myself running from
the police or shooting
or living in hiding I don't know
where, in Cambodia,
in any extradition-free country, no.
I'd better stay.
And when the police come,
I'll tell them
I did it because I had a
Stockholm syndrome
like a piano.
And that has extenuating factors.
Because that's what it was, isn't it?
Stockholm.
That can be nice.
If you come with us, you...
I don't know, I could call you Stockholm.
What do I know, dude?
Get out.
Open the door.
Come on in.
"We were all exhausted.
The lack of sleep,
stress,
or the anguish of years of
carrying a secret
which in that asphyxiating environment was
becoming more and more difficult to keep.
And all of us, sooner or later,
lost our papers.
Except for Berlín, he was the only
one who fulfilled to the letter
the rest protocol.
The others were out of their minds."
I've tried to be good.
I've tried to give you what you were promised.
Get rid of Berlín,
to make sense of this.
After losing what I've lost here,
that this made any sense at all.
I'm good.
I've been good.
And the world spits in my face.
I've tried to give you oxygen.
and you guys fucked me in the ass.
Berlín.
Hey, it's been over an hour and a half.
- Don't you want to kill me
while I'm sleeping?
A little bit.
Hey, hey, you're laughing.
That means you're not afraid
of me anymore.
- Let's just say the dose of
anxiolytics I'm taking
has me neutralized.
- If all goes well, unlikely thing
if I don't take the command again...
If all goes well, I want to
make you a deal,
a romantic business.
A few days later I'll send
you a plane ticket.
Somewhere far away.
If you want,
you can come with me.
Very little time,
a lot of whimsy.
And then, already after the end,
you can keep everything I have.
It would be really wonderful
if you fell in love with me so much.
But I don't live on expectations,
of false illusions.
I have many faults and I know it.
I could settle for you being my partner
until the last trip.
You and me together till the end.
You don't understand, you don't understand.
What am I going to have to do
to get you to respect me?
What am I gonna have to do?
Hey, I'll cut off your ear
and send it to your father?
Or I'll shoot you in the leg
so you can't dance again.
in your fucking life?
- A great idea!
It's time to be practical.
The utopia of collaboration has failed.
Nairobi
I appreciate you allowing me to
take some time off
in my duties.
But we're already for me to return to command.
- All yours.
- This is a wonderful moment.
On your feet!
I told you I was going to protect
you, didn't I?
But I've changed my mind.
Much more practical: torturing you.
In the concentration camps
respect is taken for granted.
Well, it's gonna be the same here.
You're going to make the tunnel
Until your hands bleed!
At night you could cry in pain
on your bed, but then... You're
going to keep chopping stone!
You will rotate in your task without rest
and if not, an epic punishment awaits you.
Like your leader.
A man who, if he betrays again, kills.
That if he ever longs for freedom again,
he kills.
If you sweat a lot...
Kill.
A man with an explosive character.
Now you're going to scare them, Arturo,
even though we've all known that
you're the bomb.
Since you're a stinker, you're
going to stay here apart.
Helsinki, everybody else to the tunnel!
- Come on, let's go! Let's go, quick!
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Boom.
Seismographs have located unusual activity
in the basement of the factory,
it seems that the kidnappers
have increased the pace of tunnel excavation,
they're about to take him in.
- How much do they have left?
- According to the georadar, two meters, 2.5.
- And where are they going to take it?
- We believe that here, in a
collector about 15 meters
behind the building.
- Attention everyone, I want you all ready!
Warn the subsoil, be warned.
And I want 20 men on that collector now.
Do you know what the guilty ones
do when they take them
to the crime scene?
They keep talking.
Of time, of politics, they click...
It's the nerves,
because they can't stand silence.
But you...
You don't say anything.
What do you want me to talk about, Raquel?
Who are you?
Sergio Marquina.
Sergio? Salva? The Profesor?
The person who's been keeping
all the police, the CNI
and the special corps?
The man I've been talking to
five days on the phone,
I told him what clothes I was wearing.
and even what colour my orgasms are.
And which one are you?
Why aren't your fingerprints
in the database
of the National Identity Card?
I stopped renewing it before they started
to digitize it.
When?
I don't know.
More than 20 years ago.
That opens up a world of possibilities,
doesn't it?
Because no one's gonna report a man missing
that just doesn't exist.
I'm not even going to have to
make an effort
to burn your corpse well.
Is that what you want?
Kill me and burn me?
Yes.
I'm telling you, I do.
Oh, look,
maybe, as an inspector, I shouldn't
tell you this
to the person who has organized the
robbery with hostages
to the Fábrica Nacional de Moneda,
but as a woman,
as a woman who's spent years being
afraid of everything,
to everything,
and she's trusted someone,
someone who knowing
how fragile and vulnerable I was,
he's been cheating on me
from the beginning,
from the fucking beginning,
I don't think it's that far-fetched,
do you?
You could... You could have approached me,
pull me out, put me on a fucking mic,
A fucking mic, damn it!
But no, no, it's not.
Yesterday we were dreaming together.
Fucking hell.
Speaking of future, of future.
Who the fuck are you? What are you,
a disturbed fuck?
It was all planned, Raquel.
Everything, it was everything.
I'm so sorry, it was all planned.
Except for what happened between us.
I don't know, I broke my own rule.
What?
I don't know.
I haven't looked at that variable.
What the fuck are you saying,
which variable?
To fall in love with you.
You really think I'm gonna let you
go through with this fucking shit?
Hey, motherfucker?
That I'm going to stand idly by
while you keep lying to me like
I'm a 15-year-old girl?
I'm not lying to you, Raquel.
I've fallen in love with you.
Tell me again, tell me again.
Dare to tell me again, tell me.
Raquel, I've fallen in love with you.
I'm so sorry.
All right, all right.
Berlín, I want to talk to you.
- Sure, I'm the boss again.
I need my puppies' food.
- What exactly did the Profesor
say to you about Tokio?
- He told me he was going to
try to free her.
- And how the hell is he gonna
release her all by himself?
- Río, he's not going to do it.
- Who?
- The four Serbs who dug the tunnel
five years ago.
They're the wild card for extreme setbacks.
- When?
I don't know.
You notice her absence, don't you?
Those who stay always have it more fucked up.
Her, on the other hand,
will be broadening her experience,
enlarging their sensations.
Would you have liked to take the
deal with the cops?
Total
what would happen if we got out of here,
stayed together?
Are you talking about betraying your friends?
My friends with a city name?
Tokio, Berlín, Moscú, Denver...
Well, to me, my friends with a city name
they look fucking awesome to me.
And I'll tell you something,
try to hide if you take the deal.
Because if I see you,
I'll shoot you in the head.
Women always move on before.
Just in case, you should be warned.
- Tokio is impulsive,
but she's coming back.
And we're gonna end up together.
I know it.
- Sure, I'm sure.
I've always thought so.
If you betray us and come out,
and you need to call me when you're sorry...
Because believe me, you'll regret it.
You can call me on Alison's cell,
I'll keep it open.
The police will listen to us,
but what difference does it make?
Suárez, Alison Parker's phone is on.
- Try to hack it.
- Sealed chamber, sir.
They're not calling or sending anything.
What the hell is this?
- Fucking hell.
This is Convoy 727, we're being assaulted.
- This is central, we haven't understood you.
Please repeat.
- They have inhibitors.
- Fucking hell!
"My guardian angel had not forsaken me
and I felt like I was on the witch's train."
It's a fucking bomb!
- What the hell's going on out front?
- We've been glued with an explosive!
"In a dark tunnel where you don't know
where a broom's gonna rain on you,
but what fun."
What's going on?
What the hell's going on?
They're fucking killing us!
- Shut the fuck up!
- We're fucked!
- Shut the fuck up, I need to think!
- Get on the ground!
- Alert.
Okay, okay, no, no, no.
- Put your guns down or I'll kill her.
Put your guns down or I'll kill her.
- If you shoot girl, you die.
If you shoot me, you die.
If you let go girl, you live.
"May all the decisions of this world
were so easy, right?"
Río.
Down there, I realized you didn't agree
with what Helsinki was doing.
You're not like them.
You're a good boy.
I have a son your age too,
you know? The oldest.
The older one's a good boy, too.
Help me, please.
I want to see my son.
I found this passport-making machine.
No, no, no.
Mónica, Mónica.
You listen to me.
You can do whatever you want,
but what if you change your mind?
I thought you could really use a new one.
Besides, this is real, it's good gender.
I know, I work here.
Well, it doesn't cost you anything.
We do it. If you don't want it later,
throw it away, burn it
or you take it as a souvenir,
whatever you want.
It's only two minutes.
Shall we?
Come on, okay.
Did you plug it in?
Yes.
Okay.
What's my name?
Ágata.
Ágata?
What's going on?
Well, it's a name
of a porn actress.
Ágata is the name of a hot chick.
If you were ugly, I'd tell you to get...
I don't know, Felisa or Mari Cruz...
María, María Fernández.
María Fernández? That's not a name,
no one believes that.
Trust me, I understand these things.
More discreet.
Ágata sounds expensive, has class.
Write Ágata.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Write born in Madrid.
And the year, whatever you want.
We're making a passport.
- I see.
- In case she runs away or...
she's coming with us.
- Who do you think stole your gun?
- Come out.
Suárez.
- Sir, I'm calling from the National High Court.
The convoy transporting Silene Oliveira
It should've been here 15 minutes ago
and it hasn't arrived, we don't have any news.
- Keep me informed.
Gómez, I need two units doing the tour
of Silene Oliveira to the court.
He has not yet arrived
and I need to know what's going on.
- Understood.
Put this on.
Only contact: Profesor.
He says what to do.
"Never in my life have I felt so free.
But that time the Profesor's plan
was not going to work."
I know I may have been under pressure.
That I was wrong, but please,
I don't deserve this.
Please, I'm asking you,
if there's any dignity left in you...
Please.
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe, help me.
Help me, please.
We're coming in.
We take food and sit down.
Each one a metre away from the other.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
That's it, that's it, with joy.
Helsinki, say hello to Arturito.
Arturito.
There's something here that doesn't
make any sense.
I've been told before that if I sweat at all,
I will blow away. And yet,
they have me here,
enclosed with this unbearable demon heat,
with this heat...
It's best if you're calm and quiet.
It doesn't make any sense.
What?
The bomb doesn't make any sense.
Do you think these people
was going to risk me tripping
or to sweat so that the whole plan
to will blow away? No.
No, it would be really crazy,
these people don't work that way.
Shut up.
They're making us
psychological terrorism,
don't you see?
They're trying to scare us, it's not real,
it's a bluff.
I have no idea, but I don't want to know.
So shut up.
I'm going to take it off, I've decided.
I take it off, I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna take it off. It's all right.
Don't you see that if I were to explode,
You wouldn't...
Be still and sit down.
Who the hell are you to tell us what to do?
It's your fault that we're locked in here.
Because of me?
Yes, because of you.
You're the director of this place
and you've been snuck eight crazies
like Peter in his house.
Are there any Money Factories in the
world that have been robbed?
Just this one, right?
Congratulations, because you've made history.
Now, please, don't make us all blow away.
Have a seat.
Central, do you copy?
The van has been assaulted,
there's no sign of Silene Oliveira.
- Received. Wait for instructions.
- Attention, we have a fugitive,
we activate Operation Cage!
"He wasn't there.
He wasn't there.
If he'd arranged everything,
if he'd sent for me to be saved,
how could he not be there?
That October afternoon they had
deployed for my escape
Operation Cage. You will know about it
when there were attacks.
It consists of the police cutting in
all the exits from the city,
everything collapses.
and you get trapped,
you can only hide.
My problem was that the hideout
was the hangar
and it was the Profesor who had to open it for me.
And the truth is, I was never good at waiting."
What's that?
The only real thing I know about you
is that you're a professional liar.
And call me paranoid, but you're
not gonna lie to me again.
not one more time, I assure you.
What do you think, I don't know,
I'm an asshole?
Of course she stole my gun,
but she regretted it.
If he doesn't regret it,
he'd be in a box with Oslo by now.
- Okay, he helped you, and welcome,
but that's not why
you have to give her a passport
or take her on the run.
- What if I want to do it?
What if I want to go live with her
and take care of her son, what's going on?
- Pretty fucked up
you're gonna have to carry someone else's backpack.
- They're not backpacks, she's an woman
who loves me and her son,
as far as I know,
he's not to blame.
- Nor do you have the obligation to get in trouble.
- I don't do it out of obligation.
- Sometimes we try to help someone,
but the first to sink is oneself.
- Well, I'll swim, like we've done
all our fucking lives.
- It's not like that, damn it!
I know that.
That I tried to help your mother
every fucking day of my life.
- What's with the shit now?
Mom left us.
What the fuck is that all about now?
Hey.
- We abandoned her.
Because it was going to lead us to the abyss.
I admitted her to a clinic in Barcelona.
200 000 pesetas cost me.
And in less than 24 hours he
showed up at my hostel.
High as hell.
- What did you do?
- It was the fourth time I
lost my savings.
- What the fuck did you do?
- She wanted to go buy some more.
I put her in the car, left her in a
Martorell roundabout,
next to a village that sold drug.
But I didn't wait for her.
I came back to get you to move us.
- Did you leave my mother in
a roundabout?
- That's why I got you into
all this stuff,
because I don't want you to live
the life I lived,
because I want you to be free,
I want you to start...
- A mother isn't abandoned,
she's detoxified.
All my life making me think she was a bitch,
thinking that maybe she was gone because of me.
It was her or us, son.
- Oh, my God!
I'm not opening your head because we need you
to get out of here.
As soon as we get out, you and I are nothing.
Two strangers, Denver and Moscú.
Are you done with your passport?
Yes.
Denver, are you okay?
I've put on Ágata.
"He was driving frantically nowhere.
I knew where to go in a fraction of a second.
The bad news is, it was the most watched point
of all Spanish geography."
Take a deep breath.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm fine.
See those lines over there?
Every lie of yours will result
in some very ugly curves
for altered blood pressure,
heart rate, respiratory rate...
So don't lie to me or I'll know.
Name.
Sergio Marquina.
Place of birth.
San Sebastian.
Did you know you were going to destroy Ángel?
Yes.
Was it you who caused his accident?
No.
Was the Fábrica de Moneda
robbery your idea?
No.
Who came up with that?
My father.
He died before he could be executed,
this is a kind of tribute.
The story of the fucking apples.
The fucking history of Organic Cider
you told me yesterday in bed was
the story of the robbery.
And me listening to you like an asshole,
you've been laughing at me...
I haven't been laughing at you.
From the first moment.
I haven't been laughing at you,
Look at the polygraph, please.
Look at it.
My father had a sick child,
not a fucking cent.
What would you have done?
He spent the day thinking about robberies
to pay for a hospital in the U.S.
Out of desperation,
for saving my life.
Me.
Because nobody,
no one helped him.
And in that endeavour,
he was shot to death.
In the door of a bank.
That's the reality.
I guess there's a lot of ways to
understand what's fair.
You thought I was easy prey because
I was a battered woman.
Yes, I did.
When you leaked to the press my
refusal to release eight hostages
in favor of Alison Parker,
you knew I was going to be publicly lynchered,
that you were going to destroy my career
and my mother was going to see it.
and my daughter.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
You slept with me just because
I'm the lead inspector.
of the case, right?
No.
You slept with me because
I'm the lead inspector?
No.
Stop fucking lying to me!
I'm not lying to you.
You want me to believe you have
feelings for me?
I'm not making you believe anything,
Raquel, that's how I feel.
I didn't expect it,
but it's happening to me,
it's happened to me and
it's happening to you too.
It's happened to you too,
otherwise what are we doing here, huh?
Why am I not in a cell,
what the hell is this?
What are you now, Misery's crazy or what is this?
It's something that's happening
to both of us, you know?
It happened to both of us.
Yes, Suárez.
- Inspector, Silene Oliveira has escaped.
- What?
- I was on my way to the courthouse,
had asked to testify before the judge.
The convoy has been assaulted
by a group of subjects from the east.
I have activated Operation Cage,
I hope they haven't left the
Community of Madrid.
- Ask the judge for an international
arrest warrant,
I want you to shield roads,
ports and airports.
Have them patrol all the borders.
Tokio has escaped.
You're the one who pulled out a murderer
from a maximum-security prison
while I'm holding you here?
I actually left everything ready
before I met you
in the cafeteria.
I'm sorry to see you like this,
but I just got here.
Darko, I'm so sorry about your brother.
Let's go.
You've got it all figured out
to the millimeter, haven't you?
Raquel, I told you everything.
I came all this way without offering
any kind of resistance.
And if I let you interrogate me,
It's because I wanted to be honest with you.
I can't take it anymore
this lie.
Shut up.
I didn't mean to hurt you anymore.
Shut up!
All this is...
Shut the fuck up,
Holy shit!
I'm not listening to you anymore.
Look, from now on
whatever you have to say,
you say directly to the judge.
Get up.
Get the fuck up!
Go, go, go
Keep walking.
I'm so sorry, Raquel.
Keep going...!
I'm going to shoot.
I'm go...
"Have you ever heard of putting
yourself in the wolf's mouth?"
It's a call to Alison Parker's phone.
from an unknown number.
Locate it.
Yes?.
Río.
I'm Tokio.
It's Silene Oliveira.
- Record. Locate the call.
- Where are you?
Wait, they're listening.
I don't care, this is a love call.
And the police love love.
Listen, do you remember the door
my mother used to draw for me
when I was afraid?
What door are you talking about?
- Yes, love, of course I remember.
What's wrong?
I'm gonna cross it,
I'm gonna cross the door to heaven.
Because my guardian angel doesn't show up.
In a minute.
I love you.
And I love you too.
What the hell was that call?
- It looked like a farewell.
- Attention, sir, an unauthorized
vehicle is entering.
on the perimeter.
- Let's go, everybody!
Hey, hey.
That's her.
Door, door.
Fuck, the door.
Hey, hey, hey.
Attention, it's Silene Oliveira!
Tokio's coming back!
- Tokio's coming back,
get back on the ground!
- We have to open the door, dammit!
Shoot the target, shoot the biker!
Let's go! Let's go!
No! We've got to cover it up,
damn it!
- Kidnapper in sight.
Dad, look out!
- Unit three, behind you, behind you!
Fucking hell!
Moscú!
- Moscú!
You have to get out as soon as possible.
I've been discovered, Andrés,
I don't know how long
it's gonna take the police to show up here.
Have you located the inspector?
Fucking hell!