We're going to request
unconditional and isolated imprisonment.
The convoy has been assaulted
by a group of Eastern subjects,
Silene Oliveira has escaped.
Río, it's Tokio. I'm going through
the heaven's gate. In a minute.
Tokio is coming!
We have to open the door, dammit!
Shoot the target, shoot the biker!
No, we have to cover it up, damn it!
- Dad, look out!
Wait, wait.
He's bleeding out.
You're being held for
collaboration in the hostage assault.
to the Fábrica Nacional de Moneda.
You want me to believe
that you have feelings for me?
- It's happening to both of us.
From now on what you have to say
you say it directly to the judge.
- I'm so sorry, Raquel.
Keep going...!
How are we going to get out?
- Through a tunnel.
You're gonna have the hostages
digging in the boiler cellar.
We'll go out through another tunnel,
just take it from vault number three...
Soil!
to a hangar I already have planned.
That wall's got three blows.
Start digging,
I'll take care of imyself.
- We're going to dig
from this side too. Anyway,
we have to get out as soon as possible,
I've been discovered, Andrés.
Any news?
- Did you know that Sergio Marquina,
aka the Profesor, is Salva,
the brain from the heist?
- You got a call from that man,
minutes later you went
and destroyed the record with his fingerprints.
- I didn't know who that man was.
- Hand over your badge and gun.
Will you marry me, Ariadna?
- He wants me to marry him
when we get out.
And you're gonna do it?
- I'm going to keep all his money.
When he's by my side and he
can't even move anymore,
I'm gonna tell him
what a son of a bitch he is
and all the damage he's done to me.
Denver!
- What?
Go upstairs. You have to go upstairs now.
Agustín Ramos.
It has been a pleasure. I love you.
- I love you too, Dad.
Sergio, I'm only going in there if you promise.
that if things go to hell,
you won't let yourself get caught, you'll escape.
You're not gonna be waiting in the hangar.
Nothing will go wrong, we're the resistance.
We know it's close. Stop complicating things
and surrender.
- Surrender was never an option.
I'll wait for you.
It would be easier if Ángel was here.
- He's the only one who knows
the exact location of the hideout.
Inspector Murillo. I need the recordings
from the security camera out there.
Thank you.
Shall we cover him?
- Just like that?
We'll have to say a few words
or something, won't we?
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
- Thy kingdom come.
- Huh?
- That you skipped a paragraph.
After hallowed be thy name
It comes...
- What the fuck does that matter now?
- If you want to pray, you have to do it right.
- Do you think God will be there
seeing if you say it right or wrong?
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive our trespasses, as we forgive
those who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
"There are times in life
when you should have
a damn remote control so you can stop it.
Even if it was only five minutes.
But sometimes things happen
with a reverent obscenity.
and there's nothing you can do about it.
On one side, we had just buried Moscú;
on the other, we were opening
the way to our freedom."
All the shops in the area match,
Inspector Murillo
has requisitioned security camera footage
crucial to the investigation.
- The undeniable proof
that she collaborates with the robbers.
- The intervention protocol
must be activated immediately.
Gather your best men.
- What about the hostages?
What about Alison Parker?
And international protocol?
What about citizen safety?
Colonel, they have large caliber weapons,
controlled access with explosives,
hostages dressed in overalls
and masks just like the muggers,
we won't be able to tell them apart.
Going in is going to be a slaughter
and you know it.
- And what do you propose?
Let those criminals get away
with Inspector Murillo
holding hands?
- Yes, let them out
and catch them once they're out.
- Do you know where public safety has taken us?
You want me to tell you?
To be a laughing stock. But not only from Spain,
from the whole fucking globe.
The news of half the world
follow the minute by minute of this heist
as if it were the World Cup.
Do you like being on TV with the headline:
"The assholes of the Spanish police
let in a runaway prisoner at the
Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre.
on a motorbike"?
On a motorbike!
Do you like being the fucking fool?
- Sorry...
- I didn't ask for your opinion.
The government just gave the order to intervene.
Those motherfuckers have been in there for 125 hours
and if, by any chance, they escape,
the discredit of this country
will be absolute.
- Sorry...
- What?
- The prosecution has issued an arrest warrant
against Inspector Raquel Murillo.
From this moment on
she is in search and arrest.
Where is he?
- In the warehouse.
I'm so sorry.
Come here, come on.
The one from the cell phone.
Hi.
You can call her Stockholm, if you want.
It's not all gonna be crying, is it?
Go ahead.
984 million euros.
984 million euros. Yes.
Colonel, I've got my men ready to go in.
- Okay.
- There's something new in the tunnel.
- Data from the georadar indicate
that they are only a few meters
from the sewage network. We have an elite unit
in the sewers.
- Entering the main collector.
Distance to target:
300 meters north.
- Copy that. We're holding.
Suárez, we're going
to perform this operation
together, we'll make an engulfing tactic
harassing them from the flanks to force them
to get into the hole.
Which is a fucking sandwich.
- Push them from the inside out.
and wait for them in the sewers,
so they can't go back.
or hide and seek.
- We got them in a mousetrap
they can't get out of.
Now all that's left for us to do
is find Inspector Murillo
and her boyfriend.
Lieutenant.
Unit.
- Sir!
Are you ready?
- Yes, sir!
Berlín, get everyone to transport the money,
we have to leave now.
All right.
Assault units are arriving.
and they're going in.
Let's get on with it.
- We're already in.
Son of a bitch. Son of a bitch!
Helsinki, I'm going to ruin you, I swear.
As soon as I get out of here
I'm going to sue you
for cruelty, torture
and crimes against humanity,
you bastard.
Arturito, let's go to the tunnel.
Your mission is very important, okay?
It was a fake.
Get up, slowly.
Turn around.
And now you're coming to the police station.
And you're not gonna move a fucking hair,
because this time
I'm gonna shoot you.
You know why?
Because I've taken a little walk in the countryside
and I've had time to think and to regret
not having shot the biggest son of a bitch
that's ever crossed my path.
- Raquel, please.
And I don't kill you because I want to see you
in a prison for 30 years.
And there you could ask whoever you want
what they're wearing.
Don't move.
- Don't move!
- Stop there!
He was born on Labor Day.
All his birthdays,
ever since he started at the mine,
he said he had the party ready,
a good picket.
And that the rubber balls were his gifts.
And this year they were bullets.
I guess if you're born on the wrong side,
you die on the wrong side.
What's your name?
No, Mónica.
- I need to know your name.
Because I'm gonna get out of here with you.
I don't know if through the back door,
through the tunnel or with a machine gun,
but I don't want to be separated from you.
And if I have to learn to shoot, then I learn.
Besides,
this kid's gonna need a father.
Come on, tell me your name.
This is underfloor team, we're moving forward
through the sewers.
What's that noise?
- Quiet.
- It's the subway. Line six, it's passing over us.
- We go on.
Come on, gentlemen, don't let it go!
Let it be known that here we continue
to distribute magic
until the end!
In there we will take radio signal
and telesatellized video,
this way we will avoid the frequency inhibitors.
The bomb squad will breach the cargo door,
300 grams of termite explosive,
you know what that means.
Lobo, Ruiz, you'll make us cover fire
if necessary.
The rest of us, we'll line up one by one,
no one's left behind.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Gentlemen, we're going to find
some trouble in there,
so we're gonna be close, together.
All right?
- Yes, sir!
The only order
is not to shoot first if they're wearing masks.
But let's repel any shots
from anyone who opens fire on us.
- The only instruction is there's no order
for any of those motherfuckers to get out alive.
Is that clear?
- Yes, sir!
We're ready, so let's go get them.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
We shut down the machines
and delete all the records.
Then you take out the hard drives,
we'll take them.
- We have very little left to reach a billion,
is print some plates and that's it.
How much time do we need, Torres?
- Eleven minutes.
- You're rounding the figure, Nairobi.
What do you think this is?
'Wanna Bet'?
- You go pack, I'll take care of the money.
And if I say a billion, it's a billion.
- If I say stop, stop!
Do you know why I'm in charge?
Because you have cork inside your head.
You want to stay in this mousetrap
to reach a billion.
You know what that reminds me of?
A mother who leaves her child,
a baby, to go sell pills.
And they get her, of course.
And they take away her child.
Under my command these things
don't happen, Nairobi.
No, no, under your command,
hostage weddings are planned.
What? Are you going to get married,
on the beach, dressed in white?
And you who control everything, do you know
how this woman feels about you?
To retch. I heard it in the bathroom.
The only reward she' s got left
is to keep your money.
Hold on until you have a seizure
and when you're dying, tell you to your face
that every time you raped her,
because you're raping her,
she went to the bathroom to puke.
That's all she's got left,
to spit at you on your deathbed.
That's what you turned her into.
Torres, turn off the machines.
- Miss Nairobi.
- Go turn off the machines, Torres.
- All right.
Río, are you there?
- Yes, Profesor.
The frequency is code encrypted.
- How long does it take
to decode it?
- At least two hours.
It's perfect. Place the explosive charges.
Pass the intercall to Berlín.
- Right now.
- Hey.
Come here, please.
Tell me.
- I don't feel well.
What do you have?
- My chest hurts a lot.
It could be an anxiety attack.
Do you want an anxiolytic?
It would have been a lot easier for me, too.
if none of this had happened.
You've been the only real crack in a perfect plan,
a plan that was perfect and no longer is.
Do you know why?
Because even if all this goes well,
even if all this goes well, I already...
I'm going to be fucked.
Because I'm not gonna see you again.
Do you think it was within my plans
to fall in love with the inspector
in charge of the case?
I don't want to hear you any more.
You don't want to hear me?
Why don't you want to hear me, Raquel?
Because l' m one of the bad guys?
You've been taught to see everything
in terms of good and bad.
But what we're doing is fine with you
if other people do it.
In 2011 the European Central Bank
created 171 billion euros out of nowhere.
Out of nowhere.
Just like we're doing.
Only in a big way.
185 000 in 2012.
145 billion euros in 2013.
Do you know where all that money went?
To the banks.
Directly from the factory to the richest.
Did anyone say that the European Central Bank
was a thief?
Provision of liquidity they called it.
And they got it out of nowhere, Raquel, out of nowhere.
What's this?
This is nothing, Raquel, this is paper.
It's paper, see?
It's paper.
I'm making a provision of liquidity.
But not to the bank, I'm doing it here,
in the real economy of this group of unfortunates,
which is who we are, Raquel.
To escape from all this.
Don't you want to escape?
Ángel is calling you.
What's the meaning of this?
Has he woken up?
If he's conscious, he will send the colleagues
and they're gonna show up
in five minutes, for fuck's sake.
Okay, all right, you're gonna answer it, Raquel,
but no nonsense. Please, please.
You're gonna answer and you're gonna make sure
if he's awake, okay?
Please.
No, don't pick up.
Don't pick up.
My phone's bugged.
Do you have another one?
Who's that?
- Raquel, Raquel Murillo.
- Ángel's awake,
he doesn't want us to call anyone
before he talks to you.
- Raquel.
How's it going?
It's okay.
Come on.
Come on, Raquel.
- How are you?
- Me? Like floating. I can't even feel my ass.
Listen, I've seen on TV that you've been relieved
of the investigation.
- Yes, it is.
- Don't tell anyone I woke up, okay?
I need you to come see me first.
- Okay.
Colonel, we've detected a call
to Raquel Murillo's cell phone,
but there's been no communication.
- Trace the origin of this call.
I want the holder of the mobile
and the repeater. Now!
You have to let me go talk to Ángel.
If not, in 15 minutes he'll talk to the police
and tell them where you are.
And I can stop him from doing it.
It's your only chance. Please.
It's about your plan,
that your perfect plan
doesn't get fucked up.
- Let me think, please.
There's nothing to think about, Sergio.
I'm with you.
A minute ago you were yelling at me
and biting me like an animal.
Can I trust you?
- Come, come closer.
Colonel.
We have the call to Raquel.
It's been done from Ángel's phone.
- What?
- The sub-inspector Rubio.
Call to the hospital and find out
if he's awake from the coma.
If so, send three men at full throttle.
That bitch could show up there any minute.
Well, that's it, timers and sensors in place.
This'll keep the police entertained for a while,
they' Il have to deactivate them one by one.
What's your plan tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow I'll be sailing in a merchant ship,
sunbathing with my tits in the air.
The tits in the air.
So I don't get any marks.
And you're gonna be there, naked,
with all those lonely sailors who didn't see
a woman for months?
You think I can't defend myself or what?
Or do you want to defend me from the voyeurs?
No, it's not that.
- No?
That journey is our last journey.
And I don't know what the fuck you're gonna
do when we get to port,
I don't know if you're gonna hook up a jet ski
or what the hell you're gonna do, I don't know.
So I want you to be quiet with me.
And in the cabin.
Hey, we just ran into a brick wall.
Hold it.
Open that wall, faces the sewer.
That's where we're going out.
Go.
Take this.
Have you seen all those bombs?
Fucking hell.
20 years of my life, 20 years.
Jesús, give me the hammer.
We're 200 meters from the mouth.
Estimated time: six minutes.
- Let's go.
We will warn of any seismic movement.
Berlín, stop the chain right now.
Nairobi, we're leaving.
- There is still money to carry.
- We'll be right there with the luggage.
Gentlemen, it's been a pleasure robbing you,
but it's time to enjoy a well-deserved vacation.
Raquel.
- How are you?
- You see.
- I'm glad you got out of this.
I think I owe you an apology.
- Stop apologizing.
Although what you called me,
flirt from bingos and Don Pimpón,
was the most humiliating thing
I've ever been told in my fucking life.
I couldn't rest easy in the coma.
- I'm so sorry.
- Why were you relieved of the case?
- Because they think I belong
to that gang of robbers.
- And you belong?
- No!
- But you've had a relationship
with that guy, haven't you?
- Yes.
- And you're in love with him.
I'll give you the information
on where the hangar is.
From there that guy controls the whole heist.
In case you want to clean up your reputation,
solve the case and beat them.
- I know where that hangar is.
But I'm not going to give them the information.
- Why not?
- Because I don't know
who the good guys are
and who the bad guys are anymore.
Don't move!
- Hands up!
Put your hands up.
- López.
Arenas.
Gómez.
Aah!
Ángel...
You know there's gonna be laws
on our island, don't you?
You have to go naked all day long,
although I'll be able to wear loincloths.
Go put explosives in the warehouse, go on.
Tokio!
Forward!
Come on, fuck!
Shit!
Here!
Get up!
Aah!
What the fuck do we do?
Fucking armored shields.
You have to shoot them in the feet.
Cover me!
Motherfuckers!
Corporal, count!
- They've hit several agents, sir!
I'll cover you.
We evacuated wounded, come on!
We evacuate the wounded and go forward!
If we get out of here,
I'll hang up the machine gun, I swear.
Really?
- I'll never take a shotgun again,
not even at the fair.
Come on, everybody!
Besides, we'll have to pick out things
for our island, won't we?
Curtains, sofas...
- Did you say our island?
Motherfuckers!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
With everything!
Fuck. Lobo, now!
They're coming. Let's go! Fuck!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, come on!
Fucking hell. Let's go.
We've got to get to that door.
Hold your fire, don't shoot!
Aníbal.
- What?
Give me your badge.
The engagemt plate?
- One, two... Now.
Take cover!
I love you.
Okay.
Tokio!
Tokio.
- You're under arrest. Stay still!
Río, Río.
- No, don't shoot!
- Get away from her, hands up!
- Río, down, down!
Shit!
Fucking shit!
We're leaving now!
Run, run, run!
- Lobo, Ruiz! How are you?
Ruiz, for fuck's sake! We evacuated Ruiz!
Río, Denver!
What?
Go get the Browning, see you in the vault.
Come on!
Formation and we'll go on, now!
Come on, let's go get 'em!
Yes, sir.
I'll pass it on.
CNI has taken over, it's Colonel Prieto.
- Ángel, how are you?
- Well, I've been better by Christmas to be honest.
- Hey, I'm curious, why did you call
Inspector Murillo as soon as you woke up?
- Because we're friends.
- Don't fuck with me.
Come on, tell me, why did she come to see you?
- He came because we're friends.
- She humiliated you like a shitbag
in front of the whole team
and almost killed your career and your life,
so stop breaking my balls
with the fucking friendship thing.
I'm going to repeat the question, Ángel.
Why did you call Inspector Murillo?
- Because she's my friend.
- You were in the hideout
of that guy, the Profesor,
I know you took a spoon out of his lair
and gave it to the scientist for analysis.
Tell us the address.
- I don't remember anything.
I don't remember a fucking shit.
- Yeah.
You know that any information
you withhold from us
will make you commit a cover-up crime,
you might end up sharing a cell
with the kidnappers
or with your friend.
Tell us the address.
- Prieto.
You really know how to treat
a guy who just came out of a coma.
No one's left behind, let's go!
All with masks!
They're inside. You have to take the Browning
to vault three.
- Denver is doing it.
What do we do with the hostages?
- Hand them over.
Everybody disorderly, on your back and knees, now!
Come on!
Well, not everyone.
Ariadna's coming with me.
Let's go, Helsinki!
They're in the museum.
Attention, hands up, where I can see them!
Everybody, hands up!
- Don't shoot, we're hostages!
- Everybody, masks, out!
They're hostages.
- They're hostages, get them out now!
- Prepare rescue protocol.
Hostages released.
- Suárez, we go on with the plan,
we go to the basement.
We have to get them out through the tunnel.
- You two, with them.
The rest of you, with me, to the basement!
Let's go, now!
We got Parker.
Get me the ambassador.
Have them count and identify the hostages.
- Colonel, we're advancing through the basement.
Open up.
What the fuck is that?
- Let TEDAX advance,
the basement is full of explosives.
- Bastards.
Can you deactivate it?
- Yes, but I need time, sir.
The detonator may be very close to the RDX,
there may be trapping wires.
- My men are detecting movement in the tunnel, sir.
- Reaching target.
They're on the other side of the wall.
- Five, five robbers.
No, wait, they' re six robbers.
- That's them.
- They're about to come out of t
he hole into the sewer.
- Underground agents, stand by,
they're on top of you.
- Received.
- We got you, motherfuckers.
- In six seconds.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
- Hold on, hold on.
Hang in there.
Don't shoot!
- Hands up!
Don't shoot, please don't shoot!
Turn that light off!
Don't shoot, I'm Arturo Román!
They're hostages, don't shoot!
- Confirmed, they're hostages.
- Fucking hell!
I may not always have known
how to understand women,
maybe because I'm egocentric.
But with you it's different,
I know perfectly well the way you feel.
I know that even if there was no money,
you'd come with me to the end of the world,
because you're completely in love, aren't you?
- Yes.
- That's why I want you to know that I love you too.
- Berlín, "presto"!
- And the little time remaining, it' s gonna be fireworks.
Wonderful little toy.
Wonderful little toy, Helsinki!
Nairobi, how's it going?
- The trench is in place,
only remains the last batch of money.
Helsinki, come on!
- Come, on.
Colonel, they've got another tunnel.
- What do you mean?
- They're taking the money to the vault.
We've seen it.
They've made a hole in the ground
and they get everything out there.
Come closer.
There are four vaults,
two on either side of the corridor,
would you tell me which one it is,
could you point it out on the map?
- Vault number three.
- Are you sure, Alison?
- Yes.
- Suárez, Suárez, do you receive me?
- I copy, sir.
- Change of plan, vault three,
top priority. Repeat, top priority,
they've got the tunnel there.
- Received, colonel.
To vault three, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Do you have any idea where that tunnel ends?
- They don't know it, but I do.
They're going to take the money to the hangar
from where the fucking Profesor speaks.
And they're thinking of escaping that way.
Have Inspector Murillo brought in now!
- Gómez, we need Inspector Murillo here now,
immediately.
Are you gonna go after your son when you get out?
- No, not yet.
I've run out of plan.
- We can share a flat.
- Helsinki
Let's go now, now!
- They're in the basement.
Come on, come on, get out now!
- And Denver?
They're on their way to the hangar.
I said get out.
That's an order.
- Berlín, let's go.
Berlín, they're coming down the stairs,
they're all over you.
Okay, heard.
You know where we are, go away.
- Let's go now or we won't go out anymore.
- Helsinki, take Nairobi. I resist.
- What do you mean?
- I said go out!
If they go into the tunnel, we're all dead.
What are you doing, Berlín?
- Someone has to stay
in the trench.
- No.
- Yeah, they're on our heels!
- Well, we're all leaving together!
- Nairobi
You and I agreed that I was
a male chauvinist, didn't we?
Well, women and faggots first.
- Let's go.
- I hate you.
- I hate you! I hate you!
Come on, come on.
I want each of you in your place, let's go.
Hey, hey.
Where are you going, honey?
We had agreed that you and I,
here, together until the end.
- No!
Berlín, please.
No, no. Let me out, let me out!
Fuck, let me out!
- Don't move!
- You bastard!
Motherfucker, motherfucker!
- You and I are the resistance.
It's a shame to see you.
Where's the hangar?
- I don't know.
- Not only does you know where the hangar is,
but you know perfectly well
I know you know, so let's save this part.
Big caliber, take cover!
We have to go back.
- No, Nairobi, no.
There's no time, let's go, come on.
Ariadna, charge!
Charge!
- Now!
Let's go!
This is a custody claim lawsuit.
And it was presented by the hero of the case,
the policeman who managed to identify
the brain of the operation.
Your ex-husband.
Hold on, hold on!
Charge!
- Now!
We're Romeo and Juliet, we're Bonnie and Clyde!
We are the lovers of Teruel!
He's applying for full custody of your daughter.
And the moment a judge finds you guilty
of any of the charges you are charged with,
it will automatically be granted.
And if your ex-husband is an abuser,
as you claim,
your daughter has a problem.
Charge!
- Now!
Son of a bitch, you son of a bitch,
you fucking bastard.
- Intelligence can drop all your charges.
And I'm Intelligence.
But don't ask me for more guarantees
than my word, because
the offer will disappear
if the kidnappers manage to escape.
And that can happen in a few minutes.
Come on, let's go!
So choose, or your daughter
or a guy you didn't know a week ago.
Lobo, we can't stop that machine gun,
that position must be lowered!
Grenade!
Charge!
- Now!
Take cover!
- Now, we're going!
Come on, move, jump!
Take cover!
You're here, you're here.
Where's Berlín?
- He has remained inside.
What do you mean, he's inside?
- We had the GEOS on top of us
and he has insisted on covering the tunnel.
- He saved our lives.
We're clear. Formation.
- Surprise!
You don't have much time left.
Raquel, not only are you going
to lose your daughter,
you' re gonna throw your whole life away.
Tell me that address.
Tell me that address!
- Alcántara, 33.
- Alcántara, 33!
I want everybody there!
Andrés?
Andrés.
- Profesor.
Right now you're catching me a little busy.
Get in the tunnel.
Negative!
Andrés, we're going to blow the tunnel,
you have to get out of there.
They're on me, it's late.
- Forward!
- Go now!
I'm not leaving here without you, you know that.
Charger.
Decadence is not meant for me.
Can you imagine me drooling or losing control
of my sphincters?
No, it takes courage to do that. I prefer this.
Come out, please.
- Sergio, don't screw me!
You promised me you wouldn't stay if things got ugly.
And they've gotten ugly.
Helsinki, blow the tunnel.
No, no.
Get down! Get down!
Helsinki, that's an order!
Soldier, blow the tunnel!
No, don't.
Helsinki, that's an order!
Soldier, blow the tunnel!
No, no, Helsinki, no!
I love you so much,
little brother, don't forget it.
- No, Profesor, no!
Don't do it, Helsinki! Andrés!
Ari, Ari.
Andrés, please!
I've spent my life being a little bit
of a son of a bitch,
but hey...
I think I want to die with dignity.
Fire, with everything!
Andrés.
Open up!
Fonollosa down.
Repeat, Fonollosa down.
Profesor, listen to me.
Let's keep going.
Colonel, units on their way to Alcántara, 33.
300 meters from target.
Change your clothes.
Entering Alcántara Street.
Colonel, reaching the target.
We're inside the hangar.
Let's comb the area.
Velero and Sanz on the left.
Rivero, with me.
Velero?
- Clear.
- Sanz?
- Rivero?
- Clear.
Confirmed, Colonel, there's no one here.
The hangar's empty.
Profesor.
Profesor!
Aah! Aah!
One year has passed since the assault on the
Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre.
The one considered as the biggest robbery
of history is still unresolved.
Just as the whereabouts
of the kidnappers are unknown,
that were made with a loot
of more than a billion euros.
Although, of course,
the forces of law and order
condemned the heist,
a large part of public opinion
continues to see in their
performance a legitimate act,
a form of protest
against the established order,
generating an intense
debate on social networks.
One of the most publicized cases
was that of the inspector in charge
those days, Raquel Murillo, who left the police
after some controversial statements
to the media in which
she showed her disagreement.
with crisis management
by the National Corps
of Intelligence.
Let's go,
you and I are going to a Caribbean country.
But are you crazy or what?
I can't imagine doing anything else.
Pick one.
Palawan.
If it's important,
you can use mine.