We know the ones in there were there before,
I want you to go over the recordings again.
from the security cameras.
- Get as close as you can.
There, stop it.
- It's a car key,
is a '92 Ibiza.
- Search scrapyards, car cemeteries and like.
The scientist has confirmed the presence
of ammonia and alcohol.
on the dashboard, upholstery, glass...
Someone related to the gang was there.
almost at the same time as us.
- I need you to step outside
for a few minutes.
There's a mole among us.
- And what are we going to do?
- Find it.
I broke the first rule of the plan,
I killed a hostage.
You've fucked everything up.
You're going to have to punish me,
because if you don't have the guts,
this isn't gonna work out.
They've managed to isolate a fingerprint
on the button you found on the Ibiza.
Andrés de Fonollosa, currently
in search and capture.
We could talk to his cellmate.
- He shared a cell with that man.
- He injected himself with medication,
every day.
Retroxil, is a rare medication,
ordered on demand.
Used to palliate tremors of
a degenerative disease,
in less than 24 months he will be dead.
- That man has nothing to lose.
If you really want to negotiate with me,
release eight hostages.
Look, I'll give you something,
I'll give you Alison Parker.
and no one else.
I have to consult it.
- I'll take the responsibility.
- Alison Parker.
"The profesor had ordered me
to filter the conversation
with the inspector."
Well? Alison Parker.
Would you rather save Alison Parker's life
than eight hostages?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm not a fucking Nazi,
I remind you that you got yourself
a cell phone in my panties,
that I was sent to kill you.
And what did you do?
You shot me in the leg,
you've got me locked up,
I can't even breathe.
I can't go to the bathroom,
I have to take care of myself.
in a bucket.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna take you to the bathroom,
okay?
I want you to leak everything
about this guy to the press.
- I don't think the public will
be won over
saying that the boss of the kidnappers
he's an eccentric,
he'll need something else.
- Andrés de Fonollosa is also
credited with
other crimes of a sexual nature.
Denver. My face keeps coming
out on the news.
And all for one button.
You just fucked up my life.
- I'll make it up to you with
10 or 15 million of mine, okay?
- Leave him, Berlín.
- What's going on here?
Denver?
Denver, is that you?
I sent you to kill her on a Friday.
And today is Sunday.
Resurrection Sunday.
Praise the Lord.
Excuse me, I'm going to let
you finish calmly.
I don't want to be the one
who disturbs your privacy.
I'm going to make a confession to you, Denver.
When I saw her lying there, dead,
something in me stirred.
Sometimes I rush.
This character of mine.
Of course, this is still
an awkward situation.
and we're gonna have to fix it,
but how?
On one side of the scale, Denver,
you've got the bad.
You disobeyed me.
I asked you to kill her,
because that woman jeopardized
the plan,
our plan. And you saved her.
Not to mention the button,
that because of your clumsiness
has put my face in the news,
airports, police stations...
And now you have definitely broken
my future.
And on the other side of the scale
you have that woman...
is alive.
And I ask myself: which side of the scale
Do you think it weights more?
- Don't fuck with me, Berlín,
this isn't a Tarantino film, huh?
Put the gun down.
- Nairobi, you put the gun down.
- What? I don't know.
- You put the gun down.
We're gonna fix this.
Put the gun down.
Who are you gonna blow off now,
huh, freak?
Let's all calm down and put down
all our weapons.
Berlín, Denver, everybody,
you too.
Tell it to your cousin, come on.
- I'm sick of your orders and your
little shitty speeches.
Shall I tell you which side of the scale
weights heavier, shall I tell you?
- Wait, Denver, take it easy.
I'll tell you, hold still.
- Careful.
- No, listen to me.
You know what weights the most.
Life, of course, Denver.
Yes, sir.
So for once, gentlemen,
we're going to lower our weapons,
because there are certain occasions...
that life is a miracle...
that's worth celebrating.
What are you doing?
Holy shit, she's alive.
She's alive, Tokio.
Look at her, Denver,
like those flowers that grow.
in the cracked asphalt.
- That's it.
- That's it, yeah.
That's it.
Berlín, I'm sorry to cut you off,
but you have to go upstairs,
the Profesor calls you.
Are you there?
Where were you?
Let's say a kind of spiritual journey.
And the truth is,
I'm back as a new man.
I'm glad.
Because there's something important
you need to know.
I put the button on your jacket
on the Seat Ibiza.
You killed a hostage, you crossed
the red line,
so this is your punishment.
It hurts to hear that,
it hurts horrors.
And frankly, I think it's a very
unfair measure.
You see, I want you to hear something.
What's your name?
My name is Mónica Gaztambide.
And how are you?
Good.
And you're alive.
I am alive.
And very pretty.
Thank you.
Now do you understand why you
are an unjust man?
You punish me for something that
hasn't happened yet.
I admire your cynicism, but I understand
if that woman is still alive,
it's not exactly thanks to you.
Unfortunately, there is no turning back.
The good news for everyone is
that thanks to this happy ending
we can implement the Valencia plan.
Gentlemen, the Valencia plan is activated.
Now.
Fire!
What's that?
- M-16 bursts.
Several guns firing at the same time.
- Listen up, there are people screaming.
I've spoken to scientist and ballistics,
I've sent them the recordings and
they say they have at least
three M-16s.
- How many bullets?
- Approximately 150, five or six magazines.
- It's a carnage.
- It's not an execution, it's a brawl.
Get me the factory.
What the fuck is going on out there,
what have you done?
Aren't you going to say good afternoon?
Good afternoon?
After you've leaked our conversations
to the press,
that you sold me out in front of
the public.
and after hearing that shooting in there.
But what kind of insane are you?
Inspector, really
I don't recognize you.
You are an intelligent woman,
we have conducted this negotiation
with mutual respect,
both professionally and personally.
I would even dare say that even with
a certain affection
on my part.
So if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna hang him and
we're gonna start over.
But what...?
Call.
Good afternoon, Profesor.
Good afternoon.
Look, I was here thinking about
my stuff.
and suddenly it occurred
to me to think:
what kind of music will this
man listen to
when you shower every morning?
It's going to sound strange,
but what gives me more energy...
is a Greek sirtaki.
I don't know,
it puts me in a good mood.
Funny, isn't it?
You are of Greek descent.
No, no, not really.
But I don't know, I love Anthony
Quinn's movies.
It's cheerful music, really.
Not as much as the shots we heard in there.
No, of course not.
Could you tell me exactly what it was?
Of course, with great pleasure.
You see, we've been testing
weapons that we thought had gotten wet,
but they work perfectly.
Thank you very much for asking.
You're welcome.
It's a very plausible explanation,
but there is another possibility,
that everything was twisted
and they had to open fire.
against the hostages.
Yes, that would be another possibility.
I imagine that in his hand is to
be more or less optimistic.
Then you won't mind me asking you for something.
Inspector, I'm so sorry,
but I dance very badly.
How?
The sirtaki,
if you ask me to dance with you,
I'm so sorry, but it's not gonna happen.
No, it's not that.
Look.
I want proof of every hostage's life,
recorded to this day,
in front of a live TV set.
And it's non-negotiable.
I wouldn't dare haggle
with something so sensitive, Inspector.
You have one hour to send them.
Yes?
Prepare the proofs of life.
There's no butler here to wash your hands.
You're gonna be the only one who's gonna get out,
we're staying here.
- Well
- So brave
What do you think?
Daddy's not here, huh?
- Look at us in the face.
- Look at us in the face
- I'm sure you've gained followers
with the tit thing.
- Hey.
- Quiet, eh.
- I don't like you.
- We're here because of you.
- Nobody will save you from here.
- Well, no problem, enjoy it.
- Don't touch me!
- Calm down, huh?
- Stop it! Stop it!
Hey!
That's what they teach you in pay schools,
to go all for one?
Pretty brave, isn't it?
All in a pack for the poor girl.
What are you?
The bravest, aren't you, athlete?
The one with the fattest eggs,
right?
Let's see it.
He's got them for quail,
he's got them for quail.
How do you make quail?
Let's see, how do you make quail?
- I just don't know much about birds.
- Well, how does the hen do it?
- Cocorocó.
- Higher.
- Cocoroco.
- Cocorocó. Very good.
Helsinki, take these children
and this one, the first.
- Come on, blondie, come in.
Come on, you too.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Are you all right?
- Can I have another one?
- No, honey, this is not an outlet.
Take it off and rub it.
I'm going to take advantage too.
That is more than 50 hours,
going up, going down,
Printing money...
And a shower is necessary.
Do you know what happens to you?
What happens to you
is that you don't know
the potential you have,
Isn't that right?
You had to do really bad
to be the class loser.
You can still be prom queen, huh?
It's not that hard, it's like
in American movies.
where the loser gets her glasses off
and suddenly... Boom, he's a hot chick.
- No, I don't wear glasses.
- Honey, I know you're not wearing glasses.
But I don't know, you'll know something,
won't you?
- Dancing.
- Well, all right. And what do you dance,
what do you know how to dance?
- Classic and contemporary.
- Oh, yeah.
Another little thing,
something else you know how to do.
- Hunting.
- Hunting?
With weapons?
Don't tell me.
Fuck, with the goody-goody.
Well, that's scary enough,
because what you have to do
is for these suckers to see what
you're capable of,
is to show them you're not afraid.
Oh, look.
You have to wait patiently for your
moment to come.
You put yourself in the spotlight
and do something that says...
"My name is Alison Parker
and I'm the fucking boss."
Boom.
You say it, repeat it. Look at yourself
and repeat it, say it, say it.
Say it, come on.
- I'm Alison Parker and I'm the fucking boss.
- No, but good, really say it.
Really, look into your eyes,
Look at the superfemale you are.
Repeat it.
- I'm Alison Parker and I'm the fucking boss.
- You're what?
- The fucking boss.
- The fucking boss!
- You're what?
- Boom!
Have they sent anything yet?
Sorry, I'm going to make a personal call,
Can you turn down the audio?
And don't record it, okay?
Yes? Hello, Salva,
this is Raquel.
Hi, there.
Excuse me,
did I catch you at a weird time?
No, no, absurd rather, is that I was doing
some sport on the mobile bank.
Mobile bench?
Well, yes,
a device to make...
Well, it's for gymnastics.
Well, it didn't take long.
I just wanted to ask
if you have already chosen a place
to go for dinner tonight.
Well, honestly, not yet,
you'll see,
every time I read a restaurant review
on the internet.
I feel like seeing us in the same place
as always,
in the Hanoi.
Well, that's fine with me.
And we leave the experiments
for another day.
Does 9:00 sound good,
for example?
Nine o'clock, for example,
is very good.
All right.
- Raquel.
I have important information
about the retroxil.
- Listen to me, all of you,
I want you to get out of the tent again.
it'll only be five minutes.
- Hey, don't you think you're a
little paranoid?
- I have to remind you that we have a mole?
- He doesn't have to be a cop,
a lot of people pass through this tent.
I don't know, the SAMUR,
Civil Protection, the municipal...
Even your cafeteria friend has been here.
- Okay.
What do you got?
- Like I told you,
retroxil is a medicine
used for Parkinson's,
they are experimenting with it
in some muscular dystrophies,
such as Helmer's myopathy.
It is administered intravenously.
As it is necessary to ask for it by order,
they have all patients very localized.
- Yeah. And I guess the pharmacies
will always make the same order
for the same sick people, right?
- Exactly.
But in Toledo there has been an
unusual demand,
in the last five months, look,
the distributor has sent
medicines to treat 40 patients.
- And there aren't 40 sick people
in Toledo.
- No, there are three in all
Castilla-La Mancha.
- Where are these pharmacies?
- They are all in... Around Illescas,
about 35 km.
- And where was the last purchase made?
- Look, here, in Palomeque,
on October 18th.
- Just three days before entering
the factory.
- They bought ten boxes of medicine.
- Get me permission from Judge Andrade.
and go to that pharmacy by yourself.
I want you to get
with all the shopping records.
And I don't know,
see if you can find anything.
Please don't discuss this with anyone.
- Absolutely.
By the way, Raquel.
You see...
I don't want you to think that because
of what I told you yesterday.
I'm having a bad time with Mari Carmen.
In fact, this very morning...
Well, we've made love.
Yes.
- That's good, isn't it?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- You can all come in now.
Arturito, I have a good surprise for you.
Look, I want you to know that I...
I respect any option.
I even have a homosexual brother,
he lives in Sitges and...
Well, he hasn't openly
acknowledged it yet,
but the whole family thinks he is.
He does pilates and...
It's actually a door I'd rather not open.
If I'm being honest with you.
What door are you talking about?
Don't understand.
This is the good surprise
I'm telling you about.
We talked about door another day.
- Helsinki, let them,
they'll have to talk.
I thought they killed you.
I swear to you that I sensed it,
that I would see you again.
And that's what gave me the strength.
Even in the moments when I was debating
between life and death you were there,
you never left.
This has never happened to me.
I swear I'm gonna get you out of here.
It is coming, isn't it?
Give me the girl's.
- My name is Ariadna Cascales and I feel fine,
physically and mentally.
The treatment received
by the kidnappers is good.
and I have no objection.
- The newsreel next
to the hostage is today's.
- A kiss for my family.
- So what's the problem?
- IT have analyzed the video,
it looks like they used a program to edit it.
- Are you saying that in 40 minutes
they've had time
to put special effects on it?
- We think they've superimposed
the images from the newsreel
over old images.
The quality of the video
doesn't allow us to give it as
real proof of life.
They've lowered the quality to 240
and they've done it on purpose,
is a bad symptom.
- Shots fired at the factory are front page
in all the news
of the country, press demands at least one note.
And presidency order us enter.
- I need time.
- And me, a face-lifting,
but they want us to go in now.
- Give me two hours.
If in two hours I haven't gotten
those proofs of life,
we're going in.
- All right.
Manipulating that evidence
wasn't very clever,
I'd say he's been rather foolish.
Please, Inspector,
we can't reduce our relationship
to these dry and disqualifying messages
without a "how are you?,
how was your day?"
You're only going for what interests you,
don't tell me you're like that.
Look, frankly, I don't have time for nonsense.
Well, by the 15 seconds it takes,
our lives aren't going to change.
Tell me,
let's say you know someone
and you sleep with him.,
Are you the kind that wakes up
in the middle of the night
and escapes without even knowing his name?
Do these things fill you up?
Well, look, I'd really love to do that.
Yes, but I'm programmed to do other things first,
like, I don't know, chat, laugh,
tell my life,
drinking coffee, going for a walk,
going to the cinema, dancing...
Without that order of things the truth
is that I don't see myself
going to bed with no one.
Call me old fashioned, if you like.
No, I won't.
The truth is that I, too,
share that same order of priorities,
but I would add one more:
go to a karaoke.
Call me weird, but I can't help it,
I like them a lot, I love them.
But I don't want to keep you any longer.
Tell me.
It's very simple,
these proofs of life have no value,
so we have no choice but going in.
And we can do it to watch quietly
or to free those people with gas
and all the artillery.
Wait a minute,
let me get this straight.
You're asking me to let you in.
You choose: or I send you the tanks
or we'll have a coffee
you and I and show me
all hostages alive.
I will be delighted to receive you.
I don't know if we'll get to karaoke,
but I can't refuse.
Raquel, Raquel,
I'm not gonna let you in there.
- I give the orders here, not you.
- Good.
- Ángel.
I'm sorry.
Look, right now I think there's
more work out there
than in here.
Besides, you're the only person I can trust.
All right, gentlemen, ladies.
We're going in.
Raise your hands.
Proceed.
The legs.
Where is the Profesor?
- He asks me to excuse him,
but for reasons of discretion,
he cannot be present.
Think that his face isn't
on all the covers yet,
like ours.
No weapons.
Río, you're up, do the honors.
Excuse me, we must be meticulous.
Raquel...
I know they say the police aren't stupid,
but sometimes it does.
Did you really think
that you could pass with a wire?
- And you believed that my people
wasn't going to take care of my safety?
- Tokio, search the inspector again,
but this time put a little more
of that enthusiasm you know.
He just surprise me,
the police with the latest technology,
the perianal microphone.
Get rid of this.
Are you finished?
Come with me, if you would be so kind.
"At that moment Río was paralyzed.
Lightning, that's what his mother
used to call him as a child,
when he spent his summer
afternoons running.
He said he was going to be an Olympic champion,
but he traded the sport for the consoles
and outdoor plans for the risk
to end up in a prison."
Judge Andrade, this is Deputy
Inspector Rubio,
of the hostage situation
at the Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
Look, I'm calling you because we need
a search and seizure order for a pharmacy in Toledo.
Yes.
Yeah, we're on the trail
of one of the muggers.
All right.
Okay. Look, we get
the feeling that someone
is passing information
to them from outside
and I would ask for absolute discretion,
please.
Okay. Okay, all right,
thank you very much.
Goodbye, goodbye.
If you're looking for Raquel,
she's not here.
Eh... No, no, the truth is that
I was just coming for a drink.
"In this way, the police fence narrows
about the band of muggers who last Friday
assaulted the Fábrica Nacional..."
Forgive me,
How's the kidnapping thing going?
Because I've heard
that there's been gunfire and it
looks like it's getting
a bit long, isn't it?
No, no, it's about to end.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, well, I'm glad,
I am very happy because...
Oh, my God, I can imagine how much
they are suffering,
those poor people, the hostages I mean.
Not to mention you.
Do you work near here?
Yes, yes, right next door.
Ah, as Raquel told me she was unemployed...
It's just that a few months ago
I lost my job
and then now I'm trying to raise
my own company.
I see
Well, it's a small company.
You are an entrepreneur.
Yes, it is.
And what is the company about?
Cider.
What do you say?
Organic cider.
My mother was from Oviedo.
It can't be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I make it myself in a workshop
I have there.
Instead of sucking on milk,
I sucked on cider.
Well, yes, my grandfather had an apple field,
a small field. And well,
I've got into it.
And you have the workshop nearby?
Yes, very close.
I'd love to try it.
Of course, that's done.
Look, one day I'll bring you a bottle.
Oh, thank you.
The Profesor told me he asked for coffee.
I've brought it decaffeinated,
so you don't stay awake..
Let's start with the proofs of life.
Proceed!
To open our mouths here we have
Arturo Román,
director of the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre.
- Are you going to bring me the hostages
one at a time?
- That's it, so you don't get confused
about keeping score.
Arturo, this lady is Raquel Murillo,
the inspector who ordered you shot.
But don't be scared,
we've thoroughly searched her
and is unarmed.
Please be gentle with him,
Arturo is really a very sensitive man
and he's been a little traumatized.
- How are you, Arturo?
I've had better days.
I want to apologize on behalf of the police
and my own, of course.
It was an unforgivable mistake
and I hope you get better soon.
Good.
You can go on to the next one.
- No, don't be impatient, please.
On top of that, we have the deference
that they can be interviewed,
everyone.
- I'm sorry, but I can't lose all day here.
- It's a shame,
I was starting to get my hopes up.
I have scissors.
How?
I took it because I was afraid,
but with it I'm in danger.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing? Hide that,
you're going to put us all
in a good mess.
No, I don't want it,
I'm going to throw it right here.
Put it away.
I don't want it. Please.
Give it to me, give it to me.
Arturito,
Walk with me.
What were those gunshots?
Please
They're going to kill us al
One by one
"One at a time, all the hostages would go
in front of the inspector."
Would you rate the treatment you
received as good?
- I can't complain.
"As the children pass by to see
the Three Wise Men
in a shopping mall."
Have you been able to sleep?
- I was able to rest.
This one reminds me of my aunt.
She's dead, though.
Have you had your coffee?
I like this one that's coming,
it's super quiet.
Don't even think about saying anything
about the gunshot, okay?
- Mónica?
Yes.
Are you all right?
Well, I'm a little dizzy.
Because I'm pregnant.
Excuse the question,
but were you the one who asked
an abortion pill?
Yes.
It was me, yes,
but I changed my mind.
I don't know if I'm going
to get out of here and...
And if I go out, I don't know if I'll be able
to take care of that child,
but I'd like to move
on with my pregnancy.
It will be.
No matter how hard things get,
children always get ahead,
the problem comes
when we get older.
- If there's one thing I know, Inspector,
it's about women and children,
so don't worry, mom's gonna be well
taken care of.
Pass the next one, please.
Mónica, are you all right?
You've been taken in front of
the inspector too?
What did they tell you?
Well, if I was fine,
that if I rested well.
And they have asked me
To not say anything about the wound.
They are looking for proof of life.
Luckily, we're all fine Arturo.
No, fortunately not,
the opposite, if the proof of life fails,
they'd realize something's not working.
They would enter,
they would have no choice but to enter.
Listen to me, Alison.
Only you can get us out of here.
You have to disappear.
as long as the proof of life lasts.
There is a well hidden safe.
No.
All you have to do is get inside
and lock yourself inside,
there is a numerical sequence.
But I can't do that.
You're their safe-conduct. If you don't
show up on the proof of life,
they'll have no choice but to come after you,
they have no choice.
You have to, it's very simple.
29175232, can you do it?
29137...
29175.
2917...
5.
29175372.
29175232.
29137...
29175...
Arturo, leave her.
Leave it, don't you see
we don't stand a chance?
I have a shot in the leg, you...
Everything is going to be fine, listen to me.
I got some scissors.
Listen, if they attack you,
attack with it.
What are you saying, Arturo?
Listen to me.
No...
I was told your wound opened.
It's just that I tried not to limp
so they wouldn't notice
and I think I've dropped a stitch.
Is it all right with you
if we see it?
Okay.
Do you need her to undress?
How else can I be cured?
See those doubloons over there?
They were found in the stomach
of a Spanish sailor.
Mummified.
Apparently, the captain discovered
that he was stealing
part of the cargo they brought in
from the Indies.
He made him swallow all the coins
he had seized, one by one,
until he drowned.
- Imagine if we applied the same
punishment to you.
- We'd end up like a built-in wardrobe
With six doors.
You're very funny, Inspector.
- I didn't come here to make jokes, Fonollosa,
I still have four cops to see,
11 security members and three teenagers,
including Alison Parker.
- Please, you have to decompress,
don't be impatient.
Dessert always stays for the end.
- Yeah, but dessert's taking too long.
and I'm afraid my digestion
will be cut off.
I want to see Parker now.
- She's getting ready.
You know how teenagers are,
always so vain.
Deep down, I think it's that insecurity
that accompanies certain women
throughout their lives.
What about dogs?
Helsinki is taking them out of the cage.
Get up.
Happy faces, your boss has come
to see you.
Come on, upstairs.
"In that silence Inspector Murillo could hear
machines at full capacity making banknotes
and she realized we'd cheated on her,
that the shots had been faked
and that his visit to the museum
had only served
to give us two hours longer than if she'd
been outside.
we had won 16 million euros more.
The Profesor was right, in this heist.
the bloody time was gold."
In our first class I told you that somehow
we're not gonna steal,
we're not gonna steal anything from
other people, are we?
All right.
Well, I lied to you.
Because there is something we're
going to steal,
we're going to steal police time.
We're going to put crumbs in it,
they're going to sting and we're
going to lead them to dead ends.
And they won't be able to concentrate
on their main objective,
which is to get us all out of there.
And when we have their time
and their attention,
we just have to dilate it.
Stretch it, like a piece of gum.
While the machines are running
on a piece-rate basis.
They are not fools,
at some point they'll realize that
this is all a game,
which is nothing more than
a diversionary maneuver
to keep printing money.
Even so, they can do nothing,
because they're obligated
to solve the kidnapping
with zero victims.
"It seemed easy.
Maybe with another inspector in charge,
but Raquel was a woman in a man's world,
a single mother in the middle of the
divorce,
a girl who had endured her husband's
mistreatment.
And there, in front of Berlín,
she felt comfortable,
as a teacher in front of her rebellious
students.
He wasn't going to stand by with
her arms crossed
while he was teasing her."
I've given you approach stitches,
so you don't have to sew again.
Better.
What's the matter, you're a surgeon now, or what?
I mean... You've at least
washed your hands, haven't you?
Of course, Arturito.
To give you a slap
with the scent of your fucking mother.
I'm getting a little dizzy,
if I could go where I was before,
to rest and that...
Yes.
Listen to me, Alison,
this is non-negotiable.
I need you to do it,
I need you to do it for everyone.
Do you really want to keep being
the sack of shit
of your classmates?
What do you know?
What do I know?
I've seen them laugh at you,
how they murmur behind your back,
I've seen them.
I've seen how they treat you,
like a fucking loser.
And you can change everything,
today, now, it's in your hand.
You have the ability to change
your destiny,
but you have to follow my plan,
okay?
Your general condition is good, then.
- Yes, you could say that.
- Helsinki, please escort him to
his quarters.
- All right, I think I've already seen
all the hostages
except Alison Parker.
I understand it's her turn now, isn't it?
Or what?
Are you going to handcuff us?
Hey, please, ladies, peace.
It's a little early for mud and bikinis.
- Look, since I've been in here,
I've only heard you say stupid things.
I was expecting something more substantial
from a man who has left...
What, seven months to live?
- What is she talking about?
What the hell's going on?
He has Helmer's myopathy,
a degenerative disease
very aggressive, with a life expectancy
from 14 to 25 months.
Possibly his muscles have already
begun to tighten,
which translates into spasms,
hand tremors...
Haven't you noticed that it's getting
harder and harder to hold the gun?
I screwed up.
I thought there were no secrets between you,
that you were friends.
I want to see Alison Parker,
now.
- Can I go to the bathroom?
Please, it's urgent.
- Hurry.
Cóndor three, any movement?
- Main entrance clear, sir.
- All right.
Mr. Berlín.
May I have a word with you?
I wanted to tell you that I feel much better,
that I'm less nervous and I'd like to go down
with the rest of the hostages.
- You're not well here,
do you have a complaint?
- No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
That's why I might as well collaborate
on some of the tasks
you're handing out.
- Well, Ariadna,
What could you do to help?
- Anything, anything at all.
Cooking, ground chopping...
I think you are building
a tunnel or...
- Can you get a little closer?
To shatter with those hands would be a sin.
And besides, we already have people for that.
We also have people to print,
to move the coils...
Actually we have people for everything.
- Last night he took Silvia
and we heard the gunshots.
I can't stand it here anymore,
please, I need to get out.
- Everybody.
Anguish, stress, anxiety...
Me, for example, right now have the certainty
that I'm not getting out of here alive.
Me, at your age, also believed that
I could eat the world,
I wasn't going to look back on the bloody life
and that I would never regret anything.
But one day something stops you,
suddenly.
Yeah. And it's best that whatever
Suddenly stops you
Is that you've been kicked out of work
or your apartment repossessed,
and not the GEOS shooting.
What's going on is that I've already
been suddenly stop by a gunshot.
Specifically one straight to my boyfriend's heart.
Get out there and tell everyone.
That I don't feel anything anymore.
And they can come in for me,
shooting.
Units stand by for intervention, sir.
- What the fuck is taking so long?
- Waiting for instructions.
When Mussolini was losing World War Il.
and a huge black cloud prevented
him from thinking,
he realized that the only thing
that could lift his spirit
was sex.
He had a prostitute set up
in a room next to his office.
From time to time he went to see her
to give him back his joy.
- I can help you solve your problems.
- Do you think I could be with
a woman who came to me
against his will,
if I noticed her contempt for me,
is that it?
- I really want to.
Try me.
Try me, Mr. Berlín.
- I don't even know if
I want to be with you.
Because I've noticed you.
Why don't you dance a little
so I can see you?
Dance.
"For Ariadna, surrendering to the
kidnapper in command
was the most certain way to save
her life.
What she didn't know was that
she wasn't in danger yet.
and that it was as desperate
as the escape attempt
of Alison,
who had the holy ovaries of trying
to escape from Nairobi.
Maybe that's what gives you despair,
ovaries.
And the absolute determination to hold
on to life
like two fiery bitches."
You mother fucker!
Alison!
Ah, ah!
Hello, Salva.
You see, I was around here,
around the area, and...
Well, I saw you come in,
and I said, "Will it be Salva?"
And yes, it is you.
Do you mind if I come in?
Now?
Yes, now.
Sure, come in.
That's a hell of a bar you've got here,
isn't it?
I'm sorry to intrude,
but I can't wait to try
that cider you promised me.
Of course I do, man,
right now.
Thank you.
Cheers.
I told you I'm an amateur,
I'm not a professional...
No, it's not bad at all, man.
Well, a bit bitter.
Listen to me.
How's it going with Raquel?
Because you're dating, aren't you?
Well, let's see,
going out, going out, no, we are...
We've talked once and now
we have a date,
that's true, but...
I see.
And there is affinity between us,
especially on my part,
I consider Raquel a very charismatic woman.
But come on, we barely know each other.
If you're going to give her that juice,
you'd better perfect it..
Yeah, if you give her three glasses of that,
you will let go of her stomach.
It wouldn't be a very ideal date,
would it?
Sure, sure.
Well, thank you very much for the advice.
It must be because your apples
are drying out there.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
There's a lot of moisture in this place,
isn't there?
Silene, without that microphone
they can't know if I'm okay or not.
Assault units two and three prevented.
- Nine minutes.
In position.
I should put a stove in anyway.
Well, they can rot you.
You should find another place.
Look,
I have to get out of here to
avoid a massacre.
with or without proof of life,
you understand?
Have a seat.
Four minutes.
Do I speak fucking Chinese or what's going on?
Sit down.
Alison, Alison, Alison.
10 000 m2 is here, huh?
I don't know where the fuck it is.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'll call the Profesor,
keep looking for her.
Are you ready? Good.
Does it have the judge's signature?
Okay, fine,
I'll be right there.
Thank you.
You'll excuse me, duty calls.
What a pity.
Don't you want to take a bottle with you?
No, thank you.
No, I don't pay any attention to it.
After all, who calls a landline?
Yes.
Second floor, office 17, inside the safe.
Fuching child.
- No!
Alison, are you okay?
- Yes, yes.
- We didn't have much time,
if there's anything, tell me.
Weren't you in a hurry?
Well, get the fuck out.
Río, with me.
What's up, Pilar?
What, did you find something?
- Yes, there was a print.
- And?
- And the print doesn't match with the cops
that patrol it.
- What do you mean, it doesn't match,
Did you put it in a database?
- Yes, I have,
but there's no match,
that print is unrecorded
in Spain.
- I see.
Look, do me a favor.
Check it with the fingerprints on this spoon,
okay?
When you get the results, call me,
no matter what time it is.
- Done.
- Thank you.
- Where did that spoon come from?
- Hey, Alberto.
- Did you get the cutlery from
the kidnappers?
- No, it's from another source,
a hunch.
- You know we can't analyze anything
which is not sealed and documented
where it comes from.
- Yeah, but I'm asking this as a
personal favor.
- Fuck, you say nothing, Ángelito.
We found out more about the kidnapping
on TV than from you.
Don't worry, when we get the analysis,
we'll call you, okay?
- Thank you.
- What about Raquel?
Is she getting better?
- Yes, she's getting better, bit by bit.
Companions, after a severe reflection
I wanted to apologize for not being
completely honest with you.
The inspector was right.
I have a degenerative disease.
Pretty bastard.
And my days are numbered,
but it's not my intention
to make you sad.
And much less pity me.
After all, it's a disease.
which suffers one out
of every 100 000 people.
And that makes me someone special.
What I want is to invite you to celebrate.
Río.
We're all going to die.
That's why I drink.
Because we are alive.
And because the plan is going perfectly.
To life.
And for the plan.
Hannibal Cortés is the weakest
link in the chain.
That mic wasn't going to pass a search,
that's why I told the scientist to place a message
into it.
- And how do we know that kid saw the video?
Hello, son.
We've hired a very good lawyer
and I got you a collaboration act
with justice.
If Hannibal Cortés surrender,
it will mean
that our plan works.
We've also talked to the police
and they say that if you turn yourself in
and agree to help
to the investigation,
the judge will grant you
a favorable sentence,
you wouldn't spend a year in jail.
We're doing everything we can from here
so you can be okay when you
get out of there,
because you don't belong there, Lightning.
Think about it, please, Lightning.
Think about it,
you can still back up, honey.
Lightning, we're still in time.
Tell me, what is it?
- Are you coming to dinner?
- No, I don't think I'll make it to dinner,
I've got a business at a pharmacy.
- I'm waiting for you, I don't care.
- No, honey, it's not in Madrid,
is in Toledo, in a village,
in Palomeque.
I'll call you back.
- Help, please, we just got mugged.
- Don't worry, I'm a cop.
- He just wanted the records of
purchases without prescriptions,
accounting, inventories
and sales books as well.
"And as in chess, there are occasions
where, in order to win, you have to sacrifice
one of your pieces.
In this case, one of the most valuable,
our Trojan horse.
The Profesor had put Ángel in a
fucking situation
when he visited that pharmacy,
a situation that would
bring him down to hell."
Raquel, listen, there was a guy
in the pharmacy before me.
No, I don't know,
I don't know how that happened,
only you and I knew.
"And that's how it happened.
With great pain in his heart,
when Angelito
stuck his nose in the hangar,
the Profesor decided to sacrifice him."
until when are we going to keep calling
each other formally?
When you look at me
under the table.
Dirt!
Could you put your hand on the fire
by your deputy inspector?
Try to hide, because if I see you,
I'll shoot you in the head.
Do you know how they say in my village
two men make love?
Comb for the inside.
I am Aníbal Cortés,
what do you want?
- I want you to tell me the Profesor's name.
- I think it's time to have a friendly chat.
with Alison Parker.
The lives of 67 people are in your hands.
Suárez, put him the handcuffs
and get him out of here!
- She's crazy, put the handcuffs on me!
- Put the handcuffs on him.
and get him out of here!
You're a bitch, a selfish,
obsessive bitch.
You're a fucking bitch!
Turn on the light.
Stop!
And we're gonna go get them.