I'm looking for people
who don't have much to lose.
I don't want any names
or personal questions.
nor, of course,
personal relationships.
Tomorrow's the robbery,
that's why I want to give you something.
Now you know my real name.
Profesor. Miss Tokio?
What are we going to steal?
The Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre.
Now. Stop!
Have you seen where we are, Dad?
We are very big.
- We're small.
Do you know how to do something?
Have you submitted your résumé anywhere?
- The résumé for what,
to get you out of Alcalá Meco?
- Because I'm not very smart, son.
And neither are you.
But in this blow
the brain comes from another.
And if we're lucky and you
don't do the asshole much,
you'll come out with your life solved.
- Stop being an asshole.
Be very careful, because the moment
there's a drop of blood,
we'll stop being Robin Hoods.
to turn into bastards.
What has happened?
- Confirmed: 35 employees,
11 security guards
and 17 kids from the British College.
It's essential that the police have no idea
of what we're doing.
What do they want? Time.
Time is money. Lots of money.
Every hour we printed 8 million euros.
I'm pregnant and you stay so calm.
And what do you want me to do?
I've been having sterile relationships
with my wife for 20 years,
and now you come to tell me this.
We're locked up and we don't
know how long this can last.
Let's assign some chores
so they don't get depressed.
- It's 48 meters down to the collector.
Shifts will be three hours.
They're digging a tunnel and they've
got a lot of plastic explosives.
and gas cans.
Put that down.
I love you, Mónica. And I want you
to continue with your pregnancy.
I have a cell phone in my office,
in the coat. I'll go.
Sit down!
- Come out.
- A judge has taken away your
custody and now I'll take care of you.
- It was you who didn't want her
to come to my birthday.
- I have a gift for the girl,
I'm at the door.
- You have a restraining order, get out.
- Her ex-husband has rebuilt her life,
personally and professionally,
but some women don't always turn the page.
- Thank you for your sensitivity, Colonel.
- I also have a request.
I would like to go online
and delete a photo.
- You can record a message,
we will send it.
- A phone has been turned on.
- Hack it.
- I'm in.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- No, no, no!
- It has been disconnected.
- Rewind.
Duplicate pixels.
- We've got it.
- We have the identity
of another of the robbers.
- Where's your tape recorder?
But what... What the fuck are you from?
I'm not a journalist.
My name is Salvador Martín.
I know him, he comes every day.
- I got footage from in there.
I have the identity of one of you.
You missed a phone,
find it or we're screwed.
I got distracted and saw
that Alison was trying to erase
the fucking picture, that's it.
- Love isn't the same as a couple of shags.
Are you trying to leave me?
If someone lays a hand on him,
I swear to God
that the next shot will go against
Helsinki, against Berlín, against you.
Your love story has fucked up
your escape plan.
They've got you, and Río too.
The police know who you are.
You're on all the news.
I don't think abortion
is such a good idea.
- What are you doing, Denver?
What's going to happen to our authority
when she tells the others?
Kill her.
- She has collapsed, this is inhumane.
- They're gonna kill me,
and then they're gonna kill you.
You're already dead, anyway.
Fucking hell...
Fucking hell, man.
Come on, man, come on.
Get down on your knees. No...
Don't kill me.
Don't look at me.
Please don't. Don't look at my fucking face.
Don't look at my fucking face!
- Paula?
Paula, honey! Where are you?
Where have you been, Paula?
Paula, honey!
Paula...
"I don't live in Almazán anymore.
I live in Madrid."
"The bus down to the center is number 21."
"I have two daughters."
"The keys are in the entrance drawer."
"I live with Raquel."
"I have two daughters."
"Paula always gets away with it."
"Paula's father has a restraining order."
"Never let Paula go with her father."
Thank you.
Shut up, shut up.
Thank you. Shut up.
Tell them you killed me
and disposed of the body.
I'm hiding.
Where the fuck are you hiding?
In vault 2. I have the key and the fingerprint.
No one will enter.
Tell them you killed me.
There's not a fucking drop of blood, girl.
There's not a fucking drop of blood.
Shoot me here, come on.
Shoot me in the hand. Don't talk nonsense.
Fuck my life!
Shoot me in the shoulder.
The shoulder is very close to the lung.
I can't.
On the thigh, which bleeds a lot.
I've seen it.
They nailed an iron to my brother
and he was bleeding a lot. Let's go. Come on.
Bite my hand if you want.
What the hell was that?
Nairobi, all yours.
- What?
- What happened?
- Calm down! Fuck!
Calm down. A little bit of fortitude, pussy,
or else we won't get out alive.
We need to grow a pair
Two shots fired.
Do you lack aim or
do blondes make you nervous?
- If she grabs your knee
and begs you not to kill her,
is not easy.
Why didn't you kill her?
You're a fucking bastard.
You don't want to get blood on your hands,
but you stain mine.
- If you ever lay a hand on me again,
you're a dead man.
There's a coal quarry in the basement.
Throw her in.
Then you clean up the whole thing.
Yes, it is.
Profesor, the one-hour deadline
I gave you is over.
I need to know if you' re going to surrender.
What did you play as a child in the schoolyard?
Jumping rope, bounce, 'donkey'...
To the sissies, look. That's what I was good at.
Well, I used to play cops and crooks.
Does that sound familiar?
Some of us played cops and had to catch the others.
and when they caught you, they caught you,
but I don't remember a single child
in all that playground that surrendered
before he got caught.
Children in the schoolyard
don't play jail for 8 or 16 years.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
That is why I have consulted with my colleagues.
We voted, and you know what?
That we are enthusiasts.
In the end we have decided to go
for zero years in prison.
"Hi, I'm Raquel. I can't answer you right now.
If it is urgent, leave a message after the tone.
There are many people suffering.
What do you intend to do?
Take paper and pen.
I need a three-axle truck,
with a trailer for 18 tons,
two more tankers, with propane gas to escort him.
and the ship Malaika flying the flag
of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines.
That sound familiar?
It's the one that was seized nine months ago.
with 2800 kilos of cocaine.
They have him moored at the military port of Ferrol.
It's going to be hard to get
the green light for your requests;
for logistical, security reasons...
Imagine this:
a building collapses
and there are 67 people inside.
How many media do you think
would be given the green light to save
the lives of those innocents?
Inspector, let's be clear.
You only have two options.
One: punish us; two: save lives.
And I'm afraid the two can't go together.
"You have a new message."
- Mom, I just finished. I'm on my way.
"To return the call, press one."
I'll make you a promise.
If you give up punishing us,
I will deliver those 67 hostages
to you perfectly safe.
Once we get to international waters.
I assure you, it's not the first choice
I've come up with, I hate the sea,
the fish and the sand on the beach.
But life doesn't always leave
an easy escape route, does it?
I have a message from my daughter
this morning from this number.
I don't... I am the mother of Raquel Murillo.
And I can't locate her.
Excuse me, you don't have a cell phone charger?
Would you like to use mine?
Thank you.
Please, do you know where she is?
It's urgent.
Let's get that truck
and get them out of that mousetrap.
In open field we will have it easier.
We will prepare the vehicles with narcotic gas.
- They won't come out.
- How do you know?
They opened that vault,
but they didn't wanted the money.
They waited for the police.
They fired.
They dropped two casually open bags
scattering the bills down the street.
- And?
- They wanted to pretend to be cornered
to win two days of negotiation.
But they got in there deliberately.
With a Browning machine gun,
red overalls, masks and God knows.
- They activated the alarm two hours
after they got in there.
- When they had opened the vault.
They used the money as an alibi
for a common robbery,
but it wasn't casual.
- They entered when
- the ambassador's daughter was there.
- That's why that man
speaks without hesitation.
He's in control because he knows
that everything goes according to his plans.
- What better plan than to get out of there
with the 8 million from the vault?
- They are printing their own unmarked money.
It can't happen. I bring a call
for Inspector Murillo, for Raquel Murillo.
Good. It's urgent and it's personal.
It's urgent. Come in.
Thank you. Extend your arms.
Come with me.
There's a call coming into the repeater.
- Record it. Now.
- It's recording.
A civilian is approaching the control point,
he' s going with Almansa.
He's asking for the inspector,
a personal and urgent matter.
Excuse me, inspector,
but I've got your mother on the phone.
I guess she' d call you from my number. Sorry.
You see, I think there's something wrong
with your daughter.
Yes?
- Oh, dear.
- Mom, what's going on?
- Stop recording.
- Paula went to lunch with her father.
- What?
- She told me it would only be a while.
- Mom, what have you done?
- She's not back yet.
- Alberto has a restraining order.
He can only see Paula every 15 days
and can't get in the house.
- I know, dear.
- Stop recording, damn it!
- It can't be done.
- Then turn it down!
- Mom, mom.
How long have they been gone?
- Two hours, I think.
- Okay, wait for me there.
What a mess you' re having, huh?
Almansa, escort the gentleman, please.
"Hidden behind a metallic voice with
its cameras and its strategy
negotiating the heist,
the Profesor felt like a fish in the water.
With all the other things in life, he was a real alien.
As different as Clark Kent and Superman.
Maybe it was because he had spent
his childhood and youth
bedridden at the San Juan de Dios Hospital
in San Sebastián
talking only to veteran nurses
and reading books.
He was neither very normal nor very social.
Much less a seducer."
May I sit down?
Sure.
"So I loved to make him nervous."
Hey, you, when you don't plan a hit,
what do you do?
You mean in my spare time or something?
Are you going to dance or...?
No, I don't. I don't have the slightest
sense of rhythm.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Wife?
We said no personal information.
You're not a virgin?
I've had relationships.
Several.
They haven't been many and they haven't
lasted either, but I have.
Relationships... Well then...
Sporadic.
Sporadic, I don't mean prostitutes,
don't get me wrong.
Well, I don't know, maybe you're gay.
For God's sake... No.
No, it did not come to me.
I'm not in any closet or anything like that.
People find a lot of things sexy.
Dancing, muscles, blond hair,
the French accent...
You know what I think is sexy?
Intelligence.
The men who talk to you and you
can't help but admire them.
It doesn't matter if they are tall,
short, ugly, handsome...
It makes me so horny that they talk
to me about things I don't know...
Well, who has that particularity
is recorded in the dictionary,
is called sapiophile.
You know everything, huh?
Look, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna watch the launching.
One thing.
How did you come up with this hit?
It didn't occur to me.
And who came up with it?
Well, that sapiophile thing sounds to me
like fucking a 'sapo' (toad).
- It's here, isn't it?
- Yes, wait.
Careful, careful, careful.
- Why don't it go?
- I have blood on my finger.
This one doesn't have a delayed
opening like the other one.
No.
Okay. Let's go.
The shots you heard came from
a run-in with the police.
It's been provoked by a hostage
who didn't meet my standards.
and has tried to contact...
with this phone.
And I wonder...
If I have Miss Gaztambide's telephone,
whose will this be?
Does anyone know about this little music?
What happened?
What are you doing?
We've all heard the shots.
I asked you what the hell happened.
Not here.
We said no victims.
She had a phone.
What did you want me to do, spank her?
Scare her, not kill her. Cut her off an ear,
as in the movies.
- If she had given information
to the police of how many and where we are,
now you'd be the one with the shot.
But you'd keep your ear.
Who fired?
Denver.
Too much hot blood.
- The Profesor said we weren't going to spill blood,
those were the rules.
- Well, a change has just taken place
regarding hostage control.
Okay?
Don't be nervous, public opinion
is on our side and that's not going to change.
When they realize there's a hostage missing,
we won't be here anymore.
We'll be far away.
Does the Profesor know that? Huh?
Does the Profesor know that you've skipped
- the first fucking rule of the plan?
- Are you going to talk to me about rules?
You, who for shagging that idiot
almost shot a cop?
- You have to call the Profesor and tell him.
- Little boy.
You call him Río.
He doesn't take it.
You can't be alert and controlling
everything 24 hours a day.
You have to eat, sleep, visit the toilet.
That's why in here I'm in charge.
We'll only get out of here
if we're professionals.
What the hell's going on here?
You could be heard from the outside.
Berlín has had a hostage executed.
Who was it?
Your son.
"The thief is by definition
an incorrigible optimist.
He always thinks everything's
gonna be all right,
but the first to be aware of all
this was about was Moscú.
He was one of those men who went straight ahead,
who give you confidence,
take care of you and tell you bad jokes.
He gave me tenderness."
What are you listening to?
Musicote.
Do you know how music was invented?
- No.
- Well, on a train.
There was a father and his son,
whose name was Pachín.
And the boy was very worried that the train
was going to stop in his village or not.
Besides, the child was very tiresome.
And he was all, like,
"Did this will stop, Dad?"
"Yes, it will stop, Pachín". "Did this
will stop, Dad?" "Yes, it will stop, Pachín".
"Parapapá, parapachín...".
What about you and Denver?
Family and artistic couple in the raids?
Yes, like the Dúo Sacapuntas,
but in burglaries.
"That evening Moscú told me
how he had dragged his son
to that madness of hold-up."
My son wouldn't have to be here.
But when the Profesor
proposed the plan to me,
I dragged him along with me.
- Oh.
There.
- Give me a fucking hug.
Hey, you don't disgust the food
in the gaol too much, do you?
- What the fuck, these are gases.
- Gases, yes.
- And the saturated fats they feed you in there.
- Yeah.
- Give me a cigarette, come on.
- I've got it ready. Here.
- How about you? How's life?
- Well then. Here we are.
- What's the matter with you?
- What's going to happen to me?
- The thrill of seeing you, Dad.
- Stop breaking my balls.
This is the sixth time
you've come to pick me up
and you've never brought that face.
What the hell is going on?
- Well, I screwed up.
- What the hell did you do?
I had lost 800 pills.
From some Polaco,
a fucking dealer from Alcorcón.
Apparently she had been lifted from her car.
- And he has a boss.
The twisted son of a bitch.
And then they start to break your nostrils,
leaving you crippled...
Let it be seen forever
that you've lifted the drug
to whom you didn't have to.
Dad, the deadline is going to end
and I don't have the money.
I swear to God I don't have it,
they picked it up from the car,
I didn't sell it or anything.
I didn't even take it, Dad,
I feel very bad about drugs.
- The bastard says he doesn't
do drugs anymore.
Maybe it's just that he's gotten sick or nauseous.
But he's a good kid, you know?
And he's got a heart that big.
To get his meniscus broken
with a baseball bat, you said:
"I'll put him to print bills."
He has already done all the bad jobs for me:
fur shops, savings banks, wagons...
And now it's a big one.
And if I get it right, I'm gonna take my son to a country
where we don't even know how to pronounce the name.
No Polacks, no pending lawsuits,
a fresh start.
But with my mojito and my beach.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- What do you sorry?
Boy, can't you see the floor's scrubbed?
- It's just that I left my notes to study, Dad.
- You left your notes... Then get out now.
- Don't be annoying.
- You want to leave...
- Dad, I have to study
and I left my notes. I'm coming.
- Get out now, come on.
Come on, damn it. Come on, run.
- Oh, oh!
You stop.
For the last time, return to your position.
What are you going to do?
Shoot me?
And then who?
All of them?
Are you going to stay alone in this mousetrap?
Son.
Did you kill that woman?
- Oh, Dad.
- Not a thing.
- I can't breathe.
- Dad.
Dad, what's wrong? What's wrong?
Dad, is it a heart attack?
Are you having a heart attack?
Dad, no, no, no.
It's an anxiety attack.
Lie him down.
Lie him down. Lie him down.
Dad, dad, dad.
"Thrown on that floor full of blood,
Moscú knew there would be no caipirinhas.
Nor any country that they did
not know how to pronounce.
That he hadn't taken Denver there
to save him from anything,
but to sink him in a hole from
which he would only get out jailed.
Or with a shot in the chest."
This is going to take time,
but it's neither the first
nor the last time. Okay?
We're all tired, but we have
to keep one's composure.
- Attention, incoming signal.
Attention, everyone to your posts.
A signal has entered.
- It' s a cell phone.
It has been connected inside the factory.
- Whose number is it?
- From Mercedes Colmenar,
the professor at Brighton College.
- Get into the cameras on that phone.
- Accessing selfie camera.
- Black. It has been condemned.
- Then go to the main one.
- Blinded too. They are sending a video.
- Who's the recipient?
Come on
- I'm downloading it to the main screen.
- Hi, honey. How are you?
- It's being sent to the teacher's boyfriend.
And another a recipient.
- He's leaking it mainstream.
- Yes, it's an email from Onda Cero.
- They have let record a video and...
It's just to tell you we're okay.
- Yes, I'm seeing it.
- What... Nothing, I'm...
- Contact the editorial office of Onda Cero.
We must prevent the broadcast of the video.
- Honestly, the kids are taking it as a joke.
- All right.
- What was her name again?
- Mercedes Colmenar.
And you, Aitor, look,
I know I've spent many nights
marking exams and talking to you about...
I don't know, of fractious boys,
instead of us.
So I promise you, when I get out of here.
I'm not going to take work home.
And that I'm going to be more... You know.
Crazy stuff.
Like that one in Salamanca, remember?
Wait for me, okay?
This will be brief, you'll see.
"Denver's gunfire
had broken the fragile balance
of the hostages.
The Profesor had understood that
they were in a kidnapping
that left dead on the way.
And for all the efforts
Nairobi made to encourage
the gloomy atmosphere,
fear fell by its own weight.
And among them all,
a quiet man was chewing on his guilt.
Suspecting that the shots
had been fired at his pregnant lover."
The shots we've heard before,
have they hurt anyone?
Calm down, okay?
No one's been hurt. Okay?
We fired to dissuade an intervention.
That's all.
Thank you. Thank you.
- You have heard it.
No more thinking strange things
about those shots, okay?
Those men are thieves,
they're not from the Jihad
or anything like that.
Let's tell each other how we feel.
- I heard your name is Río.
I also heard from your buddies
that the police have a picture of you
because of me.
I wanted to apologize.
When I turned on my cell phone,
I didn't want to expose you or anything.
And I didn't realize
how dangerous it was for you either.
what nonsense it was to me.
The tit thing, I mean.
- Well, according to the tit, right?
- Well... Thank you.
But I already knew the risks
I took breaking in here to steal.
That's what this world has, isn't it?
You know if you get caught, you end up in jail.
Or worse yet, a bullet.
The playtime bell rang
and I didn't even know, hey.
Bring the rice.
Oh, Mom.
- I'm sorry, honey.
- Mommy.
We've been to the amusement park.
It's really cool.
- Sure, honey.
Mom, can you go upstairs a
nd leave the teddy in the room?
- Of course, daughter.
- Come on, little girl.
I just took her to the amusement park.
It was my birthday present.
- You've broken a restraining order.
Turn around and stand against the wall.
- Raquel, I'm her father.
You can't keep me away from Paula.
- You disobeyed a restraining order.
Turn around and stand against the wall.
- You've already fucked up my life.
Isn't that enough for you?
- I said put you...!
- What are you doing?
Is that so?
Are you going to point the gun at me?
- Hello?
Raquel, it's Salva.
I'm calling from the cafeteria.
It's an emergency, you took my cell phone.
Raquel?
Hi.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm a mess.
No, don't worry, really.
I don't think anyone called me.
Let's see. Look, not a sad wasap. See?
So no...
Excuse me, it's none of my business at all,
but is everything okay with your daughter?
I stole your cell phone,
I frisked you, I almost arrested you,
and you still care about me?
Let's see, you took the cell phone accidentally.
It's been the nervous moments and all.
And the frisking, well... Well, it was fun.
What do you want me to say, it was exciting.
"The recorder. Where's the recorder?"
And me with the arm here. I'm sorry.
Antonio was petrified.
But then he invited me to something.
So, we are even.
Everything's fine, thank you.
Okay.
Ah... Can I ask for your
mobile phone for a moment?
Are you serious?
- Sure. You won't frisk me again?
- No, no.
- You sure about that?
- Really.
Ángel, it's Raquel.
I'm here in the cafeteria.
Everything okay there?
Can I have time to eat a sandwich?
- They've opened several phones.
- How? I'm on my way.
- No, no, don't come.
- Vegetable.
- They have only sent a few videos
from the hostages to the relatives.
- Wine?
They've also been leaked by the media.
- Fucking hell.
Did you hack into the phones?
- Nothing. They've covered the cameras.
- Well, anything I'm here in the cafeteria.
Call me at this number.
- Yes, yes.
I left my cell phone in the tent.
- Okay.
Hey, do me a favor, eat something
other than a sandwich, okay?
Okay.
- Thank you.
- All right, then.
Everything all right?
Okay.
I'm glad to hear it.
In the end you worry about a lot of things
and we shouldn't give so much importance to things.
Nothing's really right.
Everything, everything's pretty bad.
Worse.
Fuckin' awful, I'd say.
Sorry, but no...
No, the urgency was that my ex-husband
had taken my daughter and...
Well, he's got a restraining order
for mistreatment.
Thank you.
Dad, dad.
How are you feeling?
- I'm cold.
- Cold?
- Yes.
- Get a blanket.
- Yes, I am going.
- And some sugar, whatever.
- Come on, move, get some sugar.
- I don't know what happened to me.
I guess I've been digging t
he tunnel all morning.
And I've only had one of
those fucking sandwiches.
- Now let's get some rest, Dad. Rest.
Do you know what's good for you now?
A good stew like those you like, huh?
With his chickpeas and his pork.
- That's it, the blanket, come on.
Right there. That's it, Moscú.
- Thank you.
- Look, four little corners has my bed
and four little angels who keep it for me.
- You just relax now, okay?
- What are you doing here, Dad?
Come on...
At four in the morning I wake up
and you're not in bed.
- Nothing, damn it, I couldn't sleep and
I went out to see the sky for a while.
- The sky.
It's a big sky, isn't it?
Where will all that end?
What's going on? What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Do you know why I left the mine?
- Of course I know.
Because of the shit that ate your lungs.
The "symphilis."
- Not syphilis.
- What's going on?
- You're so fucking brute.
Silicosis.
- I told you.
- But that's not why.
It's because I was claustrophobic.
- You?
- Yes.
I couldn't stand being stuck in that hole.
And then I went to burglary to get out of that hole.
And I ended up in the gaol.
Locked up, same as my whole fucking life.
- Are you all right, Dad? You look weird.
- Not weird.
I'm fucking great, here, in the country,
and outdoors.
I am not fit to be overwhelmed.
- But we're fucking great, Dad.
- Yeah.
- And we better be when we get out of here.
You know what I'm saying?
Fuck the Maserati and the gyms.
You know what we are going to do
with the millions?
We're going to buy an island.
So you can sleep naked in the middle
of the palm trees.
In a hut. A hut for you and another for me.
- Yes.
- No sleeping together like here,
that you snore a lot.
- What do you say? I don't snore, kid.
- Dad, you snore awfully, I said it.
- Snoring?
- You snore a lot.
- I don't snore.
- You sound like a trombone, Dad.
Put this in.
Let's go, huh?
Right there.
Let's let him rest.
You finish cleaning the bathroom.
And then you switch to Helsinki
to keep an eye on the hostages.
I've brought things to cure you.
Does it hurts a lot?
- A little bit.
We're gonna make that tourniquet right, okay?
Okay.
Let's see.
Aah!
I think it should be removed.
Yeah. Okay.
Can I help you?
Slowly.
Aah!
Come on, that's it, that's it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Aah!
Fucking hell.
Okay.
Ah... Okay, that's it, that's it.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
You guys don't have to talk
to the kidnappers at all.
Is that clear?
We have said that they are not of the Jihad,
but you have to understand
that they are under great stress.
Alison. Alison, please,
I'm talking about you.
I don't want you talking
to any kidnappers again.
Is that clear?
- I just wanted to apologize.
I think he's been booked because of me.
He was recorded on my cell phone.
Because I wanted to turn it on
to get on the Internet.
- You turned on your cell phone
to get on the Internet?
- I wanted to delete a photo...
- Will you shut up now?
- No, no, let's talk about it.
Now, tell me, what about that picture?
- One that Pablo made me.
She cheated on me and took a picture of me naked.
And he uploaded it to my profile.
- Pablo, what you have done to your partner
seems to me to be in very bad taste
and I think you should apologize to her.
in front of all your companions.
- I don't give a fuck about the picture.
I don't care. Are we crazy?
- We could be here or anywhere else.
What I'm not gonna allow is
any lack of respect, okay?
Neither between you nor with me.
So apologize to your partner.
- What?
- That you ask her for forgiveness.
- Was it gonna be a joke of what? Two seconds?
Until you deleted the photo?
But then they came and fucked it all up.
I'm sorry, Alison.
But it wasn't my idea alone, was it?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, girl.
It's out of our hands.
- I'm sorry.
- And I, dude, really.
- It's gotten out of hand, dude.
- I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
- I think we should take out the bullet.
No, no, no. No,
there are muscles, bones and everything.
Maybe we're gonna mess it up.
- I'm going to do it carefully.
How are you gonna get it out?
- Take out the bullet and...
You can't take it out with that.
- Better to take it out than leave it inside.
Not at all. Some people have bullets
and nothing happens.
I've seen it on TV.
And pieces of glass. It's all right.
Okay, okay, okay.
- We'll leave it.
We cover the bleeding and we see how you evolve, okay?
Yeah.
- Don't worry.
Okay, okay.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
That's it. That's it.
Okay.
This is like when we used to play
the operating bug when we were little...
Okay.
I brought antibiotics for a wedding.
Soothing, muscle relaxants... Everything.
Won't that be bad? Huh?
See if he's gonna have
contraindications or something.
Well, more contraindications
than a bullet I don't know, huh?
I was saying that about the baby.
It's true.
Okay, okay.
I read the leaflet and see what we do, huh?
Let's see.
"Read the entire package leaflet
before you start taking the medication.
Keep this leaflet,
since you may have to read it again.
If in doubt, consult your doctor or pharmacist.
This medicine has been prescribed to you..."
Okay.
- No.
Hey! Do you have any more noodles?
- Noodles, no. I've got rice left.
- It doesn't matter.
- Moscú
Moscú, what are you doing? Hey!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- Tokio, what's going on?
I don't know what's going on.
- Moscú!
- They're opening the doors.
- Attention, everyone.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- In position.
- Stop!
- Snipers.
- Alpha 1 in position.
- Alpha 2 in position.
- Alpha 3 in position.
Down on the ground!
Everybody down on the ground!
On the ground! Now!
- I've got a shot at him.
Three, two, one.
- Cover your face! Cover your face!
- Let me out.
- They're not wearing a mask.
- They are struggling.
- No.
- I have to go out.
- Record it.
- I don't see their faces.
- I've got to get out.
- Go out for what?
- Sir, I've got a shot at them.
- It's my fault.
You didn't have to kill anyone.
- I've got them in range, sir.
- Let me out of here.
- You wanted to get in
to take my rap.
- We don't know if the robbers...
- Let me out of here.
- I didn't kill her.
I'm hiding it.
- The doors are closing, sir.
Three seconds.
- Nobody shoot.
- Fucking hell!
- Let me out of here.
- Dad, we're going to go out into the open
so you can breathe fresh air.
- I need air.
I'm so sorry that you went through a...
For an experience like this...
Well, if you need any help that I can give you...
A phone always available,
a bodyguard with glasses...
I beg your pardon.
I shouldn't have joked about something like that.
I'm an asshole.
- Don't worry.
I beg your pardon.
I see you, and you don't fit me.
It's not what I imagine if I think of...
In what? In a battered woman?
Because I carry a gun, don't I?
Look,
the fact is, it doesn't start with a slap.
If so, no one would be with a violent man.
On the contrary, it is...
You are...
You fall in love with
a charming, intelligent man
that makes you feel
the center of the universe.
And when he asks you
to change your profile picture
and put your daughter's,
you find it tender.
And when he tells you not
to wear a miniskirt to work,
you think, "I'm a woman who works
in a man's world and
he's actually protecting me."
And then, one day, he raises his voice...
You don't have to tell me.
- Yeah, yeah.
I need to.
Look, it's like...
It's like descending steps slowly.
Like in those scary movies
where someone goes down to the basement
and everyone thinks,
"Don't go down there. Don't go down there.
But you go down.
And that's when he gave me the first slap.
And then the second and third...
And I finally got divorced.
You didn't denounce him?
No. He was a cop,
the most popular guy in the station
and I just wanted to let him out of my sight.
I guess I was embarrassed to sit in front of my boss
and recount to him a year
and a half of humiliations and blows.
I got a 9 mm HK in the pouch,
but I have no fucking idea
how to take care of myself.
Don't say that.
But the real drama came a few months later,
because my sister fell in love with him.
They began to go out, to travel and...
And then I denounced him,
late and with no evidence,
because I didn't want my sister
to be in that hell.
Do you understand?
But, of course, the only thing I got
was to look like a pathological jealous woman
making a false report.
And, 'Look, the Inspector doesn't report it in time.
and denounces it now that he' s with her sister'.
But, Raquel, the police or the judges
have to believe you,
it's impossible not to believe you.
Raquel, I've just felt the emotion and helplessness
of having someone to help you.
Somebody. Who's gonna help me?
- Me.
Forgive me, I don't know how I could help you,
but...
Thank you.
Raquel.
- Ángel.
- There's movement in the building.
They opened the door for a few seconds
and there's been a brawl.
We think with a hostage.
- Let's go.
He wasn't a hostage.
- Why would you say that?
- Because, unless they're Gandhi's disciples,
they would never let a hostage go this far
without shooting him in the back.
One of them wanted to surrender.
- Inspector Raquel Murillo?
- Now, I want you to know that this is not a threat,
but a favor I ask of you on a personal level,
not as a robber.
I want you to put on the masks, the hoods.
and go out on the roof without
doing any signs or nonsense.
Just 10 minutes, okay?
Get out, get some air and get in, okay?
What are you trying to do, entertain the police?
The police are already entertained,
so leave it alone and don't mess with my henhouse.
The bait. They want to use us as bait.
What's that? They send us to the lions
while they take advantage to go out the other side.
We'll go out for humanity,
because a colleague of ours needs to breathe,
and I'm not gonna tell you again.
- Don't move.
- But what fucking world do we live in?
No one's willing to do anything
for anyone anymore, right?
A partner has an anxiety attack
and you do nothing but think of the bait.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Nothing's going to happen
because I'm going out with you.
Why did he have an anxiety attack?
Because of the shots.
It was the shooting, wasn't it?
It was the shooting. Who did you kill?
Who did you kill?
Open your mouth, Arturo.
Open your fucking mouth, Arturo.
Open your mouth.
Now raise your left hand
if you're gonna keep breaking my balls.
If you're gonna keep your mouth shut,
raise your right hand.
Okay.
- Stop it, stop it.
Cut it out.
Stop doing the nerd, please.
Who was that?
- Interior.
That we accede to their requests or that we enter,
that this is going on too long.
It's on the news halfway around the world.
What's the guarantee of getting in there
and get everyone out alive?
- Ninety percent.
- If your daughter was there, would you come in?
- No, I'm not.
Look, they started all
this shooting from close range,
we can come in with gas or everything,
but that they raise their hands
and surrender is unlikely.
- I know.
I'm not going to give an order that endangers
the life of a child.
- I know.
- I'd need to go home
and take some antidepressants
and take care of mine,
but I'm not going to resign
if while I'm in command I avoid funerals.
Now, yes, Dad.
Get some air.
- You don't have to do this for me.
- I remember when Mom left,
it was hard for you to breathe,
that you went out on the balcony
to try to do it every night.
No matter who it is, you're going out there,
You're gonna get some air.
and when you're calm, we go in.
Everybody with the mask on and the hood.
Arturito, near me.
This is Cóndor 3 for command center.
Roof movement.
- Suárez, attentive snipers.
- They're a big group.
- All to position.
- Maximum attention, we have visual.
- They're advancing, they're advancing.
- Dad, calm down.
- Okay.
- Look what a fucking day it is.
- Yes.
- What a sun, huh?
You breathe and be calm.
- They're a big group.
They keep walking on the roof.
- They advance to the edge of the roof.
Yeah? What's going on?
Why are they on the roof?
- Moscú went out to breathe fresh air
flanked by hostages with fake weapons.
As you well know, I would never
have allowed this madness,
but right now my companions
are convincing me
that it's a good idea.
- I don't want any more improvisations.
Keep me informed of everything.
They're still walking. They are reaching
the edge of the building.
- If you don't start keeping a cool head,
forget the millions, the life in Acapulco
and the garden full of kids, because
you're going to fuck everything up.
There was only one thing you had
to do: be professionals.
- Doesn't this look professional to you?
Huh?
- Lovely.
- No, not precious.
A better fucking bill than
the one they give in the banks.
It can't even be traced. A work of art.
And you know why?
- Enlighten me, Nairobi.
- Because it's made with love.
I'm a professional.
What I don't know is what to do
when your father gets crazy
in the middle of this mess,
You're a thief before you're a son?
Huh, Berlín?
Before being human?
For a shit like you, maybe so,
but I don't know.
You didn't kill that girl, did you?
- No.
- Tell me the truth.
- No!
Berlín caught her with a cell phone,
ordered me to kill her and
I had to shoot her,
I couldn't do anything else.
- You're talking about Mónica.
You're talking about Mónica.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- What have you done with Mónica?
Go back to your place.
- This is not a courtesy call, Profesor.
If you want me not to withhold
information from you,
you should do the same with me.
Everyone has the right to stretch their legs.
Doesn't it seem supportive of me
to let the hostages come out to breathe?
I assure you, I have no intention
of torturing or frightening them.
I just want to give them back
to you safe and sound
as soon as you give me what I asked for,
nothing else.
Repeat, they're armed,
all under cover in the operation.
What the hell did you do with Mónica?
- Go back to your place.
- There's something wrong.
- Request instructions.
You fucking killed Mónica.
She was innocent.
This is Cóndor 1. Target viewer.
- Request green light.
- Get on your knees.
- What?
She was pregnant.
- Snipers, for fuck's sake.
Let them think we're hostages.
Hands on your head.
Don't play games with me, get up.
I'm talking to you, dammit.
Something's going on.
- They're crouching.
- They've been kneeling to execute them.
- There are snipers.
On your knees, there are snipers.
- Everybody down.
- This is Cóndor 3.
There's a Dalí pointing at another.
- I'm seeing it clearly.
- I request instructions, sir.
- I need authorization.
- They are still kneeling.
Waiting for instructions.
- Give me the green light.
- They're running.
- I'm shooting the kidnapper.
What the fuck are you doing?
- There are snipers, for fuck's sake.
Get on your knees.
- They're fucking pointing.
- Give me the green light.
- They're going to execute you.
They intend to shoot.
- They're going to kill them.
- Green light.
- Cóndor 3, open fire.
Target down, sir.
- White down.
White down.
We've got a visual.
- He's the factory manager, Arturo Román.
Hold your fire.
- Cóndor 3, cease fire.
- We've got a hostage down.
Aah!
Where the hell is she?
- The motherfucker escaped.
Good!
They had it all figured out
except this one shot
and we have to take advantage of it.
Are you ready?
- Yes, sir.
Come on in.
Do you like tequila?
Hearing. Active plan B.
Nobody's getting out of here.
They're coming in,
but I don't know which way.
You're two meters from the entrance.
- We're losing communication.
- Suárez.