We'll make a control call every six hours.
Third unanswered call, that's 18 hours
without news of the Profesor.
- He'll be tying up some loose ends.
- We're in a critical situation.
- No, in a critical situation
we'll be if the Profesor doesn't
call in six hours.
And then we would activate the Chernobyl Plan.
I need you to look for all the farms
with hunting grounds within a radius of 100 km
from Palomeque's pharmacy.
If they bought the medicines there,
They were very close.
- Inspector, we have the estate.
- We have to check this house,
every corner.
The whole damn plan,
schedules, photos, plans...
This doesn't make any sense.
Call Alberto.
- Your ex-husband?
- Isn't he the best of the CSI?
Well, let him come.
- Hello, Raquel.
- This is Salva, my current partner.
Salvador Martin. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
None of this is worth a shit.
Ángel went further than you
with the fingerprints he found.
- What fingerprints?
- Got a spoon, found someone in the band.
Or at least, it was very close.
The Profesor has been arrested.
But if he's being questioned at the
door of Toledo's house.
They've got the Profesor.
There's not going to be any tunnel
in the hangar, because the GEOS are
gonna be waiting for us.
Who still believes in the Profesor?
- I believe in the Profesor.
- I believe in what I see.
- I still trust the Profesor.
- I vote to get out of here now.
- I have a very good reason to be with the profesor,
I'm with Berlín.
Are you sure you want to do that?
That was your father, that's what matters.
And we're gonna do it for him.
- If there's anything useful here,
I know where it might be.
- Whatever they really wanted to erase,
they'll have burned there,
is the safest way to destroy something.
And that's what we'd all do.
Raquel, sorry...
I'm going to take this to Canillas.
Ah, look, I was just going to Madrid,
I was going to catch the bus.
I'm a little scrambled.
Do you want me to stop?
If you don't mind, I'd really appreciate it.
I was thinking about what you said before,
that you want the best for Raquel.
If it were true,
you wouldn't be fucking his sister.
Rubbish.
Get out of the car.
You're under arrest for assault on authority.
Listen to me, I need to ask you a favor.
When the action starts, you have to turn yourself in.
When things get complicated, I'll be with you
to an open grave.
Give me the gun.
Tell us what the Chernobyl Plan is.
I'm the only one here who knows the plan,
you're not gonna have a fucking clue
how to get out of this mousetrap.
What are you gonna do to me?
Son of a bitch, I hate you.
Why should this be the end of something?
Couldn't it be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship?
No!
Attention, she looks like a hostage.
Waiting for orders, sir.
- We're going down.
- Looks like one of the muggers.
- I heard.
Who is she?, I can't see her face
- It's Oliveira, sir.
We got her, sir.
- Why the hell did they
give up one of their own?
I want everyone within 20 yards,
she can carry explosives.
- On the ground! Perimeter, perimeter!
- Explosion-proof protocol.
Repeat, anti-explosive protocol.
It may be a trap.
- On the ground! On the ground!
Perimeter of a possible bomb!
- Take off the clothes.
- Okay. Take off your boots and clothes.
Take off your boots and clothes!
Come on, let's go!
Take off your boots and clothes! Now!
The shirt, lift up the shirt!
- Reduce her.
- Get on the ground. Get on the ground!
Hands up.
Put your hands up.
Aah! Aah!
- Don't shoot. Repeat, do not fire.
Nobody touch that woman, I want her alive.
Tokio.
Tokio!
Freeze, freeze!
Fucking hell!
The risks are three: getting killed,
getting hurt,
to get caught. Today we're going to talk
about the third one.
Tokio, any idea what to do if you get caught?
A kick in the balls?
You must always have in mind what
the goal of this robbery is.
Win...
Time
Win time. And indeed, you must exhaust
every possible way to get it.
Oh, my stomach. Let's go.
I can't breathe.
You guys fucked me up, for fuck's sake.
Sir, the detainee says she's in severe pain,
says he can't breathe.
I seek medical assistance.
- All right, take her to a doctor.
- Acknowledged. Let's go.
It hurts. Carefully.
It hurts, it hurts. Oh, it hurts so much.
A little further back.
Holy shit.
You lied to us.
Are you telling us that no personal relationships
and Berlín calls you by your name?
Sergio?
Because that's your name, isn't it?
Tokio, maybe tomorrow, daylight,
we'll see things...
Tomorrow I'm not going to see anything.
I got into this because I trusted you,
because you were gonna be our guardian angel.
And guardian angels don't lie.
My name is Sergio.
Sergio Marquina.
My father was a robber.
He was killed in a shootout with the police
at the doors of a bank, it was he
who came up with the idea of the robbery.
Tokio, of all the ones who are about to enter,
you're the one with the hottest blood.
And there's gonna be a time when you think
everything's falling apart,
that it's all going wrong,
that you're all alone.
But I promise you that's not gonna happen.
I've got it all figured out.
And besides, I'm a lucky man.
You are a lucky guy
Tokio, I won't let you down.
I want you to remember it forever.
"The worst thing that can happen to you
when you run a robbery is:
First, get arrested for knocking out
the ex-husband of the inspector in charge."
Take his fingerprints and lock him up.
"Second, have them ask for your ID"
Your ID?
"And you can only give them a fake one.
Third, get your fingerprints taken.
And if, in addition, they match the ones that appeared
in a car that's part of the investigation, worse."
Take the tray and empty the pockets.
"Fourth, have them ask for your belongings.
Especially when these are the keys to the hangar.
where you have mounted the operation and
where they are going to escape
the thieves. And a bottle of poison..."
It's a medicine for a heart condition.
Digoxin is called.
"...with which you were going to kill
the inspector's mother...
a few hours ago."
Come with me.
Sit here until your statement is taken.
- Rafa.
"A few minutes ago the kidnappers
have literally thrown on a stretcher
a person bound and gagged,
that has been rescued by the troops
of Special Intervention.
This is Silene Oliveira,
one of the kidnappers
that remained locked in the factory,
and that she's being cared for by
the medical services.
that are in the security perimeter."
"Fifth, let your companions lose their heads."
Tokio lost its head.
She couldn't take it.
And it's not easy.
But I had no choice but to give her.
Take your hands.
Please.
We're here risking our lives.
It doesn't take so much courage
to take your hands.
When a wound occurs, the platelets join together
to close it.
If they don't, the body finally dies.
There's been a wound and we need to unite.
- What the fuck are you talking about platelets?
- Río.
- What do you think, a preacher?
The leader of a cult?
Are you all going to travel
hand in hand into space with him?
- Río, you need to calm down. Now.
- I'm not reassured, you've sent Tokio to jail.
Don't have the guts to ask me to calm down,
she's my girlfriend, my girlfriend.
And you fucked up her life.
- It's the first love.
You're at the end of the summer
and you say goodbye to Susan
on the Côte d'Azur.
It looks like the end of the world,
but it's not.
- Shut the fuck up,
you fucking psychopath.
You have no fucking idea
of what you're saying, okay?
Is there anyone here who isn't crazy?
Moscú
Are you okay with Tokio?
- Son, he lost his papers.
We all saw it.
- Nairobi
- Here are some rules. We voted, she didn't accept it
and then his head went off.
- Denver.
You do see what a piece of shit this is, don't you?
- Of course I see it, man.
But he did the fucking Russian roulette to Berlín,
what do you think?
- Nothing fucking happened.
- But almost, we've been this close.
Wise up, kid, open your eyes.
Tokio lost her mind. We can't have a bomb
in here.
- I can't believe it.
You're all with Berlín, you're all
with a fucking psychopath.
- No, no, we're not all with Berlín,
we're all with the Profesor.
- With the Profesor? He is under arrest.
We've all seen it on TV.
He's not gonna call, he's not gonna be waiting for us
at the end of the tunnel.
Now you're gonna start with the two hours left.
for the control call, right?
Awesome.
Because it's the last one.
Let's see what the fuck you do
when he doesn't call.
I'm certainly not staying here to see it.
Hostages are gone, Tokio is gone.
I guess you don't care if I leave
too, do you?
- You know it doesn't matter, Río.
But it's your decision and we
respect it. Go ahead.
There you stay.
Well, someone come and close the door.
- Wait.
When you get out, take this and lift it.
Let them see that you come out in peace.
There are snipers, I don't want anything
to happen to you, take it.
Give me a hug.
I want it to go well for you
I want you to never stop believing
in love, it's beautiful.
Trust, trust, trust.
Hey, you have to empty your mind
so you can think clearly.
Trust, do it, let go.
Let go, that's it, that's it.
- You need to get some rest and that's it.
"Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín.
Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín.
Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín. Kill Berlín.
That was the only phrase that sounded in my head,
but there was no way,
no matter how much I thought,
I couldn't find a way to destroy Berlín's life
without taking Río's too.
I could tell how we were going to get out,
where the hangar was,
but those vengeances would also fall on Río,
my little Río. And I remembered
everything I had fought for
so my love would be in there."
I think we can finish today's class here.
I'm hungry, aren't I?
Río.
Remember I told you we had to do
a facility?
Yes.
Well, the time has come.
Fucking hell.
That's some bachelor flat, huh, Profesor?
Are you bringing the girls here or what?
Let's get to work, come on, we've got a lot to do.
Fuck, Profesor, who did this botched job?
Eh... A company.
My balls a company, this smells
like brother-in-law
playing the handyman.
Well, I did it
with some tutorials I found on the Internet.
Well, that's some shitty tutorials, isn't it?
That's what you're for, isn't it?
That's it, I've installed the voice
modification program.
To talk to the police, you press MS.
To contact the museum, zero.
And that's it,
the modification is made by the program
as soon as you contact anyone.
Can I try it?
Yes.
"Talk to the robber."
Can you put on a voice that's not
a woman's voice?
Oh, I'm sorry.
"Bitch. Bastard. Faggot."
Okay, fuck, okay, okay.
Try it now.
You talk to the robber in command.
Okay, that's good.
Now we have to enter the illegal internet network.
To buy some illegal stuff.
On the deep web.
Deep Internet.
Can you explain to me what we're doing now?
I've deactivated all defenses, the wifi,
and we're entering
over Ethernet. I'm diverting data traffic
through a VPN through the Tor network.
Well, then...
Keep going.
That's it.
There's everything: there's rifles,
there's grenades,
there are rocket launchers...
This is like an outlet,
but with the arsenal of the USSR.
Look, a tank,
we could go into the factory with it
as the A-Team,
all with rifles...
Do you know what a Browning is?
Oh, yes, of course.
Okay, let's buy a Browning, assault rifles,
guns and ammunition.
A V-750 missile, dude.
That's amazing. Imagine messing with that
at the factory.
Open the doors and bam!
V-750 missile pointing directly at the faces
of all police officers.
And bam! Fuck it all.
He'd be gorgeous, dude.
Besides, look, it's not that expensive,
60 bitcoins.
It is... 150 000 euros or something like that
at the exchange rate.
Cheap.
Why did you take Río out of the plan?
Tell me.
I don't have to explain myself to you, but...
I don't think he was ready.
You're wrong.
Are you sure about that?
You've been working with him for months.
You know him and you know that his personality
is marked by deep immaturity.
He's not aware of what we're going to do,
out there the bullets are real, no extra lives.
He knows perfectly well what he's doing.
It is my responsibility
and I'm not putting a kid in all this.
I'll pay you a portion for the upheavals,
but I'm gonna leave him out.
Río is the best at its best
and you know it, that's why you chose him.
It's a fucking coconut.
The thing is, geniuses are weird.
You think you're an example of maturity?
Tell me, do you consider yourself
a normal person?
Do you think it's normal to sort your
shirts by colour?
Have you seen yourself? Tell me,
who buys your clothes,
your aunt the nun, Gertrudis?
What about this?
What's this? What's this?
Origami Figures,
is an ancient technique. Please...
Hey, what's the matter, you're afraid
I'll break your
paper dolls?
Hey, hey, welcome to Jurassic Park.
Oh, help, the dinosaur eats me.
What's the difference between this and
playing video games?
I'm so sorry, but it's not a decision
that's in your hand.
Yes, it is.
If Río goes, don't count on me.
I'm not mature enough either.
All right, then.
Maybe we'll all have our immaturity plot here.
And that makes us all a bit...
Specials
Different.
Maybe that's not an impediment.
Maybe it's a virtue.
Maybe
I'm sure it is.
But don't tell me.
Tell it to him, who's behind the door.
Thank you very much, Profesor,
you won't regret it, I promise you.
Thank you.
You're the one who hits cops?
Well, I'll read you the penal code.
Article 550, offence of assault on authority.
With penalties ranging from one to
four years in prison.
And we're gonna do everything we can to
make you stay four years
in the shade.
Could I, please,
talk to my lawyer?
Sure. Talk, talk,
you're gonna need.
No, but I need my cell phone,
I've got his number there.
It's been taken away with my
personal belongings.
Wait here, don't move.
- I'm sorry about the chick, because
among the bastards
of the cops and them, I prefer the kidnappers.
It's just that it's so great what they've done.
Well, let's see how it ends.
I'll tell you that, with all the kidnappers
shotgunned.
Oh, fuck.
Sons of bitches, for fuck's sake.
Look, Mr. Prieto.
Miss Tokio.
How long have you been questioning
women in panties?
Why did they give yourself?
Well, things happen.
Why'd they tie her to a stretcher?
I had my differences with the person in charge.
I tortured him for a while and it
seems he didn't take it too well.
Oh, yeah.
I want you to know that your money
is still insured.
Just as I looked for you a first time,
I would look for you
when you got out of jail and you'd have it.
By this I mean that the plan goes ahead,
because in the worst case scenario, over the years.
you'll get your money. And in the best...
Well, I'll try to get you out of the hole
when everything's a little calm.
That the plan goes forward means
not talking to the police,
not talk to the judge and
not talk to the prisoners, right?
That's it.
- I'd rather bite my tongue,
chew it and swallow it
than to give anyone away.
Well, let's see, it's an effective method.
It's a bit rough, but effective.
I was going to propose, however,
something a little more...
More subtle.
An interrogation is like a game of expertise,
like flying a kite that at any moment
can fall to the ground. With the right hand
you're letting go of the thread
of the truth.
Exactly how many of you are in there?
Eight.
The same eight of us who planned the coup
in a town in Toledo.
And how much time did you take to prepare the coup
in the town of Toledo?
Five months.
When the kite takes flight, when they consider
that there is truth
in what you say and be sure that they
can get something out of it
of you, with your left hand you pull the thread
and stop the kite.
You entertain them.
Do you wear boxers, Colonel?
It's just that I've always thought
that the military
like to wear that hanging around.
Am I wrong?
hanging around
- Can anyone tell me why you guys fucking have
this woman like that?
Sorry about the treatment.
Good to see you again, Miss Tokio.
This time we are going to be practical,
I ask and you answer.
Who's the Profesor?
Yes?
Hi, I need to talk
with Inspector Raquel Murillo, it's very urgent.
Who's calling?
It is a private matter.
Inspector Murillo, urgent call.
Listen, I'm not moving from here.
Subject reserved.
- Who's that? Raquel, thank God.
I'm Salva, I'm calling from the police station,
I'm under arrest.
I'm accused of assaulting a service agent,
your ex-husband, more specifically.
How?
I'm handcuffed and they're talking
about four years in jail.
and I don't know what else. But...
What police station are you in?
Canillas.
Well, quiet,
as soon as I can, I'll be there, huh?
Thanks.
Let's move on.
He was about to tell me about the Profesor.
You'd look prettier with short hair, inspector.
That's how she looks like a mother.
It's just that I'm getting the urge
to tell you everything.
Perfect, because I'm here with open arms
waiting for you to do it.
Look on the bright side,
that's the end of living on the run.
Now it's your turn to start from scratch.
You want to know how it all started?
The Profesor picked me up.
With a red Seat Ibiza.
While the police were ambushing me.
No
No, no, it started earlier.
A boy, his name was Miguel.
He took my panties down in front of the class.
Can you believe they expelled me
instead of that six-year-old son of a bitch?
That's where everything started to twist.
Hey.
Is it true what they've said before,
You ever beat up a cop?
You have to claim it was a fight.
If you're the only one who hit him,
you're fucked.
I see you in one piece, actually.
Excuse me, could I go to the bathroom?
Keep an eye on him.
- I didn't come here to be anybody's nurse.
Not to put up with anyone's little
speeches, not to do shitty therapies
I've had to shut the fuck up before
for not screwing up the group
any more than it already is.
- It's a detail.
Worry about your companions.
- You know what really worries me?
The Profesor, Berlín. He's not here, it's just you.
And he's the head of all this.
- And precisely because he's the head of all this.
he drew up a perfect plan and that's
the one we're going to follow,
step by step, without doing anything he
hadn't foreseen.
- But you've already done something unforeseen,
you've taken Tokio out.
- Tokio will get its share if she behaves well
and it doesn't count for anything.
- Bullshit!
The thing about having her share
was if she got caught,
Not if you got her out of here and
threw her out like a bitch
down the stairs to the lions.
And with the bad shit he's got,
Do you know what she has done?
He must have thrown it all away.
And the GEOS will be in the hangar digging
the tunnel on the other side.
to get in here.
- I write down your comments
for the suggestion box.
But, unfortunately,
as you've seen with Río,
that's not gonna do any good,
because this... It's patriarchy!
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means I'm in charge here!
And if you don't want it to happen like Río or Tokio,
I advise you to take a lime blossom.
What the hell is wrong with you, Nairobi,
your period has been synchronized
with Tokio?
You and I are alike.
I don't think my life is as exciting as yours.
No, I don't think so either.
But it mustn't be easy to wear a
skirt in the police force.
Neither is in a gang of muggers.
We are few.
That's why we have to be putting the ovaries
on the table all the time.
Really.
Don't you think it's exhausting?
Silene, I think you're wasting my time
and you're fucking all your chances
of sentence reduction.
Every minute you lose costs you a year.
Look, you're young and pretty now.
And you have everything in place.
Twelve years from now, you'll still be fine,
maybe with some interesting wrinkles.
But if you get out of jail
in 24 years,
you will have entered the menopause terrain
and that must be pretty fucked up, right, Prieto?
I know it from his mother.
And I'm not talking about hot flashes,
I'm talking about the feeling
of having lost something important.
Something profoundly yours,
which has vanished forever.
Your life.
Inspector.
Do you really see me in a garden
raising a family,
changing diapers?
Please.
Look, I'm gonna give you one last chance
before I call the judge.
If you don't talk, goodbye,
you're going to jail now.
And you will have lost collaboration,
repentance and extenuating circumstances,
what they come to be between
10 and 12 years of life.
So think carefully before you
throw it all away.
You want some advice?
Oh, sure.
Think of a nice place,
at some point in your life when
you've been really happy.
And take a deep breath, reflect.
Tokio!
I can't.
- How can you? If you've been put in
giant killers.
It's a hypnotic sedative.
Relax and enjoy.
- Water.
Please.
- Go back to sleep.
- How can I fucking sleep?
If I don't stop dreaming about Tokio.
- Tokio is a motherfucker.
- What?
- Do you know what your girlfriend did
with the only illusion of my life?
When was the last time he saw you,
when he was three?
He put it in his mouth,
chewed it and spit it in my face.
He doesn't have a fucking memory of you.
Shut the fuck up.
He doesn't even have a memory of you,
he won't recognize you.
You know what the worst thing about it is?
She's right.
He's right. He's right.
I was going to kidnap a child who doesn't
even know who I am.
I was going to kidnap a child
who doesn't even know who I am.
And now I don't even know what
to do with the money.
- look, maybe not now, but a few years from now
you go, you look for him and...
And you explain it to him.
You say, "Fuck, look, I'm your mother.
I live in Jamaica with a lot of money
and if you want me to tell you
the rest of the story,
I buy you a plane and you come to see me."
Besides, you're a young woman.
But you have two ovaries, don't you?
You can have another one.
- Oh, yeah.
Five minutes, not one more.
Easy, right?
Oh, look.
You'd give me a son, would you?
- Oh, sure.
- Yeah?
- How do you want it, blond or dark?
- I'm not kidding.
If I get out of here,
I'm gonna need a reason to live.
- Nairobi, what do you want me to say?
Having a child to have a reason to live...
I don't know, I don't think
it's a very good plan.
- You don't?
- Besides, I'm with Tokio.
- I'm not asking you to marry me,
I'm just asking for a little sperm.
Two little pushes and I'm pregnant.
Because look, with how handsome
you are, how smart...
And that pretty little smile of yours.
And it's that easy. Hold it right there.
It's that easy, huh?
You trade one son for another,
what difference does it make?
Because in the end the only important thing
is to have a reason to live.
- Fucking hell!
Fuck, then you say that Tokio is crazy.
You're worse.
- Where are you going?
- Fuck it.
- No, no, hold still.
No, you have to fuck Berlín in a way
that's not turning himself in.
Salva.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
I really do. I screwed up, I'm so sorry.
But what did that animal do to you?
No, it was not his fault alone,
I... Well, I brought up the subject
of what he's done to you,
about the mistreatment and your sister.
Fucking hell.
Well, I'm really sorry,
I'm not like that, I don't
know what happened to me.
But my blood was boiling.
I'm not a violent man,
I've never hit anyone, ever.
I'm more of a quiet talker.
Have you defended yourself?
Well, I'm no Mohamed Ali,
but I've got my pride and I've hit him,
I've hit him.
But my body is like a punching bag,
I think he beat me.
Let me see.
Wait.
Fucking hell.
I'm calling a doctor right now
to see that, don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
I'm telling you I have a boyfriend
and you don't have time
to beat him up?
- Hey, hey, he hit me,
I haven't even touched him.
- I want you to drop the complaint now.
- Yes?
You take back the one you have against me.
- This is going to come in handy
at the trial we have pending,
the fact that you also hit my partner.
- He knocked me unconscious,
he's fucking Chuck Norris with glasses.
- Look, you tell your lawyer the bullshit.
This isn't gonna help you with custody.
- Raquel, I didn't do anything,
I didn't touch it.
- Oh, you don't? Come with me.
I'm Inspector Raquel Murillo from headquarters.
I want to know who has taken the attestation
of the complaint against this man.
And I want to know
why he hasn't been seen by a doctor,
given that he's been beaten
by this agent.
Salva, open your shirt.
This man wants to file a complaint
for abuse of authority,
You have to make a declaration of injury.
For the declaration of first instance
you are witnesses.
- Raquel,
I don't know how he got these wounds,
I swear I didn't touch him.
- The victim has contusions in the chest,
ribs and abdomen.
He's clearly been beaten up.
Is someone taking the statement, yes or no?
- Raquel.
All right, stop it.
I'm withdrawing the complaint.
- Very well.
Then he withdraws his.
Have the handcuffs removed.
Where are your personal belongings?
Raquel, I wouldn't want to look
like one of these.
of conspiracy theory,
but my fingerprints
and data are around, I don't...
Ok.
Where's the attestation of his arrest?
Let's go, Salva.
"I've never felt so lost.
I didn't have anything anymore.
I just had to decide whether or not
to betray out my companions
and seek a minimal clemency from the
judge for collaboration."
You want to say something?
Could somebody make me some
fried eggs, please?
Fuck, I've been eating garbage
for four days.
"Tokio, I won't let you down,
I've got it all figured out.
And besides, I'm a lucky man.
I want you to remember it forever.
Tokio, I won't let you down."
I can't take it anymore.
It's been 30 boxes like this.
These people don't care if you
have a gunshot wound.
I don't even want to think about the
after-effects we're gonna have,
mostly psychological.
Having to come here to work every day.
Having to relive all this.
Well, it's gonna be hard on all of us, huh?
It's even likely that some of us
let's go into post-traumatic shock.
Well, I have all the ballots
I don't know what could be more traumatic
than losing everything.
I've lost everything and that
doesn't make up for it.
Not by a long shot.
As for the million euros... I laugh.
Anybody can trust these people,
they've got us locked up
like we're cattle.
Will you shut up now?
I beg your pardon?
Shut the fuck up.
- Alison, please.
- I'm sick of hearing this guy complain.
If you're so bad, why don't
you do something?
I was complaining about everything, too.
From my parents, from the school where I was bullied...
I swallowed and swallowed.
Well, it's over.
- Now it's normal for you to see
everything very black.
- On the contrary.
You guys have been fucked up,
but it opened my eyes.
I've realized that we are what we eat.
And I don't know about you,
but I'm not eating any more shit.
So I'm gonna go.
- Alison, don't talk nonsense.
I'm your tutor
and I'm responsible for your safety, so...
- You're here for the money.
You'll be comfortable with your
little pinch.
and being accomplices to this mob.
But I don't.
Besides, it's not that hard to get out of here either.
Get out of here?
How?
I'm gonna hurt myself.
They'll take me somewhere else
and I can escape there.
- No, no and no.
Don't even think about doing that nonsense.
Mercedes, Mercedes, let the girl
explain herself.
I've seen it more than ten times since
we've been here.
They press the button and the door only
takes
four seconds to open.
Four seconds and run away
that's all it takes.
Four seconds is more than enough time
to get shot.
We'll see about that.
What's the matter, hostages? Do you sleep
comfortably thinking on your million euros?
Well, keep dreaming, because nobody's
gonna give it to you.
It's a lie, just like no one has released
any of your comrades,
the ones who chose to go out
instead of the million, no.
They are locked up
two floors below you.
- This one's an asshole.
- Chained to a pipe. It was a strategy
to keep you tame like sheep
working for us. But smiling,
because here you have to be
always smiling!
Isn't it, Don Andrés de Fonollosa,
that we don't want bad faces?
- Are you done yet?
- We're not going out through the
hole you're digging,
No, we're going out for one that goes straight
in the vault.
Aah!
- What you've done is high treason, Río.
Unforgivable.
Let's go.
- Aah! Aah!
Anything new?
- No, she didn't say anything.
Apparently, Miss Tokio has no
interest in collaborating.
- Colonel, one question.
Did Deputy Inspector Rubio mention
anything to you
about a spoon?
- A spoon?
No, why?
- Ángel had it analyzed before the accident,
the prints match the subject
who forced the zeta
to threaten the Russian.
It's the same person
who helps them from the outside.
- And who the hell is he?
- I don't know.
Looks like the same guy who tampered with Ángel's car
so he'd have the accident.
But only Ángel knows that.
And her.
Tell me one thing.
Are you silent for everyone or
just for Aníbal Cortés?
You look very much in love
in these pictures.
What would you say if I offer
you a two for one?
Like happy hour.
The same deal I'm offering you,
for him.
Mitigating, repentance and collaboration.
That's as long as the information
you give us
Help to put an end to this nightmare.
- We're talking one-third of the sentence.
That's impossible. We have crimes to
resurrect several times
in jail.
No judge can promise us that.
Except you.
Look, I don't know what they told you,
but you regret it,
you collaborate and help save the
lives of 50 victims,
and I assure you that any judge
is going to be benevolent.
- Hannibal Cortés has no blood crimes,
I'd be out in five years.
- At 24 years old,
like I just got out of college.
I think it's a better plan
Than to end up like your last boyfriend,
don't you think?
It was a bad idea to talk to
the hostages, Río.
- You can get me out like Tokio
now, huh? Tied up.
Because I'm not gonna shut up.
- I trust Tokio,
but you're a worthless little boy.
It's a pity.
Look at the paradox, Helsinki.
Tokio's gonna shut up to protect him.
And yet, you're gonna disappear without her knowing.
- What are you gonna do, huh?
- What you shouted for me.
Execute you.
Indeed, you have lost your mind.
I can't let you go, and I can't
let you stay either,
what you told the hostages ended
up condemning you
and my pulse isn't going to tremble.
Aah!
Well, it will shake a little.
It's important that you face
death with humor.
"To those of us who do things
unconsciously
it's not that we don't care about
the consequences, no,
we care as much as anyone else.
We just can't see them until it's too late.
We only see those consequences when
they're in front of us.
of our noses."
You want to say your last words?
- There's still time to learn
from your mistakes.
and stop being a piece of shit.
- Oh, my goodness, Helsinki!
This boy has just come of age.
If you had lived longer, you
could have been
Paulo Coelho's successor.
Too bad, the world's gonna
have to miss it.
- Berlín!
What the fuck are you doing?
- Put the fucking gun down.
- The time for allegations is over.
Unfortunately, democracy has only
brought us displeasure.
and I just passed sentence.
- Enough of this bullshit,
that we're very nervous.
Berlín, let's not fuck around anymore.
Berlín, we can't keep fucking around.
- Come on down.
Berlín.
You'd better put the gun down, otherwise,
you're gonna fuck with pain,
I found your painkillers.
- What are you going to do, Nairobi?
Break them one by one
like Tokio did?
- As I am with the the period...
What a bitch we women are, isn't it?
And what a tempered we get when
they step on our asses.
- You son of a bitch!
- Berlín, you have a missed call, my love.
- Ok, man, ok. That's it.
All right, you've made your choice.
Bad, but you have chosen. Take her away.
"And with that clarity I saw myself
at the trial, in jail.
And I knew the inspector was right,
that it wasn't worth sacrificing for a plan
that had already failed, because
of the Profesor's plan.
And more thinking that he had also deceived me."
Sergio!
His name is Sergio.
- Wait a minute. Let her speak.
The Profesor's name is Sergio Marquina.
And the blow occurred to his father.
And who's the person outside?
- Inspector, they're calling from
inside the factory.
How are you, how was your day?
Well, I think good.
To tell you the truth, I was a
little worried about you.
I thought we weren't going to talk anymore,
something terrible had happened.
Sergio.
Thank you very much for your concern,
Inspector, but...
I'm a lucky man, never forget that.
I was just calling to say hello,
I'll let you interrogate Tokio,
has a lot of things to tell you.
And when you're done, call me.
I'm not moving from here.
What do you have to tell me?
I've been kicked out to give
you a message in person.
We've got a hydrogen bomb in there
of 17 megatons.
We're gonna blow it up tomorrow at 12:00.
I'd like to talk to a priest.
I need to confess.
All right, let's apply for unconditional
incommunicated prison.
Gómez, write the report and emphasize
in his lack of cooperation and repentance.
Have her admitted to the nearest prison.
Lobo, take her away.
Control call.
Everything goes like silk around here.
Like silk? Like silk is Tokio
is being interrogated
by the police?
Like silk is that you've been about
to execute Río?
Berlín, what are you doing?
Profesor, it's Nairobi.
Berlín is in no condition,
so from now on I'm in charge.
The matriarchy begins.
We have to do something,
steal a gun from them.
Where do we get a gun?
- Changing one of them
for one of the fake ones.
His colleague Silene Oliveira is going
to be remanded in custody
Tonight without bail.
Nairobi is now in command.
- You tell me,
Are you with me or against me?
I'm releasing 11 hostages.
I want a journalist to come in.
and a camera to cover the news
from the inside.
Let's go. Let's go.
I ditch this from the cider in a few days
and you and I are going to a
Caribbean country.
I'll go get the gun, wish me luck.
We move on to Plan Cameroon.
Sub-inspector Rubio is coming out of the coma.
You're gonna have to show up
there and check if it's a trap.
And if it isn't, finish him off.
Let's set up the operation,
but we'll be there.
to catch him like a cat to a rat.
We're out of here, quick.
The hostages, damn it!
- Hey!
- Don't open the door!