You're asking me to let you in.
You choose; either I send you the tanks
or we have a coffee you and me
and you show me all the hostages alive.
I'd be delighted to receive you.
- Raise your hands.
Proceed.
- Hannibal Cortés is the weakest
link in the chain.
That's why I told Scientists
to place a message inside.
- Hello, son. We've hired a
very good lawyer
and I've got you a collaboration act with justice.
- You can still back up, sweetheart.
- If Aníbal Cortés surrender,
It will mean that our plan works.
- Do you work near here?
Yes, right next door.
Like Raquel told me she was unemployed.
It's just that a few months ago I lost my job,
so now I'm trying to set up my own company.
Ecological cider.
And you have the workshop nearby?
Yes, right here, very close.
I would love to try it.
Sorry to intrude, but I can't wait
to try that cider
that you promised me.
Of course, right now.
Thank you.
Cheers.
What, did you find something?
- Yes, there was a print.
It doesn't match the cops who patrol it.
- Do me a favour,
Check it with the prints on this spoon.
When you get the results, call me.
- I search you, almost arrest you,
and you still care about me?
Well, if you need any kind of help
that I can...
Thank you.
- I've given you approximation points,
so I don't have to sew again.
Better.
What if I could go where I was
before to rest and stuff?
Retroxil, used to alleviate tremors
of a rare degenerative neuronal disease.
- You have to order it on request,
they have all patients very localized.
- But in Toledo there has been an
unusual demand.
- And where was the last purchase made?
- Here, in Palomeque, on October 18th.
- Just three days before entering the Factory.
Get a warrant from Judge Andrade.
and go to that pharmacy by yourself.
Don't talk about this with anyone.
Help, please, we just got mugged!
He just wanted the purchase
records without prescriptions
and sales books as well.
Raquel, I don't know.
The pharmacy was robbed,
all records were taken.
I don't know how this happened.
Only you and I knew, you and me!
"Do you know that moment when you tie
up loose ends
that you didn't want to tie up?
It hurts, doesn't it?
You're there, with your usual partner,
and you think:
"What a son of a bitch."
I'm on my way.
"Or: 'What a bastard'.
You don't want to believe it,
but you know there's a traitor.
And it can only be you or your partner.
And Ángel knew he wasn't.
Raquel was trying to find an explanation
for that robbery,
but when explanations don't come alone,
there's always someone willing to
give you a little push."
I'm an old fashioned and
I still believe in good and bad.
And I put my hand on the fire
that you are one of the good ones.
Could you put your hand on the fire
for your sub-inspector?
Because I wouldn't put someone else's dick.
"Ángel believed that nothing could get worse.
But it could.
Of course it could.
When you hit the bottom,
you still have something to scratch
into the abyss."
Dirt!
What's going on?
- We got it!
"Not even Sunday night had fallen,
when we were invaded by a climate of euphoria.
We had found dirt and Nairobi
had the presses
in full power.
We had exceeded 400 million euros."
"We had sealed the entrances
with explosive charges
and we had the feeling of being in a bunker.
It was our ten minutes of glory."
Who the fuck wants the sound of the sea?
This is poetry.
This is the heart of the world
beating here,
beating for us, because we're making it beat.
Because the world moves
because of this, damn it!
- What's going on? What party are you
having here? What's going on?
- Hey, hey, hey!
What's the matter with you?
Viva!
"Without a doubt, it was the happiest
moment we were in there.
And then, we relax."
Hold still.
- Do you want to comb your hair?
Thank you.
Do you know how they say in my village
"two men make love"?
It is said: "Comb for inside".
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. With so much medicine,
my stomach is loose.
Could you go to the bathroom, please?
Sure, man.
Jacinto.
Jacinto, this is Arturo.
Do you hear me?
Jacinto!
Mister Arturo.
You're alive!
I was convinced you'd been shot.
I didn't sleep.
We are in the boilers basement.
Tied up like dogs.
We've been locked up with four cops.
They just take us upstairs to go to
the bathroom.
Listen to me, Jacinto,
I have scissors
and I can get you more tools
Screwdrivers, a saw...
I don't know.
Tools I can get you in two hours.
Do you have a watch?
Yes.
Find yourself an excuse.
Try to get you back here in two hours.
Two hours.
From this moment on.
Remember, second from the left.
I'll leave the tools here.
What the fuck do you want us to do
with scissors and a saw?
These people have explosives,
M-16, everything.
The lives of 67 people are in your hands.
Believe me, everything's gonna be fine
and in a few hours we'll be out
of this nightmare.
All right.
Yes, yes,
I'll be right out.
The photos sent by the kidnappers
show explosive charges connected
to photoelectric cells.
They've been placed in all the entrances.
Even in the underground ventilation.
- What explosive is it?
- The Tedax think it is C4.
But I see it much more orange,
so we've sent it to CSI for verification.
- Who at CSI?
- We sent it to Alberto.
- Okay. Isn't there another inspector
in the entire CSI
who can do the same job as my ex-husband?
- Inspector, they gave it to Alberto
because he's the best.
- This is a direct order
from Commissioner Sánchez.
- Yeah.
And what does the CSI say?
- They think it's P-4.
Very similar to C-4,
of British origin,
and that the connection is perfect.
- They're making it hard for us, huh?
Alison!
I think it's time to have a friendly chat
with Alison Parker.
Colonel.
- A cell phone call is coming
in from inside the building.
- Record it!
- It's from Yum Li, a hostage.
- I am Aníbal Cortés.
What do you want?
- To help you, Hannibal.
For that we need you to help us
get into the factory
and get the hostages out in the least
aggressive way possible. Understand?
- There are plastic explosives at
all access points.
- Yes, it is.
Entering is not a problem,
but we need an ally.
An ally to tell us where
the robbers are
at every moment,
do you understand?
- Yeah. And why would I sell
my colleagues?
They'll tempt you with a better future,
with sentencing benefits,
that in one or two years you'll be out...
No.
If you help us, you'll get prison benefits.
A reduction of your sentence
to two years.
When you're 22,
you'll have a future again.
Think about it.
Divide and conquer.
This slogan served a small town in Italy
to dominate the whole world.
Then it served to Napoleon.
And now it serves the National Police.
They will take advantage of the slightest
contact to tempt any of you.
When you've been in there for more than 48 hours,
the pressure will start,
anguish, negativity
and that's when they try to go
for the weakest link.
The weakness isn't in us,
it's in what we have outside.
You can still back up,
sweetheart.
But by the time they try to contact,
you have already committed at least
six or eight crimes.
No judge is going to guarantee
your freedom. None.
Once you're in there, the only one
who can offer you freedom...
it's me.
- Hannibal,
listen to me carefully.
The judge guarantees you freedom
in a very short time.
- Okay.
Let's do the math, Inspector.
Look, robbery with violence: 2 to 5 years.
Crime against freedom, kidnapping
and establishment of conditions for release
of the four policemen in the convoy: 40 years.
Checking the alarms.
Computer crime.
We're talking six months to two years.
Disturbance of public order due to
the assault on the factory:
from 1 to 6 years old.
And with the hostages, it's much harder.
67 hostages. And the Penal Code says
which are 6 to 10 years for each
of the kidnappings.
Then the shots to the police at point-blank
range on the first day.
From 6 to 8 years for each agent.
But on top of that we wounded them,
which leads to a felony for injuries
and an aggravating factor of up to 8 years
for each agent injured.
We would be talking about...
If we get a bastard judge,
723 years
of request from the prosecution.
The minimum you can offer you
both the judge and the prosecution itself
without wiping his ass with the Penal Code
is 173 years old.
So don't be fooled.
Let's see, the Penal Code
Is the game rules of any country.
No one can skip them. No one.
Although there is one thing we
can agree on.
The president's pardon.
- Tell him yes.
- You want me to ask the president
to sign you a pardon?
- No, I want you to ask the president
that will appear on all televisions and in
front of the whole of Spain say
that if any of the kidnappers decide
to cooperate
to end the crisis, the possibility
will be assessed
to offer him a pardon for his collaboration.
First the president is on the news.
- He's bluffing.
- And then I'll think about it
about being a sold out piece of shit.
- All right, we'll do it.
But for that we need a gesture
of goodwill from you.
I want you to tell me the name of The Profesor.
and the number of robbers in there.
Come on, Hannibal, give me a name
and a number.
and I assure you that you will
have a future again.
- Okay.
A name and a number.
Take paper and pen.
My balls. 33.
- What a son of a bitch!
Fuck...
- Attention, we've cut off communication
with the inside of the factory.
But, dude,
what the hell did you do?
He fucked up our chances of winning time,
that's what he did.
- They didn't believe it.
I was hearing fucking whispers,
for fuck's sake.
- But let's see,
who do you think you are?
You had to execute, not decide or
change plans, damn it.
What the fuck is that whispering?
Hey, hey, Río heard the conversation.
And if he says they didn't believe it,
that's it, ok?
We've been making that fucking
inspector dizzy for days.
So it's not his fault, ok?
That's it. Besides, she wasn't even going
to call the president,
or the TV, or her fucking mother on a bicycle.
- That's enough for you.
You assholes...
"In spite of his brilliant interpretation,
Río knew at all times that he wanted
to take the deal,
stop time
and get out of there like none of
this ever happened."
Would you have liked to take the
deal with the cops?
You know this isn't gonna work out,
right?
Do you know what a reviewable
permanent prison is?
What awaits me.
I killed a security guard
and a few months later I came in here to steal.
And I shot a cop.
With all the manners you look!
Do you think a judge is going to believe
in my reinsertion?
No.
I trust The Profesor.
I fully trust him.
You didn't answer me.
Would you have liked to accept?
Anyway, what would happen if we got
out of here?
Were we going to stay together?
Or were you going to spend the whole time
trying to give me my badge back?
You're talking about betraying your friends.
My friends?
My friends with a city name?
Tokio, Berlín, Moscú, Denver.
Well, to me, my friends with city names
look awesome.
And I'll tell you something:
try to hide if you take the deal,
because if I see you,
I'll shoot you in the head.
I just got off the phone with the factory
security guard.
I found him in the bathroom.
He says they are locked up,
11 security guards and 4 policemen.
They are our only salvation.
No, I'm not hungry,
thank you.
Are you sure?
Yes, thank you.
Our salvation?
What if they're locked up?
We have to arm them anyhow,
get tools and pass them on.
But what tools do you want to steal?
Well, drill bits, hammers, screws, whatever.
You've seen they have an arsenal down there.
Well, we have to take it and hide it
in the bathroom.
Look, Pablo, I can't do this alone.
All right? I need your help.
When this one, the Slavic gorilla,
takes me down for a walk,
I need you to entertain him.
Yes, he has healed my wound,
he is very attentive to me,
helps me walk... And I don't know
if you've noticed, but...
It's a little gay.
Yeah, who knew!
Well, he is, so offer yourself,
he's going to want you for sure.
He's gonna want what?
So what's it going to be?
that, for fuck sake, that.
And while you seduce him and
he's with you for a while,
I sneak out and steal the tools,
okay?
Listen, everyone here has to use their weapons,
you know what I mean?
You're a fucking adonis,
so take advantage of it.
To save life.
Look, you are crazy. You are crazy.
What do you care?
Today all of your generation
you're half ambiguous.
Stop, huh? Stop it.
Are you saying I should be sodomized
by that orangutan?
Listen, here the limits are set by yourself.
If you distract him, that's fine with me.
All right?
Look, you distract him.
And I steal the tools and whatever it takes.
- That's it. It's over.
Arturo, you rest.
Take care of your wound.
I come later.
Come on. The ones in the tunnel, here.
Do not discuss the plan with anyone.
The plan is just for us.
The less we are, the better the chances of success.
We'll help the others from the outside,
okay?
Arturo, I'll be right back.
All right.
Come in.
And sit down.
- Mercedes, hi.
I've called to see what we
can do with your student.
He's escaped
and we found her locked in a safe.
What do you think this rebellion is about?
Could it be the rebelliousness
of the virgins?
- What the fuck are you talking
about virgins, man?
- Nairobi, in many species we see it.
The virgins are rebellious because
they are still unbroken.
With all due respect, it happens
just like with mares.
They are not tamed until they are mounted.
They can run away, they kick-ass,
they're completely unpredictable.
You've heard of this concept,
haven't you?
- Eh...
- At what age did you lose your virginity,
Mercedes?
Mercedes, it's okay.
Speak up, please, we're here.
In family, in trust.
Teacher...
- Well... Eh... I'm from a small town in Soria.
At 24.
- And didn't you notice that virginal
rebellion before?
- Well, I don't know.
- Think.
- Maybe so.
In fact, before I lost it,
I escaped three times to the
Medinaceli parties.
I don't know if that's what...
- That's it. Exactly.
- Here you go.
Intense coffee with a sugar cube.
- Thank you.
The festivals of Medinaceli...
What about you, Alison?
Are you a virgin?
- Yeah. So what?
You don't scare me with your
crazy speeches.
You're not gonna do anything to me,
you know why?
Because I'm not just a hostage,
I'm your safe conduct.
- That is, the rebellion of the
virgins here is undoubtedly.
Ariadna, dear, please,
Can you give me that red booklet?
- Sure.
Let's see what we got here.
Your aunt Becky,
a development worker in a village in Mali.
Here's your cousin Elsi.
Gorgeous, at King's College.
Brian, this is the brainiac of the family.
In Wellington.
And here we have several photos
of your sister Lis,
here on the side, in La Moraleja.
Study in the same school as you.
Although I don't think he has the
same temperament as you.
A girl from your social station sure
doesn't have a clue
how much a hitman costs,
right?
We can find a decent one for 30 000 euros.
Although to unlock your aunt's shot in Africa.
with 10 000 euros we fix it.
Your family's life is in your hands.
Nairobi.
- Let's go. Let's go.
When I told you to assert yourself,
I should have told you
that the most important thing is
to choose the right moment.
Control call. Berlín.
Everything's fine here. In there?
Everything is in order.
Perfect. Well, next call in six hours.
- Inspector, the subsoil found oscillations.
in the seismograph.
They are working with heavy machinery.
Indeed, they are making a tunnel.
- We must bring the georadar now.
Let's see if we can find out where
they're doing the damn tunnel.
- I'll take care of it.
- Now, listen to me, all of you.
If you are not indispensable, you can go.
Essential means
who's doing something right now.
The rest of you to rest and shower,
please,
that this is already starting to smell awful.
I correct, all of you come out
for a moment, please.
I have to take you off the case.
I'm sorry.
I think this is going to clear up,
but right now I can't trust you, Ángel.
- You can't trust me.
Because it turns out that the Toledo thing
you and I, Raquel, knew.
You and me.
- What the fuck are you saying?
- That I am not the traitor.
So... it's just you.
- Look, you must have courage.
They knew we were going into the museum
with the masks
when you knew.
They knew we were going to the junkyard
And they knew about the fucking pharmacy
when you knew.
- Yeah? And it can't be anything else?
- What is it?
- I don't know, a call, a phone,
a fucking microphone.
- Only you and I knew about the pharmacy.
- And you haven't told anyone,
have you? No?
And you didn't say anything to the weird
guy in the cafeteria?
Huh?
How?
- Yes, to your cloth of tears.
A guy shows up here yesterday and
you tell him your whole life,
as if you were new.
And you don't suspect him,
do you?
He's been in here, Raquel.
He's been inside the tent.
Have you looked into it?
Because I do!
Did you do your damn job?
He's got this guy next door who
says he makes cider.
And he's got everything covered by tarps.
Who knows what the fuck he'll cover!
- Don't fuck with me you've been following him.
- I have been following you.
And it doesn't make cider,
it doesn't make shit!
He does bottle shit and throws
it in a cauldron.
And it's all full of garbage, damn it!
He's got a junk car.
And he sleeps in a bunk surrounded
by wheels and grease stains.
And it smells like a chemical,
which cooks methamphetamine.
I don't know what the hell he cooks.
It's not clean wheat, Raquel!
It's not!
And you suspect me,
I'm the only suspect.
Me? Me? Me?
- How much do they pay you?
A million? Two?
- Look, Raquel...
Listen to me carefully.
Go fuck yourself.
- Suárez!
Suárez!
- I can't believe it!
- Put the handcuffs on him and
get him out of here.
- Take it easy, inspector.
That's not the procedure.
- Yes, it is.
Suárez, put the handcuffs on me, dammit.
- I'm in the middle of the fucking procedure.
Put the handcuffs on him and get him out of here!
- If you want, I can call Internal Affairs
but here, for now, no one's gonna
handcuff anyone.
- Raquel...
I've been with you for 15 years.
- With me? No.
You've been snuggling up to me for
15 years to see if I fall.
Always with the fucking Cercedilla
in your mouth.
With the "I will leave Mari Carmen".
And with your fucking bingo flirt jokes.
And now that I finally say no,
it turns out that this horny don Pimpón
has become a traitor, a traitor!
You've sold out, Ángel.
Our friendship...
this operation...
Look...
Get the hell out of here right now.
"Do you know what collateral damage means?
It's a term coined during the Vietnam War
by the American army.
When they didn't have balls
to talk directly about the murder of civilians.
But sometimes it's also used to get rid of guilt,
like a boomerang.
And that was what was about to happen
to the Profesor."
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Hurry up, let's go!
Come on, hurry up!
Take a couple of bags and pick this shit up.
Then comes the dinner.
- I managed to steal some things
from the toolbox.
What things?
Well...
Saw blades, screwdrivers, files...
All right, all right. Chist!
What are you doing, what are you doing?
Hide it.
In 35 minutes,
ask to be taken back to the bathroom.
You enter the second toilet on the left,
you take the tools and stick them under
the toilet seat,
inside.
They'll be here in, like,
40 minutes, okay?
It cannot be. I mean, me?
Me again?
I've already stolen all the tools,
I'm loaded with junk, for fuck's sake.
And what do you want,
to give them to me here?
You do your part, I'll do mine, kid.
"Raquel...
Is something wrong?
Are you all right?"
Eh...
Well, I'm here alone and bored in the
cafeteria and...
And a little disappointed,
if you want me to tell you the truth.
Excuse me, I don't understand.
Disappointed?
I was just meeting someone for dinner.
My first dinner in eight years with...
With someone who wasn't in my family, I mean.
But I think he stood me up.
And isn't it that you're about
36 minutes early?
It's possible.
The truth is, I'm a very impatient woman.
Excuse me, Salva.
Forgive the joke, no...
I just wanted to make sure you
remembered about the dinner.
The truth is, I'm afraid of the sit-ins.
I wouldn't know what to do, how to get out of here,
if you didn't show up.
I don't know, I guess I'd stay here with...
With my heels and alone and...
And drinking pints until they came to evict me.
Inaccessible to discouragement.
No. Dead of shame.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be right with you.
In five minutes.
So far.
Until now.
When you're near me,
it's hard for me to breathe.
Then breathe.
Because nine months from now,
you're going to have your breath cut off.
It's a joke, right?
Please tell me it's a joke.
No, it's not a joke.
It's not a joke.
No.
Mónica, I'm technically sterile.
You must be Shiva, the goddess of fertility.
Do I call my wife, tell her to pick up the kids
and we all go out together
to celebrate?
Do we do as any marriage
that has three children?
Not that I was going to separate.
I brought you an awesome menu.
A sandwich that... that...
Well, I ate it a couple of times
and I didn't die,
so more or less...
Biscuits that...
I took them gluten-free.
Because I thought: "Maybe...
can be celiac, right?
Like a lot of people.
Yeah.
I say, "Well, you better be."
And a chocolate bun because I like it a lot.
Ah, well, and...
And some sweets.
Do you want some?
Hi, I'm Raquel.
I can't attend you right now.
If urgent, leave a message after the beep.
- Raquel.
Raquel, this is Ángel.
Listen, I'm asking you to reconsider.
Look, I understand the bad moment.
I too have gone too far.
Hell, it's not the first fight
you and I ever had, is it?
Look, I'll be an asshole or
whatever you want, but...
But I'm not the mole.
I'm not the mole, damn it.
You're gonna fuck up my life, Raquel.
You're gonna fuck up my life, damn it.
Give me a call.
It's a good thing I introduced myself,
since the date you have didn't appear.
Oh, yes, I don't know what would have happened
to me if you hadn't shown up.
Sure.
And is this date was of particular
interest to you or...?
No, not anymore.
What a pity.
Well, let see if I'm at least good for something.
I'm sure you do.
Well, I'm glad. What happens is that
I have to confess to you that...
that we are both in danger because...
If I take another one of this,
I'll start humming songs.
So, we're going to find ourselves
in trouble..
I'm sure you'll be very funny.
How long will we keep calling each other formaly?
When you look at me under the table.
Eh...
Come on, Salva.
Take a look.
Look at me under the table.
I warn you, if you're going to
make me a "basic instinct,"
I still need something stronger because
I'm a little classic.
Salva, do as I say.
I don't want you to make anything strange in here.
I have well-founded suspicions that
you're hiding something in that workshop
where it supposedly makes cider.
So, two options, or you take me there
for good
or we wait here to get a court order,
but I'm warning you,
it's gonna take a couple of hours.
So...
it's up to you.
Hey, what do you think the morning
before a robbery?
I mean, you get up and what goes
through your head?
Well, I don't know.
You get up at dawn...
You smoke.
You talk bullshit.
What are you doing smoking so early, son?
- He said the frying pan to the saucepan.
How are you?
- Good, and you?
Well, nothing from other world.
Yes, it does take a lot of courage.
I'm telling you because I think about
those things, you know?
In the people who are on death row.
or guys like you, who shoot their way into a mousetrap.
It's no big deal.
Yes, it is.
I'm telling you, I'm a coward.
Look at me, with a married guy to
avoid the fear of failure
or to be abandoned.
You are no coward.
Yes, I am.
You are not. You're not.
You stole a cell phone in the middle
of the robbery,
you insisted that I shoot you in the leg
and you stood up to the Berlín moron.
And you had the balls to grab
my neck and kiss me,
and fuck me.
You must have a big balls to fuck a crazy man
with Dalí's mask.
You are Nikita in secretary.
Actually,
on the morning of the heist
I was really scared.
Scared as fuck.
- What?
- All this, Dad.
This guy, who seems very clever,
but I don't know, it is crazy.
- At least he knows what he's saying.
- I began to doubt everything.
I don't know what the fuck I'm doing here.
- Well, be with me.
- Here everybody is an expert
the girl who prints bills, you who...
You're a master at your thing, Dad,
but I...
I haven't done anything good in my life.
I was a hell of a guy.
He told me he needed me and here I am,
meeting the prettiest girl in
all this madness.
One minute.
These are the tools we've managed to steal.
Undress and stick them to your body
with insulating tape.
so you can take it to the basement
and let loose.
Cut the tubes from the boiler room
and anything you can arm yourselves with.
At 21:00 you have dinner,
you will seize that moment to
disarm your captors
and run away.
We'll meet at the warehouse
hidden behind the coils.
I'll try to take as many
hostages as possible
without jeopardizing the plan."
- One second.
- Get out.
Hey, what did you do before in life?
You haven't always been a robber.
Not at all. I've worked on a lot of things.
On what?
Mainly commercial.
And, well, also in the chemical industry,
of security in a park.
Well, I also dance in a disco.
What?
Yes, yes.
Shirtless, with a bunch of chicks
in a cage giving it all.
But like "chunda, chunda"?
And whatever they put.
Samba, twist, rock and roll.
What do you say?
Yes, I do.
What do you flip? That you flip.
Let me dance, show me how you dance.
Here? Come on, dance with me a bit.
Give me a minute.
"Hi, I'm Raquel.
I can't take care of you right now.
If it's urgent,
leave a message after the beep."
Raquel, may I ask why the hell
won't you pick up my phone?
Huh? After 15 years with you by your
side like a fucking loser.
And not for getting close to you,
no, no, for friendship, for love.
Do you hear me? For love.
Come in, please.
No, you come in.
Come on, let's go.
What's this?
It's a warehouse.
What about these plastics?
They're just plastics to
protect from the cold,
don't be scared.
I'm not scared.
Go on.
Turn on the light
and don't do anything stupid.
Listen, I almost sent everything to hell,
to send Mari Carmen to hell.
for a bitch who wouldn't fuck anyone.
Do you hear me? You are a bitch,
a selfish and obsessive bitch.
You're a fucking bitch!
Fucking bitch! A pussy-eater!
A fucking frigid! A fucking frigid!
Raquel, it's me, Ángel, again.
Forgive me, I didn't mean to
call you a bitch.
Really, I'm sorry.
You'll sink me.
I don't know what I'm gonna do
if I'm kicked out of the Police.
Hell, I don't know how I'm gonna be.
You will destroy me.
I know I told you I was unemployed,
but this cider thing is not a job as such,
is merely a project.
I don't know if it's going to be
right or wrong.
And, honestly, I don't know
what's going on.
I don't know if your partner
saw anything illegal.
Well it's true
that there are some nights I sleep here,
in the bunk beds, and I don't have a
certificate of habitability yet.
and I don't know if that's what he saw.
or that I need to pass
some kind of inspection.
I don't know, I don't...
Cider.
Can I try the cider?
Sure, sure.
"It was foreseeable that the inspector
would want to enter
in the Profesor's little secret corner.
And for a handful of euros
it's easy to rent a crappy warehouse
and turn it into the perfect set
for the function.
Whether you want to believe or not...
was the part the inspector
was supposed to play."
I'm sorry, Salva.
This place is wonderful.
I feel very embarrassed...
for showing him the gun
to force him to bring me here, the truth.
I would have preferred to show you
something else.
I want to say something else like you say,
the "basic instinct" thing.
I'd feel a lot less ridiculous
and ashamed of what I am now.
And to think I almost sent my ex-husband.
Your ex-husband?
Yes, I know he's a fucking bastard,
but he's the best in the entire CSI,
because since I'd been described as if it were
a drug lab...
Drugs.
Yes.
Come on, I almost screwed up even more.
I want you to know I'm never
pulling out the gun again.
Yeah.
Neither to frisk you nor
to doubt you any more.
About you.
Of you, of you, of you.
It's about time we stopped
dealing with formalities,
don't you think?
I think it's time we use
first-named, yes.
Yes, yes.
Ángel, do I get you all right?
- Yes, tell me, Pilar.
- I have the results of what you asked for.
I ran the print from the car
and also the one with the spoon that brought me
and, bingo, they match.
The person who touched that spoon
is the same one that forced the patrol car.
- It's awesome, Pilar, it's awesome.
I'll call you back.
"The voice mailbox of the number
you are calling is full."
Fucking hell.
It is time. The guards must be
letting go by now.
At 22:30 you will arrive at the warehouse.
Do you know where it is?
Yes.
Can I warn someone, 5 or 6?
No way.
Are you crazy?
Why?
You want to fuck this up before we start?
Three people suppose a serious
risk to the plan,
four would be crazy.
We'll help you from the outside.
Who's that third person?
Mónica Gaztambide.
Ah!
She's pregnant and we need to
get her out of here.
Yeah, yeah.
Where the fuck are you going?
To find her.
What about me?
Do I stay here?
How do I get to the warehouse?
I can't go in and out the way I want.
Don't fuck with me.
Much worse is what I have to do.
I have to convince that guy
to take me to Mónica.
and then get rid of him.
You gonna kill him?
What I'm not gonna do is stand here
like a lamb
to get shot.
A man has to do what he has to do.
Helsinki.
What's going on?
I'm still not feeling well, huh?
What's up, Arturo,
you want more pills?
No, I don't.
I wish mine could be solved with an aspirin.
It's not that, it's that before,
when I saw Mónica Gaztambide
and I saw that she was alive,
that she was fine,
I've collapsed.
and I don't think I reacted as she expected.
The thing is, then that fellow of yours,
Denver,
He's taken her down or wherever you have her
to rest.
and I felt a need to talk to her.
I've felt it very strong.
Please, man help man in love.
Yes?
It's all right.
Okay, Arturito, okay.
Come on, let's go.
Thank you.
"And as our first defeat approached,
the brain of the operation was absent,
because as brilliant as it was,
He only had two eyes.
and at that time they were
for the inspector."
What?
Nothing.
You were looking at me.
I just don't know,
without the glasses you look
like someone else.
Like Superman and Clark Kent.
I like you more with glasses?
No. I didn't say that.
I'll put them on right now.
It's a little weird to sleep with glasses,
nothing happens.
I usually take them off, but today...
today is a special day.
Better?
The thing is, I can't sleep over,
I'm sorry.
I don't know, I want to wake up
with my daughter,
take her to school,
who sees that he still has a mother.
Sure.
"Hi, I'm Raquel.
I can't take care of you now.
If it's urgent,
leave a message after the beep."
Raquel, it's me again. Call me.
Your answering machine is full.
We got him, listen, we got him.
We've got the guy who's helping
them from the outside.
But to take your daughter to school,
they must still be
at least 7-8 hours.
I mean, maybe being there at 00:00 or 01:00
or 7:00 would be enough.
And it's Salva, Salva,
Salva, the one with the cider,
he was in the junkyard, he threatened the Russian,
for fuck's sake.
- I'm sorry.
I'm not staying.
Hey, what about that piano over there?
Do you play the piano?
He's using you, damn it,
his fingerprints were on the zeta.
He's come to you to take advantage of the investigation.
He's using you.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Is that your wife?
No.
Mónica's not a scandal maker.
Must be one of your companions.
Don't stop it.
Fucking hell.
What the fuck are you doing here, man?
"Arturo had finally made a heroic gesture.
And instead of running away alone,
had decided to rescue his princess,
but it went off the rails,
because princesses have their lives too."
What is it, Mónica?
"And its secrets."
Was this savage raping you?
No, he didn't rape me,
don't talk nonsense, Arturo.
"We've always heard stories of
husbands discovering
their wives with the lover,
but when Arturo found his lover's lover,
he forgot the escape plan."
Arturo, man.
"And he could only hear one word."
I'm fine.
Breathe.
Give a deep back.
"Revenge."
Get dressed, honey,
get out of here, please.
What?
Get dressed and get out of here,
please.
No, I'm not leaving.
Take it out, leave me alone
with this one.
What do you want to do?
Let's not mess it up, Arturito,
We need to talk about this.
No, I don't want to leave.
I said get her the fuck out of here.
You take her out and leave me alone
with this shit.
Yes, you and me.
Yes, here, now, you and me.
Huh? Son of a bitch.
Please.
Get out.
No.
Get out, it's okay.
It's all right, it's all right.
No.
It's all right.
I don't want to leave.
Get out. Get out.
I want to stay here.
Get out, it's okay.
- Let's go.
You've got big balls to take advantage of
of a defenceless and wounded woman.
Let's see if you have the same
balls to face me,
you son of a bitch.
You'll hurt yourself, Arturito,
be careful.
Stop!
- No, I am a hostage,
I'm meeting Arturo Román.
- Where is Don Arturo?
- I don't know.
He told me to be here at 22:30.
Let's go now, please.
- Let wait for Don Arturo.
Two minutes to go.
She's pregnant, you know that?
She's pregnant with my child.
From me!
And I don't think my son's
gonna fucking like it
for you to come knock on her door,
faggot.
Arturito, you're winning a smack with a prize,
stop it now.
I'm gonna kill you, motherfucker.
Fucking hell.
Who's laughing now, huh?
Huh?
I don't hear that stupid polygon fool laugh.
Did you try to kill me with round scissors,
Arturito?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it, I swear.
It's this demon stress that makes me wrong.
Forgive me. I'm sorry.
You're stupid.
Don't hit me.
Give me a fucking reason...
Look at me.
Give me one fucking reason
not to open your head now.
Give me one fucking reason.
They're escaping, they're escaping.
What?
They're getting away.
16 hostages, 16 hostages, right now,
and I know where.
Time's up, gentlemen. Let's go.
Halt! Halt!
Plastic explosive.
- They're escaping, 16 hostages,
through the loading area.
- Tokio, go find Nairobi.
Río, Denver, bring Oslo and Helsinki.
- What's going on?
What's going on?
- 16 hostages are trying to escape.
- Fucking hell.
- And we're gonna go get 'em.
- Ah.
- Are we?
We are.
- Let's go, let's go.
Take cover, take cover.
Is everyone covered?
- Yes.
- Let's see.
Where the fuck have you been?
No one's getting out of here.
We've got the bloody guy helping
them from the outside.
It's the cider guy.
Raquel!
- Raquel!
The time has come to make a decision.
Assault team prevented, we're going in.
Fuck!
Get down!
On your knees.
Helsinki!
Now.
Three, two, one, fire!