THE FACTS AND SCENARIOS REPRESENTED
IN THIS SERIES ARE FICTITIOUS
I'm looking for people
who do not have much to lose.
You do not know each other
and I want it to remain that way.
I do not want any names,
no personal questions
nor, of course,
personal relationships.
Tomorrow is the robbery,
that's why I want to give you something.
Now you at least
know my real name.
- Profesor.
- Miss Tokio?
What are we going to steal?
The Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
The little lamb is coming in.
I tell you I'm pregnant,
and you just keep calm?
What shall I do, call my wife,
tell her to pick up the children
and we all go to celebrate?
- Now!
- Don't move!
Let's go!
I can't find the girl.
I can't fucking see her.
Let's take a picture with your phone.
With this photo you'll be
all the rage on the Internet.
I'm the person who's in charge.
But you're here as hostages.
I guarantee you'll be left alive.
12 years of my life
in and out of prison.
Do you know why?
Because I'm not very smart,
son, but in this hit
it's another one who puts the brains.
But be very careful,
because by the time there's
a single drop of blood,
we'll stop being Robin Hoods
to become
into a bunch of motherfuckers.
- 30 seconds.
- Two police wounded.
Who fired?
Tokio, apparently has
a relationship.
The last thing I think about
is to have a relationship
with a kid. Things don't always
come out as planned.
- What happened?
- 35 workers,
11 security guards
and 17 students from the British College.
It's essential that the police
have no idea
of what we are doing.
I'm Raquel Murillo,
inspector in command,
- What do you want?
- Time.
- What are those armored cars doing here?
- We're going in, with everything.
They'll come in because we've got
our little lamb, Alison Parker.
The time has come
to follow my orders!
There's a person in there
of priority one.
My name is Alison Parker,
daughter of the UK ambassador.
I'm calling you
from inside the factory,
we've been dressed
as the kidnappers.
What's that?
It's impossible to know
who they're going to shoot.
- Don't get in, for God's sake.
- Stop it.
Abort the operation.
Finish what you have started,
I don't want anything to do with it.
Y 20 minutes later,
the best paid job
of history.
Everything depended on time
that we could hold in.
Can I have a decaf, please?
Hello, this is
Mariví's answering machine.
When you hear the beep,
you can leave a message.
Mum, I've just finished. It's...
Excuse me, do you have a phone charger?
No.
Do you want to use mine?
20 HOURS OF ROBBERY
- Really? Don't you mind?
- No, no.
Are you sure? Thanks.
I have to make a couple of calls.
- It's all right.
- Thanks a lot.
SATURDAY 6:25 AM
Mum, I've just finished, I'm on my way.
Superintendent Sánchez,
leave your message.
This is inspector Murillo.
I know it's late,
but I wanted to tell that,
if Intelligence is in charge,
due to I don't know
which type of diplomatic interests,
I'm not gonna be your straw inspector.
while those gorillas
enter there with everything.
I would love to be more flexible
and put my panties down
every time that Prieto squawks,
but I don't have the guts
so I see myself in the obligation...
to resign. Good night.
Good morning.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Excuse me, but you're...
It's you...
I started telling
the story of a kidnapping,
because everybody will remember
those days of siege
in the Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
The streets downtown were closed,
the TV made live broadcasts the 24 hours,
the police burnt their academy manuals
and they didn't know
how to eat that pie in the sky
of those poor wretches trying to print
their own money,
but many other things happened
and nobody remembers them,
things that changed us all
to the point of not knowing
who the bad guys were...
and who the good guys were.
Excuse me,
when you negotiate with those people,
do you give them what they want
or do you just have a chinwag
to buy some time or...?
- Well, don't answer me, I just...
- Every case is different.
Sure, I'm sorry.
But...
But well, yes,
we try to calm things down
and buy some time.
Thanks.
In fact, we were the ones buying time,
the sentence time is money
had never been better used.
A lot of money.
Every hour we printed eight million euros,
1400 sheets of paper money
from which we cut
140,000 50 euro notes.
Everything was so calm
during the hours of dawn
that it seemed the plan
was going smoothly.
The Profesor was our Big Brother,
controlled the police radio
and 18 cameras,
so if somebody wanted to fuck us,
we'd knew it well in advance.
We took turns to watch the hostages,
the entries and of course
the production.
After only 20 hours there
the presses had already spit
52 million euros,
so at that point
we all thought it was possible.
But all that calm was just the dead calm
before the storm,
things were going to screw up so much
we would be on the brink
of losing the game.
And if you ask me why,
I'll say it's due to a simple love story.
After all, love is a good reason
to make everything go wrong.
My daughter, I know
you don't like Paula sleeping in your bed,
but she insisted
and I didn't want to argue with her.
Don't get angry.
He has also insisted
on having pasta and melon for dinner.
I know it's a little stodgy,
maybe she'll wake up.
My dear, it's two o'clock.
The girl has woken up
and has puked a little bit,
next time I don't give her melon.
She's already asleep,
she told me she's very nervous.
Remember that tomorrow
it's her birthday.
I'd like to ask you a favour.
May I?
There's movement.
Everyone ready.
Deputy inspector,
they're opening the doors.
There are seven men,
armed with M-16s, sir.
Everybody stand by.
Stand by my order.
Don't do anything, all right?
- It's a unique opportunity.
- Don't do anything.
Take out your mask.
I'm begging you, please, not to shoot.
My name's Mónica Gaztambide.
She's a hostage.
I'm just here to read a statement.
I'm speaking on behalf of the robbers.
The situation is this.
We're 67 hostages,
all of us in perfect health
and well cared of.
There are no victims or wounded.
We're all dressed alike
and it's impossible to tell us
from the robbers,
so any attempts of assault
- could cost the lives...
- The Dalí with the megaphone
is giving her orders.
The one with the megaphone is a robber.
They wanted to take some money
which still belonged to no one.
Alert, all units stand by.
Target in range,
waiting for instructions.
... will tell the press
the whole truth about negotiation,
both the requests
that are accepted
as well as the ones that don't.
I require a green light, sir.
Still, still everybody,
All right? Hold still.
They regret the wounded policeman
and hope wholeheartedly
he recovers.
The one with the megaphone, sir,
is a robber.
I request the green light, sir.
Target at range.
They're coming in, last chance, sir.
Last chance, sir.
They're coming in, I repeat,
they're coming in.
No, don't shoot.
Don't shoot, do you hear me? Let them in,
let them go back in.
Do you hear me? Let them in.
As we have just seen,
the robbers have read a statement
where they said they regret
having hurt the police officers.
It seems the hostages
are in perfect health
and the assailants
do not intend to use violence.
Come on, ladies, a little energy
in the morning, and wake-up.
Come on, go to the museum.
To the museum, go!
Come on, man.
Oh, Helsin.
I want dough, dough.
You want dough, dough.
We want dough, dough.
And I want dough, dough.
Oh, God, Helsin.
Helsin, the one we're messing with, Chicky.
Do you know what we're doing?
Do you know that now
the whole world, the whole press,
all the newspapers, the radio
are going to start talking about us.
because we are heroes,
because no one has done this?
I'm gonna tell the truth.
We are locked up
and we really don't know
how long this could last,
but as long as they don't blow
my head up, I'll take care of you.
As long as you don't try to trick me,
or communicate with the outside,
everything will be fine.
If you have any heroic concerns,
I advise you to forget it.
There are nicer ways
to make your co-workers fall in love.
From now on we're getting organized.
We're giving you some tasks
so you don't feel down.
- What's your name?
- Pablo.
Do you do sport?
Yes, I'm the athletic captain at school.
Step forward, captain.
Step forward.
Man!
Arturito.
- Did you sleep well?
- Well, yes.
Fine. Tell me, are you good at DIY?
No, no, sir, I'm totally hopeless.
In fact, when I have a flat tyre,
my wife changed it.
Are you telling me you don't have a drill?
- No.
- Think carefully what you say,
because I have
a fucking lie detector right here.
Yes.
Let's see... Second chance.
Are you good at DIY?
- I hold my own.
- Step forward.
What's your name?
- Sonsoles.
- Sonsoles, step forward.
Would you feel better
if we brought you an anxiolytic?
- Yes, please.
- Very well.
- Does anyone else need medication?
- Me. I'm diabetic.
I'd need the insulin
for this afternoon.
Come with Sonsoles, please. Quickly.
And me.
I'm taking sertraline.
Anyone else?
Me.
I'd like to ask for an abortion pill.
You said you don't know
how many days we'll be here
and I'd like to sort this out
as soon as possible.
You'll get it today. You, come with me,
I'm taking you to Mr. Román's office,
you'll be more relaxed there.
I also have a request.
Yes?
I'd like to erase a picture
from the internet.
I'm sorry, that's not in my hands.
I've been tricked,
they took me to a toilet
and they got a picture of me naked.
And now my parents, my teachers,
all the media are seeing it.
You can record a message,
a video, so they calm down,
and we'll send it.
All of you will be allowed
to record messages for your families.
Nairobi, come on.
Come on, tough guys,
your hands behind your head
and move to the left in a row,
sticking your chests out
as if you were the national team.
Move, athlete.
Move.
Do you see this dotted line?
Do you see it, damn it?
You're going to break the concrete
not going one centimetre away from it,
as if it were a cut-out for children.
There are 48 metres downward
until you get to the sewer pipe.
The shift will last three hours.
And when you finish your shift
and you go back with the hostages,
not a fucking word
about what we're doing down here.
- Any questions?
- No.
That's good, which means I was clear.
Come on, let's get to work.
You, put on the hearing protection
- and take the hammer.
- I've never used one of those.
There's a first time for everything.
And be careful.
You wouldn't be the first one
to lose a foot with that.
Stop, stop, stop.
Let's see, relax your knees,
that you're going to shell out.
And enjoy, damn it.
- Dad, mum, I'm fine.
- In Spanish, please.
Hi, dad. Hi, mum.
I think a lot about you and Lis.
I'm fine, they feed us
and I've slept in a bag,
like in a camp.
Mum, this is not awful, okay?
There's no violence.
I guess you'll be crying
all day long
thinking we'd have to be
in Belfast,
but you just have to think
I'm fine,
that I'll get out, that we'll all get out.
Mum, mamá.
I guess you've seen the photo
I uploaded on the internet.
I didn't upload that photo and it doesn't
have to do with the kidnapping,
it was a classmate who tricked me and...
I can't.
It's that I don't know very well
what to say to your parents
when you're in a kidnapping.
And you show a tit over the Internet.
Well, you think the phone
is not active.
So we can repeat the video
as many times as you want
and then we send the one you like the most.
Like in the outtakes
from a movie?
Yes.
Do not give so much importance
to this photo. It's...
It's just like when you go topless
on the beach, you know?
Nobody cares.
I don't go topless on the beach.
And I don't kiss with boys
in the toilets of a museum.
When my arm was put in a cast
it was the most exciting thing
that happened to me this year.
A kidnapping is more exciting.
Well, think about
what you're telling your parents, okay?
And calm down, I'll wait for you. Here.
- You're serious. What's wrong?
- Why the fuck do you care?
I'm just a child, the bedtime hobby
of the last five months, right?
The silly guy with the badge.
I said you were a child
and that I never would be with you
so that you didn't get a bullet
in your breastbone,
because I don't give a damn
if it's me who gets it.
You don't believe that,
you didn't do it for me.
What's the matter with you all?
Since I came here
you're always making scenes.
They've turned on a phone.
It's Alison Parker's.
Hack it.
You know what's up?
I'm sure you've waited
until we got of Toledo to start
with all this fucking shit
that I'm a child.
She's trying to log in in her profile.
Come on, come on.
If I was your fucking gigolo,
just tell me.
You were my fucking gigolo.
You were everything.
- I'm inside.
- Record it.
I don't want to go on
with this conversation.
You have the fucking nerve
to tell me you're mourning
for your boyfriend, right?
You didn't seem to be mourning
when you asked me
to push you against the wall.
I didn't see the rosary
among your fingers.
If you ever talk to me that way,
I'll smash your face.
Change to selfie camera.
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
- No, no!
- Fucking hell, give me that!
Hold on!
It's offline.
Rewind.
Stop it. Double the pixels.
We've got him.
You know my bubbles
are magical, aren't they?
Yes!
Because the wishes are fulfilled.
Yes?
I have a gift for the girl,
I'm at the door.
You have a restraining order,
Get the hell out of here.
I want to see my daughter
on your birthday.
And you can trample on me,
but not her.
I'm recording you.
Aitana.
What do you got there?
- What's in your hand, honey?
- I don't have anything.
Show it to me.
Let's see, open your hand.
Open your hand. What is this,
where did you get it from?
Where we paint ourselves
the butterflies.
- Hello?
- You call me at six in the morning
and leave a confusing message
where you talk about being a figurehead,
thugs and empty words.
That you would like to be elastic
and get your panties down.
Well, I'm not bearing that in mind.
You resign and leave a robbery
with 67 hostages inside.
I'm just phoning you
so you fucking tell me
you're not taking on it.
I'm taking on it.
Raquel, there are things
which are above you.
National Security,
the Foreign Office, the CNI...
But, remember well,
you're the only person I know
who can solve this without violence.
Thanks, superintendent.
And now go back to that tent
and take the lead.
We have the face of one of the robbers.
Cheer up, come on!
I know they're tired,
but that's one hour, one hour!
One more hour,
one million in one hour
and what's left over for you,
I swear on my mother!
Come on, man!
To burst the machine,
to put it to the top!
Nobody did this!
- They're going to kill us.
- But what are you saying?
- Hush!
And then they'll run away
using the tunnel
we're making for them.
It'll be a slaughter.
Shut up, you don't know anything.
Think for a while, huh? Do you think
they are so stupid as to let us free
so we go to the police station
to recognise them? Think, jeez.
We're fucked up.
Two times they've told me
I'm a dead man.
- Look what's under the canvas.
- Huh?
Look what's under them.
I'm not staying here
waiting like a guinea pig
on my knees to be killed
without doing anything.
Look under the canvas,
see if you find weapons at least, come on.
- I'll cover you, come on.
- No way, no way.
Put your gut into it.
What's the matter, captain?
- No way, no way.
- Weren't you the captain
- of the rugby team?
- Athletics.
Hurry then.
There are containers.
- It's petrol.
- Jesus!
- And ammunition.
- Holy shit!
What's that?
Are they drugs?
This is heroin. It's heroin, man.
Jeez, leave that right now,
it's fucking plastic explosive.
Leave it, come to dig, come to dig.
Can anybody tell me why that machine
- isn't working?
- We're resting.
You'll rest when I tell you.
Or when it's your turn.
Okay, we're going on now.
Inspector, please.
Inspector, is there a conflict
between Intelligence and the Police?
Were the negotiations cancelled
because of your family situation
- after your complaint for ill-treatment?
- What?
That's all, okay?
- How does that scum know that?
- I don't know.
You're already back?
- Have you got a minute?
- Sure.
Colonel Prieto.
Look, I've been a bit nervous
these last hours,
but I'd like to keep
a smoother communication with you.
I think both of us
can contribute a lot in this crisis.
I appreciate your "mea culpa".
So here I am,
completely at your disposal.
But I want you to know,
before there are any misunderstandings,
that I'm a married man.
Raquel, Raquel.
A male, not older than 25,
we recorded him with Alison Parker's
- mobile phone.
- Identity?
We're on it, facial recognition
are checking the PERPOL.
- I want to see the whole video.
- Play the image.
We couldn't record more than six seconds.
Stop it there.
It looks like a Makarov.
No, it's a Strizh 9mm, it's also Russian.
It's rare to see them here.
Tell the judicial police to question
all the informers from the East
in control of the black market.
- What's that on the wall?
- Telephones.
Play the images of the back camera.
What do the labels say? Enlarge.
The hostage list?
They're their phones.
Recognition can have his identity
- in an hour or two.
- No.
No, we're not waiting so long.
Don't you find striking
such a special connection?
I was just about to call you,
at this very moment.
Well, considering I'm the negotiator
- and you the robber...
- But we shouldn't allow
this crime interfere
with our relationship.
Don't know about you,
but I see this as a chance.
- A chance for what?
- To get to know each other.
I assure you that if we had met in a bar,
you wouldn't have paid
any attention to me.
Tell me, inspector.
Have you ever faked an orgasm?
No.
Please, inspector,
I beg you, don't lie to me.
Think about it, please.
Maybe yes, maybe I've done it.
Look, men are programmed to ejaculate
within the shortest time.
Women, to last
the longest time possible.
And that small feature of nature
sometimes is solved with a fake orgasm.
of nature sometimes is solved
with a fake orgasm.
And that's nothing but a small swindle.
A lie.
Such as last evening's intervention,
with three elite corps.
Inspector, I'm begging you
not to lie to me,
you'll put at risk innocent people.
I won't. And now tell me,
why did you want to call me?
Look, we need food and some medication:
insulin, sertraline, albuterol,
an abortion pill
- and anxiolytics.
- An abortion pill?
Requests from the hostages.
We all have personal problems,
don't you think?
- You'll get those requests.
- Fine.
Civil Protection will make the delivery,
in transparent bags
to avoid hidden weapons.
And now tell me,
you phoned me to...
So you surrender immediately.
I've got images from the inside,
I've got the identity of one of your men.
If I keep on pulling the thread,
I'll know the identity
of the rest of the gang.
- Inspector, I think...
- I'm offering you a deal.
I can lower your sentences
from 16 to 8 years,
if you get out of there right now.
Nobody has died
and that gives me a little margin.
I don't think it's a fair deal,
we lose out.
You've already lost.
Look, in the rare event
you get out of there,
your faces will be in the news,
police stations and borders.
You're left without a plan B.
- Then we'll activate plan C.
- You think I'm bluffing, right?
Frankly, yes.
I'll tell you something
so you see I'm not lying:
you've got 67 mobile phones
attached with Velcro on the wall.
I give you one hour to accept my offer.
Listen, inspec....
What if it doesn't work out?
- What's gonna happen if it doesn't work out?
- Let's see, puppy,
the same as always:
back to the gaol,
to the cigarette in the courtyard,
to the four prawns for Christmas,
- the vis-a-vis, sometimes.
- A luxury!
The fucked up is if it goes well.
What the hell are we going to do
with so much dough?
I'm going to get a Maserati,
clear blue sky, huh?
- Say yes.
- And a martial arts gym.
I see it.
And a big joint,
but three-story, huh?
With speakers that bleed your ears.
- Boom, boom, bam, bim bam bum.
- Say yes.
- This one with three million has plenty.
- And for you some lungs,
that you've got them fucked up
of the mine.
You're going to spend it on that,
in some lungs?
You're a piece of work.
And can you tell where the fuck
are you going to take out some lungs?
If there are people who sell their kidneys,
there'll be people selling lungs,
I think.
Well, I in a wine cellar in Provence.
In hectares of vineyard
to grow my own wine,
oak barrels...
But you can go to the supermarket
that you like
and buy the bottle that you want.
Why are you going
to set up a wine cellar?
For art.
So I want an island.
- And me another.
- Then put on three.
- Three is a crowd already.
- An archipelago.
No, I want a little island
with an enormous house,
and a balcony
that is attached to the sea.
It's me getting out of bed
and straight into the water.
Well, finally someone smart.
I think some of us first have to fix
some business, don't we?
Come on, at least I do.
And listen, then with what
I can spare for a plane.
- To drive it myself.
- Being able to have a very hot pilot...
You don't get it,
what's cool is to tease
the guy in the control tower and say:
"Hey, give airstrip for the artist."
If we buy all those things
let's say for a price...
I don't know, an expensive price,
a very expensive price.
Even then we'd still
have a huge amount of money.
If we're going to steal big,
dream big.
I would record an album.
Of corridos.
Like that, and on the cover all my face.
You are going to be like Bertín Osborne,
but with 30 kilos more.
- Uy, uy.
- What are you talking about?
Bertín sings rancheras,
I told you corridos,
which is something very different.
Show him what a corrido is, Dad.
- No way, man...
- Come on.
- Come on, come on.
- Come on, go for it.
- But if you love to do it.
- How am I going to sing?
Sing! Sing! Sing!
He's even up.
For the lack of your lips
I cried for the first time
and I cursed to know you
for not stopping loving you.
I wanted to make you my wife,
without love I sought luck,
I was pulling a gun
and fate brought death.
María, my life, my love.
I won't stop loving you,
to bullets I lost you,
you'll never see me again.
Hello, Profesor?
They have an image
of all the phones on the wall.
There are no security cameras
there, right?
No, of course not, only the one we set.
So it was one of the hostages.
You missed a phone, so find it
- or we're screwed up.
- Give me permission to punish him.
Either we block them with panic
or they'll keep on playing the heroes.
- What punishment?
- An exemplary punishment.
- His execution, for example?
- No.
Find that phone.
We must call the police
and guide them through the assault.
There's a phone in my office,
in a coat that's hanging
- from a hanger.
- No way.
- Listen, you've had 40 seconds...
- You go!
I can't, I can't.
You know what'd happen
if there's somebody there?
- They'd shoot me.
- Just like...
I want to hear
that machine working, jeez!
- I don't want to say that again!
- Sorry, sorry, we're sorry.
- He's very tired. Sorry.
- I can't go on.
- I'm going to die, I can't go on.
- Come on, get out of there.
Get out and rest.
That phone that for Arturo
it seemed like salvation
was actually
stained with death.
And what they didn't do
cowardly
would make him the most innocent
with that fatality that love gives,
sealing your destiny
for the rest of his days.
Are you really going to abort?
Sorry about what I said yesterday, Mónica.
It was out of place, I was an arsehole.
I've never been a very brave guy,
you know?
I've spent all my fucking life
doing what the others
wanted from me,
never what I wanted to do.
And I needed to be
in a situation such as this, jeez,
with guns and bullets,
to realise
what I really want.
And I'm going to think about me.
Me and you.
And that baby you have inside.
I love you, Mónica.
I love you so much, that I know.
You're the best
that's ever happened to me.
I want you to continue with the pregnancy
and I want you to let me be his father.
We're going to have a baby.
And I want to form a family with you
if we get out of here.
What do you mean, if we get out?
- They're digging a tunnel.
- What?
Yes, they have a lot of plastic explosive
and petrol containers.
- Stand up!
- It'll be a slaughter.
There's one way: contact the police
and guide them in the assault.
I've got a phone in my office,
in the coat.
I don't know how to get there.
- I'll go.
- No, no, no.
There's always a hero...
who thinks he can save the others.
Who thinks...
nobody will notice that he's plotting
a strategy to contact the police.
Bravo.
Congratulations,
because one of you made it,
recorded an image from the inside
and sent it to the police.
Aníbal Cortés, born in Getafe.
He's an alarm expert, worked for two years
in security companies,
he's associated with the robbery
of a mansion in Geneva.
He's got a warrant
issued by the Interpol.
So I'd like to give him the chance
to step forward
so you can all thank him.
And also give me that phone.
He must have visited the Casa de la Moneda
to study the alarm systems.
Check the hard drives
of the security company.
With a bit of luck,
maybe he went there
with some other gang members.
Helsinki.
Undress him.
Come on.
Are you sick or what?
Pay attention.
Come on, take off your shirt.
- Come on.
- It was one of you.
I don't know who it was.
Denver, undress her.
You recorded a video
in the phone room, right?
- What's up?
- I can't breathe.
Let me go with the girls.
Let me go with the girls!
Berlín, I'm taking her away.
- Berlín, Berlín.
- What's the matter now?
I know what happened.
"An assault to the epicentre of money,
the most outstanding robbery ever.
Bizarre robbery calls
international attention."
- What do you think? Do you want a coffee?
- Jesus, we have an officer in the ICU,
67 hostages,
a lot of guys armed to the teeth
and for the reporters
this is something colourful.
I don't care about the headlines,
what worries me
is that they have too much information
and that doesn't help us.
- Listen.
- Wait.
Listen to me, all of you.
Some of you
is talking too much with his brother-in-law,
with a neighbor
or with a journalist without knowing it.
The one who opens its mouth too wide
if only to give
the bloody hour will be suspended
of employment and salary.
Are you okay?
I'm going out for lunch.
I'll be back in 15 minutes.
All right.
Do I go with you?
No. It's better.
Don't let your wife see us
and get jealous.
Listen, the inspector is coming out.
Move the paparazzi away.
I got distracted for a while
and I saw Alison trying
to erase the fucking photo, that's all.
A mistake, that's all.
What's up,
have you got an attention deficit?
Because if you're
one of those children with problems,
I should be the first to know.
I haven't got any problems.
Tokio came in, all right?
And we argued, that's it.
- It won't happen again.
- Now I see.
One more time, it all comes down
to a sentimental reason.
You don't know
how much you remind me of myself.
I was 18, she was 44,
she was my French teacher,
- I was outstanding.
- I don't know what this is about,
- Tokio isn't 44.
- She's 15 years older than you.
And when you're young
and you're with a woman
who's halfway through,
everything sublimates.
They've got the experience
teenage girls don't have
and they're even more grateful
than the ugly ones.
My teacher gave me
her mature flesh every time
as if it was my fucking birthday.
You know why?
Because with you
they savour the lost youth,
before tumbling down
the slope of age.
Of course...
Of course there's a small difference
between your love story and mine.
In my case, I wasn't
in a robbery with hostages,
endangering my mates' lives.
- Are you still hurt from yesterday or what?
- A little bit.
Hey, what I told you about the rosary
was not good at all,
I was an asshole.
Sorry.
Yes, but I like you like this.
It's that I'm retarded.
I get into a robbery with 70 hostages.
and me there,
- with the engagement plate.
- You are original.
I don't think many girls
can brag about something like that.
When you had the hots
for somebody
you don't think straight.
Furthermore, you said it yourself
and you're right,
love is not the same
as a couple of shags.
Are you trying to leave me?
There's nothing to leave.
I'm just remarking on the situation.
And what's changed
from yesterday to today?
Well, what you said about age
and that I don't see you excited
with our affair.
And I've been talking for five minutes
with that girl...
With Alison. And...
And I've realized
that you're right,
I have to look for a young girl,
like her.
Fucking hell, you've got a nerve!
Do I get my badge back?
Your little plate.
Look who's coming.
So it's already clear
what you have to say?
- Yes, sir.
- Wonderful,
picking up the lesson
quick on the uptake.
Ready?
Leave the boxes on the ground
and go back really slowly.
There's a phone in my office,
in a coat...
It's very hot here.
- I'm going...
- Hey!
May I?
Sit down.
Sit down!
The medicine is here.
Hand them out.
- I'm going to sit down.
- Wait.
Come outside.
You may think
what I'm telling you is bullshit.
Doesn't make much sense
to tell you this.
a guy with a gun, right?
I don't think
abortion is a very good idea.
Thanks.
The kidnappers have been locked up
in the Fábrica Nacional de Moneda...
They're not leaving that place, right?
Those people I say.
I imagine they'll be buying time
to set some kind of strategy or...
You must be desperate
to do something like that, right?
That's what makes them so dangerous.
No, but they don't want to hurt anybody.
Well, that's what they said.
So they wouldn't be armed,
don't you think?
Sure, I guess you're right.
But you don't try to rob
the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre
with a slingshot, right?
The bill, please.
And...? Do you know how many they are?
Because in some places
they say they're seven.
Excuse me.
Yes.
- Raquel, the boy was at the museum.
- How long ago?
Three months ago, the cameras got him
- as part of a guided tour.
- Was he alone?
No, you were right, he was with someone.
Listen, we have the identity
of another robber,
they sent you his picture
from judiciary police,
you should receive
it right now.
Ah!
- Where have you got it?
- What are you talking about?
- Where is the recorder?
- But what...?
It's a coincidence you're here every day
- asking me questions.
- I don't know...
- Who do you work for?
- Pardon?
- Who the fuck do you work for?
- I'm not a journalist,
my name's Salvador Martín,
look my wallet. Antonio, please.
- What's the matter, Salva?
- I don't know...
I know him, he comes here every day.
You need dough for the baby, right?
- Yes.
- No, no...
Yes. Listen, this is a robbery,
you may get something for you.
No, not really.
Hide this in your underwear now.
20 000 bucks, you can buy nappies for him
- until he leaves university.
- It's not that.
It's really not that.
I appreciate it, but...
Give me the pill
and I'm going back inside.
Fine.
So what's up?
- He'll screw up your life.
- Pardon?
Your son.
It's better he screws up your life
rather than any
of these motherfuckers, or me.
- Are you going to screw up my life?
- Life gets screwed up very easily.
One day you're working smoothly,
four lunatics with Dalí masks come in,
one of them goes crazy,
he shoots his gun
and fuck off.
This screw up your life.
Not a baby.
- A baby doesn't screws your life.
- What do you know about what screws me up?
What do you know?
My mother wanted to abort me.
But before, she chased the dragon
with the junk he had to sell
to pay for the abortion.
And the municipal police
arrested her in a shitty portico.
I was born among the jail,
the drugs and the police.
And what do you know?
Because it seems your job
is not one adventure after another,
and when you go out
it isn't a party, either.
- Or do you do "kilates"?
- Pilates...
So I was right.
And you go for a drink on Friday.
Fucking shit, girl,
another plan screwed up due to the baby.
Who do you go out with?
Where are your friends?
I'll tell you. At home, with their babies.
Do they look screwed up? No, right?
What crazy thing do you do
that you can't do with a baby?
Do you go in summer to India
to spend 15 days having the runs?
You better go to Gandía,
that you can drink from the faucet
and eat pizza.
If his father is an arsehole
and he misses it, that's better,
all his affection for you.
Do you know how much he can love you?
What are you doing, Denver?
I'm giving her the pill to abort.
What's up? Does she need you
to put it in her mouth
with a little water?
Abortion is a private thing, right?
Women decide,
but not in front of everybody.
Anyway, I'm...
I'll think about it
until we get out of here.
Wonderful.
I'm glad you want to continue
with the pregnancy.
Really.
Now go back to the office with the others.
Did you just come from a stag party?
Or were you going there?
That wasn't the first time
Berlín put his hand
in the knickers of an honest woman,
but it'd be the first time
he'd take it out so soon.
Maybe Mónica would have preferred
him to let himself go,
follow his instinct
and forget about the phone
that had rung between her legs,
but it wasn't so.
Denver.
What will happen with our authority
when I tell the others?
Even Berlín could
distinguish pleasure from duty.
Kill her.
You heard me.
Let's see.
You can sense it, suspect it,
but in a fraction of a second.
you suddenly realize
those things don't add up
and that Río still loved me
and she didn't just leave me.
I could feel it so strongly
that pierced the walls,
as strong as love
that I always end up feeling
by all the men who take care of me,
whether they are drug dealers,
assholes, kids.
And I felt it just like the first day
that I held him in my arms,
the two of us thrown between the stones
of a field in Toledo.
Let's see, we'll be back in 30 minutes.
30 minutes, Denver.
Permission.
Well, I'm going to run for a while,
to stretch the legs a little.
Use it, there's a lot of countryside.
Learn a language
is a lot easier than it looks,
but you have to leave
semantics aside.
For the first time I realised
there was something
that had always been wrong
in all my love affairs.
They had always taken care of me.
But this time it'd be different.
What's up? Jesus, Tokio, Tokio. Tokio!
Jesus, go and find Berlín.
Listen to me. If anybody
touches him again,
I swear to God that the next shot
will be against Helsinki,
Berlín or against you.
You're out there, free,
while we're risking
our fucking lives in this mouse trap.
Helsinki, put the gun down.
What are you doing?
Helsinki.
Put the gun down.
Don't do it, please.
Why did you have to get
that fucking phone?
Why the hell did you have to trick me?
Río, don't!
Where do you think you're going?
You did more than enough today.
Helsinki.
Do you know what will happen
if I don't kill you?
- They'll kill me.
- No...
And then they'll kill you.
So now what?
I wasn't even listening to my shouts,
I only wanted to write
a fucking love letter.
While the guns and the gazes
were pointing at me,
reality fell like a concrete slab
and I knew the five months
during which I had believed in something
were over
Your love story has fucked up
your escape plan. They've got you.
And Río too,
the police know who you are.
You're in every news programme.
For fuck's sake.
Come on, man.
On your knees.
No.
Don't look at me.
- Please.
- Don't fucking look at me,
don't fucking look at me.
NEXT EPISODE
Get down, everybody!
Don't move!
For the last time,
return to your position.
Get down, everybody!