THE FACTS AND SCENARIOS REPRESENTED
IN THIS SERIES ARE FICTITIOUS
Stop or I'll shoot!
No!
My name's Tokio.
But when this story started,
that wasn't my name.
This was me.
SUSPECT'S WHEREABOUTS UNKNOWN
And this, the love of my life.
ROBBER GETS SHOT DEAD
The last time I saw him
I left him in a pool of blood
with his eyes open.
We did 15 clean robberies,
but mixing love and work never works.
So, when the security guard shot,
I had to change my job.
From robber to murderer.
And that's how I started to run away.
Somehow, I was dead too.
Or almost dead.
I had been hidden for 11 days
and my photo wallpapered
police stations all over Spain.
I'd get a 30 years' sentence.
And I'm really not the type of girl
who likes getting old
in the cell of a prison.
I prefer running away.
Body and soul.
And if I can't take my body there,
at least let my soul escape.
I had no time left and there were
important things I had to do.
Just one, really.
Hello?
Mum?
Oh, my girl.
How are you, sweetheart?
What's happening?
Haven't you seen the news?
All those things they say about me.
Yes, of course I've seen them.
You know what?
I'm thinking about going on a journey.
I may join a Chinese ship.
As a cook.
Didn't you say
I couldn't even make an omelette?
So I'll learn. What do you think?
I don't know, sweetheart.
What if they only eat Chinese food?
What does that journey mean,
that I won't see you again?
Don't talk nonsense.
Of course you'll see me.
I'll buy you a ticket
so you come to visit me.
Visit you where?
At the cemetery?
Are you alone?
Mum, are you alone?
Yes.
Then go to the street,
as if you went to the market.
I'll find you.
And that day,
the day I was going to the slaughterhouse,
my guardian angel appeared.
But you never know for certain
what a guardian angel looks like,
and you'd never imagine
he'd appear in a Seat Ibiza
of 1992.
Excuse me, have you got a minute?
No.
Cooking in a Chinese ship
only has one advantage,
you don't have to do the washing-up.
For a moment I thought about the Chinese
and that I hate people who spit.
- Who are you, a policeman?
- Wait, wait.
You're going to the slaughterhouse,
there's a squad waiting for you
and they have a car since six days ago...
Why would I believe you?
And that's how I met the Profesor,
pointing a gun to his balls.
May I?
The good thing about relationships
is that you finally forget
how they started.
May I?
They're already in your mother's house.
That's why I came to help you.
I want to propose you some business,
a robbery, a robbery that's...
singular.
I'm looking for people who...
Well, people who don't have much to lose.
What do you think about...
2400 million euros?
Nobody had done a job like that,
neither in New York,
nor in London, nor in Monte Carlo.
So if my picture was again in the papers,
at least it'd be due
to the biggest robbery ever.
WELCOME
I welcome you
and... I thank you
for having accepted this...
this job offer.
We'll live here,
far from the worldly noise.
Five months, the five months
we'll spend studying
- how to do the job.
- What do you mean, five months?
Are we crazy?
Look, people spend years studying
to earn a salary,
a salary which, in the best of cases,
is just a salary, a shitty salary.
What are five months?
I've been thinking about this...
for much longer.
Not to have to work ever again.
Neither you
nor your children.
Okay.
You don't know each other yet
and I want it go on like that.
I don't want any names,
or personal questions,
or, of course, personal relationships.
I want each of you to choose a name,
something simple.
It can be numbers, planets, cities...
- Like "Mister 17, miss 23."
- That's a wrong start. I can't
- remember my telephone number.
- That's why I said that.
- And planets?
- I can be Mars, and he Uranus.
I won't be Uranus, so forget it.
- What's the matter with Uranus?
- I don't like the rhyme.
- It'll be cities. Cities.
- So cities it is.
Okay.
That's why I ended up being Tokio.
The one looking at my arse is Mr. Berlín.
Under arrest warrant.
27 robberies.
Jewelleries, auction houses
and security vans.
His biggest job,
the Champs Elysees, in Paris.
434 diamonds.
He's like a shark in a swimming pool.
You can swim with him,
but you're never calm.
And he was the boss
in charge of the assault.
The one who coughs is Mr. Moscú.
The first thing he dug was a mine,
in Asturias.
MOSCOW
Then he understood
that digging upwards he'd go further.
Six fur shops, three clock shops
and the Caja Rural in Avilés.
He uses the thermal lance
and any industrial equipment.
The one sitting
behind Moscú is Denver, his son.
Drugs, teeth, broken ribs.
He's the king of fights in discos.
Pure hot blood.
In a perfect plan, a time bomb.
Río. He's my weakness.
He's like Mozart, but with computers.
He programmes since he was six and knows
everything about alarms and electronics.
For the rest of things in life
it's as if he had been born yesterday.
And those are the Siamese twins,
Helsinki and Oslo.
Even the most sophisticated plan
needs soldiers
and who better than two Serbs.
Maybe they think,
but, frankly, we'll never know.
Nairobi,
a hardened optimist.
She has forged banknotes
since she was 13.
And now she's our quality manager.
She might be crazy,
but she's really funny.
Think that every day
they'll talk about us in the news,
every family in the country
will be wondering
what we're doing.
And you know what they'll think?
They'll think: "Bastards!
I wish I had come up with that idea."
The Profesor,
no criminal record, no register.
The last time he renewed
his ID he was 19.
To all intents, a ghost,
but a very smart ghost.
We're not stealing... anybody's money,
because they'll even think we're nice.
And that is vital.
It's vital we have the public opinion
on our side.
We're going to be the fucking heroes
of all those people.
But very careful,
because the moment there is
a single drop of blood,
this is very important,
if there's a single victim,
we'll stop being Robin Hoods
and we'll simply become sons of a bitch.
Profesor.
Miss Tokio.
What are we going to steal?
The Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
DAY OF THE ROBBERY
FRIDAY 8:35 A.M.
Who chose the mask?
- What's up with the mask?
- It's not scary.
In bank robbery films
the masks are scary.
They're zombies, skeletons,
the death, I don't know, you feel...
With a gun in your hand
I assure you a madman
is scarier than a skeleton.
- Stop it.
- Who was this guy with the moustache?
Dalí, son, a Spanish painter.
He was very good.
- A painter.
- Yes.
- A painter of paintings.
Do you know what's fucking scary?
Dolls for children.
They're really scary.
What dolls?
Goofy, Pluto, Mickey Mouse, all those.
A mouse with ears is scarier,
that's what you're saying?
Yes, arsehole.
Do you want me to wallop you?
- Hey!
- I'm right. Listen to me.
If a guy at gunpoint
and wearing a Mickey Mouse mask
gets in a place,
the people will think he's nuts,
there's going to be a massacre.
Do you know why?
Because guns and children
are two things
you never put together, daddy.
- Am I right or not?
- That way it'd be more dangerous,
more twisted.
So a Jesus Christ mask
would frighten more, he's more innocent.
They say "It doesn't suit you,
it's like Christ with two guns."
- "Like a saint with two guns."
- It doesn't matter.
It was obvious
there was a lack of women in the gang.
A woman can spend two days
choosing shoes for a wedding,
but she'd never use a single minute
to choose masks for a robbery.
Everything we had planned was starting now
and during those fractions of a second
I thought about all the innocent people
whose lives we would stop
in their tracks.
E-80 LOCAL ROAD
The Profesor knew
there was just one way to come
in the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre
with three tonnes
of explosive devices.
It had to be done in the lorry
that entered the building every week
with the new paper money rolls
ready to be printed.
And that was what we were going to do,
getting to the very core,
escorted by the National Police.
In Spain, anything guarded
by two police cars
is something heavily protected.
But if you inhibit any possibility
for their communication
through the radio or telephone
and if you point two 26-year-old kids
with five assault rifles at their heads,
it doesn't matter if they have guns,
and they feel just like it'd happen
to any of us.
I said get out of the fucking car!
- They're scared shitless.
- You'll do as I say!
Courage and heroism have a price,
and it's greater
than the 1600 euros a month
- a kid with a uniform gets...
- Open the lorry, do you hear me?
... or a lorry driver.
Come on, damn it, open!
If those men had had their daughter
on the back of the lorry,
they'd never have opened it,
but who cares about
some paper money rolls
with a watermark?
Hurry up, hurry up!
Jeez, man! Come on!
Come on, come on!
Sit down. Now calm down, the three of you,
otherwise, a blow with the rifle.
You'll drive with a gun in your kidneys.
When you get the radio call
to know if everything's all right,
you'll answer coolly,
as if everything ran smoothly.
Am I clear?
And in the middle of that chaos with guns
I remembered the night before
I had been asked for my hand in marriage
and that I'd have preferred other plans.
But if you think about it,
you never find a good day for a robbery.
Now you know what you have to do.
Don't take your eyes off the girl.
There can't be any mistakes, all right?
She's 17.
I think I can handle her.
"Can I sit by your side?"
"Sure".
Hello.
Do you want to go out with me?
Okay. I'm leaving.
No, no.
I don't have to think about it.
I mean, yes.
Okay, children, we've arrived.
Let's go straight
to the museum's hall, where...
Pedro, please, don't behave like in class.
Let's go out in an orderly way,
using both doors...
And this is the façade
of the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre.
The little lamb is coming in.
Perfect.
Berlín, your turn.
And now, be careful what you do.
How are you, Javi? Where's Rafita?
Shift change.
Very well. Keep calm.
Okay, children, get in.
Slowly.
This is important.
As soon as we get the accreditations...
Keep you accreditations
hanging from your neck.
They must be visible
during the whole visit, okay?
Don't turn around.
When you're next to me,
I can't even breathe.
Well, breathe,
because in nine months
you will really be out of breath.
Go ahead.
Well visible during the whole visit,
children.
The accreditation in your neck.
Lower your voice.
Berlín, the first camera, on your left.
Aren't you going to say anything?
I tell you I'm pregnant,
and you just keep calm?
What shall I do, call my wife,
tell her to pick up the children
and we all go to celebrate?
For God's sake!
Go on, go on. Come on.
ACCESS TO SECURITY SYSTEM
Coming in.
Be alert, Tokio.
ACCESS TO ALARM SYSTEM
Great!
- Alarms disengaged.
- Now.
Go ahead, come on.
It was you who said yesterday
you're in a bad situation,
- you can't stand her, you have problems.
- Problems just like any couple, Mónica,
like any other married couple
with three children,
not that I want to get divorced.
Mónica, I've had three children,
all of them with in vitro fertilisation.
I've been having sterile intercourses
with my wife for over 20 years
and now you tell me this.
You must be Shiva,
the goddess of fertility.
What are you insinuating?
I didn't come here
looking for a pension, you know?
Or for a divorce,
and much less for a paternity test.
I thought you loved me.
And...
And I think it's a nice idea.
Hard to make it fit in our lives, but...
but a wonderful idea.
Listen!
What? Do you want to know
what I'm going to do with your child?
- That's what you want, right?
- Listen to me, don't rush.
Don't move!
Freeze.
Don't move! Don't move or I'll kill you!
- What's the matter? Do something!
- Stand up! Stand up!
Get out!
Come on, come on!
Hurry up! Don't move!
Come on!
Yes, yes!
Fuck!
Come on, come on.
This way. Come on.
And this wonderful staircase,
made of marble and granite...
Don't move!
Don't move! Come on!
Get back!
- Please, don't!
- Profesor, we have a problem.
I can't see the little lamb.
I can't fucking see her!
Miss Parker, where have you gone?
Wait.
- Please!
- Let's go! That way!
Stop. Stop.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm going too fast. I know.
Let's immortalize this, right?
Let's take a picture with your phone.
Wait...
Jesus...
Here? It's a bit seedy, right?
It's our first day.
You look so pretty.
I can't find the girl.
I can't fucking see her.
Open here. Open and look a bit sexy.
It's your phone.
If you want, you can erase it.
This is for both of us, for you and me.
Come on, come on.
With this photo
you'll be all the rage on the Internet.
Give me my phone! I said give it to me!
Give me my phone! Give it to me!
Give me the fucking phone!
Give me the phone!
First of all...
Good morning.
I'm the person who's in charge.
And, first of all, I want...
to offer my apologies.
Truly, this is not the way
to end the week.
Phone.
But you're here as hostages.
If you obey,
I guarantee you'll be left alive.
- Name.
- Alison Parker.
- PIN.
- 2078.
Phone.
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
PIN.
Why do you need the PIN?
Either you tell me the fucking PIN
or I'll blow you with my rifle butt.
How long are you pregnant for?
Eight months.
- PIN.
- 1234.
You look so smart,
but you've got that shitty PIN.
What an arsehole. Your name.
- Arturo.
- Arturo what?
- Arturo Román.
- Arturo Román, very well. Arturito.
You're our safe-conduct here,
so I'm going to protect you.
Hey...
Give me your hands. Let go.
Let go. Let go.
What's your name?
Ariadna.
Come with me. Come.
Calm down.
Feel my hands.
- Are they the hands of a monster?
- No, no.
Because I'm not a monster.
I know perfectly how you feel.
The dry mouth, the shortness of breath...
You have to try to calm down. Breathe in.
Breathe in.
That's it.
Please, breathe with me, all of you.
Breathe in.
Easy, easy.
Make yourself responsible
for your breathing. Breathe out.
Very well. Very well.
Miss Mónica Gaztambide, please?
Don't move. Please, don't move.
- Be quiet.
- I said don't move.
Be quiet.
Miss Mónica Gaztambide,
would you be so kind as to step forward?
It's me.
You're a star, dad!
You're the best!
You can sleep very well here, dad.
You can sleep grandly here.
Oh! Dad, dad!
Fucking. Here, boom!
Boom, boom...
Come on, stop fooling around
and let's get to work. Come on, jeez.
This smells fucking great.
It smells better than roast lamb,
dad, that roast lamb.
- Lay down here, jeez.
- Come on, Jesus!
When have you had such a bed?
You didn't have it in jail.
Have you seen where we are, dad?
We're the best.
- We're the best.
- Boy, don't get this wrong.
We're very small.
Can you do anything?
Have you ever had a job?
Have you ever left you CV anywhere?
Ah. Come on, jeez.
My CV.
My CV, what for?
To take you out of Alcalá-Meco?
Do you think I feel proud of that?
12 years of my life
coming in and out of prison.
And you know why?
Why?
Because I'm not very smart, son.
And neither are you.
But the brains of this job
is another person.
And if we're lucky
and you don't act like an arsehole,
you'll leave this place
with your life settled.
- I'm not acting like an arsehole.
- Come on, jeez!
Fill them.
I want you to answer the phone
and convince whoever it is
that we are closed
- due to a technical problem. Understood?
- Yes.
I have no choice
but to point at you with a gun.
- Can you feel it?
- Yes.
Good.
Now.
Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre, tell me.
No, I'm sorry, I can't put you
through Arturo right now.
The system is down.
No, I can't bring him up here.
No, he can't come here
to pick up the phone.
No, it can't be.
No, because...
Just because,
I don't know where he is right now,
I don't know if he's in the factory,
in the museum, in the canteen
or wherever he is!
And besides, that's not my job, miss!
That was a performance worthy of an Oscar,
miss Gaztambide.
20 minutes after coming in,
we started to wire
the analogue communication system
to talk to the Profesor.
Without phones or radio frequency,
with nobody being able to hear us.
We had sealed the doors
and the alarms hadn't set off.
We were like in a time limbo,
with nobody knowing
we had taken over
the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre.
And in that sweet peace, before the storm,
it just seemed
an ordinary day.
You look handsome, right?
Who is it?
It's me, let me in.
Río, man. If the Profesor sees us,
he'll kill us, don't you know?
I know, I know.
I have to talk to you. Sit down.
- What's up?
- Sit down, jeez.
What's up?
Tomorrow's the robbery.
And we have no fucking idea
what is going to happen.
That's why I want you to know
I'm serious with you
and I understand perfectly that, well,
that you're not a child any more and...
and you may be looking for...
a more serious commitment.
That's why I want to give you something.
I didn't buy you a ring
because we're locked up here,
but as soon as I go out
I'll buy you such a big gem
you'll need to carry your hand
in a fucking wheelbarrow.
What's this?
An engagement badge?
Now at least you'll know my real name.
Right, but we're not allowed
to know each other's names.
Well, don't look at it.
But it's yours.
How should I tell you this?
Our affair has been very well, okay?
Great.
We have slept together some evenings...
What do you mean, some?
Jeez, all of them. But four or five...
Sincerely, I don't think
we're the perfect couple.
- Don't we fuck well?
- Yes, we do fuck well, wonderfully.
That's a start, right?
But you need something more
than fucking well to be a couple, right?
Are you saying that because
I'm 12 years younger than you?
I'm going to have
300 million euros, right?
I'm not a child, my life is settled.
- Really, Río, I wish we had...
- What do you mean with "had"?
There was love. There was, I was there.
There's another man, right?
Not anymore.
Look, Río,
when all this is over,
maybe you and I will go to Tahiti
and see if this works, but tomorrow
I only want to think about one thing:
not to get killed.
Río.
Río, don't.
No, no.
You left a phone on.
Well, turn it off.
The vault is open.
Put on your vests and get ready to go out.
As soon as you're ready,
we'll activate the alarm.
Berlín, ready to open the doors.
Hostages, for your security,
all of you three steps back!
A little more over here. Very well.
Okay. Everything's going to be all right.
A little closer.
Calm down.
Calm down. I can see the bags.
They're full of money.
Now they'll leave and it'll be all right.
There's a 10-33 at the Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
Z24 on our way.
We'll get there in two minutes.
Two minutes.
- Why did the alarm go off?
- I don't know.
They're just standing there,
I don't understand.
- Why don't they take the money and leave?
- I don't know!
One minute, 40 seconds.
One minute...
What's your name?
Arturo.
- Arturo, right?
- Yes. No, I haven't seen anything!
I haven't seen anything, I swear,
I haven't seen anything!
- Look at me.
- I haven't seen anything.
Come on, Arturo, look at me.
Look at me, look at me.
Hey, hey, come on.
Hey.
Do you like cinema?
Do you like it?
I'm... I'm a big fan.
Have you realised in horror films
there's always someone at the beginning,
like this, a nice guy like you,
and you think: "That guy's going to die",
- and then it happens?
- No...
He always dies.
Arturo, believe me, you're that guy.
Z24 to headquarters,
we'll be there in 30 seconds.
30 seconds.
It's vital that the police
don't have the faintest idea
about what we're doing.
We'll make them believe
we came in for a robbery,
they caught us by surprise leaving with
the money and everything was fucked up,
we took out the guns, shot point-blank
and we had no choice...
but to go back.
And then, not having hurt
anybody,
we get inside.
Let them think we're trapped like rats.
Let them think we're improvising.
Now!
Tokio! Tokio, wait, it's too soon!
Tokio!
Go out, throw the money,
shot at the ground and go back.
I'd heard that more than 30 times.
But what the Profesor didn't tell us
is that they would
also shoot point-blank.
Río, Río!
Holy shit, man!
Holy shit!
This couldn't have started
fucking worse, man!
Fuck!
Urgent support. We need urgent support.
In the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre.
We've got hostile gunfire. Officer down.
I repeat, officer down.
An M16 bullet is fired at 3510 kph.
It flies faster than the speed of sound.
So if you're shot in the heart,
you won't even hear
the bullet that has killed you.
That's how I knew I had fucked it all up,
in a millisecond,
in the same way i always do.
Let's see...
Paula, you need a purple flower there.
Paula.
I don't understand
why dad can't come tomorrow
- to my birthday party.
- I already told you, Paula.
A judge took custody away from him
and now it's me
- who will take care of you.
- It wasn't a judge.
- Really?
- No.
And who was that?
It was you. You don't want him
to come to my party.
Am I right, grandma?
Huh... Well, listen,
dad and mum are upset now.
- Things will get better, you'll see.
- Mum, please!
Inspector.
Raquel, I know it's your day off,
but there's a robbery with hostages.
The robbers tried to go out
with the money, but they couldn't.
They've hurt two officers.
It's in the Fábrica Nacional
de Moneda y Timbre.
I want you to take care
of the negotiation.
- Send me a car.
- It's parked outside.
Explain me what the fucking shit was that!
Explain me what the fuck was that!
Are you crazy?
- You've riddled two policemen!
- Calm down.
A fucking officer appeared and shot at me.
What would you have done, spitting at him?
- Fucking shit!
- What can you do, man,
what can you do,
stick to the fucking plan, jeez,
we went over it 400 million times.
We said that,
we weren't going to shoot anyone.
- I fell, blocked by the impacts...
- Shut up!
We also covered you,
but shooting at the ground,
not point-blank to their bodies.
They're taking away the injured officers.
Are the phones connected?
Cut off any wireless or radio signal.
Let's pass to analogue.
Call the Profesor.
What are you wearing?
- What happened?
- Two officers were hurt.
Who shot?
Tokio.
Connect the Profesor's cameras.
A bullet went near Río and Tokio shot.
It seems they have an affair.
Put her through.
- What?
- Is that true?
- So you have an affair with Río?
- What the fuck are you saying?
No.
The love of my life died because of me,
the last thing I would think about
is having an affair with a kid.
I shot to protect myself and my partner.
And, Mr. Profesor,
even if you think them over a lot, things
don't always turn out
the way you expect.
- What happened?
- They opened a vault
in the Fábrica de Moneda
to take the latest banknotes.
- Why didn't the alarms set off?
- There was a manual alarm,
- we guess it must have been a worker.
- How many hostages?
It's impossible to know,
the museum was open.
Give me a number.
Confirmed: 35 workers, 11 security guards
and 17 children from the British School.
- What the fuck were they doing there?
- It was a school visit.
- Do the media know about it yet?
- No, not yet.
- The robbers?
- We don't know yet.
We're getting images
from the nearby shops.
- He's lost a lot of blood.
- How many can they be?
Four went outside, we think six at least.
- Weapons?
- We know they have at least three M16.
- And they're extremely aggressive.
- The GEO are already here.
Yes, they came here in the first place.
Please, give me some good news.
The officers who were shot are alive.
Thank goodness.
Let's go.
What's up with the cameras
inside the building?
- Where's the signal?
- There's no signal.
- Why not?
- There isn't, I don't know.
They must have broken or diverted it.
We're working on it.
What about the network?
They cut off the optical fibre,
we can't hack them.
Listen carefully, all of you,
Police, Civil Protection,
I want all the phones switched off.
We're going to use the repeater
on the roof of the building
in case they make any calls.
I want any phone signal
in the whole perimeter
to get straight here.
Okay, I want
all the listening analysts here,
in two seconds. All right?
- Do we have the building layout?
- I'm considering a possible intervention.
Intense "volluto".
The public servants are
well taken care of.
What the fuck are you doing?
We have some free time.
They have to set up the camp,
send us a drone,
find the building layout.
We must give them some time
so they organize.
Hey, why did Tokio say
you're not together?
Because we're not.
Then why did I hear
every night her headboard
banging like a slide hammer?
Is she learning to dance samba
- at 5 in the morning?
- I don't know,
haven't got a fucking clue. Don't know
if she dances or she's restless.
Tell me, do I look like a sucker
to whom you can tell lies
as if you were spitting him on his face?
I'm kidding.
I would have fucked her, too.
In fact, I might try to.
I think you're wrong.
I'm very serious with her.
Very serious?
But, seriously as having a garden
and doing home improvement
- on Sundays?
- That's right.
And fill it with children.
Sit down.
Look, boy, women will give you sex and fun
because... they're programmed
to subdue so you impregnate them.
Later you'll cease to exist.
During childbirth you'll notice that.
Childbirth must be the most exciting event
in a father's life.
In childbirth, whatever comes out
from between her legs
is a nuclear warhead
that will destroy everything.
First of all, the wonderful cave
where you used to put your thingy
will never be the same again.
And while she's cursing you
and asks for the epidural,
she'll have a bowel movement.
Do you know what she means by that?
That she'll never be a sexy woman again.
And that from now on
that sucker is becoming
the centre of the universe.
They're all the same.
Believe me, I've had five divorces.
Do you know what five divorces are?
Five times I believed in love.
What fucking shit
have you got in your head?
Huh?
How the hell could Profesor
put you in charge?
Due to my sensitivity dealing with people.
Take the little lamb out of the group
and take her to an office.
And don't leave her alone.
If she needs to change her towel,
stand next to her.
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't worry. I'm taking you elsewhere
so you can rest, that's all.
Okay?
Raquel, all the communications
we keep from the inside
must be done from this phone
or the radio, not cell phones, okay?
Put me through with the interior,
I want to talk to the robbers.
Ángel, what the fuck
is colonel Prieto doing here?
I don't know. I don't know.
There are people shooting their guns
in the place where money is made.
Don't you think Intelligence
should be aware?
Calling the Fábrica
de Moneda y Timbre, Raquel.
Boss, call to the interior in progress.
Hello.
- Good afternoon.
- I'm Raquel Murillo,
the inspector in charge of the robbery.
Who am I talking to?
To the robber in charge of the assault.
- He's got a voice changer.
- Cleaning the signal.
How are your mates doing?
So far we haven't had any casualties.
I'm glad.
Really, sincerely.
Excuse me, I can't hear you well.
Yes, I'm sorry about
this hateful metallic voice,
but you must understand
I have to protect my identity,
just in case one day you give us
a helicopter and we go to Brazil.
Is that what you want, a helicopter?
What I want right now
is to negotiate with someone"
who doesn't give us the runaround,
who doesn't need to ask a superior,
Intelligence or their mum
to give me a yes or a no.
Then you should talk to the president,
but since he's busy running the country,
I'll try to stand in for him,
if you don't mind.
- Any further questions?
- Yes.
What are you wearing?
- Pardon?
- What are you wearing?
Don't you think our clothes
say a lot about our personality?
Look, I have no objection
to answer your question,
but I think I should inform you
this conversation is being heard
by several members
of the UDEF, the UIT, the CNI
and their liaison office, the chief
of the GEO and some other officers.
In that case, I think I should say hello
and introduce myself.
It's nice to meet you.
I regret I can't tell you my name,
but you can call me
Profesor, everybody calls me so.
Hello. I'm Ángel,
Deputy Inspector of Police.
Nice to meet you, Ángel.
How are you doing?
- Hello, good morning.
- Good morning.
Hello, how are you?
Very well. I'm very well,
thanks a lot. And you?
After this emotional moment, tell me,
- what do you want?
- Time...
to try and clarify things.
Listen to me, Inspector.
We couldn't go out only for
a matter of seconds, but we're
perfectly ready to defend ourselves,
so try to avoid
any kind of intervention.
- Can I trust you?
- Of course.
But in order for me to trust you,
you must make a gesture towards me.
Release those children from the school,
they're minors.
Everything will be much better that way.
But, Inspector, you still
haven't told me what you're wearing.
A grey suit jacket, a blue shirt,
black high heel boots and...
Well, I think so far that's enough, right?
So I can picture you a lot better.
But, Inspector, a suit jacket for women
can have a skirt or trousers,
so I'll ask you that next time you are
a bit more specific.
Let me think about your request.
Tell me, what sort of lunatic
with 60 hostages
thinks about teasing his negotiator?
No, he's too calm to be a lunatic.
I want helicopters flying
all day long over their heads!
No food, water or any other type
of request. Am I clear?
Excuse me, Inspector.
Just because you leave them without
dessert I don't think they'll surrender.
Both the chief of the GEO,
here present, and me
believe it's necessary
an immediate intervention.
If they wanted a massacre
like in Moscú's Opera House,
they'd have called you straightaway,
but unfortunately
you're here only to opine and bug.
Please, Inspector,
don't be on the defensive.
I'm here to help you.
I know you're not going
through your best moment.
If you mean my period, it's not the case,
but thanks for asking.
I mean the complaint of ill-treatment
you've filed against your ex-husband.
Wow, I see Intelligence
did their homework.
There isn't a single room
where they don't stick their nose, right?
Internal Affairs also do it.
They think you've brought a false report.
Your ex-husband has rebuilt his life
both personally and professionally
in the police,
but some women don't always turn the page.
Look, I don't know if you're miserable
or... just stupid.
If somebody's interested
in my personal life,
I must say
that matter has been totally got past
and it's in the hands of a judge.
Thanks for your sensitivity, colonel.
There's an incoming call
in the museum's repeater.
- Record it.
- Yes, we're recording.
Turn up the volume. Silence, please!
- Why aren't you coming for dinner?
- I'm working.
My apologies to your mother and sister.
Why aren't you coming?
There's a good mess here.
My apologies to them. Believe me.
- Don't yell at me, honey, please.
- Almansa!
I have to go, okay, sweetheart?
Okay, I love you so much. Bye.
Cut.
It's Almansa.
Why did you bring me here?
No, don't worry.
They brought me here to protect you.
Just that.
When you get naked, please,
put on the red overalls.
Fine.
Stand up.
Come on, come on.
Take out your masks.
Take out your masks!
What's the matter?
We're going to be good.
Something has come up,
but, in spite of helicopters,
I'm aware we're going
to have some quiet hours
and you'll be able to rest.
In a few minutes
we'll give you sleeping bags,
water and a sandwich.
Oh, and let me ask you a favour.
I want you to get naked.
I want to give you red overalls like ours
so you feel more comfortable.
Excuse me, sir,
I don't want to bother you.
Among these people there are people
with heart conditions,
pregnant women, diabetics, teenagers...
I beg you, please,
release those who are more vulnerable.
I don't think they can stand
this anguish all night long.
- Do you think you're fucking Gandhi?
- Denver, calm down.
He's a friend of mine.
We share our love for cinema.
Take the gun.
I'm not asking you if you want,
I'm telling you to take the gun.
Take the gun. Take the gun.
- And now aim at me.
- No, please.
I'm telling you to aim at me.
A fucking order. Aim at me, jeez.
- Here. Fine.
- No, please.
And now you shoot me.
- Pardon?
- Shoot me.
- Please.
- Please, no!
- Either you shoot me
or I'll shoot you. I give you ten seconds.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine...
They're fake, Arturito,
but you did very well.
You did very well.
It's a present, you can keep it.
Now we're giving you some fake guns.
In a few hours
we'll need your cooperation.
As you've seen, the only thing
you have to do is obey.
Trust us... and obey.
Come on, get naked.
Come on.
What are you wearing?
Raquel, no walkie-talkie, no phones,
no electronic devices.
We haven't located
any radiofrequency inside.
Are you telling me they communicate
using an empty yogurt and a string
- so we don't detect them?
- I don't know if it's a yogurt
or it's a gang of deaf-mutes,
but we can't find any frequencies.
What the fuck are
those armoured vehicles doing here?
We're getting in with everything.
That'll be if I give the order.
I'm in charge but I still haven't done it.
They're orders from above.
Is anyone going to tell me
what the fuck is going on here
or do I have to phone
the Minister of Interior Affairs?
- What the fuck is going on?
- Let's go.
Inside there's a priority 1 person.
- Do you know what "priority 1" is?
- No.
I'm not with your Intelligence gang,
I don't know.
They'll get in. They'll get in
because we have our little lamb.
Alison Parker.
Sir Benjamin Parker's daughter.
he's the UK ambassador"
and a close friend
to the Queen of England.
That's why we have no choice
but getting in,
because, if we don't do it now,
the whole country will know tomorrow.
They'll think we don't know.
They'll think they managed to hide
all that information
from the public opinion.
Today she's just another hostage,
but tomorrow she'll be the main bullseye
and all the guns will aim at her head.
Is that what you want? Huh?
That's why they'll get in the first night.
And they'll do it before 04:15 am.
Because at 6:30 begins to get light.
Do you imagine what it'd be
for Spain a hostage crisis
managed by the United Kingdom?
And it's better
if they don't hesitate to get in
because then we'll have more possibilities
to win the first battle.
Inspector Murillo,
we're getting in now
and we're taking out that girl alive.
I have to talk to you...
You've ignored me all the time.
Shut up, they'll kill us all
and it's your fault.
Sorry.
It seems you don't like
your boss much, right?
How do you know he's my boss?
Because I know everything about you.
I've studied that.
I've also seen the pregnancy test
on your table.
And now I guess who the father must be.
He didn't like the present.
What did he say?
He doesn't want to deal with it?
It's not easy saying goodbye to a baby.
What are you going to do?
Abort.
Intervention units 1, 2 and 3, ready.
- We're getting in.
- Let's go!
- Come on, come on!
- Teams 1, 2 and 3, ready.
Now.
Team 1, hidden at the front door.
Watch the flat roof and the high flanks.
Hello?
Berlín,
- they're getting in.
- There we go.
People, the time has come!
It's the moment to follow my orders!
Follow us.
And that's how the State security forces
did exactly what the Profesor
told us they'd do,
only that afternoon, when he said that,
we were in the countryside
and we didn't have the feeling
they were going to shoot us in the head.
They'll get in through the four places
they can use to access:
the main door, the load area,
the emergency exit and the rooftop.
Watch the rearguard
of the overtaken doors.
Don't let anyone out.
But they'll wait. They'll wait
for Technical Intervention officers
to examine the place.
They'll do that from the load access.
Come on, come on.
Come on, they're already at the door.
Okay?
Insert the periscope.
Let's go.
Raquel, there's an incoming call
from one hostage's phone,
Alison Parker.
As you know, a group of kidnappers...
Turn it up.
We have another listener
on the phone to give us her opinion.
I'm not a listener.
I'm a hostage and I'm kidnapped.
My name's Alison Parker. I'm the United
Kingdom's ambassador's daughter.
- Live, in Onda Cero.
- I'm calling you
from the interior
of the Fábrica de Moneda y Timbre.
End that call right now!
- Now! End it now!
- End the call!
We're dressed just like the kidnappers.
Colonel, we have images.
What the fuck is that?
They gave us guns
and we're wearing the same masks.
- Enlarge. Stop there.
- Nobody knows who is who.
- He's got a Browning machine gun.
- Motherfuckers.
If the police come in,
innocents will get hurt.
Entrenched with the hostages,
all with the same clothes.
It's impossible to know
who they're going to shoot.
- Don't get in.
- Stop this, Suárez.
Stop it!
- Don't get in, for God's sake.
- Stop it.
Abandon positions. Abort the operation.
Inspector...
Finish what you started, colonel.
I don't want to have
anything to do with this.
And that's how we won our first battle
the first night there,
without entering a combat
and thanks to common sense.
And 20 minutes later...
we started to do what we were there for.
This is the nicest part,
we're going to work.
With me:
Torres, Sánchez, Biedma,
Lennon,
Guatsani,
Molina, García,
Domingo, De Gorza, Mateo.
Come on, that way.
Rodrigo, Molla, Pérez.
Come on.
Listen, I want the machines working
24 hours a day,
as if it was one of Pocholo's raves.
You know what I mean?
Every time we stop we'll lose a million,
so we're not stopping.
We'll do the technical amendments
every three hours,
both from the ink and the offset.
So you know: joy, party and excitement.
The best paid job ever:
2400 million euros, maybe more.
It all depended on the time
we could hold on inside.
Oh my goodness! This is wonderful, man!
This is wonderful, "coquinoqui"!
Our money, man!
Jeez!
We're making our own dough, people!
Can I have a decaf, please?
Hello. This is Mariví's
answering machine.
When you hear the beep,
you can leave a message.
Mum, I've just finished, it's six...
- Excuse me, do you have a phone charger?
- No.
Do you want to use mine?
Really? Don't you mind?
- No.
- Are you sure?
Thanks.
I have to make a couple of calls.
- It's all right.
- Thank you very much.
NEXT EPISODE
What the hell are we going to do
with so much dough?
If we are going to steal big,
dream big.
I would record an album.
Of corridos.
This way. On the cover all my face.
You are not the captain
of the rugby team?
- No. Athletics.
- Then... run.
Fuck.
Think about what you say,
because I have
a damn polygraph here.
Everyone attentive to my order.
She is a hostage.
It has 67 mobile phones attached
with Velcro on the wall.
Listen, inspec...
Did you see the coke?