Inspector, we have found the estate.
This house has to be combed,
each corner.
The whole damn plan,
schedules, photos, blueprints...
This doesn't make sense.
Call Alberto.
Isn't he the best in forensics?
Well, let him come.
- Everything they wanted to erase
they really must have burned it there.
I'm taking this to Canillas.
Ah, well, I was just on my way to Madrid,
I was going to take bus.
I was thinking
what you said before
that you want the best for Raquel.
If it were true,
you wouldn't be fucking
to his sister.
Piece of shit.
Get out of the car.
Son of a bitch.
Ah!
You're under arrest
for assaulting a police officer.
Give me the revolver.
Tell us what the plan is Chernobyl.
It's me the only one here
who knows the plan,
you're not gonna have a fucking clue
how to get out of this mousetrap.
Couldn't it be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship?
All right, take off your boots and the overalls!
Ah!
Don't shoot!
Tokio!
Fuck!
Río, you need to calm down.
- No, you sent Tokio to jail.
She's my girlfriend and you ruined her life.
Maybe you haven't noticed
because you're here against your will,
but you have a syndrome.
Which one?
Stockholm's. That's it,
go on your way
I follow mine and move on.
The Profesor, Berlín, they're not here,
you're all alone.
And He is the head of all this.
- This is a patriarchy!
- What does that mean?
- It means that I am in charge here!
Can I go to the bathroom?
I'm calling you from the police station,
I'm under arrest.
I'm telling you I have a boyfriend.
and you find the time
to beat him up?
- Hey, I didn't do anything.
- Really? Come with me.
I don't know how he got those bruises,
I swear I didn't touch him.
- Remove his handcuffs.
It's good to see you again,
Miss Tokio.
I ask and you answer.
Who is the Profesor?
All right, you've made your choice.
Bad, but you have chosen. Take her away.
Sergio! The Profesor,
his name is Sergio Marquina
and the heist was his father's idea.
And who is the person
on the outside?
I just called to say hello,
Continue interrogating Tokio.
I'm not moving from here.
What do you have to tell me?
We have
a hydrogen bomb in there.
Seventeen megatons.
We'll request
unconditional isolated detention.
Lobo, take her.
It was a very bad idea to
talk to the hostages, Río.
- You better turn me in like Tokio.
- What you have done is high treason.
- What are you going to do?
- I'll execute you.
- Put the fucking gun down.
Check-up call.
Everything is running smoothly over here.
Smoothly? Smoothly
as in Tokio being interrogated
by the police?
As in
you're about
to execute Río?
Berlín, what are you doing?
Profesor, it's Nairobi.
Berlín is is indisposed.
So from now on,
I'm in charge.
Let the matriarchy begin.
"If we took a photo
of this moment,
it could be my last memory
of the Royal
Mint of Spain.
Leaving a string of mistakes inside,
a weakened group,
and only one with the guts
to pull their weight: Nairobi.
What I mean, Profesor,
is that this out of control.
The situation here is critical.
Tokio played Russian roulette
with Berlín tied up to a chair.
Berlín
turned her in.
And then, Río deserted
and Berlín almost executed him
like some fucking Vietnamese
firing squad.
Ah, Helsinki suffocated Oslo.
He killed him?
He was a vegetal. Helsinki says
he would have wanted it.
As you can see, this is
a fucking disaster.
So I have no choice
but to take
control
until
things get back on track!
- Ask him what the hell he was doing
with the police.
I was at the house in Toledo,
it was a part of the plan.
Profesor,
we need to know
what situation we are in.
There are some loose ends,
I'm not going to lie.
"I'd say it was the biggest loose end
of all.
Assistant Inspector Ángel
had discovered the Profesor.
He had his fingerprints.
and was in a coma
waiting to wake up and reveal it.
The Profesor was living
on borrowed time.
As was everyone else.
The situation in there
isn't much better
from what you say.
Look, you do what you have to do
out there.
I fix things in here,
in the meantime.
I'll put the call through,
probably from the tent.
Inspector.
Before I get to the point
I need to clarify something.
a very important question.
¿From now on
What do I call you now?
Profesor? Sergio?
or Mr. Marquina?
I'll always be the Profesor to you.
That's how we met, isn't it?
You'll always be
Inspector Murillo to me,
even if you
become my executioner.
Remember the first time
you made love?
Of course I do,
One doesn't forget that.
Well, this is my first time
in the world of crime.
And no matter what,
I will always
remember it fondly.
You are an enthusiast.
And this world needs people like you.
I hope that when you get out of prison.
fully rehabilitated,
you'll help the country progress.
Because the truth is that...
Where did it happen?
What?
The first time you made love.
In a... In a tent.
That's wonderful.
That's a good place
for the first time.
The sounds of the countryside, the lights...
Yes, that's right.
The rest was, let's say...
experimental.
and... And brief.
Well, Profesor,
I'm calling to inform you
that Silene Oliveira
is going into
provisional custody without bail
tonight.
What did she say
to make you angry
and skip
the 72-hour custody?
She was trying to be smart.
But there's something I don't get.
Why do you let go
of your people instead of the hostages?
There have been
discrepancies in the group. Nothing else.
You're against the ropes, Profesor.
And you know it.
I admit you're winning,
but this is only one battle,
It's nothing
compared to the war.
He still teases you,
with a riot on his hands.
- He is a rock star.
Salva, how are you?
How are you holding up?
Well, I never thought
tying my shoelaces
could be this painful.
It's-it's clear that those bruises
could use some care.
A nurse.
It is a very suggestive proposal.
I would really love to take care of you,
but it would have to be at my place,
because I want to see my daughter.
And I understand that it's not
the most romantic date.
I can't think of a better date
for tonight.
All right.
When you spend years
obsessing about something,
that something is your whole world,
a perfect world.
But now the plan
was no longer the Profesor's,
It belonged to all of us.
And we were screwing it up.
For once, the Profesor felt
weakened.
and crawling
into Raquel's arms
seemed like the best refuge.
The only one possible.
Now you're a hostage too.
- What's the matter?
- They tried to kill me,
They almost did.
- Why did they want to kill you?
- They turned Tokio in.
And I was going to turn myself in too.
- Alison.
Leave her.
She has lost her mind.
If Tokio shows up,
who knows what could happen.
She won't,
You heard him,
she's been kicked out.
What Alison's doing.
could actually be good.
Good for what?
To get out, damn it!
For good.
Is it that hard
to understand?
They have locked up our colleagues
when they had promised them
freedom.
Some of us
have been truly humiliated.
They've ruined my relationship
And my future paternity.
And about the money
that they had promised us
for staying in this hell...
It's all a lie.
A fucking sham, he confirmed it.
How long are we going to stay
and do nothing?
The thieves
are weakened now.
No one can argue.
And if we don't take seize
this opportunity now,
we'll be letting them escape.
We have to finish them off.
Muster up all dignity,
the courage, that wild animal
we carry inside and...
We must do something, I don't know,
steal a gun from them.
What are you saying, Arturo?
Where are we going to get
a gun?
- Swapping one of theirs
for a fake one.
If you manage to get
one of the fake weapons,
you could swap it.
Then one of them
will be unarmed.
And one of you armed.
Oh, hello, honey.
- Mom, what are you doing here this late?
- Mommy.
- Sweetheart, come here, come here.
Oh.
But wait a minute. Tell me,
what are you doing up so late?
- I wanted to see you before going to bed.
- Me too, baby.
- Hello.
Hello.
Why didn't you tell me?
I would have made dinner.
Because you've come for dinner, haven't you?
- Yes. Well, dinner
and sleep actually. Right?
- Are you dating?
- Oh, dear..
Well, uh...
Yes, right? Kind of.
But have you asked her?
No, not really,
but we have kissed,
which is almost the same.
Oh, okay.
- Come on, Paulita, honey, let's go.
Come on, you've got school tomorrow.
Let's go to bed.
No, don't worry.
I'll tuck her in.
Thank you.
Did you really hit him?
Well...
Yes, I did.
Honestly, it infuriated me.
to think
he'd hurt you.
I don't like violence,
Never have.
I know it's wrong
and you can
defend yourself.
It's not my business, but...
Salva.
I'm glad
you hit
the jerk of my ex-husband,
I should have done it myself.
Even if it's
politically incorrect to say so.
Well,
Sometimes what's wrong
is the only choice.
I'm speaking from experience.
I'm glad you're here.
Well, from now on.
I need everybody.
closing bags, non-stop.
He won't say anything about lies.
Arturo, drop the Gandhi crap
or you'll eat shit for breakfast,
lunch and dinner.
- And besides, I can assure you
that I have not lied to anyone.
- Nairobi is in charge now,
so everybody
get packing!
Nairobi has a heavy hand
for a woman.
- Berlín, we're sinking.
So I believe
that the most important thing right now
is that we all get out of here alive.
and without making any more mistakes.
You tell me.
Are you with me or against me?
- Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
catch a tiger by the toe.
Well, I'm going with you, Nairobi.
Until the end.
- Ah.
- I will abide by your coup d'etat.
- And I have to confess
that I am turned on
at the idea of serving
to a woman who is a goddess.
- Well, you better.
pray to this goddess,
because she has your morphine,
Don't forget.
That's the office
where they keep the bag
with the fake guns.
So?
So one of us
has to get there.
and get a blank gun.
And which one of them
will you switch with?
Denver.
He's the dumbest one.
Who's going to take his gun?
Must be Mónica.
When he calls her in
for treatment.
And why would she do something like that?
It is a suicidal risk.
Because that punk
shot her.
He's put her in a den
and he took advantage of her fear
and desperation
to screw her a few times.
And apparently,
now he left you?
Yes..
I'm sorry.
But that's what happens.
Sometimes we feel like changing our lives,
we get our hopes up.
But no heist man
will take you with him.
All right,
I'll go get the gun.
Do you have the copies of the
office keys?
Oh.
- What is Plan Chernobyl?
- The Plan Chernobyl is a desperate plan,
but very beautiful. It consisted in releasing the cash
in balloons from the roof, popping the balloons with gunfire
and causing some wonderful rain. Call ingthe media,
radios, television...
- That is to say,
like the Christmas Pageant parade, but with 50 euro bills.
- Is that the Plan Chernobyl?
- Thousands of people
picking up the dough,
spreading chaos among the police.
Imagine, a billion euros falling from the sky.
- And us vanishing amongst the frenzied mob.
Very nice.
- You know the Profesor is an idealist,
He cares more about the message than the money.
And I didn't say anything
because we must respect the timing.
Wish me luck.
Mr. Torres, in my office!
Come in, Mr. Torres.
Let's see, could we increase the printing rate?
- Well, it's possible, but it would be very risky.
to fix it.
- Calculate the production rate increase.
- All right, Miss Nairobi.
Don Arturo?
Get up. Get up, Torres, God damn it, get up.
But what are you doing? None of your business.
Act like I'm not here. Walk to the door.
and don't lock it.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to report you.
If they find out I saw you, I'l be in trouble too.
Look, you jerk,
I have a gun. And if you think of giving me away,
the first bullet has your name on it,
do you understand?
Excuse me, Mr. Arturo,
but that's one of the fake guns,
you left the bag open.
Listen, because I won't say it again.
When all this is over, and I assure you, it will,
at best, a couple of hours,
you're gonna come back here,
to your crappy job.
And I'll be waiting for you the next day
with a fat layoff and a disciplinary file
that will make you shit yourself.
You'll be fucked
until you retire, do you understand?
You have three daughters, don't you?
And two of them are unemployed,
seven years, if if I recall correctly.
So it's up to you. Torres.
Miss Nairobi.
- What is it?
- We would increase production
by two million every hour.
- Do it. And the technical stops
will be every six hours, because that's
an extra two million.
- All right.
I'll get this off the ground. Mark my words.
Are you worried about something?
No.
I'm worried it's been the best night of my life.
Salva, you've already won me over, you don't need to exaggerate.
It's true.
I just wasn't planning on it,
I hadn't anticipated it.
Ah, you hadn't anticipated it.
Do you anticipate everything?
Well, let's just say...
That I'm a man who chooses
the clothes he's going to wear.
the day before.
A man who became obsessed with...
With making the best cider in the world.
And I studied everything, I studied acidity,
fermentation...
Every possible reaction of every ingredient.
Year after year after year.
And you can get a bad apple
that ruins the whole barrel.
Salva, you're really into cider, aren't you?
It was my father's dream.
And...
he died before he could fulfil it.
...He wanted to make...
2400 barrels.
I understand, I understand the homage, but I don't know,
Why don't you make half? Or half of half.
And then focus on your own dreams.
Let's go away.
I wrap up this cider thing in a few days
and we'll go to the Caribbean.
Well, I don't have the cider,
but I have a mother and a daughter.
And a heist to solve. Well, look, we take your mother
and your daughter and we'll take them with us.
Can't you imagine raising
your daughter on a sunny beach?
Raquel.
Raquel, I don't want this to wear off.
I don't want to ignore this... This desire
to feel alive that I've never felt so strongly.
You would cross the ocean with a mother,
a daughter and a grandmother?
Right now, I would.
I have a plan B.
Damn...
It is so crazy that...
that...
I can't imagine myself doing anything else.
Finish the heist, do what you have to do.
And then we go.
Okay. Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Everybody listen up!
We're going to solve this heist
in 24 hours and get back to our lives,
We've neglected them enough.
Suárez, call Chief Sanchez.
I won't even let anyone else get killed,
destroyed or caught.
Nairobi, listen, coming as far
as you have is already epic,
so I give you my most sincere congratulations.
Listen, I'm going to take you out there.
before they catch you all.
Get Lobo and the rest of the UCO here.
- What are you thinking about?
- I'm starting to think
that the man out there is the real brains
of this operation. He drew a trail
of clues to lead us to the estate in Toledo.
but I think I know how to catch him.
First we'll get the hostages
out of the basement.
Well, thank you, because
we don't have enough people
to watch over the hostages. And besides,
we promised them freedom,
So let them have it. We'll release them,
but give me an hour. It's a very big spectacle.
for such a small audience.
Yes?
I'm going to release 11 hostages
under one condition, I want a reporter
and a camera to cover the news from the inside,
Live news feed.
Look, I'd like to help with your propaganda,
but I can't force any civilian to go in there,
You know that very well.
- It's true.
You're absolutely right, Inspector.
But you don't have to force anyone,
you just have to suggest it.
I'm sure many reporters
will volunteer for an interview like that.
I'll think about it. Of course. Think about it.
But remember, I record these conversations
and the last time you refused to release hostages...
it wasn't taken very well by the public.
But of course, take your time.
Son of a bitch.
- Oh, God.
Well, let's talk about something else.
How can I explain...
Do you like soccer?
- Oh yes, Profesor, in my country soccer is big.
Then imagine a soccer match.
- Again with soccer?
But a World Cup match.
and it's playing Brazil against Cameroon.
Who wins? Easy...
Or rather, who do you want to win?
I'd say Brazil wins.
But I'd root for Cameroon, for sure. Cameroon.
Yes, Cameroon.
- Cameron all the way.
Look, instinctively human beings
always, always side with the weaker one.
The underdog.
So if we show the world
our weaknesses, our wounds,
that we're on the verge of surrendering,
It will produce a shudder.
If you're not Brazilian, I think any guy in the world
would go with Cameroon. Even some Brazilians guys.
Or Brazilian girls.
Yes, or Brazilian girls.
Okay, gentlemen. To Cameroon.
- How does that soccer chant go?
Cameroon, Cameroon, Cameroon!
Let's move on to Plan Cameroon.
We're gonna release the hostages
we have in the basement.
and we're going to get a reporter
and a camera to record it.
We're gonna need someone to be interviewed.
And my suggestion is you, Río.
I understand your anger, but we need you.
You can do it without a mask,
you are empathetic...
- You think I'll go out on TV?
For Tokio to see me from jail,
with a smile doing an interview
as if nothing had fucking happened here?
Now I'm a hostage. Don't count on me for anything.
- Fuck it, I'll do it, I'm a natural crybaby.
and you can tell just by looking.
- You're no crybaby. You make others cry.
I'll do it. If there is not much to talk about,
I'll do it.
- Could be, but no.
I'll do it with a mask.
- With a mask?
On a live interview?
But what are we now, ETA?
From the Jihad?
No, no. This interview has to be done
open-faced, so all of Spain
can feel our eyes,
our breath,
so that they can understand the pain.
And a little bit of the sorrow.
- Right. You want to do it.
But you know what the problem is?
If there's someone who I've never seen
feel sorrow or pain, it's you, Berlín.
- Tokio's gone-- and Río doesn't want to do it.
Don't look down on someone who 's good at his job,
Nairobi
I can be a good master of ceremonies.
- He's right, he's good at acting.
- All right, you'll do it.
An interview in exchange for releasing
11 hostages...
I don't know, it's more justifiable, isn't it?
We'll be criticised on every front,
but we have to accept it.
- Well, let's take the credit
and sell it as a display of transparency.
- You can sell it however you want,
Prieto, but what about the other thing?
The operation you want to set up in the hospital.
In exchange of what, on what evidence Raquel?
A plate of fresh anchovies?
- On the evidence that they have
a guy outside who keeps messing with us.
Ángel caught him and they tried to kill him,
it wasn't an accident.
- Inspector,
we have all read the forensic report
on the accident and there's no evidence
of an attempted homicide.
We can't forget he was driving
under the influence of alcohol.
- Do you want evidence? Let's set up the operation.
Let me leak to the press that Ángel, the only one
who knows who he is, will wake up from his coma.
And I assure you,
before five in the afternoon.
that guy will be in the hospital
to kill him. But we'll be there to catch him
like cat and mouse.
- You're asking me
to fill an entire hospital with undercover agents
like some police comic strip?
- We should focus our efforts here,
on the factory. What about the reporters who are coming in,
What if they end up hostages too?
- That interview
It's nothing more than a smokescreen, another trick.
to waste our time.
Chief, let us for once
be the ones who we set them up.
- Can't you do it with ten?
- 20.
Mónica Gaztambide, you're up for the treatment.
Let's go. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
If you take off the jumpsuit,
maybe I can treat you.
Do you mind turning around?
Since we aren't together anymore, right?
Ha.
No problem.
Can I? Wait.
Now.
How's the wound?
It hurts a lot.
And it stings.
We'll get only chance. And I want him alive,
No one fires unless under extreme danger.
The first thing we're gonna do is taking Ángel
to a safe place. To do this, we will set up
another room on a different floor.
Once he's relocated, we'll leak the news.
of his recovery and the target will soon
be on the move. By that time
it will be essential that everyone is in position.
I want each of you to get deep into the role.
This is a very complex operation,
so we're going to need
extreme concentration.
We'll have access to
the closed-circuit surveillance cameras.
I don't want anybody from security on the floor,
not even the hospital's security,
no police cars in the vicinity either.
Let's get that motherfucker a fucking red carpet.
into Ángel's room, where, instead,
Lobo will wait for him. And Agent Valmaseda
will take Mari Carmen's place.
They'll be there ready for a welcome surprise.
And remember, we're looking
for a middle-aged male.
- There'll be 20 agents and he'll be alone,
it's very difficult for him to escape.
Did you get it?
Here.
It's... It's loaded.
It's- It's loaded.
Stop packing the fucking bills.
and stash what you can. We're out of here.
Here, stash them.
Here you go.
Quick.
We're going now, this has lasted too long.
Fuck that.
Let's go. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Fifth day of the heist: one hostage
and two police officers wounded.
An explosion, hostages escaped.
And now Channel 6 cameras are about to enter the place
that the whole world is watching.
- Reporters are heading for the entrance.
- And remember, Cristina, the historical impact
of this moment. Hundreds of television channels
all over the world are broadcasting our signal.
- Cover them until securing entry.
- The first time a television crew
goes live on...
- They're opening doors. Attention, guards.
Stop at the bottom of the stairs as requested.
- Special at the Royal Mint, a crucial moment.
In less than a minute we'll witness something historic,
a reporter and a cameraman from the Channel Six.
will enter the site of the heist.
That's as far as the police can go,
From this point, on the reporter and the camera
will be on their own, unprotected.
We've never seen such a thing,
all over the country the streets
are empty.
Return to your posts.
Hello, good morning.
- Good morning.
- I am Andrés de Fonollosa,
thank you very much for being here.
- Can you put this on, please?
- Yes.
- We're already getting the signal, we're going live.
Inside the factory.
- Mr. Fonollosa, I have to ask you
why you've allowed a team of journalists
to broadcast live.
- This is a turning point for all of us
in here and we needed you here
to record it and to make it public.
Please come with me. This way.
- That's Andrés de Fonollosa, a familiar face
to the police. Bank robber, informer
and convicted for human trafficking.
- These are the 11 hostages
who are finally to be released.
- There they are. I recognize... Manuel García,
Alfonso Martínez and María Cornejo.
It looks like they are going to be released for real.
- We're all a little nervous.
- Medical services ready.
- like kids waiting for the school bell to ring.
I want to thank you all.
For the courage and bravery you have shown.
And...
You in particular, you and your child.
You've proven to be a very strong woman.
- Why have you decided now,
after five days of captivity, to release hostages?
- Five days.
It's hard to believe it's been just a few days,
Right?
You see
We have to confess it's...
it's a very hard time.
for us, the situation is critical.
We have no choice but to surrender,
that's why you're here.
This gesture is the beginning
of the end for everyone.
Helsinki
It's time, you can go.
Thank you.
- Snipers ready. Assault Team One,
keep your distance.
- Copy that.
We're going to release hostages in order to negotiate
a more favorable surrender for our interests.
- Have you made the decision to surrender?
- We are aware that we've lost.
Open the doors!
- 11 released, we're watching it live.
- They're coming out.
- Finally some good news at
the Fábrica de Moneda.
There they are, it's an exciting moment.
Looks like the heist men are giving in.
But there are more headlines,
big one. Fonollosa has admitted
that the situation is critical,
that they have no choice but to surrender.
His literal words were:
"This is the beginning of the end
and we are aware that we have lost."
I don't know if you've ever seen a corpse.
For some of us it's the first time too.
You've come here to tell the truth.
Here it is, this is the truth.
We've been beaten,
we have been defeated.
It is important that you confirm it,
please.
- Yes, he doesn't have a pulse, he's dead.
- The hostages who escaped hit him in the head,
He died within few hours.
It's possible that for the people, out there,
this man is no more than a thief.
But to us he was a companion and a friend.
No one prepares you for that, no one. It's one of the reasons
why we've decided to release hostages.
Some of us here thought
we weren't going to make it out alive, but, frankly,
I never thought it would be him.
- What do you mean, there were people in the group
willing to sacrifice themselves?
- No, no, no.
No, not at all. We're simple people,
We have gone through hardship
of all kinds, just like anyone else.
Including terminal illness.
And we've had
to take desperate action like this.
in order to leave something for our families.
Leave something to our loved ones.
Sorry..
As I matter of fact,
I have a degenerative disease.
called Herbert's myopathy.
The police knew it.
That didn't stop them from spreading lies about me.
And I want to tell you something. I may be a thief,
I've always been, I've robbed banks,
I've robbed jewellery stores, robbed mansions...
But I've never sold anyone.
I've never sold a woman.
I'm not a pimp who traffics,
or rapes minors, I'm not.
Ask the police, when you leave,
in which files are these cases.
- Do you mean that the police
have lied to the public?
- The police lie.
They lie to the public.
They've lied to my friends,
They've soiled my family's name.
I'm a thief.
But I have every right in the world not to be defamed.
I have the same right as anyone to die in peace.
And with dignity.
I can't go on with... Cut, please.
"That morning we were
a trending topic worldwide,
people went silent in cafeterias and taxis."
Fonollosa says the police are lying,
that they have been lying about his past.
And dares them to come up with legal files.
"We were the Cameroon team
barefoot against Brazil.
and everyone wanted us to win."
We're now going to our news colleagues,
Cristina Saavedra, go ahead.
- Breaking newsr:
Deputy Inspector Ángel Rubio
could awake from his coma.
He was kept in an induced coma
after a traffic accident.
The Deputy Inspector suffered an accident
on road M-506, when his car crashed.
into a construction booth in one of the lanes,
causing it to roll over multiple times.
Profesor, have you seen us on TV?
Nairobi, I want you all to be one,
like a rowing team, okay?
I want you to tell Río that
I'm going to get Tokio out of jail.
no matter what.
That is my Profesor, yes, sir.
Put Berlín on.
Berlín.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Yes?
Deputy Inspector Rubio
is waking from his coma.
What are the odds of that being true?
I don't know.
That's elementary police work:
Saying that he's waking from his coma
to lure you in.
That doesn't even work on sitcoms.
And if it isn't?
He's the only one who knows who I am,
the only loose end.
What room did they put him in?
Room 119
It's a trap.
Yes, it's a 90% chance it's a trap.
Ninety-nine percent.
But are we going to leave
one percent to chance?
No, you'll have to make sure.
And if it isn't, finish him off.
Get into a hospital in which, surely,
there'll be 50 cops waiting for me.
Sergio, think, damn it.
You spent half your childhood in a hospital.
What's the way to get into a trap
without getting caught?
knowing that the cavalry is waiting for you?
That would be
by making the cavalry run away.
One moment of attention, please.
Let's see, as you already know,
we've released your colleagues
who chose freedom, so here
no one has deceived anyone,
we have kept our promise.
The promise, my ass.
And likewise, I swear that the million euros
will be sent to the addresses you gave us.
Lies and more lies.
We'll keep that promise too,
I give you my word.
Attention to all units, no one gets in
without identification.
- Copy that.
Hey, you.
- A clown has entered
- Could be him in disguise.
- Another one is entering the E.R..
- What the hell is this?
- There're more coming in.
- What's going on?
- I've been called too.
Get those people out of there.
You can't be here, get out
Who wants a funny crazy rabbit?
Inspector, they put out
an ad for a fake casting.
- Lobo, watch out, he may be inside the building.
- He's entering the room.
- What's going on, somebody talk to me!
- False alarm, it wasn't him.
Inspector, the TV interview.
- We've verified that
there is no open case against Fonollosa
for human trafficking,
pimping or pedophilia.
For some sources the information leaked could be
part of a scheme orchestrated by the authorities
to reduce the popularity of the heist men.
The latest events, as well as the death
of one of the kidnappers,
has earned them the sympathy of the people.
You missed me. Let go.
Listen
As soon as Helsinki leaves,
we take action, got it?
Is it the right time?
I've got a gun here, he's got a blank gun,
What do you think might happen?
Either you tell him or I will.
- I'll tell him.
The Profesor will try to free Tokio.
Where are you going?
¡Eh! For fuck's sake.
Where the fuck are you going?
What's this, are we at recess?
Come on, everybody sit down.
And I suggest the same to you,
I'm not in the mood. You know what?
I feel like breaking
some skulls. And yours is the best one to start.
Try my gun. See if you can relax.
Arturo.
Arturito.
You've got a toy gun and
I've got a bad bad fucking temper.
What are you doing? A toy pistol?
No.., it doesn't look like it.
Why don't we test it?
I'm gonna give you three seconds,
or so help me God.
Make it one. Three, two...
One.
Surprise.
Cheer up, Río.
Because we can be a family again.
Turn around.
I said turn around.
Son of a bitch.
Come on, let's go.
Quick, Get moving.
They're gonna escape
They're gonna escape.
- Who?
- The hostages.
Come on, come on, we don't have all day.
Mónica, open the door.
Just don't fucking listen to him,
this guy's taking advantage of you.
Don't open the door!
Shut up or you'll get a shot, champ.
Don't listen to him,
open the door and we'll get out of here.
Let's go.
What's going on? It does not open.
Fuck, those motherfuckers must have blocked the door!
It was me.
Get back.
Arturo, put the gun down.
Drop the gun.
- Arturito, I know you love movies
but this is getting out
of hand.
Another step and I'll shoot him.
I may not get out of here alive,
but I'll make sure he never smiles again.
Berlín, Berlín, calm down.
Open the door for me!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Take it easy.
Let's talk like civilized people.
Let him go and if you want to get out,
I'll help you.
Open the door for me now.
No one's opening any doors here.
You really don't think so?
Look, I'll count to five
and then I'll shoot him.
I have nothing to lose and I don't give a shit.
So it's up too you.
Five, four, three, two, one...
But how could he have found out?
- He wore a GoPro camera.
controlled from a distance.
- Bastard
- We're trying to trace the signal.
- It's no use, it's too late.
We've been deceived again.
- What is clear is that you were right,
That son of a bitch tried to kill Ángel.
- So Ángel must have come very close
to get that evidence.
- It's possible they were even face-to-face.
- You'll forgive me, but I'm exhausted.
"Leave your message after the signal."
Salva, it's Raquel. I'm going to have a coffee.
at Hanoi, If you feel like it.
I could really use someone to talk to.
Antonio.
- Here, they left me an envelope for you.
- Who?
- I don't know,
it was here when we opened.
What can I get you?
- A beer.
How was your day?
Well, I take it that it's going well.
No, it's been awful.
I set up an operation so
I could leave tomorrow with you.
to these beaches, but it's been a disaster.
- What can I get you? The same.
Raquel.
Sooner or later, all this will end.
And then, you and I'll meet on a beach.
But you have to choose a place.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
It's just that I haven't had time yet.
Let's see.
How about we choose it together?
That sounds great.
Pick one. Such a responsibility.
Let's see, ah...
Palawan. Palawan.
Let's see.
What a wonder.
And where's this?
Palawan, yes.
It is an island in the Philippines.
It's southwest of the archipelago,
a little to the north.
of Borneo. It has 849 000 inhabitants,
more or less, and the capital is Puerto Princesa.
Ángel must have come too close
to get the evidence.
- It's possible they were even face-to-face.
- Have you investigated him? Because I have.
Have you done your damn job?
The best fine sandy beaches in the tropics.
You don't like the Philippines.
Oh.
This is a wonderful moment.
Stand up!
You're gonna sting till your hands bleed!
I want you to armor roads,
ports and airports.
Take off your clothes.
This is for not killing when we had to.
Turn around.
Don't lie to me, I'll know.
Who do you think stole your gun?
- You don't understand.
What am I going to have to do to get you to respect me?
What am I gonna have to do?
What did you do,
what the fuck did you do?
- It was her or us.
Attention, we activate Operation Cage!
Get down, get down, everybody!
Shoot the target!
- What's going on?
Let's go!