Listen to me, all of you.
I want you to get out of the tent again.
- I have important information
about Retoxil.
As you have to order it on request,
they have all patients very localized,
but in Toledo there's been
an unusual demand.
- Just three days before
entering the factory.
Go to that pharmacy by yourself.
Don't talk to anyone about this.
- Help, please, we just got mugged!
- I don't know.
The pharmacy has been robbed.
They've taken the records.
The pharmacy thing
was only known to you and me.
- And you didn't tell anyone, did you?
Didn't you say anything to the guy
in the cafeteria?
- How much do they pay you? A million?
- Go fuck yourself.
It's Arturo. Do you hear me?
- We're in the basement of the boilers.
Try to get you back here in two hours.
- I stole some stuff from the toolbox.
Ask them to take you back to the bathroom.
You take the tools and stick them under
the toilet seat.
- Come on, Salva,
look at me under the table.
I have well-founded suspicions that
you're hiding something
in that workshop where you supposedly
makes cider.
I'm sorry, Salva.
This place is wonderful.
Don't stop.
What the fuck are you doing here, man?
Get it out. Leave me alone with this one.
I'm gonna kill you, motherfucker.
Give me one fucking reason not to
open your head right now!
They are getting away.
What?
16 hostages. 16 hostages, right now.
I already got the results of what you
asked for.
- The person who touched that spoon
is the same
that forced the patrol car.
- You're awesome, Pilar.
Raquel, it's me again. We have the guy
who helps them from the outside.
It is Salva. Salva.
- They're escaping through the cargo area.
- Tokio, go find Nairobi.
Río, Denver, bring Oslo and Helsinki.
- Take cover, take cover, take cover!
Is everybody under cover?
- Let's go get them.
- Let's go.
- Attention, explosion in the building!
I want communication with the assault team now.
Intervention team 1 and 2,
go to the incident area.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Priority: hostage rescue.
Evaluation of possible entry.
- Show me the loading area.
Show me the loading area.
That one, that one.
- Attention, there's movement.
Someone is coming out.
We've got them in range.
Repeat, we have them in range.
- They're hostages. They are hostages.
- We've got a visual.
We're waiting for confirmation.
"Do you know that when there's
a traffic jam after an accident
isn't it because of the accident itself?
It's because the rest of the cars stop to look.
They can't help it,
because deep down we're so basic
like a mosquito going towards the light,
like any insect that tries to escape
if you lock him up.
And inspector Murillo
it wasn't much more complex
at the end of the day."
Can I have a long latte of coffee?
"That's why she was there,
washing his armpits and smiling
at the mirror,
while his companion struggled
between life and death."
Confirmed. Confirmed, they're hostages.
Rescue protocol.
I want a clean extraction.
- Let's go!
- Come on! Let's get out of here!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
- Let's go!
- To the vehicle!
- Quick, quick! Go, go, go, go!
Let's go!
- Come on! Let's get out of here!
- Medical team, stand by. I want all
hostages here. Let's go.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Come on.
- Everybody out.
- We've got a visual of the inside.
- He's wearing a Dalí mask.
- Favourable conditions for an assault.
- We await orders.
- Assault team, stand by.
We're going in.
"The world could crumble while she
thought of nothing,
that's how you stay when you've just
Get laid, but there's always something
that brings you back to reality and
doesn't usually do it softly."
"Witnesses speak of a great deflagration
at the Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre
and the possible escape of 15 to 16 hostages
whose identity has not yet transcended.
Apparently, they haven't suffered
any serious injuries.
And a breaking news story.
Sub-inspector Ángel Rubio,
one of the crisis command officers,
has suffered a serious traffic accident
on the M-506,
from Getafe to Pinto, in Madrid.
His vehicle has gone off the road
and it's been spining several times.
The sub-inspector is being attended to
by the health services and their condition
is not known at this time.
There have been no more vehicles
involved in this accident.
and it is not yet known whether it
was due to mechanical failure
or a distraction."
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Nairobi, are you all right?
I think I have a fever.
Ouch!
Let's see.
No, it doesn't look like a fever.
Maybe it was the barbecue, because
I don't feel very well either.
Well, lie down here, there's room.
Profesor, I'm not going to bite you.
It's up to me...
or do you breathe tension into
the environment?
Tension? Yes
Here? Yes.
Let's see, maybe is the four months
locked in here, the fever
or that you have sex appeal.
Isn't it the same with me?
Well...
Nairobi, there's no doubt that...
That you're a woman of character,
you're a racial woman,
Pretty... so, a woman...
And I, of course, am sensitive to
those stimuli,
It couldn't be any other way.
but interpersonal relationships
are not allowed.
Yeah, but I'm not asking you to
marry me either, profesor.
I know, but I really don't...
A "quicky."
Please.
Oh, God!
Okay, okay, okay.
Ugh!
I wouldn't want to hurt you,
but we can't.
No, you can't hurt me.
In fact, I think you're the man
who's treated me the best in my whole life.
You and your plan.
Tokio told me the plan didn't occur to you,
but you haven't told her whose idea it was.
The most important person in my life.
I was a sick kid, you know?
And a sick teenager.
So I spent many years prostrate in a bed
in a hospital reading, reading a lot.
My father used to tell me stories.
He used to tell me about the movies
he saw about robberies.
That's quite a figure your father,
isn't it?
Instead of telling you "The Ugly Duckling"...
Well, one day he told me the most
extraordinary film
they've ever done.
"You know money is made in a machine,
right?" he said.
And I said no.
"And that machine is in
a place called the money factory
and with a master plan...
It has to be masterful,
don't ever forget it.
You could go in there
and make all the money you want,
without stealing from anyone.
Do you understand?"
That day he was shot at the doors
of the Hispanic American bank.
He didn't tell me about movies.
He told me about his own robberies.
"You could fulfill your dreams
without hurting anyone."
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- Sir, there's movement inside.
They're closing the door.
- Cover fire! Cover fire!
- Take anything to hold! Run!
- Take that back!
- I can't, I can't!
- Get down!
- Ah!
- Holy shit! Helsinki!
Helsinki!
- Take it! Get it, get it!
- Ah!
- I'm going with Helsinki!
Cover me!
- Cover fire!
Three, two, one! Fire!
- Fucking hell!
Helsinki
Help! Help!
Where?
No, no.
- The vest has stopped the bullet.
- You've got nothing, you've got nothing.
Assault teams, we launch smoke and
enter from the flanks.
We're going in.
Cover fire.
Now!
- Look out! Look out!
- We launched the smoke on my command.
Now!
- They have thermal vision equipment.
That smoke's only gonna hit us,
get it out.
Come on, Moscú.
They're coming in!
- We have to put the wall back on.
- Go inside.
- Cover fire. Three, two, one.
Fire!
- Fucking hell!
- They're coming in!
- They're on top of us!
- They're coming in, they're coming in!
- They're all over us!
- Cover up, cover up, cover up!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Take cover!
- Machine gun!
- Take cover. They are shooting
with large caliber.
Wall, wall!
Fucking hell!
- Come on, come on! Help!
- The drill! Come on, hurry up, Berlín!
Come on, let's go!
- Where's Oslo?
- I don't know, I haven't seen it.
Mari Carmen, I'm sorry.
- Ángel's things.
What happened?
He was drinking before the crashed
I talked to the police.
He made 16 calls to you.
What happened?
What did you say to him?
- Nothing. I didn't pick up his phone.
I was in an operation.
- Tell me what happened between you two,
please.
Ángel overturned, invaded the opposite lane
and swerved like he wanted to end it all.
A friend of his from Traffic gave me this video.
Tell me, why has my husband
attempted suicide?
- I don't know.
Things weren't going well at work.
- At work?
I've been waiting seven years,
seven years waiting for one day to stop
being in love with you.
And now all I hope is that he wakes up.
Why didn't you warn us? Why?
Where the fuck have you been?
- Man down! Man down! Help!
- Helsinki, what happened?
- Hostages, escape, very strong blow,
Trauma.
Did you know about escape?
What hostage made the escape?
- Arturo said it,
but I didn't get there in time.
- Arturo.
- Helsinki. Helsinki.
Oslo is wrong.
- No, He's not.
- He's badly hurt, Helsinki.
- No, no.
Not badly hurt, not badly hurt.
He just needs rest and medicine.
Medicine. A medicine.
- Why are his eyes open?
- And now I give prednisone,
anti-inflammatories and heparin,
and go to sleep.
And tomorrow Oslo better.
- Hey, Moscú.
You don't worry.
Oslo and I have had worse colds than this.
Worst colds.
"Oslo's gaze was never sparkling,
but now it was the gaze of all of us:
sad and absent.
Hope is like dominoes:
when one falls, they all fall.
And the hostages realized we were screwed."
We heard all the gunshots last night.
Is anyone hurt?
I'm not gonna shut up.
- Have a seat.
- One of my students is missing,
Pablo Ruiz, and I want to know
where he is.
- Have a seat.
Sit down!
Your student escaped with a group of hostages.
They blew up a cargo and it went out.
You don't have to worry about anyone,
they're all fine.
What's the crazy one doing?
Ma'am, sit down and leave the claps.
Have a seat.
Sit down!
Ma'am, sit down.
Get on the ground.
Get on the ground!
Everybody down to the floor, damn it!
Sit the fuck down!
Get on the ground!
Make them stop. Make them stop!
Stop it! I said stop it!
Sit down, all of you.
Have a seat.
Sit down, please.
Oh, look.
- No, Moscú.
No.
- What?
- Open your eyes first.
Watch where you shoot.
Grab a gun.
Low elbow.
Hey, but you wear thong, don't you?
I'm not wearing panties.
- Won't you wear panties?
- No, I'm not.
- Well, neither do I.
With the dick free you rob.
Don't be a slut.
With the dick free.
The hostages.
Shut up.
- What's going on?
With the passage of hours, the hostages
will cease to be docile.
When they see that there are no deliveries,
that there are no advances,
their survival instinct will lead them into action.
And what are they going to do?
Are the numismatics gonna make a Bruce Willis'?
Something like that, Nairobi.
They'll try to escape or they'll escape.
No.
It's possible that will happen.
We are armed.
At that point, the rest of the hostages
we'll lose our fear.
If that happens, it's very important
to reestablish control.
and in that case we'll do it through empathy.
generating a much stronger climate of trust
than what we've had up to that point.
Well, trust and M-16s don't marry, do they?
Then we'll have to find things that
unite us to the hostages.
Let's see, what unites people?
Well, football.
Football is a very good example,
but there's one thing that unites
even more than football.
Sex?
Sex unites, but two by two.
Or not.
Careful.
Normally
Well, there are threesomes and...
And there are quartets,
even more group structures.
Structures?
Needless to say
that has no place in our plan.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
Thank goodness,
because as lucky as I am,
if we have an orgy,
I'm sure he'll touch me behind this one.
- But, Profesor, what unites more than sex?
What unites us?
Uh!
I mean all of us.
Well, let's see, I've grown
very fond of you all,
but... Sincerely?
The money.
Not one other thing, but we'll
have plenty of money.
I've been thinking a lot
on how we could transform our hostages
in our partners
and, well, I've come to a conclusion:
money or freedom.
Have you ever thought, I mean by fantasy,
to put a price on yourself?
- I can tell you that yes.
- Think about it, you've got two hours.
- I have nothing to think about.
- I'm talking about the pain,
the damage we're inflicting on him.
- I'm here working better than
I've ever worked in my whole life.
- What would be the minimum wage
for a hostage?
I've thought of a million euros.
Like that, free, no taxes.
You're not gonna fool me,
I know perfectly well how all this works.
Is that so?
- You know how much this costs.
And he knows that the profession is
something you carry in your blood.
I've never had a boss like you,
Miss Nairobi.
Is it that or the second choice?
What's that second choice?
Just go out?
Just like I'm telling you,
but empty-handed.
- How are we gonna get a million
euros out of here?
Hiding in our underwear?
You give me the address of a carnal cousin
of yours, a friend,
and I'll send you a postcard envelope
with your money.
within five or six months of getting
out of here.
- Think about it, it's not
the same raising a child
with a million under the mattress.
- Well...
- Freedom...
or the money.
- There was a camera here,
at the entrance to the restrooms.
And in this hallway I think
there was another one.
- You mean apart from the security cameras.
of the building, had they installed more?
- Yeah, those were different.
- They had us digging a tunnel.
It was in the basement.
There was a lot of ammunition,
like for a war,
there were boxes of bullets....,
chargers, explosives.
- Yeah, these three were part of the band.
There were eight of them,
two of them foreigners.
- Would you know if one of them
is the profesor?
- They had city names:
Berlín, Moscú, Denver...
- Nairobi...
- Helsinki...
- She was Tokio.
- This was Río.
- It was the least dangerous of all.
He was Alison's keeper.
- They had Alison separated from
the rest of the hostages?
- Yeah, sometimes they split it up.
- One of the foreigners is wounded.
Or dead.
We hit him in the head with a pipe.
- Oslo called him.
- If you'll excuse us. You can take a break.
If you'd like a cup of coffee or something to eat.
Lobo, escort him out.
You'd better sit down.
These are Ángel's glasses.
They had inserted a microphone with a
coverage of 1500 meters.
They should have put it on when
he entered with the doctors.
Ángel is not a traitor.
- Raquel,
I know what's going on in your head right now.
But he was doing his job.
Any one of us would have done the same thing.
All the clues pointed to him.
I was wrong, too.
"You have a new message.
- Raquel, it's me again.
Call me, your answering machine's full.
We got him, listen, we got him.
We got the guy who's helping them
from the outside, yeah.
Yeah, it's Salva, Salva,
the one on the cider.
He fucking threatened the russian.
He's using you, dammit.
He's come up to you to take advantage
of the investigation.
He's using you, Raquel.
- To return the call..."
"Hi, I'm Raquel. I can't take care of you now.
If it's urgent, leave a message after the beep."
"The voicemail of the number
you're calling is full."
Ángel's been calling me all afternoon.
But I didn't take his cell phone.
16 calls.
He called me 16 times.
And I didn't take it.
"Raquel, Raquel, it's Ángel.
Listen, I'm asking you to reconsider.
I understand the heat of the moment.
I've gone too far..."
Disconnect the speakers or turn it down.
"It's the first brawl you and I have ever had.
I'll be an asshole or whatever you want,
but I'm not the mole.
I'm not the mole, dammit.
You're gonna fuck up my life, Raquel.
Call me."
"Raquel, can you tell me why the fuck
you're not picking up the phone?
Huh?
After 15 years with you, by your side,
like a fucking loser.
And not for getting close to you, no,
for friendship, for love.
Do you hear me?
For love."
"I was about to send it all to hell.
To send Mari Carmen to hell
for a bitch who wouldn't fuck.
Do you hear me? You're a bitch,
an obsessive bitch.
You're a fucking bitch! Fucking bitch!
A pussy-eater, a frigid."
"How many blows can you take before
you fall to the ground?
If you are Raquel Murillo, many.
But there's something wrong with being
a good hitter.
- Attention, Inspector Murillo is
approaching the facade.
And if the blows don't stop, you're gonna
end up falling just the same.
And when you fall, it'll be like all those
blows come together.
- Raquel!
Raquel!
Murillo stopped hearing.
Stop thinking.
He just walked.
She was an empty body
looking for the end of it all.
Raquel!
Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm sorry, I didn't...
I didn't understand you.
- Freedom.
I said I want the...
- No, no, no.
Wait, before you seriously answer me,
I want...
I'd like to make a couple
of considerations.
The first is that you must contemplate
that you and I have a relationship.
And the second is that freedom is full
of unforeseen events,
of dangers and terrible things, perhaps,
I'm scared personally,
I'm afraid of it.
Do you know the eagle chicks
that jump before their time and
shatter against the rocks?
I'm afraid of that.
Or the bunnies, the rabbits in their burrows.
They see the sunlight and they come out.
And a wolf breaks their necks with a bite.
I'm afraid of that.
No, Ariana, because...
Maybe now, right now, it's much more dangerous.
to get out of here than to stay.
And I wouldn't want anything bad to
happen to you, Ariana.
I don't want you to be anxious either.
I don't want that.
I'll give you a couple of hours to
think about it.
I've got to get out.
I'm pregnant.
I have to go to the gynaecologist and...
Well, and the traumatologist,
or the doctor you go,
I don't know which doctor you go to
if you've got a bullet in your leg.
Well, it's internal medicine, isn't it?
I don't know.
But let's see, what's going on?
You don't like the million?
With that your life is solved.
No, it depends.
Because if my wound gets gangrene,
I'm left lame...
If that happens, we'll think about it.
You don't have to get into the worst.
I think.
Hey, besides, you're luxurious here.
With your own room, Mónica Gaztambide's
presidential suite.
Or not?
Maybe, if you leave, you even miss us.
Why do you insist that I stay?
You haven't fallen in love, have you?
That's not true.
Look at me. Look at me.
Are you serious?
What if he's serious?
Let's see, you can't fall in love in 60 hours.
Well, 60 hours. Well, in 60 hours I shot you.
And I got it out of you.
You found out you were pregnant,
that if you abort,
not abort, if you leave the boyfriend.
That you're sleeping with me.
If you give me 24 more hours,
maybe I'll ask you to marry me.
And in the other 24 we got divorced.
What the fuck does time matter in here?
If in the end time is one thing...
Okay.
Okay what?
I'm staying.
But to get married and that's
gonna give me more time,
All right? I don't know, 16 minutes or something.
Hello?
Look, I'm sorry to call you back.
I'm Raquel's mother.
As you were the other day
so close to my daughter. I have an urgent message
of Deputy Inspector Ángel. And I don't locate her.
Are you near her?
Not right now, but I'm going to see her
in a moment.
If you tell me, maybe I can get it to her.
You don't know how grateful I am to you,
because it seemed important.
What message?
Wait, I'll read to you.
Yeah. "We've got him,
we've got the bloody guy
who helps them from the outside.
He's the cider guy.
The one who was in the junkyard,
the one who threatened the Russian."
Just a second. Uh...
"His fingerprints were on the Z. We have it.
I'm going to the tent and
I'll tell you everything."
Did you write it down well?
Yes. Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Well, thank you very much again,
thank you very much.
You're welcome.
The Profesor had built
his plan millimetrically:
every move of the police,
every possible mistake of his gang,
hostage behavior, every variable; everything.
And then, when he thought he was in control,
found out that he didn't.
It never occurred to him that in order
for the whole plan
didn't go down the toilet he was
gonna have to kill.
Kill the mother of the woman he was
falling in love with.
And of course, no one is prepared for that.
What did you put in me?
- An intravenous pain reliever.
- Have you talked to the hostages yet?
What did they say?
- So far we've confirmed they're tunneling.
We're going to locate the exact position.
And what we already know, they're
heavily armed.
Raquel, you're the most qualified person
to take command of this operation.
But it's about time to rest.
- Don't worry about anything.
The commissioner is on his way
to take his place.
So you'll go home for a few hours.
You have to sleep.
- Can I make a call?
- Sure.
Here you go.
Salva.
I'm Raquel.
I need you to...
come and get me out of here.
This is the worst day of my life and...
And I have to escape from this tent,
from this city.
Salva, are you there?
I can't, I have an engagement.
Sure, I understand. Call you like that...
Morning.
Hello.
Tell me.
I am Salva, your daughter's friend.
We spoke on the phone.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Come in, come in.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
He's not reacting.
I don't mean to be ominous,
but I'm afraid the blow to the skull
has caused irreparable damage.
- What's the matter, you're a neurosurgeon?
We don't know.
We have to get him to a hospital.
Maybe he can still be cured.
- Nobody's getting out of here, you hear me?
With or without a hole,
you know what the profesor said.
- I don't care about the profesor.
Where was the profesor
when 16 hostages escaped?
Where was him when Oslo's head was opened?
We open the doors, we call the police.
and let the doctors take him.
- What the hell are you talking about?
The rules are clear, no one leaves.
We accept everything, Oslo too.
Sixteen hostages have escaped.
The rules have changed.
The hostages don't know what's
going on here, Oslo does.
- So what? I don't know.
He can't even talk.
And even if he could, he wouldn't turn us
in to the police.
Let's vote.
- This is not a pretty democracy.
- It is not, no.
We open the doors and let Oslo out.
- No one's getting out of here.
Oslo doesn't come out.
I talk to Oslo before I go in.
Doesn't matter about the wound.
Death before prison.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- I'll take care of Oslo.
The truth is, you have a beautiful house.
Thank you very much.
Raquel is not at home, the poor one
works so much...
I was having a coffee,
would you like me to make you one?
I wouldn't want to disturb you.
I won't be long.
Well, thank you very much.
Have a seat.
"There are 10 000 ways to kill a grandmother,
but the Profesor was no hitman.
More like a chess player.
The world of crime was big to him.
So he chose the cleanest and smartest option.
Pour 2.5 milligrams of dioxin into
grandmother's coffee.
Waiting for the heart failure that it
was going to cause.
and evaporate."
Would you like some sugar?
Oh, yes, please. Three tablespoons.
You're greedy, aren't you?
So do I, although I shouldn't.
"Three spoonfuls of sugar
and one spoonful of dioxide.
In 15 minutes, heart failure would occur.
In 30 minutes, Raquel
would find her mother's body.
In an hour, a judge
assisted by a medical examiner
would order the removal of the body
for cardiovascular infarction,
with no signs of violence,
with the victim's age, with the door
locked inside his house.
There would be no autopsy."
Thank you very much.
"Clean and simple."
My daughter didn't spend the night here.
Was she with you?
Well... Well, the truth is that it is.
We saw each other yesterday.
Good.
Did you make love?
Well...
Well, we do, actually.
I'm glad.
All right, then.
And forgive the intrusion,
but I'm really glad.
My daughter needs as May water
Someone who love her and make love to her.
And be a good man.
And you seem like a good man.
I can see it in your eyes.
Ouch. Excuse me. I dropped it.
It's just that over the years,
we get very clumsy.
I beg your pardon.
Oslo won't talk anymore.
I'm so sorry. It is not a tragedy.
You knew about the escape.
Denver told me.
To know, to know, I didn't know.
I sensed something
and I told Denver to help.
He was hit with this tube
from the back.
Oslo friend.
Me and Oslo warfare together,
peace together.
Robberies together.
Jail together.
Oslo friend. Do you understand, Arturo?
On your knees.
Did you really think we weren't gonna try to escape?
That we weren't going to defend ourselves?
That we were going to stand idly by
watching you kill us?
How you tortured us, how you raped us.
Once and a thousand times I would,
so if you're gonna do it,
give me strong because,
if you leave me alive,
maybe I'll finish you off later.
I came to work
like every day.
Without hurting anyone.
Just doing my duty.
Who do you think are the good guys, Helsinki?
You?
Finish quickly, please.
Bring me the dustpan and the mop.
It's right there in the corner, please.
Thank you.
I'll take care of it.
"I no longer live in Almazán.
I live in Madrid.
I have two daughters, Raquel and Laura.
I'll never go to a residence.
Raquel is serious,
but she loves me very much."
We got him. He's the cider guy.
His prints were on the zeta.
Do you mind if I make a call?
No, of course not.
Raquel, it's me again.
Give me a call.
Your answering machine is full.
We've got him. Listen. We got it.
We got the guy who's helping them
from the outside.
Yes. It's Salva. Salva, the one with the cider.
He was at the junkyard.
He threatened the Russian. Fucking hell.
He's fucking using you.
Her fingerprints were on the zeta.
"to listen to the message again press 1.
To delete it, 2.
"Message deleted. No more messages."
They don't get it.
Salva?
What are you doing here?
This was my engagement.
The only thing I left you
in the garden was a shame.
Isn't he a heaven?
He already told me you've made love.
- Mom... I didn't say anything.
She must have figured it out on her own.
Let's eat.
Sure you don't want to try my custard?
We'll have to try them,
if they're as good as this soup...
Of course, it's the best I've tasted
in a very long time.
Thank you.
Daughter, don't be dizzy, you eat very little.
That's the job.
He's got her under a lot of stress.
About the kidnapping,
you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, man, you're gonna tell me.
I follow it a lot, I'm following it a lot.
In the press.
It's tremendous what's going on.
I can't stand it.
It's just that there was gunfire yesterday.
And explosions, really,
those people heavily armed,
I don't know, any day
there's going to be a tragedy.
Yesterday there were shots...
People heavily armed...
"They have at least three M-16s.
A floor machine gun.
Retoxil, it's a rare drug.
- In Toledo there has been an unusual demand."
Where was the last purchase made?
- Here, in Palomeque, on October 18th.
Excuse me, I have to make a call.
- But, daughter.
Every day like this.
Suárez, put me through the speakers.
- Connect my cell phone,
we have communication with the inspector.
Turn it up.
- Listen to me well, I need you to
look for all the farms
with hunting grounds
within a radius of 100 km
from Palomeque's pharmacy.
- I want a map of Toledo now, look for it.
Palomeque perimeter.
- If they bought the drugs there,
means they were very close.
Fuck, how come I didn't notice before?
They needed a place to get organized,
to prepare the plan step by step.
They had to do target practice.
before entering the factory.
Somewhere where the shooting
won't arouse suspicion.
- I want units around
Palomeque's perimeter.
within a 100-kilometre radius and I want them now.
- It has to be a farm of more than 100 hectares.
- Search the cadastre.
- With a house inside.
Call me as soon as you have something.
- Count on it.
You heard the man. We don't have time to waste,
let's go get 'em, okay?
That farm, those units,
I want it all, I want it now.
Yes?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yeah, a little tired.
Come in.
Stunned too,
they had to inject me with a painkiller.
and to tell you the truth, I'm not very used to it.
I'm not very lucid today either.
Sorry, Salva, but I need to lie down.
I have to get some sleep.
Sure, sure.
The time has come to make a decision.
You have to choose
between becoming accomplices
and getting a million.
Or be whole and get out of here.
Freedom
or the million.
Those of you who stay
with us to see the end,
you will receive 20 000 banknotes of
50 euro at home.
Vacuum-packed, like good ham.
All those who wish to leave,
please cross the line.
What are we going to do with those
who choose freedom?
You'll take them to the factory basement.
and lock them in there.
I know it's regrettable,
but they are precisely those
that could ignite another mutiny.
And I need to protect you.
Why didn't you give me the
option to go out?
- Because you're the big star, honey.
Do you really think there's any need
to explain it to you?
Get out of the way, you're in the middle.
Well, time's running out.
Now or never.
You can cross the line and get out of here.
or stay with us
and get the million.
All right, all right, all right,
those who want to get out,
hands on your head.
Go ahead, through the loading dock door.
"What the profesor had achieved
was to divide the hostages
among those who were to become
in our partners
and those who could still complicate things.
Or so we thought."
Yes?. Suárez.
- Inspector, we have the estate.
It fits the description perfectly.
- Where is it?
- Very close to Palomeque, the village
of the pharmacy.
It has 640 hectares and private
hunting grounds.
Inside is an abandoned dwelling
large enough
to plan a heist of this magnitude.
- How did you find it?
- A neighbour claims to have seen
to a group of young people on
St. John's night.
They didn't look like hunters,
but he heard detonations.
throughout the summer.
- Detonations?
- Yes.
He don't know what they were, but he is sure
that they weren't hunting shotguns.
I'm mobilizing units into the area and preparing
an assault team for possible armed intervention.
- All right, send all the information to my cell phone.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Lobo, we've got a green light,
we're on our way,
teams 1, 2 and 3 ready. Now!
Salva, look, I don't feel very well.
Do you know how to drive?
Yes.
I need you to take me somewhere.
Tomorrow it all starts.
Sergio,
I want you to promise me one thing.
If things get ugly, you'll get away.
You're not gonna wait in the hangar.
Nothing's gonna go wrong.
You know as well as I do that everything
can go wrong.
I'm only going in there if you promise me
that if the thing goes to hell you're
not going to get caught.
I'm not gonna promise you that.
Either you promise me that now or you stay tonight
without a captain in charge.
You already know me.
Nothing's going to go wrong, Andrés.
We're the resistance, aren't we?
"The profesor's life revolved around a single idea.
Resistance.
His grandfather,
who had resisted with the partisans
to defeat the fascists in Italy
had taught him that song.
And then he teach it to us."
Six kilometers straight ahead.
and then the first detour to the right.
Salva, can you go a little faster?
You're not gonna get a ticket with me.
You're going to 40.
It's true, I'm sorry, I'm just a little thick.
The left side and the right side as well.
Don't let anyone in without the suit.
And anyone who's not indispensable,
outside perimeter one, understand?
- I got it.
We've won the lottery.
Here's all the colored DNA.
Bring in the CSI photographers,
I want pictures of everything.
You have to cover this house, every corner.
"We're upstairs.
There's an attic, you're not going to believe
what we found."
Inspector, you have to see this.
It's all on the walls, timetables,
photos, plans...
The whole damn plan. We got 'em, fellas.
Your time is up.