What happened?
They blew up a mint vault.
with the latest printed plates.
It's essential that the police
have no idea what we're doing.
What do they want?
- Time
- They won't come out.
- How do you know?
They opened the vault,
but they didn't wanted the money.
They waited for the police.
They fired.
They dropped two bags, casually open,
dropping the bills down the street.
They pretended to be cornered
to win two days of negotiation.
What better plan than to get out of there
with the eight million?
They print their own unmarked money.
- We're locked up and
we don't know how long this can last.
As long as you don't try to fool me...
everything will be fine.
I love you, Mónica. I want you
to continue with your pregnancy.
And that we form a family
if we get out of here.
If we get out of here?
There is a way.
Guide the police in the assault.
I have a mobile.
In my office, in my coat.
- I'll go.
Sit down!
Come out.
I don't think it's a good idea for you to abort.
- What are you doing, Denver?
Kill her.
Get on your knees.
Say you removed the body. I hide.
There's not a drop of blood.
Shoot me here.
We said no victims.
- He had a phone.
What did you want? A spanking?
- Scare the shit out of her, not kill her.
- What's going on here?
Berlín had a hostage executed.
- Who was it?
Your son.
It's here, isn't it?
Paula? Paula, darling. Where are you?
I'm Raquel Murillo's mother.
I cannot locate her.
Excuse me, Inspector.
I have your mother on the phone.
What a mess you' re having, huh?
Escort the gentleman, please.
Son, did you kill that woman?
- I can't breathe.
- Dad, what's wrong with you?
My husband... my ex-husband
had taken my daughter and...
He's got a restraining order
for mistreatment.
I feel the emotion and the helplessness
of having someone to help you.
Someone... Who's going to help me?
- Me.
Forgive me. I don't know how...
Thank you.
Raquel...
Do you know why I left the mine?
Because I was claustrophobic.
I couldn't stand being stuck in that hole.
Moscú! What are you doing?
Everybody down on the ground!
- Hold it right there.
- Dad!
- Cover your face.
- Let me out.
- They're opening the doors.
- Record it!
A shot. I don't see their faces.
- It's my fault.
- I didn't kill her.
I've got her hidden away.
Put on your masks and hoods
and get out on the roof,
without doing any signs or nonsense.
Now, Dad.
You didn't kill the girl, did you?
He ordered me to kill her
and I shot her.
I couldn't do anything else.
- You're talking about Mónica.
You killed Mónica!
Fucking hell!
- Get on your knees.
- What?
Snipers, for fuck's sake!
Let them think we're hostages.
Hands on your head.
- They kneel them to execute them.
- Everybody down on the ground!
Cóndor 3. One Dalí points to another.
I request instructions.
I'm waiting for authorization.
Still on your knees.
- Instructions?
Give me the green light.
I have a shot at the kidnapper.
What the fuck are you doing?
There's snipers, for fuck's sake.
Get on your knees.
- They're being targeted.
- Give me the green light!
- They're going to execute you.
- They'll shoot.
- Request to open fire.
- Let's open fire.
- They will kill them.
Green light.
Cóndor three, open fire.
Oh, good! Okay, Mr. Torres. All right.
But now we're changing series, okay?
We changed the letter, okay?
Another country, yes.
You didn't reject me.
Helsinki! Go down, hurry.
You killed her, motherfuckers.
Water, please. Water.
Thank you. Arturo, hold on.
Alcohol, alcohol.
Don't remove your hand...
- Raquel.
- "Ex-employees of the factory
they revealed to us the identity
of the person wounded by the police.
This is Arturo Román,
general manager of the factory,
who's just been wounded by police forces,
while he was on the roof with the robbers.
The events occurred
after 32 hours of kidnapping."
I need to talk to my wife, please.
I need to talk to my wife.
"They say that when we're at death's gates
we can finally see our life clearly.
And Arturo Román,
bleeding to death on a table,
was expecting just that:
the clairvoyance of death.
Find out once and for all
who was the love of his life.
Laura, with whom he shared
14 years in holy matrimony,
or Mónica, his secretary and lover
with whom he returned to youth?
Unfortunately, the only certainty
Arturo had at the time
was that if they didn't take off the bullet,
he'd kick the bucket without solving the riddle.
And, frankly, our first-aid courses
didn't guarantee anything."
Inferior vena cava.
Renal right.
Left.
Mesenteric.
Pulmonary right.
Left.
This is the heart.
Cava.
Right Subclavian
and left.
Brachial.
Humeral.
Internal jugular.
External jugular.
And in red the main arteries.
Stop it, stop it.
Let's see.
You want us to learn
medicine with two markers?
If anyone gets shot,
he won't be able to go to the hospital.
You'll manage inside.
It'll be a bloody suicide.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Lock us in that mousetrap, okay.
It's a different matter to kill us.
- Denver.
We're asking you to learn
how to take out a bullet.
Don't start with your epic of the suburbs.
- It's not difficult. You take the tweezers,
you take out the bullet without fucking anything else.
- That's it.
- Nothing but a shot.
If I get shot, you take me to the hospital.
The answer is no.
I'd rather be lame and free
than healthy and in a cell.
No one's coming out.
Each one is a clue and a thread to pull.
If anyone resigns, this is the right time.
He stays during the robbery and then leaves.
Will the talk last long?
I'll keep my dick like Helsinki's.
- Hey! What do you say about my willy?
You want to see my willy?
- That's enough.
Please...
Get dressed.
Please have someone else stand here.
- Willy.
Let's go.
You don't? No, no, no...
Well, here we are.
- Well...
- Come on, Nairobi.
Nothing's going on, is it?
But what a sexy girl!
You go on.
- Oops! Okay.
Let's see what you learned.
Well, here's the carotid...
- Uh-huh.
"And so, playing doctor,
I discovered that Nairobi was more
interesting than it seemed.
...the little heart.
The aorta...
"And though no one
knew anything about anyone,
I never suspected Nairobi had a son.
Or a daughter.
And that seemed to indicate
the scar from her C-section."
What are you doing?
Hey! What are you doing?
- Where are you going?
- What's going on?
What are you looking at?
- Easy, huh?
No, no.
You're gonna eat the marker.
- What's going on?
- She's a bit of a dyke.
I don't know what the fuck she' s looking at.
Dyke, you. That you had
your bean melting like a sugar cube.
- My bean melting, I'm going to...
- Hey!
"And that's where our friendship began."
Raquel, Interior on the phone.
What do I tell them? Raquel?
Raquel! What do I tell them?
What?
- They'll ask who gave the order.
- I gave the order.
Tell them... the one injured is a hostage.
And hang up the fucking phone!
- He looked like a robber.
I asked for a green light. I insisted.
Inspector, I'm taking responsibility with you.
Inspector, the ambulance is ready.
Let's talk to the kidnapper.
- Preparing communication with the kidnapper.
- A decision had to be made.
It seemed like they were going
to execute them and we didn't have time.
Quiet, please!
Profesor?
You fired on the hostages.
There's one between life and death.
I guess that's why you call.
I've got the ambulance for the wounded man.
- No one is going to get out of here.
He's bleeding out.
Because of the bullet fired by you.
Will you let him die?
Let a medical team come in.
Profesor, listen...
I know it was my mistake,
but if a hostage dies,
it'll be the same for you as for me.
Because I assure you
that in less than five minutes
all public opinion will know
that he died because you wouldn't
let us come in and save his life.
Two surgeons, a nurse and surgical supplies.
Let me know when they get here.
Thank you.
I must also ask you something.
He wants to talk to his wife.
Of course.
Fucking hell.
Find Mr. Román's wife.
How long before we have the medical team?
- By helicopter from La Paz,
10 or 15 minutes.
Bring them in. Now!
Okay.
Excuse me, can you drive?
- Yeah, yeah..
- I need to go out, take a ride.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Hey, Raquel.
What's going on?
I have to think.
Start.
Don't look at me like that.
I will not leave you alone.
Where the hell is she?
The motherfucker got away!
Let's see.
Go, go.
There we are.
Tell me, daughter.
Will you come to sleep tonight?
- I don't know, Mom.
- Why? Is something wrong?
Mom, I'm...
I made a very serious mistake at work.
- Daughter, your job is very difficult.
Go on, tell me about it,
because nothing seems so serious.
within five minutes of telling it.
- I was drinking some wine with...
- That's fine with me.
With whom? Do I know him?
- No, Mom. I don't even know him.
The fact is, when I got back to the tent,
there was a very serious situation,
of risk, in the roof of the factory and...
I thought one of the hostages
was in danger, so I gave...
order to shoot.
And the shot was taken by an innocent man.
- Yes, yes. I saw it on TV, daughter.
And now I don't know what to do.
I don't know whether to call his wife,
give a press release, resign...
I don't know what to do, Mom.
- To begin with, take it easy
and don't blame yourself.
Aren't they there with masks and guns,
locked up, all stirred up?
You just wanted to protect
the hostages, didn't you?
What if you saved someone's life?
You wouldn't be calling me
on the phone right now, would you?
Well, I wouldn't have known in passing
that you're meeting strangers to drink beer.
- For God's sake. I'm not meeting strangers.
- Did you kiss?
- How can I kiss him? If I don't know him.
- Bah... Knowing him, what a nonsense.
The lovely thing is the crush.
Daughter, we have so little time
in this life...
- Well, Mom, that's not the point now.
I'm in a critical work situation.
- Well, then fuck that job of yours.
Why don't you ask them
to put you to stamp passports
so you can enjoy yourself a little?
Or do you think that in the future
you'll be holding hands with
the kidnapper in a nursing home?
Well, no, daughter, no.
But, maybe, with that stranger...
Yeah, laugh at me,
but I know what I'm saying.
I've been a widow for 20 years and...
Time doesn't stop, daughter.
And it doesn't go back either, you know?
- Entering the perimeter.
- I'll think about it, mother.
And you, if I don't make it,
go to bed, okay?
- Okay.
- Hey, and you go to bed with someone, too.
Mónica.
What are you doing here? Are you crazy?
I wasn't feeling well.
I think it's the meds
that didn't sit me very well.
Medicines?
That will do, the drugs.
That's what it's going to be.
Oh, my God, she' s boiling like a coffee pot.
We've got to get her
out of here running like hell.
I'll help you. Wait.
Can you leave me alone for a moment?
Please.
How do you see her?
- I think she's under the weather.
I see her very badly.
If we don't get that bullet
out of her, she's gonna peg out.
- Dad, take it easy.
She' s gonna be fine.
Why the fuck did you shoot her?
- Because Berlín was going to kill her.
I couldn't do anything else.
- Son of a bitch.
If he wants to kill someone
he can pull the trigger, not you.
We're here to steal, aren't we?
Not to kill someone.
Or save lives.
Fuck, we're bastards.
It's up to us...
- Dad, relax.
It's okay.
Mónica, are you done yet?
Yes.
- Let's go.
- Raquel, wait a minute.
I want to talk to you.
I want to go undercover with the medical team.
Someone will come in, but not you.
- Oh, sure.
There's always someone better
for everything, isn't there?
Raquel, I'm a firearms expert.
I can get in there.
At a glance I know how many they have,
what they are
and whether they're fake or not.
We can find out who the robbers are.
- You're right.
You'll come with me
and you' Il cover the doctors.
And now I'll tell you what we'll do.
I heard a gunshot before.
The police.
They shot a hostage.
A hostage?
- Yes.
Who's that?
Who did the police shoot?
The head of the factory.
Arturo?
Did the police kill Arturo?
No. He didn't kill him.
Is he all right?
- Yes.
Is he alive?
Is Arturo all right?
- It's okay. Yes.
Are you sure?
- Sure.
Is he all right?
- A surgeon is coming in.
With his team.
You'll have surgery
and you'll be saved, okay?
Are they going to do the surgery?
- Yes.
You have to tell him I'm alive.
To Arturo. You have to tell him.
Do you hear me?
- No one here will say anything to anyone.
Because you're gonna be fine
and so will he, okay?
Let's go. Let's see that wound.
Relax.
It's just that he thinks it was all his fault.
I picked up the phone
because he asked for it.
And now I'm dead because of him.
You must tell him I'm alive.
And his son too.
Are you pregnant?
All right.
Congratulations.
Give me a pen, please.
- Okay.
When?
Thank you.
Ángel!
I want you to know
that I've decided to come in.
I'll take advantage of the medical intervention.
I welcome these decisions you make
for an ambulance ride.
But my presence is only in response
to the government's wish
that there's no violent outcome.
- Oh, wow.
What a pacifist
has suddenly become that one of the CNI.
Wasn't he the one who wanted to come in
yesterday with the tanks?
I wanted to surprise them.
Get this finished as soon as possible.
But now the priority is zero victims.
So my advice is to negotiate and wait.
It must be so fucked up to be here all day
believing himself to be more than anyone else,
without making a single decision, right?
The fellow member of the hostage crisis.
Inspector, I'm not going to go on the attack
because I understand that at a certain age
hormones take over in there.
I know that from my mother.
- Where are you going?
- As you can imagine,
I have to report all this, don't I?
Oh, of course.
So far the kidnappers are always ahead of us.
They had it all figured out.
Minus this shot.
It's the first thing that
gets out of their plan.
And we have to take advantage of it.
The only way we can get in here
without being detected by their cameras
is to advance through this tube in the subsoil.
Which leads directly to the basements.
It's the ventilation nozzle.
- It's seven months old,
to release heat from the press.
The work is in progress.
They probably don't know about it.
I need two of your men to come through here.
Officer García Lobo,
here, and I'll go with him.
- Okay. The sub-inspector Rubio
will accompany the two surgeons
and enter as a nurse.
18:09.
All on time.
At 18:15, the medical team will be in.
According to the chief of internal medicine
the surgery won't last more than 30 minutes.
But they can extend it exactly until 19:00.
The departure of the doctors
will concentrate a greater number
of kidnappers to watch them.
At this moment, Suárez and Lobo
will enter through the subsoil.
They'll enter through
the basement chest dressed in red overalls
and masks of Dalí.
They will infiltrate with the hostages.
We will succeed
if we operate with clock precision.
Inspector!
- Arturo Román's wife.
- One moment, please.
Suárez, go.
Take care of the doctors.
And be careful.
- We prepare operative!
What happened? Is my husband all right?
Your husband is conscious and stabilized.
He has been shot down by mistake.
- Shot down? What do you mean, shot down?
- He is wounded, but alive.
Relax.
Relax
The kidnappers allow us a surgical team
and he's going to undergo surgery immediately.
- Excuse me, but...
I wasn't even listening, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Sit down, please.
- Thank you
- Can you talk to him right now?
- Yes.
Put this on.
Almansa, record it!
Hello?
Profesor, there's Arturo Román's wife.
Okay.
That bullet needs to be taken out now.
You do it, Dad.
You have colder blood.
Where's the kit the Profesor gave us?
There's a scalpel.
- Berlín has it.
Fucking hell.
I don't think it's a good idea
to ask him, do you?
The surgeons! Go steal their instruments.
- Run!
- Okay.
Hold on! Hold on!
Give him the note, please.
Now I'm gonna wash your wound, okay?
It's all right.
You're gonna be all right, okay?
Arturo. Arturo!
What's your wife's name?
Laura.
That's a pretty name.
Well, you're going to talk to Laura.
Wives are good for these moments.
They're comforting.
No one remembers his wife
when he is stoned to death
at the door of the disco, but
if you have a problem, an accident
or merely fear...
things change.
You' re not thinking about
your secretary now?
Yes?
No, I'm not.
But who can remember now lovers
with children who could be abortions...
Or just nothing.
- Spare me the speech, will you?
Listen to me.
If you say something weird,
I'll put a deathblow in you
and your wife listens to it in a minute.
Can you imagine?
Inspector!
They're turning on a phone.
That phone needs to be bugged.
I want to see the selfie and main cameras.
There, there.
Oh, hi, sweetie.
Arturo, darling, how are you?
All right, all right. I'm fine.
The shot was clean.
- There is no image.
Neither selfie nor principal cam.
They've been plugged.
They're gonna let some surgeons in now.
I know, I know.
Look, I've been...
I've been thinking about you and...
And in everything we've done wrong.
Don't think about it, honey. Not now.
Not now.
Besides, it's my fault.
I know we're not fine.
That we haven't been well in a while.
I've neglected you and the boys.
I've been selfish.
I promise you all that will change,
you hear me?
I promise you it's gonna change.
You've been saying for ten years
that you want to see
your sister in Australia.
To take advantage of the opportunity
for children to learn English.
And meet the kangaroos.
Well, that's the first thing we'll do
when we get out.
I owe you.
I'm gonna do it for you.
For how much I love you.
All the years wasted chasing...
Thinking that the only important thing
was money and position.
When all that matters is you.
It's always been you.
Since the day I met you.
I swear to you, there are times that...
That I try to remember that day...
And I wonder
what the hell you saw in me, Mónica.
Laura.
Now just think about getting out of there.
Just think about it.
I love you.
I love you, my darling.
Are you okay?
Calm down.
- You really tread the boards, Arturo.
Your secretary in the familiy way...
Laurita waiting for you
in the 4x4 with the children.
You, surrounded by money,
are a legend.
- Berlín!
The doctors are out there!
- You're gonna have to excuse me.
- Does everyone know what to do?
- They know!
Of course they know!
Are you ready?
Well, they're ready.
Mercedes!
Are you ready?
- Yes, sir.
- I want her out of here.
Río, take her to an office.
Nairobi
- We put on the masks!
And with me! Rock and roll!
Come on in.
Leave everything on the floor.
Close the doors.
Advance.
Hands on your head and legs open.
We're going to frisk you.
- Almansa, escort the gentleman, please.
Listen to me carefully.
One of the paramedics is an undercover cop.
Which one?
- The one with the glasses.
You know what to do.
Perfectly.
- Let's do it. Berlín!
It's got to be a hell of a goldsmith job.
I know.
Gentlemen!
The one with the glasses is the cop.
They'll come in.
I don't know if during an assault,
an emergency.
Whether it will be the one from the Red Cross
or the one from the pizzas,
but what's clear
is that they're gonna try
to infiltrate someone.
And that will be our chance
to try to put them on a Trojan horse.
Do you know what it is?
I don't know, but the rhyme is easy.
- No!
The Trojan horse...
- Got anal intercourse!
Shut the fuck up and stay focused!
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
The Greeks were at war with the Trojans.
One day the Trojans found
at the gates of their city
a wooden horse.
A huge wooden horse!
And carried away by their vanity they thought
it was a surrender gift from the Greeks.
So they opened the doors...
and they put it inside.
What they didn't know was
that that horse was hollow.
And replete with Greek warriors.
That night the Trojans lost the war.
And that's exactly what we're going to do.
When they try to get in
and think that they' re winning the battle...
Put the metal objects in that tray.
Glasses.
Watches.
If you have weapons...
Microphones.
I also advise you to deposit them.
We're going to track
any kind of radio frequency.
Take your shoes off too.
Please.
And now lie down.
Get on the ground.
That's it.
Cockroach way.
On your feet.
Put your shoes on.
Take only the glasses.
You' re going to need them.
Welcome back.
Take your things and come with me.
- Thank you.
What?
Sometimes people like you are on TV.
Like me what?
Robbers.
But you don't fit in very well.
It looks like this isn't your thing.
Why is that?
The way you pick up your rifle.
I thought you were the ambassador's daughter
and not Rambo's.
Well, my father always wanted to have a son.
and since I've been five years old,
he's been leading me to shoot.
Shooting?
To what?
To the carnival sticks?
Wild boar, red deer,
antelope...
But what my father would like
is to hunt ecologists.
But I don't like guns.
Once, in Norwich,
a friend of my father's had his rifle shot.
I saw it all.
Shot in the back, people screaming...
It's like when...
you see an accident on the road
and it gets engraved the...
the bloodstain.
Well...
It's unloaded, okay?
Don't be afraid.
How do you see it, Doctor?
Will I get out of this?
The bullet is lodged
on the collarbone.
There's no interest in vital organs
and there's no bone splinters either.
Nobody's gonna die.
- Do your thing.
"Denver didn't have time for diagnostics."
Anesthesia.
"Mónica was bleeding to death.
If he didn't steal the scalpels soon,
to have spared his life
wouldn't have done any good."
What anesthesia are you going to give him?
Total sedation is preferable
in case of setbacks.
- No.
Better give him a local anesthesia, huh?
so my friend Arturo and I can talk.
during the intervention,
eh, Arturito?
- Take it easy, take it easy.
What's that watch for?
It's to control the duration
of local anesthesia,
Twenty-five minutes.
If there were any inconvenience
during the intervention,
we should give him another dose.
Put the watch on the screen.
"That operation was scheduled
and it had to last exactly
the 25 minutes ordered by
the inspector.
That countdown would leave
two policemen with Dalí masks.
inside the factory
or if it went wrong,
two corpses in the ventilation ducts."
Drop the fucking rifle.
It's unloaded, let it go
before it pisses me off.
- The bullet from the breech.
Suárez, do you copy?
Tube's clear.
We're advancing towards the target.
Turn around and put your hands
on the back of your head.
Let's go!
- Let's go!
Let's go.
What's going on?
You're not so tough anymore, huh?
Come on, damn it, come on!
Shoot,
you stupid little bitch.
On your knees!
Scalpel.
- Stop it, I'll deliver the weapons here.
- You've crowned yourself before, eh, Arturo?
Changing your wife's name.
Of course, it's normal.
Fornicating in the mornings with Mónica,
spending afternoons with Laura...
It's normal for you to get confused.
But I love them both.
That's the truth.
When you're in my situation,
it's very easy to judge.
Everybody thinks you're a scoundrel,
a son of a bitch.
God forbid I should make moral judgments.
I can understand everything.
You can talk to me
quietly of anything.
But I'm really a miserable man,
a poor man who's in love with two women
and that he doesn't have enough guts
to choose one.
Why the fuck did you do that?
I don't know, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Get on the ground!
You're 11 meters from the entrance.
Received.
We continue.
- Fucking little posh girl,
motherfucker.
- I'm sorry.
- Shut the fuck up!
Don't tell me about your life, okay?
I'm not the fucking friend
of the outcasts, is that clear?
If you're begging friendship
from the one who kidnapped you,
is that you're so fucked up.
You know what...?
That I'm only six weeks pregnant
and I care more
about the kid's life than mine?
It takes more than an infection
for children not to go out and eat the world.
Hey, what's your name?
Moscú, they call me Moscú.
Hey, Moscú,
and how is it...
about...?
Well, about being a father.
Being a father...
Well, look, being a father
it's like if suddenly falls over you
a chariot of problems and also for life.
I mean, to be worried the rest of your days.
First, baby colds.
That's every weekend in the ER
instead of going out for drinks.
I don't care, I don't drink.
Well, it's worse for you
because you don't know
how good a Pacharán feels
when you leave him there
asleep in his cradle.
And then school.
The fear
that we parents have that...
that your son will not be the fool
and punching bag of his class,
what they call now bullying.
What happens is that in my case...
it was my son who punched.
Every now and then he was expelled.
I don't know how many schools
we went through...
And then his mother,
the poor thing, who had her trade...
Well, poor thing...
She left me alone, lying there like...
In front line
because after all, all you want is
that he' s normal,
that he doesn't stay in the corner
smoking junk
instead of going to high school.
But being a father...
It's okay.
It's very...
Hey, no, no!
Mónica, do not sleep!
Look at me, look at me!
Do not sleep, honey.
Come on, look at me!
- That's it.
- What's going on?
- Nothing, it's fine.
- Yes?
- You have very high fever.
No, don't stop looking at me.
All right, look at me, that's it.
I bring everything.
Five minutes to get the doctors out.
I got it.
- I've got it.
Thank you.
And now you sew.
Me?
Yeah, you.
You're a nurse, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah.
Well then.
- It's local anesthesia.
We put it in the wound
and pain-free in a moment.
I'm coming.
- Come on, let me, I'll do it.
Keep an eye on the pulse.
Okay.
Come on, let's go...
That's it, that's it.
You know what I'm gonna do when...?
When I get out of here?
I'm going to study online.
- You haven't studied in your life.
- I'm not telling you I'm going
to do medicine, but...
Yeah, pick up where I left off, you know?
This one's gonna hurt
a little bit more, okay?
Look, look.
Well...
Okay, that's it.
- That's it.
Now in five minutes it takes effect and...
And we start opening, okay?
Let's go. Okay.
You're two meters from the entrance.
We visualize target.
Wait,
I feel a little sick.
I think I'm gonna throw up.
Are you a nurse, a dancer
or what the hell is wrong with you?
I'm a nurse,
but I'm not used to
working surrounded by guns.
- Well, that's enough.
I sew,
but I want everyone to be quiet, please.
- Come on, let's go.
Tweezers.
- The Profesor wants to talk to you.
- All right.
Take the nurse to the bathroom
so he can throw up.
If he doesn't, you stick his head
in the toilet until he does.
Until he does.
Goodbye, Arturo.
- Go.
Let's go.
They're transmitting in shortwave
and ciphered, so they're coming in,
but I don't know which way.
Hearing, active plan b.
Activate it and get the medical team out now.
Now.
My love, be strong.
I'm fine.
I love you.
Mónica.
What the fuck do you want?
How should I know?
I've seen that before and...
And it's caught my eye.
I didn't know what it was.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay, sorry.
See you later.
What are you doing?
Do you want to leave?
I don't want to talk.
How old is...
your son?
Seven.
He's seven.
Where is he?
With his father?
Not with his father.
He's never been with his father.
There's no word from his father.
What's his name?
Axel.
His name is Axel.
It means "axe."
Axe. Yes.
Because it's an axe,
like his mother.
That kid's a survivor, you know?
He's survived everything.
It's like a cork in the middle of the sea
that don't sink.
That's the way he is.
At the age of three...
I had to take it from my mother's house
because her husband gave him anise liqueur
when I wasn't there because
he didn't like the baby crying.
So I took him.
Just the two of us,
not needing any family at all.
Him and me.
We were fucking great.
But I screwed up.
One day...
I had to go get some pills to sell.
and...
And I left him alone.
Five minutes,
it was gonna be five minutes, huh?
And he messed it up
with the fucking Spiderman.
Fucking Spiderman!
Because he wanted
to be a superhero, he said.
He climbed everything.
He climbed in a way
that you couldn't believe it.
And he went out the terrace
through the window.
Then there he grabbed a chair,
climbed into the chair.
and he started, "Mommy!
Mommy!"
Three and a half years old.
Of course, five minutes later
I had a police patrol there,
the fire brigade...
Everybody.
I got caught with the pills,
with a background,
without a job.
To the gaol.
Then my boy started going
from family to family,
from hand to hand.
And nothing for me.
Nothing, huh?
They didn't leave me one visit,
not one phone call.
Not a thing.
Then I got out of jail...
and nothing.
They didn't give him to me.
Did you see him again?
They don't let me.
But at least
I know where he is, huh?
Yes?
- He' s in the Canary Islands.
He's with a family that owns a hotel.
He' s fine.
Are you gonna go after him?
I'm going to take him...
and that's it.
To the other side of the world.
Let me tell you something,
in this heist
I'm not gonna fuck it up.
Not me, not anyone,
because if someone
misses the point completely
I destroy his life.
Of all the plans people have around here,
yours...
is the best.
And I'll tell you something else...
Do you like tequila?
It's 4:03 am.
Tomorrow there's class at first hour.
Plastic explosive.
Sorry.
It would be nice if you
were rested for class.
We are sleepless.
- To bed.
All three of us?
- Each to his own.
Those pajamas look good on you, Profesor.
Now.
And you with the lights.
This guy's makes me horny,
he makes me horny.
He makes me horny!
Well, you don't show a thing.
Do I show?
A lot.
- Well, let him notice it.
I feel dizzy, kid!
"Deputy Inspector Ángel knew
in a thousandth of a second.
that they had lost another battle.
Those sinister masks meant
that they were going to throw
two men to the lions.
Also that the guy who devised that heist
had more intelligence
and more imagination than the police,
the NIC and the Intervention Unit,
and when they get ahead of you like this,
it's time to run."
We have to leave now.
Miss, please, we're done here.
Can we go, please?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Quietly.
You' re following me.
- Doctor, doctor!
Wait a moment.
One minute 30 seconds.
There are frequency inhibitors.
Suárez, do you copy?
They've put in frequency inhibitors.
I think we're gonna lose communication.
Do you copy?
There are inhibitors.
We're losing communication.
Suárez...
How was the intervention?
Fine, but we'd have to be back in 24 hours.
I appreciate the interest,
but for the post-op
we have people sufficiently prepared.
Is my friend the nurse feeling better now?
Yes, yes, thank you.
I'm glad to hear it.
Forgive me for not accompanying you,
but I leave you in good hands.
Good-bye.
- Good-bye.
- Goodbye.
- Send our greetings to the outside!
Did you tell Arturo I'm okay?
Huh?
Did you tell Arturo I'm alive?
Yes...
I didn't tell him.
- Did you tell him or not?
I gave him the note.
And what did he say?
Fuck, he's gone crazy.
He's gone crazy, what's he gonna say?
That...
- Go on.
That he loves you very much...
- And what else?
He said that...
That when you get out of this,
he takes you to Australia.
To Australia?
Yes, it is.
I don't see it.
He also said he doesn't know
what you saw in him to notice him.
To Australia?
- Yes, Australia.
It's his wife's dream destiny.
Besides, Arturo knows I'm afraid of planes.
She came in, didn't she?
Did his wife go in with the doctors?
Was Laura here?
No.
Yes.
He told her on the phone.
- Suárez!
- Command post, do you copy?
Command post, do you copy?
Oh, shit.
Inspector, the surgeons are coming out.
Don't stop.
Run, run now.
Run now.
Run now!
Let's go!
Come on, get out!
Ángel comes running.
Something's happened.
Abort!
The masks have been changed.
They're not about Dalís.
They go straight to the slaughterhouse.
- What?
Attention, abort entry.
Suárez, do you copy?
Target achieved.
We proceed to remove
the lid and we are already inside.
What are you doing?
One bullet.
A gunshot wound.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, Moscú!
You're making a slaugther!
Give it to me!
"Then something unexpected happened."
- Leave it to me.
"Nairobi put all its effort
and meticulousness to the service
of the common good.
Instead of ratting them out,
he helped them save Mónica' s life."
I'm gonna get some air.
"Or at least her leg."
You bastards!
"She didn't come here to kill anyone."
Fuck, come on!
"And as I told you before,
she wasn't willing for anything
to screw up the Profesor's plan."
Suárez, do you copy?
The masks have changed.
There's interference.
Command post, do you copy?
I can't hear you.
They're not wearing the Dalí mask!
It's a fucking suicide.
Attention, do you copy?
Abort entry, repeat, abort entry!
We proceed
to draw weapons and we're in.
Abort entry!
That's an order!
The masks have changed.
They don't wear Dalí masks.
Attention, do you copy?
Abort entry!
I have breached
the first rule of the plan.
I killed a hostage.
But do you like men?
Don't women?
You'd rather save Alison Parker
than eight students?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I didn't expect this answer from you.
I think it's time to have a reflection,
back to the source.
That car is a loose end.
Tell me why you wiped the fingerprints.
They're the ones who are afraid now.
Hey, you!