Call Alberto, isn't he
the best of the scientist?
Well, let him come.
Get out of the car.
Son of a bitch.
Aah!
You're under arrest for assault on authority.
I'm calling from the police station,
I'm under arrest.
Where's the record of his arrest?
I want you to cross-check all the fingerprints.
with the spoon of sub-inspector Rubio.
How are we going to get out?
- Through a tunnel.
You're gonna have the hostages
digging in the boiler cellar.
We'll go out through another tunnel.
Just open it from vault number three.
from vault number three...
to a hangar I already have planned.
Earth!
I want to make you a deal.
If you want, you can come with me.
After the end, you can have everything I have.
with everything I've got.
Where the fuck are you going?
Turn around.
Quick! Mónica, open the door!
I'm gonna count to five and
then I'm gonna shoot him.
One...! Ah!
- You're coming with us.
If you crossed the line,
You crossed the line,
I'm not leaving you lying in the gutter.
Sometimes we try to help someone,
but the first to sink is oneself.
I tried to help your mother
every fucking day of my life.
- What'd you do?
- I left her in a Martorell roundabout,
it was either her or us.
- As soon as we get out, you and I are nothing.
Sub-inspector Rubio is coming out of the coma,
is the only person who knows who I am.
You have to go and check if it's a trap.
And if it isn't, finish him off.
They left me an envelope for you.
Sooner or later, this will all be over.
And then you and I will meet on the beach. Pick one.
I'll meet you at the beach. Choose one.
Palawan.
- Palawan.
The archipelago is a little above.
You're being held for collaboration
in the hostage assault to the
Fábrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre.
You slept with me because
I'm the lead inspector.
You want me to believe you have feelings for me?
It's something that's happening
to both of us, you know?
From now on what you have to say
you say it directly to the judge.
- I'm so sorry, Raquel.
Keep going...!
What are you gonna do to me?
We're going to request
unconditional and isolated imprisonment.
At 24 hours you say you want to make a pact,
it's possible that in that transfer
I can do something for you.
"If he had commanded me to be saved,
how was it possible
that he wasn't there?"
It's a call to Alison Parker's phone.
Río, it's Tokio. I'm going through
the heaven's gate.
In a minute.
Tokio's coming back!
- Tokio's coming back!
Get down!
- We have to open the door, dammit!
Shoot the target, shoot the biker!
Come on!
No! We've got to cover her up, damn it!
- Shooting kidnapper.
Dad, look out!
- Unit three, behind you, behind you!
Aah!
It's fucking crazy.
- What's that?
- Well, all this, Dad.
- This time it goes well, I'll tell you.
- This time?
- It's got to go well.
- We deserve it, don't we?
- Of course!
Help! Help!
- The first-aid kit!
- Get the fucking first-aid kit!
- Cover the wound!
- Look at me, look at me.
- Don't worry, this is a scratch
on the side, that's all.
On the side, on the side.
There's no exit wound, the bullet's inside.
- Nairobi!
- I am, I am!
- Fucking hell, he's bleeding out.
- Don't worry, I've got a lot blood.
Can't you see I've eaten a lot of black pudding?
- Okay, hold him for me. Berlín, morphine.
- Take it easy.
- Okay, let's see. Okay, okay.
I'm going to put him an IV.
Let me go, let me go.
- It's okay.
- Pull there, Denver.
- Wait, wait.
I'm going...
I'm going to put him an IV.
- Breathe slowly.
Breathe slower.
Pulse is firing.
- Gauze.
That's it.
Easy, Moscú.
It's all right.
You're gonna be okay.
Hey, are you gonna be okay?
- Yes.
Oh, yeah?
- Easy, Moscú.
Easy, Moscú.
It's okay.
He's been shot three times, Río.
That's three shots.
What a son of a bitch.
- Raquel.
I freed myself. I could have escaped,
I could have killed you, Raquel.
You didn't want to believe
that polygraph you brought either.
Well, look, this is proof that I'm telling the truth.
Well, you just screwed up with this act of love,
cause I'm gonna put you
in the gaol for 80 years.
Get up, slowly.
Hands on your head. And turn around.
Don't move, what the fuck are you doing?
Stay, stay! Stay! I told you!
Hands on your head.
Don't take another step.
Raquel, I will not stop.
You're gonna have to kill me.
Fucking hell.
Son of a bitch, my phone.
Three shots, three shots in the stomach.
We have to call a doctor,
we can't do anything.
It's time to keep a cool head, Tokio.
I'm not just thinking about Moscú.
I'm going to call the Profesor.
- The Profesor is not here!
I've called him a thousand times,
I don't know where the hell he is!
We have to call the inspector.
- We can't do that,
you know, it's not in the plan.
- What plan?
You know what my plan was?
Kill you.
But now it's Moscú that's dying,
so don't ever tell me again
what's not in the fucking plan.
This is Colonel Prieto.
- I'd like to speak to Inspector Murillo, please.
- NIC has taken over.
- Colonel, it's Fonollosa.
I would like to ask you
what you're wearing,
but I don't have time for small talk.
One of our men just got shot three times,
I want a surgeon in here now.
- You know what I want? Stop breaking my balls.
You pulled Silene Oliveira out of a police van.
and snuck it back into the factory,
have placed explosive devices that,
thank God, have failed.
Do you really think you're in
a position to ask for anything?
Look, it was a clean rescue on our part.
You, however, have started to shoot.
It would be nice if you could help save the life.
of this man.
- Listen to me carefully.
If you want to save that man's life,
take him out the front door, unarmed, and an ambulance
will be waiting to take care of him.
- We're not giving up our man, Colonel.
- Then you' Il have another corpse in the band.
Have you located the inspector?
- We're on it.
Helsinki, how do you see it?
- It's not a shot in the leg.
Stomach is a very bad area, Moscú. Very bad.
We need a surgeon.
- How much time do we have?
- Hours.
- 11, 12, 13.
But without a surgeon, we don't do anything.
- How many impacts do I have?
- That's three, Dad.
That's three.
- What a racket I've got down there.
- Moscú, they don't want
to put surgical equipment in,
but we have an ambulance out there
to take you to the hospital.
- Well, you can tell the police
to be fucked a lot, because I'm not going back
to jail.
That wall's got three blows
to go to the other side.
That's ten hours of work.
Start digging
and I'll take care of it, okay?
- Hold on, Dad, hold on.
I'll open that tunnel
even if it's head-butting.
Gentlemen, we're out of here.
There's been a shooting.
What happened?
I've got Moscú like a sieve, three shots.
Where is it?
- In the belly.
I don't think they hit the liver,
the rest I don't know.
How do you see him?
Fucked up.
But Moscú says it doesn't want
to go out, that in a few hours
we can enter the tunnel.
I've got the Serbs here,
we're going to dig, too
from this side. And I will locate
the Ukrainian doctor.
Anyway, you have to get out
as soon as possible.
I've been discovered, Andrés.
I don't know how long
it's gonna take the police to show up here.
What's new?
What's going on?
What's he doing here?
Will somebody tell me
what the hell is going on?
- Did you know that Sergio Marquina,
aka the Profesor, is Salva,
the brain from the heist? The man
you've been seeing in the bar for five days.
- Yeah, I just found out a few hours ago.
- You got a call from that man,
he was calling you from the police station
in Canillas, where he was being held.
Minutes later you went, set up a scene
to get him out of there and destroyed the record
where his fingerprints were.
- Then I didn't know who he was.
- The evidence you destroyed
would have identified him
as the man who forced the zeta
from which the Russian was threatened
not to make the robot portrait.
from the Ibiza that you found in the scrap yard
and from which Ángel stole a spoon,
incriminating him before the accident.
- Then you took him
to the gang's house in Toledo, right?
- And you put him in my car,
where there was the only evidence
of judicial value I could get out of the house.
- The chimney papers and the evidence are gone.
- After knocking out Inspector Vicuña.
- And when Ángel did his job
and threw his suspicions at him,
you kicked him out of the investigation.
- And as a culmination
of this beautiful story,
while you were destroying your partner,
you were banging the boss of the gang.
- All right, all right.
To begin with, that man can't be here,
He has a restraining order,
so if he's not
500 meters from me in five minutes,
I'm gonna have him arrested.
I didn't know who that man was.
And I'm gonna prove it.
I can tell you where he's hiding.
What the fuck did you do,
leave my mother in a roundabout?
All my life making me think
she was a motherfucker.
- It was her or us.
I'm not breaking your head
because we need you
to get out of here.
As soon as we get out,
you and I are nothing.
Two strangers, Denver and Moscú.
Fucking hell!
Can somebody explain to me
what the fuck this is, please?
Not that way. We said in one million rolls,
please. To the limit I want it, shit.
We're gonna keep printing bills
for a few more hours.
Then stop the machines
and erase all the records.
I want everybody working full!
We're leaving now!
As you hear it.
I've heard of another very good place,
at the Federal Reserve.
- Come here for a minute.
How's Moscú?
- Steady.
- We still have a few hours left, don't we?
Shall we make 500 bills?
- The 500 notes are from Russians
and people with lousy taste.
I'm not Russian, do I seem to you
to have lousy taste?
- Berlín...
- I have dubious tastes...
- Berlín, should I print or not?
- 100 and 200.
- Torres!
Torres.
We stop machines, change plates
and start making
200 and 100 bills.
- In hand.
You like to jump from
stone to stone in puddles.
And at every step you take, a stone sinks.
You're leaving corpses on the verges.
Who came up with the armored car heist,
you or your boyfriend?
Well, now your boyfriend's a corpse.
And so is your mother.
I'm sure you were aware of the damage
you were doing to your mother.
I thought I'd never see you again.
What's the matter with you?
- He told me.
That I'm leaving corpses
wherever I'm going.
Berlín kicked me out and I went back in.
And I've put everyone's life in danger.
For fuck's sake I had to go back.
And now the body is Moscú.
- Moscú is no corpse, okay?
He's gonna be fine and we're all
gonna get out of here together.
together.
I'm a fucking black cat crossing paths.
You're a black panther.
My black panther.
How are you?
- Fucking right now.
You have no fucking idea
how much I love you,
no fucking idea.
I love you, too.
Let's start getting the money out of here!
Come on, come on!
The ones in the other room, too!
Ariadna, Ariadna. Ariadna.
Not you, come.
Leave that there.
Denver.
You have to stop, you have to stop,
this doesn't make any sense.
Leave the pickax.
Put your pickax down and
go convince your father.
He needs to be taken to the hospital,
can't wait any longer.
- There's only one way out
and it's through this tunnel.
And I'm going to do it with my father.
You know why, huh? Why?
Because when we get out of this,
you're not going to be dressed
in a red overalls, you're going
to be in white, gorgeous.
And I'll be waiting for you at an altar.
And I need my father to be there, by my side,
so he can see it, so he can grab my shoulder
and get excited, you know what I mean?
I'm not gonna stop, I'm not gonna stop.
- Well, we get to work?
- To work.
Shall we go?
- Let's go.
- There's not much left!
- There's nothing left, damn it!
- There's little left, Río, there's little left!
- Not two meters!
Have you thought about my proposal?
A short but passionate love story?
In a tropical country?
What about a fully-fledged inheritance?
800 million to be divided.
- That's the least of it, Berlín.
I like the idea of going away with you.
Although I'm very sorry,
because you're going to die.
- You're gonna be a beautiful widow.
You and I have
to get married, huh, Ariadna?
I've never made it in a white dress.
At night.
How about on a beach, under the stars,
by some wild rite with a lot of light
and a lot of fire?
Beautiful, huh?
Will you marry me, Ariadna?
Hey.
I'm sure there are people who think
that living with a dying man
it's boring. And they're wrong,
it's the opposite.
It's going to death.
Driving without a seat belt.
Riding a motorcycle without a helmet.
Diving without a bottle.
Releasing the reins definitively to a borderless.
And drink.
How do you see it, some little
Berlín kids running on the beach?
It's a joke.
So in that direction you've given us
is where Mr. Marquina is supposed to have
his center of operations,
in that cider factory, right?
- Yes.
What's this?
- It's a warehouse.
There's nothing in there.
A dilapidated car,
a lot of junk, but no sign
of an operations center.
- Are you sure about the address you gave us?
Oh, yes, I do. And I was there.
And what did you go to do?
Make love.
"Our first slogan was no names,
no personal relationships.
The Profesor had imagined
an affectionless heist,
but when I saw him there, smiling at me,
I realized He was the closest thing to a father.
I've ever had in all my life."
What are you laughing at, big guy?
Of your witticisms.
Escape and return to the factory again.
You see.
Dressed as a cop and everything.
James Bond style.
Now that' s really fucked up the cops.
He's shaking.
Moscú, Moscú, eh.
Hey.
He's white as snow in Stalingrad.
His pulse is 35.
He needs a transfusion, get the plasma.
Moscú
- Let's go.
Zero negative.
- Hey, hey.
That's it, you're here again.
That's it, you all right?
That's it, you're here.
You're here, huh?
How's the tunnel going?
We're very close now.
Honey, honey. Baby.
Why don't you get some rest, huh?
Isn't it?
Let's go.
Dragan, downstairs.
Inspector.
I'm afraid the inspector can't speak to you,
is being investigated
for possible collaboration
in the robbery and for obstruction of justice.
But you know all that, don't you?
Because of the special trust
you have in her.
We know who you are, Salva.
Or rather, Sergio Marquina.
So you no longer need to use that GPS voice.
Colonel Prieto.
We've got a man dying because of your gunshots.
If you don't get a doctor in here by now,
you'll have been convicted him.
The only one who's condemned that man is you.
Him and all the people whom you' re tearing apart
with this heist,
including your friend the inspector.
How can his conscience bear it?
Listen, if you want, afterwards,
we talk at length about
the health of my conscience and yours,
but now we need a doctor.
There's no more afterwards, Mr. Marquina,
we know you' re close.
And we know the position
of the three repeaters
who logged the calls you made to the inspector.
for the last five days.
We will search house by house.
And when you least expect it,
we'll knock at your door.
So stop complicating things
and turn yourself in.
As I said to the inspector,
surrender was never an option.
I'll wait for you.
Not everyone lets us into their homes,
There's a lot of people on their side,
they're the heroes of TV
and we, the guys who want
to put them behind bars.
- Call Judge Andrade and get a warrant.
- We can't break down the door to 10 000 homes,
we're talking about a radius of 850 meters,
that's what the repeaters cover.
We have to be more precise.
- All right, we'll be more precise.
But call Judge Andrade and get a warrant.
- I see you have everything under control,
so I don't quite understand
what I'm doing here.
Am I under arrest?
No, inspector, you' re not under arrest,
you' re being investigated.
- All right, then I'm off.
- Inspector.
Before you leave,
I need you to hand over
your badge and your gun.
- And now you can bug my phone if you want.
Wait, wait.
You go ahead, I'll go get you new overalls.
Hi.
Ari.
Why did you sabotage the escape plan?
Because of Denver?
Is that why you hit Arturo,
because you have something with him?
Mónica, did he rape you?
- No.
Why are you with him?
Because I love him.
Because I love him,
I know it may sound absurd,
that maybe you think it's crazy,
but... But it's real.
It's real, Ari.
It's the first time anyone's ever
looked me in the eye and been honest.
He really loves me.
What about you?
Are you with Berlín?
Pure survival.
I thought he was killing people.
That they'd killed you, too.
I thought it was the only way to save me.
I hate Berlín, I hate him,
I hate him, I hate him.
And now the asshole thinks
I have feelings for him,
that we're living a love story.
He wants me to marry him
when we get out of here,
to take care of him. He is sick.
- I know.
And you're gonna do it?
It'll only be a year,
I don't know, we'll...
Travel around the world, living like kings.
And going to fancy places and that's it.
There are thousands of people
who accept proposals like this on a daily basis.
Ari.
But is it worth it?
I'm gonna take all his money.
This guy fucked up my life, Mónica,
he fucked up my life.
I take four tranquilizers a day
so I can withstand his presence.
He raped me, he raped me.
When he will be by my side
and can no longer move
and depend only on me,
I will tell him what a son of a bitch he is
and all the damage he's done to me.
The calls made by the suspect
the last five days have been recorded
by these three repeaters
located here, here and here.
Except for the one he did
from the police station in Canillas.
- You were right,
it's a very wide radius.
Gómez, ask the Telecommunications Department
to triangulate the signal
to delimit the area of action
of the suspect.
- Everything would be easier if Ángel was here.
- He's the only one who knows
the exact location of the hideout.
"The inspector was on the edge of the abyss,
doing a balancing act to avoid going to the hole
definitely, thinking about
how ridiculous and absurd
was to switch from inspector
to suspect in a couple of minutes.
And she decided to do what his mother
had told her so many times:
to run after the bad guys.
Raquel had smelled a trace.
And in the absence of a sub-inspector
with whom conduct the investigation,
she opted for another kind of help."
Look at Paula's markers, with the bitten caps,
like you did.
- Thanks, Mom. Give it to me.
Let's see, the day of our first date
I arrived 25 minutes early.
I called him, he told me
he was leaving at that moment.
See you now.
We meet here, at the Hanoi.
He came on foot and it didn't take him
more than five or seven minutes.
Too bad, for one that didn't turn out crooked.
And what good is it to know
how long it took him to get here?
- To find how many meters
he was from the cafeteria.
In that time he could only travel, at most,
500 meters.
More or less...
The place where he's hiding
is inside this area,
he had to pass through one of these streets
to get to the cafeteria. And I'm sure
that some security camera
recorded it. I have to delimit,
Give me another one.
I'm going to seize
the surveillance footage from that area
to try to reconstruct his route.
Are you sure what you're doing?
Mom, I'm gonna find that man no matter what.
Be careful, daughter.
We've got a very badly wounded,
with three bullet impacts in his abdomen
and he' s been like that for hours.
Where is he?
- It will take me a while to get him out,
I don't know exactly how long.
And listen to me,
I've got the police tracking me down.
Is it safe for them?
They already know and agree with their part.
Yours would be ten million.
I need a box of abdominal laparotomy,
volumetric respirator and surgical equipment.
Can you get it?
- I'll take care of it.
Good morning, sir. Inspector Murillo.
I need the recordings
from the security camera out there,
those of October 23rd.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Good-bye.
- Good-bye.
Thank you.
Have you figured anything out yet?
I'm starting to draw the route
he came to the cafeteria by.
Look, that segments the area in this triangle.
If he came to Hanoi through here,
means his lair is very close, in this area.
I gotta get back out there, Mom.
The bulk of the calls
have been made in this area,
so he had to move through these streets.
I want you to seize the security camera tapes
in this área. Get a warrant from the judge.
I told the kid.
What's that?
What I did to you.
That I abandoned you
in that Martorell roundabout.
I went back to that roundabout.
because I dreamt you were cleaning windshields
at that stoplight.
I took the car and drove.
Hours and hours.
Because I wanted to fix my mistake.
Don't talk, rest.
I showed your picture to everyone passing by.
And now your son
he told me he hates me.
Your son adores you.
It doesn't matter what he says,
I know he doesn't hate you.
I deserve it.
I took his mother away from him.
- No.
No, you did very well.
You have a wonderful son.
Strong, noble...
And if so, it's because of you.
I did what I could, honey.
He comes out a little reckless.
I've never been happier
like the day I met you.
If I have to go somewhere now,
I'd like you to go there, to the village party.
And dance with you, together.
With the moon, under the coloured lights.
I love you.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Very much.
Father, I come bleeding
from the ports of Cabra.
If I could, young boy,
I'd help you fix that trade.
Green, how I want you green,
green wind, green branches.
300 dark brown roses
Your white shirt has grown.
Your blood oozes and flees
around the corners of your sash.
The two friends climbed up.
up to the high balconies
leaving a trail of blood.
Leaving a trail of teardrops.
But who will come? And from where?
Where's that bitter little girl?
How many times she waited for you!
How many times would she wait for you,
Green, how I want you green,
Big hoarfrost stars
come with the fish of shadow
that opens the road of dawn.
Green, how I want you green,
green wind, green branches.
They come with the shadow fish
that opens the way to dawn.
come with the fish of shadow
that opens the road of dawn.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
- Listen.
Can you hear it?
- That's them.
- It's them.
- How much further do you think it is?
- 30 or 40 cm.
I'm telling you.
- Come on, throw it.
Profesor!
They're here, they're here.
Hey! They're here.
It's them, for fuck's sake!
- Come on, the last one, the last one!
Profesor!
Daughter, the ink will go through the wall.
Mom, where are your car keys?
Daughter, that car hasn't been started in a long time.
Well, it's about time we took it for a spin.
Profesor, eh!
- Hey, excuse me.
Denver, Denver.
- What is it, Mónica?
Tell my father to hold on, we're almost there,
we're almost there.
- Up you go.
What? Mónica, I'm not going up there now.
- Listen to me, Denver, Denver.
What?
- Go upstairs.
You have to go up now.
I'm not going up there now.
Denver, stop, stop.
- I'm not going up there now!
No.
It's very close, Mónica.
- Listen, you have to go up now.
Do you hear me? Look at me,
if you don't come up now, you'll regret it
the rest of your life. Get in.
Get in, come on.
Hey! Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go!
I'm here, Dad.
You just have to hold on a little longer,
because we're gonna make it.
Isn't that right, Río?
We were digging like crazy.
You can hear the Serbs next door.
- You take it easy.
- Oh, Dad.
What...
That thing I told you I hated you...
I don't get that from you.
I don't get to hate you, okay?
You did what you had to do with Mom.
And me, hating you, it doesn't work for me.
- Mónica.
- What?
I'll give you 300 million if you keep it.
This guy's a dead loss.
I brought him to you here.
Now I'm going on vacation.
- Of course I will.
Take care of her.
Gentlemen.
I haven't introduced myself.
Agustín Ramos.
It's been a pleasure.
I love you.
- I love you too, Dad. Very much so.
And I'm not gonna let you go.
Río, bring all the fucking explosives
that we have left,
I'm going to blow that tunnel anyway.
- No.
If you blow up the tunnel, you bury them all.
- Oh, Dad.
- We've got to move on.
And remember, no mirrors.
All right.
But I don't know if I could.
- I love you.
I love you, too.
For the lack of your lips
I cried for the first time.
And I cursed to know you
for not stopping loving you.
I wanted to make you my wife,
Without love I wasn't going to stay.
I was pulling a gun
and fate brought death.
Mary, my life, my love,
I promised I'd come back,
But I won't come back,
I got caught by the police.
Mary, my life, my love,
I won't stop loving you,
I shot you down,
You'll never see me again
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
Forgive us our trespasses, just as we forgive.
those who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation
and deliver us from evil.
Amen.
The only instruction is there's no order
for any of those motherfuckers to get out alive.
Get everyone to transport the money,
we've got to get out now.
Going in is going to a slaughter and you know it.
If they go into the tunnel, we're all dead.
Unit, ready?
- Yes, sir!
The prosecution has issued an arrest warrant
against Inspector Murillo, from now on
she is in search and arrest.
You were in the hideout of that guy, the Profesor.
Tell us the address.
I need to know your name.
I hate you! I hate you!
Son of a bitch, you son of a bitch, you fucking bastard.
Take cover!
They're in the basement.
We got them in a mousetrap they can't get out of.
Let's go now. Now!
Now!
Aah!
Hands up, where I can see them!
Come on, come on!
Tokio!