We're locked up and we're really
we don't know how long this can last.
As long as you don't try to fool me,
everything will be fine.
We said no victims.
He had a phone,
Did you want me to spank him?
What the hell is going on here?
He's had a hostage executed.
Who was it?
Your son.
It's here, isn't it?
Your love story
has ruined your plan.
They've got you, and Río too.
The police know who you are.
You're on all the news.
Air intake.
You didn't kill that girl, did you?
I was ordered to do it and I had to do it.
You fucking killed Mónica!
- I have a visual of the targets.
- Behind you!
It's the first thing
that gets out of your plan.
They had it all figured out.
minus this shot,
and we must take advantage of it.
I have the ambulance.
No one is going to get out of here.
Let a medical team come in.
Two surgeons
and a nurse.
I frisked him, almost stopped him,
and you still care about me?
If you need any help...
Thank you. Thank you.
- Raquel, I want to go undercover.
with the medical team.
- Someone will come in, but you won't.
- Of course, there's always someone
better than me for everything.
- I've made the decision to enter.
They'll come in through the chest.
with red overalls and Dalí masks,
and infiltrate.
The sub-inspector will accompany the
surgeons and enter as a nurse.
A health worker is a policeman.
You know what to do.
They emit in short wave and encrypted.
They're coming in, I don't know where.
Active plan B.
Don't stop. Now.
Run now. Run now! Come on!
Abort! They have changed
the masks. They are not disguised as Dalí
They go straight to the slaughterhouse.
- Eh?
Attention, abort entry.
Suárez, do you copy?
- Objective reached
We proceed to remove lid
and we are inside.
Suárez, do you copy?
The masks have changed.
There is interference.
Command post, I can not hear you.
They do not wear Dalí masks.
It's a fucking suicide.
Abort entry...
That's an order!
they have changed the masks.
They do not wear Dalí masks.
Atenttion, do you copy?
Abort entry!
Abort.
- Yes!
Berlín, all calm.
Plan B has worked
as planned. They go.
What the fuck were the masks?
- I don't know.
They had their mouths open
like that, as anguished.
Como, no sé,
"The Scream" by Munch. That.
¡Munch, the expressionist painter!
Dalí, Munch...
What will be next?
I'm very glad you ask me
that question.
If you had to change it,
which painter would you choose?
Eh... I don't know, ¿Picasso, maybe?
Goya.
Velázquez.
Velázquez... Hm, hm...
Da Vinci.
Yes, with the beard.
I like it, with the beard.
Andy Warhol.
- ¿ The one with the soup?
¿Andy Warhol? Ángel.
- Yes, Andy Warhol,
that of Marilyn's painting.
He es a painter...
well-known, iconic.
The hair and the glasses.
Ángel, you are a box of surprises.
A bof of surprises with
a mic in the glasses.
without us ever anticipating.
But that is not the question, inspector,
and you know it.
That is not the important thing...
How the fuck they knew
that we were in there?
How much time have they spent studying
every movement what we are going
to do in each moment.
If I tell you the truth
half of my life.
How long are they going to stay inside?
Nothing, only nine more days.
10, 11 as much.
We're playing a fucking chess game
and we are loosing it.
But I have a Trojan horse.
It's very difficult for you to win this.
The moment has come to reflect...
and look back,
return to the origin.
We know that all this started
a long time ago,
and that those who were
inside were there before.
We have images of Cortés
and Oliveira entering the museum.
But did they come alone?
Was it the first visit they made
or the last?
How many more visits were there?
Did they talk to someone?
A gesture, a look...
and, above all, did they leave
some fucking thread to throw?
I want you to check again
the recordings of the cameras,
that you study them second by second.
The rest
let's try to rest.
Some of you
more than 30 hours without sleep.
Suárez, whatever you call me.
You are in command.
Brawl in Marcelo Usera,
Any patrol nearby?
- Please,
Leave channel eight free
for the hostage crisis!
Nobody issue
for channel eight, thank you!
- Do you want to take something
before going home?
- Between eating and sleeping,
I would choose the first, but...
I'm tired Ángel.
Sorry, thank you.
"Have you never thought that if you
could go back
maybe you would not make the same decisions?
Look at me:
If the day the Profesor
found me I wouldn't have gone with him,
now possibly I would be
telling you this from jail,
and not from where I do it."
How 2.400 million euros sound to you?
I guess at this moment
I only have two options.
I just see one.
I can surrender,
do therapy in jail,
play basketball,
go to mass...
and coming out at 50 knowing how to cook.
That...
or could make the snowball
larger and continue to slope down.
And...
What do you choose?
I choose snow ball.
"And it's that we all do
our own snowballs
with our bad decisions,
balls that are becoming giants,
like the Indiana Jones rock,
and he's chasing you down the slope
to crush you.
Berlín didn't care either.
shit his snowball,
no matter how big.
It was clear to me that whatever happened.
happened, he wasn't going to jail.
What about Allison Parker?
That dead mosquito, too.
had made a bad decision:
not going to the ballet audition
from Martha Graham's school.
for hiking with Pablito,
a fucking asshole.
All decisions
that we took in the past
take us inexorably
into the future.
That's what Río was going to realize...
as soon as I lit up
the only television
that we had left at the factory,
in case we ever lost.
communication with the Profesor."
Come on, kid!
Put him to see what they say about us.
This, not even the train robbery!
"An undetermined number
of assailants agreed to...
- The one we messed up!
"Is it a blow to the system?
The largest..."
- My goodness!
This, not the Americans!
This, Spain's brand
but with M16! Take it now!
Fuck, my parents!
"- A teenager... so rare...
- Shy...
- Shy.
Our son was always
locked in the room,
but we thought
he was playing with the computer or...
But you don't think
he is a criminal.
And then... you see it on TV
with a rifle, firing,
with 60 people locked up.
And you see it's like those jihadists.
- Paco...
- It's just that he's not your son anymore.
- Please don't say that.
- For me...
it's like he's dead.
- But, Paco...
We just heard
the testimony of the parents..."
The profesor said
nothing of external news.
"But he had also said that he wanted
a white heist, no blood,
without violence,
that only with intelligence...
we could perpetrate
the robbery of the century.
Sometimes intelligence
is not enough
to stop the snowball
that's coming for you.
And then you have to run...
and run...
and run.
But I got ahead of myself,
I'm telling you something
that hadn't happened yet."
Ángel, tell me.
- Hello, Raquel.
Were you asleep?
- No, no, no, what is it?
- No, no, no, no, no.
It's all right, don't worry.
Look, I'm walking around
to a topic. Do you have a minute?
Leave her alone, man,
she'll be devastated.
Yeah, sure, yeah.
- Forgive me for being so direct:
What's with Andy Warhol?
- Excuse me?
- The thing about the surprise box.
What's the matter, that I can't like
museums or modern painters?
I can't like something
other than Atleti?
- Yes, of course.
It has caught me from... surprise,
because I didn't know.
The same thing I didn't know
that you are a fan of Atleti.
- But it does hit me, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Well, yes.
Hey, Ángel, I'm really tired.
Shall we talk tomorrow?
- The guy I saw you with,
that you were holding hands.
Would you sleep with him?
Tell me, I want to know.
- Ángel, what's this all about now?
- Would you go to bed with him?
yes or no?
Answer me.
Yes, yes, why not?
I'm a 40-year-old free woman,
and the truth is, I could use it,
a good wiggle,
to... have something different
to think about.
So I'm sure you do.
So what?
I understand. You want to give an opportunity
to a random guy. I get it.
- Ángel...
What happened between you and me
in Cercedilla was an adventure.
It's been eight years and look,
I cut to the chase
because we're partners.
- And friends, Raquel.
- And friends.
And you're married, Ángel.
- I'm married.
Because you said that between
was not going to work.
Then you got married,
and on top of it with a partner.
And because you never look at me like...
to a winner, you always look at me
like the loser who...
can't like Andy Warhol.
But if for a moment
you look at me like a man,
I swear it didn't take long.
nor ten minutes to leave Carmen...
Forgive me. Raquel, I'm sorry.
Hell, I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
It's this... job,
that's driving us crazy.
- Yes, yes, that's true, but to everyone.
Ángel, it's late. Go to bed, huh?
We'll talk tomorrow.
- Good night, Raquel.
- Good night.
Who were you talking to?
- I can't believe it.
that you were spying on me.
- I couldn't help overhearing you.
- To bed, which is late.
- A good time.
I've already slept.
Look, let's see,
And you now, what's up?
- What?
- Two suitors.
- He's not a suitor,
it's Ángel, my partner.
- Oh, well, I thought
that you were making him jealous
with the stranger at the bar,
with the one with the reeds.
Please, Mom,
I wasn't making him jealous!
- You... don't close doors.
And now that you're not married,
you can go pecking.
- Ah, pecking.
- Yes, pecking.
- Of course.
- Daughter, in the end love is...
what makes us see other colour of life.
And you lately
you see everything very black.
Maybe it's still
you haven't gotten over... all that.
- Let's see, Mom, let's see,
What haven't I overcome, huh?
Do you also think I've put
a false allegation...
and that I live bitter because my ex
He's hooked up with my sister
and I want to fuck them up?
Does your husband
made out with your sister?
- Mom, what do you say?
What?
- Nothing. Yes...
I just wanted to calm things down.
In the end that man
has made out with the two sisters
as in the movies...
erotic films.
Mom. Mom, are you okay? Mom, are you okay?
- Eh...
How are you doing with
the robbery, daughter?
- Eh... Bad, bad. Bad.
Well, sitting there all day,
in a blocking situation, and...
Yes.
- But are you sitting, my daughter?
What you have to do
is run.
Bad guys get caught running.
As if you didn't know.
Good night, sweetheart.
Ah.
What a pleasant visit!
You should come here more.
I see you've put yourself
a very cuckoo dispatch.
You already have two.
I like offices.
Always...
I've wanted to have one.
with the mahogany desk,
but the crime and the dispatches
do not marry.
It's hot, isn't it?
You put on your vest.
bulletproof to come see me.
I would have preferred a corset,
Venetian.
See?
If I'm not done
to get the point.
What are you here for, Tokio?
To ask you...
please...
that you call the profesor...
and tell him what you've done,
that you've had executed
to a hostage.
Bad boy.
Because you know what happens?
That the profesor
is my guardian Ángel,
and if you don't tell him,
I'm gonna have to do it myself.
You?
Uh-huh.
Ah. And you'll look like an accuser.
A snitch, a filthy rat.
I am a gentleman,
is something I couldn't allow.
Yes.
I have breached the first rule.
I killed a hostage.
Well, not me, but Denver,
but that's the least of it.
Let's just say he's done it in compliance
strictly my orders.
I preferred to tell you myself.
personally.
It was the only red line.
You fucked it all up.
I understand your shock.
That woman had a phone
between the legs.
Maybe he wanted to use it
to call his cousin Chelito...
and tell that she was fucking
the director,
but I actually think
she wanted to call the police.
There won't be any more phones.
You can be sure of that.
Who was she?
Mónica Gaztambide.
Are you going to punish me?
You should.
I know you're an idealist,
you think they're gonna give us
the tickets by asking for them please,
that you want to be a good guy
while you give us weapons and explosives
to blow up this building,
but that's enough of games.
You're gonna have to punish me,
because if you don't have the guts,
this isn't gonna work out.
I've told you many times.
for years...
it's not me who has a problem,
it's you.
You're gonna have to punish me
because then I'll know you're a captain,
that can hold the rudder steady,
that you're someone
who can be trusted.
Looks like you don't want to talk about it
now.
At the moment no one knows outside
about this death,
so the plan goes ahead.
They'll ask for proof of life
in less than 48 hours.
Yes.
- Inspector, this is Suárez.
We found something
in the security footage.
It's important.
- I'm coming.
Here.
- Thank you, Ángel.
We've checked the hard drives
from the cameras of...
- Listen, listen, Raquel,
I wanted to apologize.
for last night.
I hadn't slept in 48 hours,
I'd had a few too many wines.
I don't want you to think...
- Ángel, don't worry.
It's okay, okay?
Look, Suárez has found
a breakthrough for the case.
It's the recording of the day
that Aníbal Cortés and Oliveira
visited the museum.
Look at the elements that deposit
in the inbox.
Get as close as you can.
There, stop it. Enlarge.
It's a car key.
From a Seat, old,
with original key ring.
- Presumably
between 89 and 96.
- We have the day and the hour
they entered,
and the model of car
when they did it.
Let's comb the area.
Security cameras,
car parks, shops, banks,
regulated parking tickets,
everything.
- Discard.
The other file, upload.
You have to find that
car anyway.
- Go on through. Good.
We got him.
- It's a '92 Ibiza.
- That's perfect.
Those keys and that car
they're going to take us where it all started.
Shut up.
Here are the car keys.
Nairobi and Río, change your clothes.
to go to the museum.
Me? Really?
You.
To the city?
Ah! No, but don't send me with the
child, send me with a big guy,
with Helsinki. Why don't you send me
with Helsinki?
- Helsinki likes
more hair on his chest.
- Huh?
Weren't you and I going?
Check the security cameras against
the sketch of my previous visit.
We need to confirm the location,
angles and targets.
Come on, change your clothes.
Helsinki, trout.
Oh, my God!
But you like men.
War, prison...
- Oh, yeah, yeah. Not the women.
- Mmm...
No, you don't.
Wasn't I going with Río?
No, I changed my mind.
Yeah? What happened?
I've changed my mind and that's it.
What has happened?
Don't you trust me or what?
Did I do something?
What the hell did I do?
So...
Yes, he, he.
I didn't do anything, did I?
It's not that.
No, no, no, no.
Did something happend?
My mother?
Cardiac arrest, I'm sorry.
When?
Yesterday.
I've decided
that you don't go out to the museum
to avoid the temptation
to say goodbye.
I'll stay with her.
Let another go.
I don't need to say goodbye.
I already did.
The last time I talked to her.
I wanted to turn myself in to the police,
so that woman
was no longer my mother.
Profesor.
You tell me what to do with Berlín.
Did I throw him to the dogs
or do I shoot him?
You're the boss.
We'll talk later. Put me through to Helsinki.
won't it be the police?
Come on, here.
Helsinki.
Yes?
The picture you brought me
of the scrap bucket
is from the Ibiza, isn't it?
I'm saying this because I'm looking at it
in detail and...
I get the impression
that the colour of the paint
is not exactly the same.
I leave car in scrapyard.
Helsinki, the photo
you brought me is from the Ibiza?
No.
Another car, but they said:
"It will look like this.
I gave you 1000 euros,
1000 euros for you to pay them...
and scrap your car
in front of you.
What did you do, did you keep
with 1000 dirty euros
when we're going to strike a blow
of 2 billion?
Two billion,
money flying...
and 1000 euros,
money in hand.
Me locked up without working
five months in Toledo...
and family...
I send all money to my family.
If for you 1000 euros...
not important,
very important to me.
Important, Helsinki.
That car is a loose end...
and from there they can get another one,
and another, and another.
We in here
leave a lot of loose ends,
you out there just one.
It's all right.
Tell me, at least, if not
scrap the car in front of you,
if you cleared the fingerprints.
Yes. Yes.
Helsinki, what are footprints?
Fingerprints? Yes, Profesor, yes. fingerprints.
What does "fingerprints" mean?
Mmm.... No... I don't know.
Did you clean the steering wheel with ammonia,
the gearshift lever,
the windows,
the whole damn car?
Yes.
No. I didn't do this.
Get me the kidnapper.
- Sleeping is good for you.
This morning he took a run.
- To thieves
they are caught running,
and we're too passive.
Where's my pencil?
Let's squeeze the pins.
Good morning, Profesor.
How is Mr. Román
after the operation?
All right.
Resting and the best of all,
without fever.
I thought I'd forgotten.
On the contrary,
in point of fact
I keep thinking of you.
Wow, that sounds like fantasy.
We should keep investigating
that way.
If you're going to ask me
what I had for breakfast,
if I've had a morning orgasm
or if I like preliminaries,
I'll tell you that's not what this is about,
but yes, it is a fantasy,
a fantasy about handcuffs.
I put them on...
and put him in the van.
Well, it's a fantasy,
after all.
Sure, and then if you want to
tell me yours in a vis a vis.
Listen to me carefully:
I'm going to give you some bad news.
First of all, the ship
you asked for, the Malaika,
is docked awaiting trial,
whereby
is still their owner's.
That's no excuse, Inspector.
The police can ask the judge
the authorization to use that ship
in repression or persecution
of crimes, as long as
the judgment has not been delivered,
so you can ask permission
to use it,
especially in a matter
on such a large scale.
Don't tell me you haven't.
I see you also know about laws.
Well, just amateur.
I like
read court judgments.
You'd be surprised how passionate
that they can become.
All right, I'll keep that in mind.
now that I'm going to have time.
I'm going to be relieved of the case.
We're on a dead end.
Too many hours have passed...
and, as you will understand,
my superiors have a limit.
If you really want to negotiate with me,
release eight hostages.
Eight hostages,
and I want them to be minors.
Why should I?
Because now it's your turn
to have a gesture with me.
If you want credit,
release those hostages.
If not,
they'll put another inspector in charge,
someone with other ideas
and other objectives.
I give you an hour to think about it,
not one more minute.
That guy doesn't want the Malaika.
for nothing.
- Why do you say that?
Why ask for one
that it will take five days to get
could have any one of them?
- To see who has it longer?
Look, inspector, I don't know.
give them that boat and get them out of there.
- They're thinking of going out
somewhere else.
Ángel.
- Tell me.
- Call those in the Underground,
to comb the sewers
within a radius of 500 meters.
Ancient tunnels, drainage...
Any hollow.
- Okay.
- Let's get to work!
Ah! Ah!
Ah...
Hey! You!
Hey!
I finally found you!
I was trying to...
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Put me down!
Please put me down! Please!
No! No! Please!
Put me down! Please!
I'm in the trunk!
Oh!
Save.
Salva?
Yes, tell me.
Salva, I am Raquel.
Nothing, I'm here at the Hanoi...
ingesting sth.
y... well, that... as I don't see you here
and it's almost a custom
to find us here, then...
I thought that maybe...
he wanted to take a cup of coffee
or make a "break"...
Well, then...
I would love to, but is that...
just got me out of Madrid...
Salva, are you all right?
No, forgive me, it is that...
how I'm distracted,
a truck almost rolled me up!
Well, forgive me,
I won't keep you any longer.
Nothing, I'll see you around.
And if you come back soon and feel like
eat something today...
Forgive me, Salva, who...
The thing is, yesterday
I told my mother about you and...
Like the woman is a hippie
crazy of life, then...
nothing, that goes and told me,
in point-blank,
that maybe I should put
a little colour to my life
and get to know each other better, peck each other...
Don't get me wrong, huh?
Peck... She was referring to...
to have a social life,
That's why I told him about eating today.
Okay.
What...? Oh, is that so?
Oh, that's great!
Dinner, better?
Perfect!
Of course I do.
Well, that's fine.
Well, I'll see you.
Bye, bye!
Bye, see you later!
Please!
You don't smoke?
Good, good.
It won't be me.
who damages your health.
You're all right here, aren't you?
All together.
Without perceiving the horror,
the shots,
blood, interventions...
I have to come more often.
It's all complicated out there.
Tonight...
I called a friend.
I've told him how difficult it is
maintain order and harmony
in here,
and I have... said
I've had to kill,
that I have ordered killed...
a woman.
If you don't put corpses on top of the
table, you're not respected out there.
And you see, I...
I have been able to feel...
the emotion of my friend,
his awe,
your breathing...
agitating...
and your pain.
He...
He wasn't here,
nor did I know that woman,
Mónica Gaztambide,
and for a moment...
For a moment I thought
that it would be very nice to feel...
how my friend feels.
To feel that...
kind of emotion, that pain,
that guilt, but not...
It doesn't move me.
Horrible, isn't it?
I'm bothering you with my
nonsense, you have to forgive me.
Silvia.
You're having a seizure.
of anxiety, right?
- She's just a little nervous,
but it'll pass right away.
Of course.
Of course she'll get over it.
Come with me.
Silvia, give me your hand.
That's it.
No... No...
"Spasiba".
I got in because my car is here
and I forgot something very important
in the trunk, very important.
"Ochen' vazhno".
You jump fence.
Now, tell police.
I count five and let go of dog.
Do you understand?
What are you doing?
I'm mounting the cells
for placing explosives
in the entry lanes.
Did Berlín ask it for you?
The Profesor, as a deterrent,
to be seen in the tent.
What's that?
This one, which I had here
a sherry and I'm giving it a way out.
Fuck!
Boss,
the post of Director-General
suits you... very well.
Sit down, please, Miss Tokio.
I saw that you were late.
I'm going to have to account for that.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Director.
Ah... Yes...
If I show you a breast,
You won't fire me?
A tempting offer, no doubt,
but you have to offer me
something else.
Ah...
I know how you feel.
Río...
I am here,
stuck in this hole,
and I'm starting to think
on how I got here...
and I don't remember.
I remember one day...
they asked me to check.
a security system
and it turned out to be a mansion.
in Geneva,
where not even the carpets remained.
I wasn't even there...
But, fuck it,
hack security systems
is so much more fun than being
the computer scientist of a company.
So I didn't even think about it.
For me it was a game...
and now I don't have any parents.
I don't have a mother either.
But it's a little different, isn't it?
My parents are still alive.
I could have been a legal uncle.
He was good at what he did,
could make money.
I could have had
a normal life,
to meet a normal girl,
have normal friends...
I wasn't like you.
I just don't know what to tell you.
I think I need your door.
Which door?
The door you told me about the day
that we came to visit the museum,
the day we found out
that your mother died.
Cameras 12 and 13
have changed targets.
Now you have
a wider viewing angle.
Camera 14 is still the same.
He's focusing for the lobby.
We can go now.
And what are we going to leave for?
For a day we can do
a little tourism...
Kissing in bars,
in the street...
In the street?
Don't fuck around.
Let's see if someone will catch you.
No, not on the street.
Follow me.
I feel like I killed her...
So pretty that it was...
I've killed her with grief,
of absence, of displeasure,
of my fucking life, fuck...
She just wanted to protect me.
He loved me.
Ugh...
He loved me madly.
And if I wanted to turn myself
in to the police, was...
so I don't look dead
in the news.
When I was little,
I knew that by his side
nothing would happen to me.
The bad thing was when he wasn't there.
And your father?
Father, there is none.
My mother
worked in a suitcase factory.
And when we didn't get there.
at the end of the month,
he took a night shift.
And since I didn't have
with whom to leave me,
for I was left alone.
I was scared...
How old were you?
Eight, nine.
A little younger than you now.
The case...
is that my mother invented a trick.
He painted a door...
on the wall of my room...
It was a magic door,
and if I was afraid,
I could open it
and she'd be on the other side.
And when he left, did you open it?
He told me
I could only open it once.
Only once,
in life,
when he needed it,
but once.
So when I was afraid...
I always thought:
"You can still hold on
a little bit more."
"A little more."
I thought the next day
I could be more afraid...
and feel more alone,
and need the door.
I would have opened it the first day.
I never opened it.
You're the person
stronger than I know,
the most incredible...
y...
So what?
Y...
Holy shit!
You, the parking lot.
A fine?
- Yes, of regulated parking,
of a '92 Ibiza.
Two streets from here.
Look at the date and time.
It coincides with the day when the
robbers visited the museum.
Good work, Ángel.
Put the license plate in.
in the database.
It'll be the most expensive fine
of history.
It'll cost you
a lot of millions of euros.
Get me the robber.
Inspector.
Profesor,
I need an answer. I want
those eight hostages, the minors.
Write down the names
of those who are going to come out.
Pablo Holgado,
Silvia Moreno,
Abraham Salmerón,
Ignasi Castell,
Magdalena Ribot,
Rocío Huertas,
Jessica Sánchez
and Alicia Villanueva.
What about Allison Parker?
She's one of the Brighton girls.
I want you to put her on the list.
Well, I see you've noticed,
inspector.
You know as well as I do that Allison
is a queen of hearts
in this house of cards.
I can't.
It is an indispensable condition.
I'll propose something to you:
Allison.
in exchange for the lives of those eight.
I beg your pardon?
I will give you Allison Parker...
and no one else.
We both know
how important it is to both of us,
so if you want me to go out,
will go out alone.
I have to consult him.
You have one minute.
Call him and say yes,
that Parker comes out.
- I don't intend to make that decision.
It is immoral to choose one's life,
being able to save the eight.
As much as you and your ethics
think otherwise,
this is a matter of state...
and the first thing is going to be
to remove the ambassador's daughter.
I'll take responsibility.
Get me the robber again.
Well?
Allison Parker.
Are you sure?
Would you rather save Allison's life
Parker to the eight-student?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Wow.
Now I have to think about it,
I didn't expect this answer from you.
Give me an hour to think about it.
All right.
I look forward to your call.
If I don't call her,
you will also know
what decision I've made.
What did he mean by that?
- I don't know, but look:
Ibiza has been out of business for 10 years.
No insurance, no owners.
He's out of circulation.
Attention everyone.
Come, please. Come closer.
What would you do if you had to do
disappear a car?
- Burn it.
- Good.
Look for crowds of burned cars,
and Guardia Civil. More.
- Sink it.
- See if there's news of a car.
appeared in swamps, Ríos...
What else?
- Dismantle it, sell it by the piece.
- Bury him.
- I beg your pardon?
- A ditch is made
and the car is buried.
Eh... I saw it in a movie
and it worked.
Anything else?
What's the legal way
to make a car disappear
and erase all his fingerprints?
Make a junk bucket out of it.
in a junkyard.
Priority: search in scrapyards,
car cemeteries, and so on.
- Raquel, it's Sunday,
will be closed.
- I don't care. You take out the owner
of your home if necessary.
Quickly!
Don't worry.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
Here you will be more protected,
more isolated,
without knowing about things.
that afflict your soul.
- I feel better now.
Can I go with the others?
- Can't you hear me?
You'd better stay here.
I'm gonna have to tie you up,
because you'll be alone,
but you'll be better.
Let's see, don't let him hurt you.
That's it.
Let's sit down.
You don't want to stand here?
Look how you've gotten...
Where have you been?
Let me go with the others, please.
- Take it easy!
Don't you get it?
The ones who are afraid now...
...it's them.
Girls, he's coming back.
He's coming back.
I'm sure they'll bring her in now.
It's a girl, they won't do anything to her.
And now, rest.
What are we going to do with so much pasta?
I've got it all figured out:
I'm gonna get a Maserati.
colour blue clear sky.
It's this red car.
- How long has it been here?
I don't know.
I don't know well,
Boss is on holiday and...
- Oh, yeah?
Well, your boss said that you control
the entrance of all vehicles.
How long?
About 20 days.
Who brought it?
- Foreigner.
Eastern, not Russian.
Go get the gloves.
and call the scientist.
Tell them we have the car.
I understand that whoever left you the car
showed him his documentation.
I'd give you an invoice for the purchase.
Ah!
Ticket.
- "Da, da". It can.
What do you mean, "can"?
- Ángel,
go to the office and look to see
If you find something, go.
- Yes. Pull.
Ah... Ah...
Ah...! Ah!!
"...no statement
with regarding this filtration,
a conversation where the inspector
Raquel Murillo
negotiate with one of the
kidnappers, supposedly..."
Inspector.
Hey!
Let's see who that is.
and what it's doing here.
"The inspector had taken the
left to a checkmate almost certainly.
But even at that moment
of despair,
the profesor had kept to himself
an extra ball
that was starting to sound
on all radios."
"The Opposition Spokesman
has described as regrettable
that come first
diplomatic relations
to life
of eight Spanish teenagers.
We remind you
the content of the recording."
Yes.
Tokio, listen to me.
"He had ordered me to filter
the conversation with the inspector.
A conversation that left
in a very bad place to the Spanish Government
and herself."
"Well?
Allison Parker.
Are you sure?
Do you prefer Allison Parker's life
instead of eight students?
Yes, I'm sure."
"Perhaps because Berlín
I had called him soft.
and had decided to give
a blow on the table
and punish
as many as went against him."
"The decision to liberate
to Allison Parker,
daughter of the ambassador,
in front of eight young Spaniards,
it's been a decision
controversial..."
"Or simply that filtration
he'd introduce us again.
like heroes
in the eyes of the public,
but Raquel was a bloodhound..."
"...the daughter
of the British ambassador..."
"...and had caught a trail,
and I wasn't going to let it go,
because that trail
was the brain of the operation."
Stop!
"The Profesor himself."
- Nothing.
What are you doing here?
I wasn't stealing.
I...
What the fuck does it smell like in here?
- Ammonia.
He wasn't stealing.
"The profesor had become
in a human plunder to flee,
but a plus was missing
interpreting
to get out of checkmate,
and then he did."
Get out.
It was him.
It was him!
There is a mole among us.
They've managed to isolate a footprint
on the Ibiza button.
Capricious, superficial,
selfish. You only know how to do harm.
Man take care man.
You may be
the best of the Nazis,
but you're still one of them.
Chief!
What the fuck did he say to you?
Ah!
Ah! No!