That's $80.
Unless you want to go double or nothing.
- You hustling me, grandpa?
- You tell me.
Did you know, Father?
Matthew? What are you doing here?
Did you know she was my mother?
Yeah.
You knew.
I couldn't tell you.
Even when I wanted to.
Don't hide behind your collar, Father.
- Wait. You're a priest?
- Take your money and go.
I'm not hiding, Matthew.
- I'm right here.
- You...
of all people...
All those times
I looked to you for guidance.
You saw me struggling...
and you chose to hide the one thing
that could have changed everything for me.
Please, Father, help me understand
why you would do that.
I prayed for Maggie to find it in herself
to tell you years ago.
She couldn't find it in herself
to walk nine blocks to visit me as a kid.
Or to comfort me when my father
was murdered and I thought that...
I knew that I was alone in this world.
- You were never alone...
- Yes, I was!
And you let me believe it.
Yes. Yes, we did.
Why?
- What did Maggie say?
- I'm asking you.
Maggie's a good person, Matthew.
Flawed, like us all.
And tortured over decisions she's made.
But she dedicated her life
to making amends.
You still haven't answered the question.
Growing up without your parents, Matthew,
you don't grow to see them as people.
You need to understand that...
to understand her.
- We should go. This was a stupid idea.
- Definitely.
No, we're here.
Let's just give it a minute.
Three weeks from now,
we're not going anywhere anymore.
- True.
- Just a minute.
- Hey.
- Me?
Yeah, you. Can you give me a hand up here?
- No, I can't.
- Yeah, you got to.
Come on, it's only gonna take me
60 seconds to put this asshole down.
Three minutes, tops.
- Okay, now is a good time to leave.
- Yes, it is. Let's go.
What do you need me to do?
Nothing much.
Just gotta give me some water,
maybe wipe off my face, like that.
Come on.
Maggie, obedience, poverty...
Chastity.
You ever done this before?
You got brothers or something?
No. Never seen a fight before, either.
Shit.
Then why'd you pick me to come up here?
I just figured a nun
wouldn't put something in my bottle.
It's gonna be all right.
You just gotta put my mouth guard
in my teeth at the start of the rounds.
Maybe give me
some water between rounds, too.
I thought you said
you only needed 60 seconds.
Yeah. Well, it's just a backup plan.
You never know.
Water.
Yeah, come on. I only got a minute.
- Can you get that?
- Get that?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
Maggie, what is wrong with you?
Maggie?
Maggie.
Damn, I don't know
what I should've done.
I guess that's not really true.
You know, when I heard Maggie
call me her son,
my thought was... my first thought...
was how stupid I'd been.
That it had been right in front of me
for so long.
And then I remembered that it had been
in front of you for even longer.
From... From the beginning.
We've talked so much about truth...
you and I.
Of my truth, God's truth.
Now it seems like all those conversations
were just a goddamned lie.
Shame on you.
We couldn't do this at the office?
We had to come all the way out here?
Once I explain everything to you
and the SAC, you'll understand, sir.
Shit, I better.
- Sorry about this, boss.
- Come in, guys.
Mom?
- Where did you put them?
- Give me a sec?
Like you'd understand.
I understand, Allison. I just don't care.
Now, move it.
- Make sure your dad signs those papers.
- I know. I know. Bye, Mom.
At least she talks to you.
I can't pry my girls
away from their phones.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Sorry about the mess.
My contractor promised
he would be done months ago.
- How do you take it?
- Black is fine, thanks.
Uh, none for me.
Thanks.
Interview with Special Agent Rahul Nadeem
and Special Agent in Charge Tammy Hattley,
conducted
by Supervisory Special Agent Winn,
FBI Office of Professional Responsibility.
Okay, Ray. You've got our attention.
What's this about?
There's no good way for me to say this.
But I believe Wilson Fisk is currently
engaged in a criminal conspiracy
and has manipulated the bureau
into becoming his unwitting accomplice.
I also have reason to believe that Fisk
has corrupted an agent on his detail.
Who?
Dex.
You're referring
to Special Agent Ben Poindexter?
Yes, sir. And as crazy as it sounds,
I think Poindexter may have perpetrated
the attack at the Bulletin.
What the hell are you talking about?
Why would you think that?
Because while I was pursuing
those suspicions yesterday...
Dex shot me.
Jesus Christ.
Sir, OPR needs to start
an internal investigation into Fisk,
into Poindexter, into all of it.
And for the record...
this was on my watch.
I personally ran Fisk's detail.
SAC Hattley did everything by the book,
and this shouldn't fall on her.
I take full responsibility.
Ray, I'm sorry, but I'm placing you
on administrative leave,
effective immediately.
I understand.
And will cooperate fully.
So...
what do we do next?
First, we call you an ambulance.
No!
Ray! Put down the gun! Please!
Damn you, Ray.
You bring this into my house?
My home?
Sit down.
Sit.
Your prints, your weapon, the recording.
Do I need to explain to you
what this means?
Answer my question, please.
Do you understand your situation now?
Ray?
You get this?
Yeah, boss.
I understand.
I'm not your boss anymore.
Wilson Fisk is.
You don't have to run.
Hiding is an option.
I'm not so sure it is, Foggy.
Not after what I said to Fisk.
- Where will you go?
- I don't know.
But I wouldn't bother paying the rent
like we did for Matt.
Come on. You'll be back.
Foggy,
Fisk is never gonna stop hunting me.
Then don't run or hide. Do what I did.
Make yourself so public
he can't touch you.
Yeah, well, it's not gonna matter, Foggy.
My DA campaign's kept me out
of his crosshairs so far.
Yeah, well, you didn't confess
to killing his BFF, so...
Valid point.
- But maybe...
- Look, Foggy. I'm running.
Right after I tell Matt
I completely betrayed him.
Come on.
You didn't betray him.
Fisk knows that Matt is Daredevil
because of me.
He can't actually know that for sure.
You didn't say anything.
No, you weren't there. He, uh...
The way he looked at me...
He knows.
Just, uh, destroy these for me?
- No, Foggy...
- Please take it.
Thank you.
I should go.
We're gonna get through this.
I don't know how, but we will.
Watch your back. Please.
Change can be scary, Marcus.
Even when it's for the good.
No, it's not.
Oh...
You know,
the Dockerys are a wonderful family,
and now you get to be a part of it.
But you will always be
a part of our family, too.
Maggie.
What is it, Paul?
Matthew knows.
Oh...
I guess you know
everything now, Matty.
Everything I need to.
Meh. Doesn't change a goddamn thing.
- Ray?
- Yeah?
You have a visitor from work.
My hand's not big enough.
Sure it is. Look.
Just keep your fingers like that,
hugging the seam,
and just snap your wrist
when you release it.
And that makes it curve?
Like crazy.
There he is. Morning, Ray.
Dad, he's teaching me
how to throw a curveball.
You want eggs?
Uh, no, thanks.
- Go get ready for school, Sami.
- But, Dad...
School first, kid.
Okay.
This is cool. Thanks, Mr. Poindexter.
Call me Dex. Your dad and me go way back.
So, Dex, what brings you to my house?
Well, you've been bragging
about Seema's cooking for so long,
I figured I'd come up with an excuse
to finally come try it.
You don't need an excuse, Dex.
What you've done for our family...
...you're always welcome here.
Honey, we're gonna talk shop.
Oh. Okay. But only for a few minutes.
I don't want Dex's eggs getting cold.
What are you doing here, Dex?
Your issue is with me, not my family.
My issue is definitely with you.
That stunt with the lawyer, Ray?
That was cold.
You convinced me that you had my back.
But Fisk wants you alive.
What does he want from me, Dex?
Your friend.
The one you brought to my home.
I don't know who he is. Or where he is.
Yeah, you do.
But it can wait.
You're bleeding, Ray.
I'll cover with Seema
while you change your shirt.
Now, let's go.
We're spending the day together, partner.
It smells delicious.
Taste as good as it looks?
Shit.
I have a super for that.
I can fix this, damn it.
- You okay?
- Peachy.
Karen and Matt can do whatever they want.
I'm not gonna run.
You can't quit now.
You're giving people hope.
Mrs. Wobschall stopped me
in the produce aisle.
At first, I didn't believe her,
but then she showed me
a clip on her iPhone.
You were a natural. Totally amazing.
What are you talking about?
Because when you get
beyond the cold facts,
and you really get worked up
about what you're doing, you can...
Holy shit.
We've got to work
on your closing,
but this video has had nearly
100,000 views in its first 24 hours.
Half the cops in New York have reposted it
to their personal accounts.
Has Blake Tower responded?
Complete radio silence.
Probably because you've successfully
branded him as the pro-Fisk candidate
and anything he says
will only make it worse.
- Wow.
- Foggy, if you play this right...
I could actually win.
And as the new DA, you make it
your top priority to nail Wilson Fisk.
I don't have much time.
Fisk is doing something.
Specifics, Ray.
I don't know what.
But when I do, I'll call you.
Be ready.
It's done.
Nice work, partner.
It's a shitty way for you to find out,
Matty, about your mother.
Yeah. You should have told me.
Maybe I promised her
that I wouldn't.
That is no excuse.
Yeah, I know, kid.
But after I took that bullet,
Maggie had years to tell you the truth
and she didn't.
That wasn't my choice, it was hers.
You both lied. You both left.
I never left you.
You didn't go down in that fight
like you were supposed to.
Knowing they'd kill you for it.
I did that for you.
So you'd know
what your old man is made of.
My old man chose his ego over a lifetime
with his son. That's what I know.
It wasn't ego,
it was living up to a code.
Being a man.
It means lovin' the feel of my fist
in someone else's face.
It means waiting for them
to hit the ground
and knowing that I put them there.
And, yeah, okay...
maybe I put that at the top of my list
and maybe it cost me everything,
including you.
But you do the same thing.
No, I don't.
You have a code, too.
You beat the shit out of people.
You tell yourself it's okay
because you didn't kill anyone.
There is something wrong with us, Matty.
It's just who we are.
That's who you were, Dad.
I'm not like you.
I don't throw fights.
And I don't let everyone else suffer
'cause of some bullshit code.
Not anymore.
When I get to Fisk...
I'm gonna kill him.
- Sister Maggie... Sister Maggie?
- Devin.
Excuse me, Sister Maggie?
I'm sorry to bother you.
They told me I could find you here.
He's gone. I don't know where.
It's a matter of life and death.
Do you have any idea when he'll be back?
He won't be.
I...
I don't understand. Why? Why not?
He learned the truth.
That I'm his mother.
Wow. Uh...
He never talked about... about you.
I was a danger to Matthew
when I gave him up.
Nowadays, they know a great deal
about postpartum, but...
at the time...
I was convinced that I was betraying God.
I hadn't yet
taken my vows, but in my heart...
I believed I had committed
an unforgivable sin.
And so I replaced that sin with another.
I abandoned my child.
Why... Why did you tell him now?
I didn't. He found out on his own.
I wanted to tell him.
When Jack was alive, I convinced myself
the truth would confuse Matthew.
After Jack died, I convinced myself
it would do more harm than good.
Finally, I just realized
that I was too much of a coward.
The Lord has a way.
Sending the Devil of Hell's Kitchen
to me now.
Showing me what became of my sin.
The Lord gave me another chance
to make things right.
And I failed, yet again.
Matthew knows who and what I am now.
He won't be back.
I'm sorry.
It's unfair of me to burden you.
I just... I don't...
I don't know what to say.
What can you say to someone
who's scarred your friend for life?
He must be in a lot of pain right now.
When you find him, he'll need a friend.
That's just it.
See, I can't really stick around.
Um...
Fisk knows... about Matt. I just...
I just wanted to warn him before I run.
- Are you in danger?
- Yeah.
Matt's not the only one
that Fisk wants dead.
Do you have someplace to go?
No, I was just gonna get
the first bus out of town.
I can help you.
Uh, yeah, no, you don't want me anywhere
near you right now. Trust me.
The church has been helping people hide
for 2,000 years.
Hide here.
Give me a day to make a few calls,
and you'll have shelter halfway
around the world by the end of the week.
Please, let me do something for you.
For Matthew.
Yeah.
Everybody,
I have an announcement.
And some good news after a shitty week.
I'm happy to tell you that
Special Agent Poindexter
has been reinstated to duty.
Turns out even DC can't hold
good deeds against someone forever.
Seriously, people...
the way you came together
and helped Dex hire that lawyer...
I'm proud of you.
If we don't look out for each other,
who will?
You got anything to say, Dex?
Uh...
I guess I just wanna say thank you.
I wouldn't be here without your help.
Especially you, Ray.
Someday, I'll pay you back
for everything you did.
You look good, Franklin.
I'm still passionate
about what the law can do.
Maybe a haircut next time, though.
He's making quite the name for himself.
Theo, you gotta see this movie
your brother's in.
Let me fix you a plate, sweetie.
Come here.
Hold on, Ma.
I need a couple minutes with Foggy.
I'll be quick.
Don't worry about her, Foggy.
She'll be fine.
So, Marci, have you considered
freezing your eggs?
- It's never too late.
- Anna!
This better be important.
All that stuff you said about Fisk
on the video, you gotta take it back.
- What are you talking about?
- You have to make a different video, man.
Issue a statement or whatever.
Say you were drunk.
Au contraire, mon frère.
That's the last thing I gotta do.
I gotta exploit this opportunity
to expose everything Fisk is doing.
No, no, no. Foggy, listen to me.
You need to apologize.
What happened?
Did someone come after you, Theo?
Fog, it's real bad.
About a year ago, some of our suppliers
stopped taking our orders.
Just stopped.
No reason I could understand.
We couldn't change their minds
for the love of money.
After a few months, the shop
was in a tight spot financially, right?
And we didn't have the collateral
to get a loan...
Why didn't you come to me?
I could have helped.
I didn't have to,
because of what happened next.
Out of the blue, I get this call
from a bank I never heard of
offering to help us out. Red Lion Bank.
- Shit.
- You know these guys?
Just keep going.
So, the loan officer there,
he coaches me
on how to move the numbers around.
Make our assets look healthier, you know.
And bam!
The loan comes through without a hitch.
I don't give it another thought.
Life goes on.
I mean,
we've been through a lot around here.
And the old suppliers came back.
Yeah. Yeah, they did,
now you mention it.
And then someone came to talk to you?
This afternoon, yeah.
This old English dude comes to see me.
He knew all about the creative accounting
on the loan app.
He said unless I could convince you
to walk back everything
you said about Fisk...
he'd have Red Lion call the loan.
Of course.
Foggy, that application...
if anyone looks too carefully at it...
You're going to jail.
Not just me.
Mom and Dad signed it, too.
We have a new teammate today.
Take a seat, Ray.
I don't believe it.
Fisk's got something on all of you?
Arinori?
Better we don't talk about it.
And in here, we don't even say his name.
That's one of the rules, Ray.
We only refer to him by his code name.
What code name?
Kingpin.
Another roundup, gentlemen.
And we're going to hit them fast and hard.
Kingpin wants this one to make a point.
FBI! Don't move!
Shit. It's the feds!
Down on the ground, now!
- Stay where you are.
- No.
John Hammer, you're coming with us.
Good morning, Mr. Starr.
I got this one.
Please come quietly.
- Shift change, guys.
- We just came on an hour ago.
Hattley's orders.
I think she's punishing me
for getting off suspension so fast.
And thanks for bringing me
along for the ride.
She's the boss.
See you later.
So what was it? Money?
I've known you for ten years,
for Chrissakes.
Shut your goddamn mouth.
Or what?
You'll frame me for another murder?
Keep your head forward.
There's no mics in here,
but you know they're watching.
You murdered Winn.
How do you live with that?
I killed him to save your life.
That's right. This is on you.
I didn't tell you
to break into Dex's apartment.
I would've stopped you,
and you wouldn't be here.
But here you are.
I can't believe you want this.
We made this happen.
We can find a way to end it.
There's no way out, Ray.
Fisk's had you marked
for more than a year.
What do you mean, had me marked?
Why do you think your sister-in-law
lost health coverage?
He made you desperate for this job,
you did everything you could
to get him this penthouse,
get him everything he asked for.
Like I said, there's no way out.
We're out of our league here.
You could've gone to Homeland Security
or the NYPD.
Not take me down with you.
Not murder an agent.
You make a report.
You get your family somewhere safe. Jesus.
That's not an option with Fisk.
I used to have two children, Ray.
They made it look like a hit-and-run.
I got a divorce.
Maybe that keeps him a little safer.
But there's still Allie, so...
Think about Seema and Sami.
And do what Fisk tells you.
- Where is Mrs. Shelby?
- She's on her way, sir.
No.
Nadeem.
Let's go.
- Yeah?
- Fisk has left the hotel.
How is that possible?
I don't think Dex
was the only FBI agent he turned.
But he's taking Fisk
to meet with other crime bosses.
- Some kind of sit-down.
- Where?
I'm texting you the address.
But if you catch Fisk in the act...
This is our chance to take him down.
Thank you, Nadeem.
We'll meet you inside, Nadeem.
What do you want me to do?
Be ready.
Daredevil will know it's a trap,
but he'll come anyway.
Red Fish Blue Restaurant,
48th Street and 9th Avenue.
You're not fallin' for that,
are you?
That guy, he ain't in your corner.
Not anymore.
That doesn't matter.
It's been a long time
since you used Muay Thai ropes, Matty.
That guy in my suit kicked my ass.
I can't beat him from a distance.
I gotta draw him in close
and do more damage.
You're too mad to think straight.
And it's gonna get you killed.
Matty, come on.
Your mother didn't only leave you.
She left me, too.
You looking for sympathy?
'Cause that's not happening.
She left us because we're cursed.
Because she knew we got the devil inside.
So it's my fault?
Would you be honest with yourself?
You put on that mask because it lets you
feel all right with who you really are.
It lets you hurt people and makes you
feel like it's for something important...
...something good,
maybe even for God.
But that ain't the truth,
and we both know it.
You and your father
are cut from the same cloth.
A corrupt boxer who takes
as much satisfaction in inflicting pain
as he does money for taking dives.
And his son,
who's trying to convince himself
he's any better than his criminal father.
You were born from nothing.
You remain nothing.
- Arrest me, or I'm leaving.
- Stay where you are.
We have a right to counsel.
This some bullshit.
What are we waiting for?
We'll know when it happens.
You know something about what's going on?
Well, they pick us up all quiet like.
No press, no perp walk.
Take us here instead of downtown.
The feds want something.
- Fisk?
- What the hell is this?
It's an opportunity, Mr. Starr.
I've brought you here
to offer you my protection.
From investigations and prosecutions
by the federal government.
Bullshit. This is a sting.
Hey, jury, if you can hear this
on tape, I'm totally innocent.
I don't even know these people.
How much? What's the vig?
- Twenty percent.
- For Chrissake.
Of everything.
I don't know how you keep that suit white
with all the bullshit you pack into it.
I know what this is.
We all know what this is.
You want us to confess to something
that buys you another month
in that hotel suite
you conned yourself into.
No. You can count me out.
The tax is now 25 percent.
I gotta hand it to you, Fisk.
You know how to put on a show.
Just one question.
Where do I drop the cash?
If you tipped him...
I said exactly what you told me to say.
You were there.
Let's go.
Moving to Stairwell C.
Weapons out.
Are you gonna kill me?
No.
Not you.
Fisk?
Oh, thank God.
When will he be back?
Minutes.
Thank you.
Karen Page
located at the Clinton Church.
Keep all NYPD units clear of that location
until otherwise advised. Copy?
What does Fisk want with Karen?
He wants her killed.