Help me!
He's back at the church!
All units, 10-34.
Daredevil reported at Clinton Church.
Mobilize level three.
Dispatch code 11.
Emergency services en route.
Dispatch 10-54 at Clinton Church.
This is a multiple-casualty incident.
What the hell did you do?
Get over there.
You need to assume command of the scene
from the NYPD.
Daredevil is a federal fugitive.
Lock down the church.
Lock down the entire area.
We cannot let them escape.
God damn it, I asked you a question.
What have you done?
It's not done.
We are not done.
Matt?
Matt, come on, you gotta get up.
You gotta get up. Please wake up.
Wake up. Hey.
- Karen?
- Can you sit up?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We gotta go.
- Where is he?
- I don't know. I think he got away.
No.
Jesus. Father...
He killed him. Karen, he killed him.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry, but you gotta run.
- Cops are outside. You have to go now.
- We have to run.
No. No, Matt, I'm gonna stay here,
and I'll tell the police everything.
Karen, the man in my suit,
his name is Ben Poindexter.
He's an FBI agent. He works for Fisk.
So does Agent Nadeem.
They find you, they kill you.
Has anyone got a coat or a blanket?
He killed him.
- Who?
- Daredevil.
He killed Father Lantom.
Who's in command here?
I am. Captain Strieber, 15th Precinct.
Nadeem, FBI.
Daredevil is our suspect.
I'm assuming command.
The suspect is still at large.
We have civilians down on the inside,
the church and surrounding buildings
are on lockdown.
How far out is ESU?
Excuse me?
I saw Daredevil leaving the church.
When?
Moments before you all arrived.
He headed that way.
Well, that lines up.
We have two additional DOA's
in an alley a block from here.
I'm aware of that.
Daredevil came back to the church.
I saw him myself.
We're looking for three suspects.
Daredevil and his two accomplices,
and a white female. Blonde, 5'9''.
Her name is Karen Page.
Matt, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you run?
Run? How could I run?
God. Karen, if you get caught,
all of this was for nothing.
Crypt gate is locked!
FBI team is on the scene.
Fall back.
It won't hold them forever.
They'll be back.
Matt, you're right.
You're right, it's my fault.
I deserved the baton, not Father Lantom.
I should never have come here.
Why did you come?
Because Fisk knows who you are.
I wanted to warn you.
That's what this is about?
Yeah. He already knew that.
Oh, God. Karen, I had him.
I just gave up my one shot
to come here to save you.
What do you mean, you had him?
I was in his penthouse.
Waiting for him.
That was it.
It was...
...the moment.
What do you think you were gonna do?
Shh!
He's back.
Poindexter is upstairs,
and he's with Nadeem.
Clear! Clear! Clear!
Stay frosty.
They're still in here somewhere.
What are you gonna do when you get him?
I did not sign up for this shit.
Yes, you did.
All clear!
This room is secure.
Copy.
Search the living quarters.
Please wait here.
Eternal Father, I beg you...
welcome Paul into your holy embrace...
and do not punish him
for my stupid decisions,
for my weakness, my sin,
and for what I have brought unto us all.
Sister, we need access
to every area of the church grounds.
Now.
I'm sorry, Sister.
I know you're in mourning,
but we need your help.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Lord.
Sister, step aside.
Cut it.
- Clear!
- Shit.
What about the rectory?
There's also a door to the roof.
It's that way.
Let me show you.
Okay.
They're gone.
All right. They're gone.
I guess we'll just wait here until...
until they leave.
Why is Fisk hunting you?
Had a plan.
Went to go see him.
You went to see Fisk?
Yeah, I thought maybe I could provoke him,
turn his emotions against him.
To what end?
Make him attack me in front of the FBI.
Jesus, Karen.
Yeah.
Don't worry, it didn't work. He...
caught me off guard, asked me
how long I'd known your secret.
I swear I tried, but he just...
He read it in my face.
You tried to outsmart Fisk?
Provoke him into making a mistake?
Fine, okay, right. You're right.
I was an idiot. Sorry.
No, you were brave.
Anyway, he didn't take the bait.
What was the bait?
I told him a secret of my own.
You remember that friend he had
that got shot?
Uh...
Wesley?
I killed him.
That's why he sent Poindexter after me.
- I was stupid and...
- and reckless,
and now Father Lantom
is dead because of it.
Because of... because of me.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know. You...
You always, uh, treated me like I was...
innocent.
That was nice... It was nice
that you thought of me like that.
What were you gonna do to Fisk?
Kill him.
- Your turn to judge me.
- No.
No, I'm not. I get it.
Trust me.
Just makes me, uh...
It makes me sad for you.
It has to be done, Karen.
Okay, you're gonna
have to listen to me here.
Okay, listen to me.
Okay, I never told you
why I left Vermont, right?
Why I left home.
Okay, see, there was a car crash.
And...
Um, I killed my brother, uh,
because I was... I was high
- and I was drunk and I was angry...
- Jesus, Karen.
...and I shouldn't have been driving,
and it changed everything.
No matter what I do...
there is no atoning for that.
Okay? There is no way
to come back from it.
What if... it is the way back?
For me?
I can't let Fisk go.
Killing anyone...
even Fisk...
it will change everything that you...
that you feel about yourself.
For the past two years,
ever since his unjust conviction
on racketeering charges,
our client has maintained his innocence
and fought to clear his good name.
One hour ago,
the Second Circuit Court of Appeals
overturned the conviction of Wilson Fisk.
Having seen the proof
that they were wrong,
the Department of Justice will not be
going forward with charges.
As of tonight, we are proud to announce
that justice has prevailed
and Wilson Fisk is once again a free man.
I know that most of you
find this difficult to accept.
That's only because
you've been manipulated...
poisoned into believing
the news media's fake story...
that I am evil,
that I am a criminal.
Quite the opposite is true.
Because I challenge the system...
because I've told the truth and tried
to make this city a better place,
the people in power
decided to tear me down...
to tear me down with false allegations.
They sent someone to frame me.
Daredevil.
The killer who's now showing
his true colors,
who has tried to murder people
in newspaper offices and churches...
attacking our sacred institutions.
Believe me.
Daredevil is our true public enemy.
Agent Nadeem?
Detective Mahoney.
I'm taking over the murder investigation
on our side.
Great. We'll share what we've got ASAP.
I promise.
Thanks. But between you and me,
there's something off about all of this.
What's that?
Well, a number of witnesses claim
Daredevil was trying to kill Karen Page.
And your people are making her out
to be his accomplice.
There's more to this story
than you're aware of, Detective.
Thanks for bringing it to my attention,
but this is our crime scene.
We'll let you know if we need anything.
Dex, this is getting
out of control.
Someone needs to call Kingpin.
Dex?
Hello?
Yeah?
What?
I'm saying we should get in front of this.
Someone needs to call Kingpin.
And say what?
That we failed?
"We"?
There something that you want
to say to me, Arinori?
Hey, this isn't helping.
Dex, they're in the wind.
And we're not gonna find 'em tonight.
I'm gonna release the ESU
and open the scene to forensics.
No. No way.
You get the NYPD to go
to every house in the neighborhood.
Door to door.
We do not stop until we find them.
Dex, they're gone.
Fine, call it off.
And you call Kingpin
and tell him you're the reason
that Karen Page is still breathing,
that you gave up.
Okay. A few more hours.
Sister, do you mind
if I ask you a couple of questions?
Do you know the suspects?
As far as I'm aware, the only one
you've identified by name is Karen Page.
And, yes, she and I are acquainted.
Do you know where she might have gone?
I thought you believed the suspects
were still hiding in the church.
We do. I do.
I meant where on the church grounds.
May I ask you a personal question,
Agent Nadeem?
Okay.
Do you consider yourself a moral person?
I like to think so.
I try to be.
My good friend died here tonight,
protecting Karen Page from evil.
If you're the kind of man you claim to be,
do you really want to help it find her?
Thank you.
What? What is it?
Thank God.
It's not safe for you to come out yet.
Yeah, we know. I can hear 'em.
I can come back with food,
but in the meantime,
you should get cleaned up.
We have fresh clothes.
Donations for the poor.
Uh, thank you.
Uh, Sister...
for what it's worth, I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
This is not your fault.
Father Lantom didn't deserve this.
Few of us get what we deserve.
These should fit you.
I'll come back as soon as I can.
You'll be safe here.
No, we won't.
They brought in search dogs.
Search over here.
Track. Track.
Not me, fellas. The bad guys.
All right.
Wait.
Tell them what you saw.
- The man in black is next door.
- What?
I saw him go in, slam the door.
It was him...
- Where?
- The orphanage.
Please tell me
we got all the kids out of there.
I don't know.
Come on, let's move.
Yeah.
They're taking the dogs next door.
Buys us some time.
Jesus, Matt.
Couldn't put it on in front of her?
You know, something just kinda hit me.
Watching you...
wall yourself off from her.
You know?
Uh, yeah. She told me.
Said she felt ashamed about what she did.
And that... everyone
you ever cared about left you.
- Can we not do this now?
- Is that why you
- insist on doing everything alone?
- I don't insist...
- Pushing Foggy and me away.
- I'm not.
I told you, I'm tryin' to protect you...
I think you're trying to protect yourself.
You wanna talk about this right now?
There are people tryin' to kill us,
and you wanna...
Just shut up for a second, Matt, okay?
Look, I was never gonna leave you
up there, and I'm not leaving you now.
Neither will Foggy.
Despite the fact that you've been
a complete asshole to him,
he'd still follow you over a cliff.
Yeah.
Okay. So, what, you agree?
That could actually work.
I don't get it. What could work?
Foggy.
Mr. Fisk's people said you had to call
a press conference and read it.
Jesus.
You're calling him "Mr. Fisk" now?
"I was acting under duress
when I falsely and publicly accused
Wilson Fisk of criminal activities.
Daredevil threatened
the lives of my family,
but in light of recent events,
I now see that I did the wrong thing,
that I must stand up for what's right."
- I can't say this.
- You have to.
It's complete bullshit.
You know what's bullshit, Foggy?
The fact that me and Mom and Dad
are caught up in this in the first place.
The only reason these people tricked us
into that bank loan...
You knew it was fraud
when you signed it.
Okay, yeah. But it only happened
because Fisk wanted to get to you.
Everything that's happened,
the suppliers cuttin' us off, the loan,
all that shit happened because you wanted
to be the big-time lawyer
instead of hangin' around here
with us losers.
Come on. That's not fair.
No, it's not. None of it is.
We didn't have any say in this, Foggy.
You went and pissed off
the biggest mob boss in the city,
but we're the ones paying for it.
Or we will if you don't do what he says.
If I read that statement to the press,
Fisk wins, Theo.
He's already won, Fogg.
Now, do the right thing.
The right thing for your family.
Hello?
Matt?
The deputy AG has ruled that you
continue to be a valuable DOJ asset
who deserves ongoing protection.
Because they're terrified
of the PR hit if you get killed.
Thank you, Agent Hattley.
That will be all.
Well, where is Vanessa?
In the air.
Her plane took off an hour ago.
Then there's only one thing
left for me to do,
which, apparently, I have to do myself.
We doubled the offer, threw in incentives,
but the owner wouldn't sell.
Not at any price.
Then I'll visit her in person.
I'll make a more compelling offer.
All the way up
to the rectory, right?
That's what they said.
Sorry, sir, this is an active...
Hey, are you Foggy Nelson?
Guilty as charged, Officer...
- "Minelli."
- It's an honor to meet you.
I signed our union's endorsement letter.
I hope you kick Blake Tower's ass.
With people like you backing me up,
how could I not?
Hey, listen, I'm here to talk to
Detective Mahoney. You think you could...
Move!
Nelson?
What the hell are you doing?
Agent Nadeem, pleasure to see you again.
I asked you a question.
What are you doing here?
You know, just observing the hard work
of our men and women in blue.
That's some weak bullshitting.
You wanna try that again?
Okay. You caught me.
Truth is, I'm killing time.
Killing time for what?
Why do you keep looking at her?
Because I need to kill a few more seconds.
Okay, I'm good.
Agent Nadeem, I'm here for my client.
- Your...
- Client.
Don't shoot! She's unarmed.
This is why I'm here.
To surrender my client.
Good.
To the NYPD.
Karen Page, you are under arrest.
Cuff her.
What the hell are you doing?
She's ours, Detective.
Like hell.
She's a federal suspect.
She's a suspected accomplice to murder.
That's state law.
And she's here to surrender to the NYPD.
Shut up.
I'm saying,
as the only attorney here,
- I could help clear...
- Put a sock in it, Nelson.
These feds know the law.
She's our suspect.
They can file a writ
and maybe talk to her later.
I will not let you take her.
You and what army?
Hey, we're on the same team here.
Detective, a word?
What part of "our crime scene"
do you not understand?
Ben, we're all cut up
about what happened here.
A word. Please.
You need to stand your people down.
Listen to me very carefully.
If we take Karen Page into custody,
she'll be dead before she reaches HQ.
No, don't react.
Just get her the hell away from us.
We clear?
Crystal.
Detective Mahoney
will take custody of the suspect.
Bullshit!
We'll have her back in an hour.
Hattley will pull strings.
No.
You can't kill her here anyway.
You messed up, Ray.
You really... really messed up.
Mrs. Falb. My name is...
I know who you are.
Take off your shoes.
It's beautiful.
It certainly is.
It's peaceful and so...
It's been through quite a bit
over the years.
But it's home now.
I hope you're not here
to offer me more money for it.
- Would it change your mind?
- It would not.
I understand
you became aware of the painting
when it was taken away from me
by the government.
Yes.
Ironic, I suppose.
It was a government
that took it from my family in 1943.
So, then, you are particularly suited
to understanding my situation.
The painting was given to me
by the woman that I love.
When I'm with it, I am with her.
She must be an amazing woman.
Yes.
Yeah, she's given me much
in the short time I've had with her.
She brought focus to my life.
Love, if you will.
This painting is bound up in that love.
It's part of me. It's part of us.
My years on this earth...
have taught me...
there is nothing more important than love.
I didn't have much of it.
And when it was offered to me,
I was too afraid to accept it.
I understand.
Well, then, you will understand me
when I say this:
that painting was not hers to give.
She was unaware of the provenance.
She gave it with love.
It was not taken with love.
I was a toddler
when the wolves came to our door.
The gestapo demanded everything we had.
Including that painting.
My father fought them...
...and they shot him in front of us.
Do you know what it's like
to see your father take his last breath
on the floor in front of you?
As they marched my family
across Poland to the ghetto...
my mother went hungry to feed us.
But of the seven members of my family,
we were the only ones who survived.
I am deeply sorry
for everything you've suffered.
This painting is my connection
to the people I love.
I know who you are, Mr. Fisk.
You are a wolf, too.
Men like you took away my family,
took my ability to love...
and almost took my life.
You will take nothing more.
You have been through so very much.
Vanessa would want you
to keep the painting.
Is that supposed to matter to me?
No.
But it matters to me.
What kind of psycho
kills a priest?
This makes me sick.
Come on out of there.
The FBI is going to freak
when they find out you let us go.
Yeah, well,
they can kiss my police-blue ass.
Seriously, are you gonna be okay?
I had to see it with my own eyes.
Fisk really has turned the goddamn feds.
- Some of them.
- Can't believe no one saw it coming.
Well, actually, some of us did.
Yeah, that's true.
Nice takedown on Blake Tower, by the way.
I posted the video on my profile page.
Brett, I'm flattered.
Even if he did crush your ass at the end.
He didn't crush my ass.
You ran out of there
like a scared little...
- Nah, uh... it's my fault.
- Yeah, whatever.
You guys aren't alone in this,
you understand?
Fisk put a lot of my brothers and sisters
in the ground,
and none of us have forgotten that.
If you can find a way
to bring down that son of a bitch,
every cop in the city
is gonna have your back.
Thanks, Brett.
Take care of yourself.
Okay, so how do we play this?
Simple. We convince Matt
to take his head out of his ass.
So it looks like you needed
my help after all.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did, Foggy. You're right.
Do you have any idea how much
life has sucked for Karen and me
while you were off doin' your own thing?
No, but I'm sorry, Foggy.
Maybe I was wrong to... to push you away.
Okay, it's insanely hard to fight with you
if you keep agreeing with me.
Good, 'cause I don't wanna fight with you.
Look, the way I've treated you,
the way I've treated you both...
You've deserved better.
Yes, we did.
Yes, you did.
Okay, so where do we go from here?
I don't want to leave you,
but I can't ask you to be accomplices
to what I have to do now.
What does that mean?
Um...
It means that, uh, Matt's gonna kill Fisk.
That building falling on you
really did mess up your head.
We put him in prison, Foggy.
Look what happened.
It's not gonna be the same this time.
They're gonna throw him
in some supermax hole...
- Come on.
- ...where he can't compromise anybody.
- I know you're not that naive.
- It's called having faith in the system.
Something you used to have.
It's called facing the reality
that some people are so rich and powerful,
the system simply can't handle them,
that they actually are above the law.
That's the bullshit that people like Fisk
want you to believe.
Nobody's above the law.
The only thing powerful enough
to take down scumbags like him is the law.
He's twisted it into something
that actually protects him.
Federal law, maybe,
but we can build a state case
that even Blake Tower can't deny,
force him to take it to the grand jury.
Fisk has been five steps ahead of us
at every turn.
You really think
he's gonna allow that to happen?
Hey, you're right. You're right.
Maybe just hear him out.
Fine. I'm telling you,
it's not gonna work.
You want to give the law another try,
sure, I'm all ears.
Simple.
Step one, we work together.
Step two, we come up with a plan.
And step three, we execute that plan.
That's genius.
Come up with that by yourself?
So I'm still working out the details.
What about this?
What about we find ourselves
another witness?
Someone who will flip on Fisk.
But unlike Jasper Evans,
we keep 'em alive this time.
Someone who knows the details
of Fisk's criminal operation...
who has nothing to lose.
Okay?
No.
No, we find someone
who has everything to lose.
Copy that.
Karen Page has been found.
NYPD took her into custody.
The police? How?
It was Agent Nadeem's call.
Your jacket.
- Sir?
- Give me your jacket.
Pull over.
Get rid of the body.
Yes, sir.
Seema! Are you here?
What's the matter?
Dad?
It's okay. It's okay, Sami.
I saw the broken vase, and I got worried.
Dad, sorry. I knocked it over.
Mom said she was gonna clean it up later.
Are you mad?
No. No, of course not.
- We have to pack. Now.
- What's the...
Just for a few days, okay?
I have to work.
I want you to go away, okay?
Someplace fun. Like Disney World. Yeah?
But it has to be right this minute.
It's okay, Sami. It'll... It'll be fine.
- We can pack together. Come on.
- Go. Go, go, go, go.
- What's going on?
- I'll explain everything when you're safe.
- You're scaring me.
- Be scared later. Now, just hurry.
Stop.
This way.
Get back.
The sliders.
Take Sami into the bathroom
and lie down in the tub.
Now!
Obviously, I'm here to help you.
I sold you out to Fisk.
I know you didn't want to.
But I did.
So maybe you're here
because you wanna be the one that kills me
before Fisk gets around to it.
If we're gonna get your family
someplace safe,
you're gonna have to trust me.
I can't trust anybody.
Well, I trust you.
You saved Karen Page's life tonight.
So I owe you one.