Father Lantom.
Clinton Church.
...bright idea to bring him in?
He's one of ours, Maggie.
What other choice did I have?
Metro-General maybe? Call 911.
He's a vigilante.
If he goes to a hospital,
the police will arrest him.
This is Sister Maggie Grace
at St. Agnes Orphanage...
It's Matthew. Jack Murdock's son.
I'm very sorry. I made a mistake.
Get wire cutters.
We need to get him out of this suit.
Go to the kitchen and bring... we have.
- How can I help?
- You've done enough.
Where did you go, Elektra?
We're gonna die here.
This is what living feels like.
Get Maggie. Tell her he's awake.
Elektra...
- How do you feel?
- Don't try to stand up.
Where... where...
St. Agnes. The orphanage.
- How long? How long?
- Lay down. Several weeks.
- Where is she?
- Who?
Elektra. I...
I don't know who that is.
Stay in the bed.
- You'll hurt yourself.
- My right ear... I can't...
Just stop this right now!
Damn it, Matthew!
Now I can't see. I can't see.
I can't see!
I can't see! I can't see!
Matthew?
Father.
I didn't know you were there.
Must feel strange to be back here.
The place where you grew up.
I haven't thanked you yet, Father.
Figured we could count on the nuns
for their discretion.
The nuns know who you are,
but Sister Maggie swore them to secrecy.
After she swore at me.
If you want to take Communion...
we could, uh...
Or we could just talk.
Elektra...
was with me when the building collapsed.
Matthew, Elektra passed months ago.
- We had a funeral for her.
- No, shh... I remember.
I know it sounds crazy.
I'm telling you, she was there.
I was...
holding on to her when...
In any case, the building was surrounded
when it collapsed.
Nobody else was seen getting out.
I am so sorry, Matthew.
How about I take your confession
and we go ahead with the Eucharist?
Not today, Father.
Mystical thinking is not my bag, Matthew.
Hell, I'm probably the most rational crank
in the whole diocese,
but even I have to admit...
it is a miracle you survived.
Our conversations,
they usually go this way.
I come to you with questions.
You tell me what you understand about God.
- Nature of the gig, I guess.
- Give it a rest, shall we?
Sure.
I'll be around. I'll, uh...
When you're ready to talk...
we'll talk.
Is he dead?
Boo.
- Who are you?
- Same as you.
I grew up here.
Damn! What happened to you?
Life.
This room is off limits.
And if you're well enough to be up,
you're well enough to be in class.
Sorry, Sister.
Hello again, Matthew.
They're scared of you, huh?
So were you when you were their age.
I need to change your gauze.
Preferably without you flailing around
like an idiot.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
by any of this.
You were always pissed off.
Of course, back then,
you were just a boy who lost his eyesight.
And now,
you're the Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
You've heard of me.
I live in an orphanage, not under a rock.
I just never imagined it'd be one of ours
running around in that Halloween costume.
The things I've heard you can do...
You are blind, right?
You weren't just faking it the whole time?
Congratulations.
You finally caught me.
It's not a fair question?
Yeah, the accident blinded me.
It just also, uh,
sharpened my other senses.
Not to worry, Sister.
Those days are behind me.
I'm deaf in my right ear,
and I can't even walk to the bathroom now.
Yeah, well, you're pretty banged up.
Your spine, your hip.
Well, the days of doing backflips
might be over, but...
you'll get back on your feet.
Now that you're out of the woods...
You want me to go.
It's not a convalescent home.
- I understand.
- I'm sorry.
I'll figure something out.
There must be at least one person
I can call for you.
No.
There's no one.
Yeah. No, I filed that story already.
Yeah! No, look...
Oh, that. No.
Uh, part five still needs a quote.
I put out a few lines.
We'll get a bite soon.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I'll have it for you
by the end of the day.
All right. Yeah. Bye.
Shit.
What am I doing here, Matt?
I have something that I need you to see.
I'm Daredevil.
How was the walk?
I just needed some space.
- It's a lot...
- No, of course. I get it.
- Please, come in.
- Thank you.
Can you see me?
No. No, not "see" exactly.
It's different. It's, um...
I think it's better.
"Different" how? "Better" how?
Well, I can sense things about you.
Okay. Like what?
Oh, God.
It's really hard to explain. Um...
Try me.
I know that you stopped
on the way over here.
At our favorite Indian place.
Probably it was a trip down memory lane,
'cause you didn't eat
but you did order a drink.
See, I can smell the curry
on your clothes, and I can...
taste the Jameson's off your lips.
I know that just telling you all that
makes you uncomfortable...
'cause I can hear your heartbeat.
This is humiliating.
Karen, I should've told you.
You have every right to be angry...
Yeah. I should be.
I should be really angry at you.
But I watched you fight for me.
Twice, actually.
You know I dreamed about that?
I played it over in my mind
again and again, and I keep...
How can I be this mad
at someone who saved my life?
Because he's your friend and you care
for him and he broke your trust.
Yeah, well, stop agreeing with me.
It's making it worse.
Can I get you a drink?
And he knows I nodded.
So, the whole cane thing,
it's just... an act?
Yep.
Sorry.
Why?
Why didn't you trust me?
- What, did you think I would judge you?
- No.
I didn't judge Frank.
Why would I judge you?
Well, maybe you should judge Frank.
Castle's a killer. I'm not.
You don't always know
what motivates people.
Uh, yeah, but I know when they lie to me.
Their heartbeats tell me.
Here's what I know.
I will never lie to you again.
That's a promise. All right?
Ask me anything.
Where do you keep it?
In the closet. In the chest.
Holy shit.
What... what happens now?
It's over. That's it.
I'm gonna leave Daredevil behind.
Really? You can just do that?
Yeah.
You know... you and Foggy
had me almost convinced it was alcohol.
It makes a lot of sense.
You know, the secrecy, abandoning social
and professional commitments.
It... It certainly sounds like an addict.
- Well, it's not like that.
- Help me out, then, because I'm not you.
I can't tell if you're lying to me or not.
I don't need him
to be a part of me anymore.
And I don't want him to be.
I want to believe you.
I'm not so sure Daredevil is the problem.
Ouch.
Shit.
Karen?
Hey, Karen, you here?
- Hey. You okay?
- Hey. Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, fine. Thanks for coming.
- Did the building manager let you in?
Um...
I thought you said
you were packing the place up.
Yeah. Uh...
Remember how I told you
I was gonna talk to Matt's landlord
about letting his place go?
Uh-huh.
Surprise.
What, so when you asked me
to help you move boxes...
Uh, yeah, I lied.
I mean, technically it was more of,
like, a ruse.
- Gotcha. You rused.
- Hmm.
Journalism has changed you, Page.
So what am I doing here?
Oh! Uh... Right. Yeah. So...
Wait! Are you living here?
Oh! No. God, no.
I'm just paying the bills,
or some of them,
until Matt gets back, but, um...
Matt's being evicted.
Yeah, I need you to help me convince
his landlord to give me an extension.
- Karen...
- No, just, carrying two rents...
I'm behind this month. That's all.
As much as it hurts me to say this,
you're a reporter.
Look at the facts.
A building fell on Matt. A big one.
And nobody's heard from him since.
Matt's dead.
That's the first time
I've said that out loud.
I don't want to accept it, either.
Especially since I'm the one who...
- you know...
- No.
- ...brought him the Devil suit.
- Hey, don't...
do that to yourself.
You know that was his choice.
He'd have gotten to that suit
whether you brought it to him or not.
I know.
But it doesn't stop me from wishing
I'd brought him some sweatpants instead.
You're right. Everything you're saying
is making sense. I just...
I know it's irrational...
but I can just feel it.
He's not dead.
I'll take care of these
and one more month's rent.
No, no. Uh...
Let's just split 'em down the middle,
50-50.
Fine, but then that's it, okay?
Come on, then.
It's away from the kids,
so you can stay here as long as you need.
Bit musty, though.
I can't smell anything anyway.
- That music...
- The chapel is right above us.
Yeah, but isn't that Arabic?
The mosque on 39th had a pipe burst,
so we're sharing our space
for a few weeks.
Hell's Kitchen takes care of its own.
This will have to do.
It's also the laundry room,
so it'll be noisy at times.
I can always turn a deaf ear to it.
See?
There's a bright side to everything.
- I'll need help getting him into bed.
- Yeah.
No, I'd like to stay up a while.
Then I can take it from here, Paul.
Matthew, if you wanna talk...
No. Thank you.
So...
the bed's right in front of you.
Sister Anne wired you up.
If you press that,
we'll hear you upstairs and come running.
Because we don't have
anything better to do.
Very Christian of you.
Angry, sarcastic... and stubborn.
Maybe you don't have any friends.
Someone once told me
that warriors were meant to be alone.
That caring for people would make me weak.
Sounds like he needed to get laid.
Ha! That actually explains a lot.
I mean, he was right, of course.
I let people in, I paid a price.
I won't make that mistake again.
What is this?
Dug those out of storage.
You were probably
the last one to read 'em.
My Bible.
All right. I get the hint.
And I get the sense things are complicated
with you and the guy upstairs.
No. Not at all.
If anything, I'd say we finally know
where we stand with each other.
"There was a man from the land of Uz..."
Book of Job.
The Book of Job.
The story of God's perfect servant, Job.
He prayed every day at dawn,
with his knees on the ground,
his face in the dirt.
Slaughtered ten goats,
one for each of his children,
and burned them
at the altar in God's honor.
Of all of God's soldiers, Job,
he was the most loyal.
I know the story, Matthew.
Oh. Then you know what happens next.
God murdered all ten of his children
in cold blood.
Scorched every inch of Job's land.
Lashed at his body till his skin
was covered in bloody welts.
God rained shit and misery
on the life of his most perfect servant.
And still... Job would not curse him.
You know what I realized?
Job was a pussy.
You see, that was me, Sister.
I suffered willingly.
I gave my, uh...
sweat and blood and skin
without complaint.
Because I too believed
I was God's soldier.
Well, not anymore.
I am what I do in the dark now.
I bleed only for myself.
You weren't listening.
I heard every spiteful word.
You might hate God right now,
but the feeling is not mutual.
No, I don't hate him.
I've just seen his true face, is all.
And, for the record, I had friends.
I had a life.
I care about people,
and I'm choosing to let them
believe that I'm gone because I am.
I'm not Job.
And I know my truth now.
What truth?
Well, that in front of this God...
I'd rather die as the Devil
than live as Matt Murdock.
Quiet!
We have good news, Mr. Fisk.
Your appeal is proceeding as discussed.
News.
That implies new information.
Let's start there.
We'll remind you,
we're only the messengers.
We've been doing everything we can
to help her.
But there have been some setbacks
regarding Ms. Marianna's return.
It's going to be
more complicated than we anticipated.
How so?
The federal government has
decided to charge her as an accessory.
If they locate her overseas
or she sets foot on US soil,
she'll face prosecution and prison.
I see.
Leave.
What on earth are you doing?
Falling.
I brought you something.
Is it food? I can't smell anything.
A hot toddy.
It'll help open your sinuses.
Thank you.
And you need to keep taking these.
Well, it's hot, but... I still can't taste
anything but blood and ash.
Cheers.
Pills and liquor,
modern medicine at its finest.
Easy, smart-ass.
If you want modern medicine,
the door's straight ahead.
- It doesn't matter anyway.
- That's the spirit.
How's the buzzing?
Not getting better.
Give it time.
After the beating you took,
everything's swollen.
Maybe your hearing will come back
when it goes down.
Or maybe it'll come back when you take
your head out of your ass.
How many of these did you have?
What you said...
about rather dying as the Devil
than living as Matt Murdock...
I just want you to know
that I think you're a hero.
Hiding down here,
feeling sorry for yourself.
I mean, just out back,
there's an orphanage full of kids
who've lost everything and everyone.
Some of them are disabled,
much worse off than you ever were.
And they're still trying to make
the most out of life, the little cowards.
Okay. All right.
And here you are,
with all the gifts God gave you.
Handsome, smart, a law degree,
and people who care about you.
And you're bravely giving up.
Well, you know, thank you...
for the tough love, Sister.
And your charmingly simplistic
view of God and the world.
I appreciate everything
you've done for me, I do,
but don't for a second think you know
anything about me or my life.
I've been a nun for 30 years.
I know self-pity when I hear it.
Okay, good.
Your father was famous around here.
I saw him fight.
I saw him go down many times.
But he never stayed down.
Oh.
What in God's name have...
- Feel that?
- Feel what?
Three subway lines run beneath us.
At any given time, there are
six different trains vibrating the ground.
That was the E train.
Was it now?
You brought food.
I did. I brought you some...
Beef ravioli from Nonna's. Nice.
Now you're just showing off.
He wants to know
that he's still got it.
I am not comfortable
with that idea.
Now you're uncomfortable?
Heal the body, and the spirit will follow.
It's the other way around.
He needs this.
It's the only damn thing
that's gotten him out of bed.
So please just do it.
Thanks for making this happen.
Hands should be used for God's work.
- Yeah? That's why he made me this way?
- No. That's why he made boxing.
- Gloves?
- Helmet first.
No, I can't. It'll throw me off.
- Don't be an idiot.
- Sister, listen to me.
For this to work,
I have to feel and hear everything.
Now, remember the deal.
Keep your mouth shut.
Beats the Hail Marys.
You want me to hit a blind guy?
All right.
Cut! Time!
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Damn. He hits hard.
It's really something.
To see it with my own eyes.
No. Something feels off.
It feels like I'm underwater.
- Maybe we should stop.
- No, no, no.
Ding-ding. Let's go again.
Matthew?
Matthew!
You should see the other guy.
For what it's worth...
you were incredible.
Thank you.
Sister, I...
Did your head spin around?
Then wear it for me.
You've been very kind to me.
I have, haven't I?
And patient. Very, very patient.
Don't tell anyone.
They'll think I've gone soft.
No. I don't think
there's any danger of that.
Let me look at you.
I used to sew up my dad.
And your stitches are perfect.
Well, there's plenty of practice
around here.
Everything okay?
Yeah. It's fine.
I just have to get back upstairs.
I don't suppose there's any hope
you'd come to Mass with me?
Maybe next time.
I'll hold you to that.
Hey! Hey, get off of him!
Hey! What are you doing? Dad!
Dad! Hey!
Help! Get off! Help!
Oh, my God! Dad! Dad...
Stay with me.
We'll get you to the hospital.
Come on!
Hey, asshole,
this was none of your business.
Come on.
We should
kill this son of a bitch.
Nah, man. Leave him.
Hold on.
God forgive me.
Leave him. Let's get out of here.
We seriously out of turkey?
You didn't swing by the deli?
I did, actually.
I ran into a little payment snafu
at the register.
I wanted to make it through the party
before I brought it up.
Huh.
Uh, which card did you use?
The red Visa, right?
- Yeah, of course. Yeah.
- Huh.
Hey, Dad.
Hey! There's the birthday goon!
Masi Savina wanted to know
if you're ruining dinner.
Excuse me?
Is she trying to undermine
my culinary talents again?
Get over here.
Let me show you
how a master chef does his thing.
Check this out.
See what I'm doing here, Sami?
This is a technique called "skimming."
High degree of difficulty.
Ta-da!
- Wanna do the honors?
- Yes.
Are you positive
you used the red Visa?
I paid that one last week.
That one should be good.
I tried the red Visa, the blue Visa,
the silver Mastercard...
I even tried my library card.
It's okay.
- Nothing we haven't handled before.
- Hmm.
If I could have the floor
for a minute?
If you haven't heard by now,
despite Nihar shouting it
from the rooftops...
...my courageous sister-in-law
is now 100% cancer-free.
We know that it hasn't been easy for you,
with all the obstacles you've faced.
Being denied insurance
over and over again.
Those asshole institutions
running you over like a tank.
Anyway...
tonight, we celebrate.
This one's for you, Saanvi.
Cheers. Cheers.
We couldn't have done it without you,
brother.
No, please don't.
I'm serious, Ray.
You two did the work.
I just wrote a few checks.
What are you doing out here, bug?
Everyone's eaten.
We're waiting to light the candles.
I don't think I want any.
No cake? He doesn't want any cake.
There must be something
seriously wrong with him.
No, seriously, bug. What's up?
I don't know why we had to have
our family party today.
I told you,
Ricky Thomas is having friends over.
I could be at his house,
glow bowling in his basement right now.
The Thomases have a bowling alley
in their basement?
Let me tell you something.
Come the summer, you're the one
who's gonna be throwing mad parties,
because the pool
is definitely happening this year.
- Really?
- You bet.
I'm gonna be tossing your butt
off the diving board by June.
Now, what do you say we go inside,
throw back some cake?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- The pool, huh?
- No, don't.
Listen, Nadia said
one of her literacy tutors quit last week.
Maybe I could pick up some evening hours
at the center...
Not another job.
We've been down this road before.
I know, Ray,
but I can't see another way out.
I'll fix this.
I'll fix everything.
I've got a nine o'clock with Salazar,
so unless you got something quick...
- Salazar just got called downtown.
- Well, make yourself at home.
Thanks.
My performance review.
That's not until
the end of the month, correct?
I'd like it moved up.
I'd like to do it now.
That's a tall order, Ray.
Performance review isn't the kind
of thing we shuffle around.
Then how come mine's
been deferred twice now?
You're denying me
the advancement opportunities
that I have rightfully earned.
No, not the Bureau. You.
Now, why you'd do something like that
to me, I don't have a clue.
But maybe it's time I file a complaint
with the EEO.
You're right.
Your reviews have been deferred
for reasons having nothing to do
with scheduling or restructuring
or whatever bullshit
I fed you at the time.
It's because I'm trying to protect you.
Protect me?
Do you have any idea
what your FICO score is?
- 557. Your FICO score is 557.
- So it's not stellar. You know, I...
You're buried in debt,
and that makes you a recruitment target.
It's Bureau policy not to promote someone
with that level of vulnerability.
My circumstances were exceptional,
and you know that.
- My sister-in-law was sick and I...
- I am sorry for that.
Three and a half years.
I haven't had a pay bump
in three and a half years.
I know it's wrong.
I know.
You're a fine agent.
But I can't make this happen for you.
Not until you fix your finances.
But look...
while I got you here...
your number's up.
Nice. Nice timing.
It's a shit errand. I get it.
We talk to this guy every month,
and every month he gives us nothing.
It's a nice drive, though.
Mr. Fisk, I'm Special Agent Ray Nadeem
with the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
The FBI would like your assistance with...
Let's cut to the part
where you tell me to eat shit,
so we can stop
wasting each other's time, huh?
Tell me, Special Agent Nadeem...
do you have anyone in your life
who you love so much,
you'd do anything to protect them?
Are you threatening me?
I have made many mistakes.
But I accept the debt I'm paying
because of them.
But what I will not accept...
is that the woman that I love
should have to pay for them, too.
I would do anything to protect her.
Anything.
I'm sorry.
What is it you're saying?
I want to make a deal.