After the attack
at the Bulletin
and the horrible tragedy
at the Clinton Church,
what will it take before people realize
that Wilson Fisk was set up by Daredevil?
People are beginning to realize
Fisk was the victim of a smear campaign.
Daredevil was the one behind it all.
And what about Daredevil's apologists
like Blake Tower and Karen Page?
- She should be in jail.
- We have breaking news
that Fisk has invited
many of New York's most powerful figures
to the Presidential Hotel
for some kind of surprise announcement.
Oh.
Kidnapping me
will get you nothing.
- What is Fisk planning?
- Planning?
I scouted his hotel. Extra security.
Preparations for some big event.
What is it?
What Fisk will do to me
is infinitely worse...
Things are about to get very bad for you.
What is Fisk planning?
Do you mind if I come in?
Marriage?
He's been planning the ceremony
for months.
He's gonna charm the press and the public
and make Hell's Kitchen love him again.
- Do I look that nervous?
- Yes, a little, but it's charming.
I never knew that I could feel this way
until the day that we met.
I didn't think that I was capable,
that there would be someone...
that I would care for
more than my own life.
That her happiness would be
more important than anything else.
And then...
a terrifying thought occurred to me
that perhaps my feelings were a trick.
The self-deception of a vain man.
That the only reason why I love you
is because of the way
I see my reflection in your eyes.
That thought, it fills me with dread.
The fear that...
that I don't deserve you...
and that I am broken.
Don't you understand we're all broken?
The point is to find the person
whose broken pieces fit with yours.
You're gonna tell me everything.
I wanna know where everyone is gonna be.
Anyone who could stop me.
Stop you?
From killing Fisk.
He controls all of the FBI agents
who are guarding him.
The hotel is a fortress.
Is that a no?
- You'll never get to him.
- Sounds like a no.
I can give you something better!
I'm listening.
I witnessed Ms. Marianna
order the murder of Agent Nadeem.
And Fisk ordered many.
Agent Winn. Julie Barnes!
I could testify!
I know about Winn and Nadeem.
Who's Julie Barnes?
The rose.
I think.
Tell me again
how you ended up dangling off a building?
I tripped.
Get him out of here.
I thought "ambulance chaser"
was a figure of speech.
Not one of your best burns, Detective.
I'm not in the mood to be clever today.
Yeah, me neither.
We had him, Foggy.
We were this goddamn close.
I know.
Instead of locking up that bald asshole,
I had to tell Mrs. Nadeem
she'd never see her husband again.
How did that happen?
I don't know.
Listen.
Something's been brought to my attention.
As an officer of the court,
I'm compelled to report it.
I have reason to believe
that someone's gonna try
to murder Wilson Fisk today.
Someone, huh?
About what time is this going down?
I wanna have some popcorn ready.
Need I remind you
of your obligation to protect and serve?
Stick your obligation up your ass, Nelson.
If Fisk disappears,
all his bullshit goes with him.
And the FBI agents on his payroll
just fold back into the mix.
Including the one who shot Ray.
Don't think of it as protecting Fisk.
Think of it as protecting
the case we can build
against the shitbags who helped him.
Once we get them,
they'll turn faster than old milk.
Still, with Fisk gone,
we'll get 'em eventually.
Brett, please.
This certain someone
we're talking about...
he's angry.
But I know he'll do the right thing
if I can just slow him down.
Give him time to think.
I'll beef up the perimeter
around the hotel.
- But I'm sending in my C team.
- Thank you.
I'm talking rookies and retirees.
After the body
of Supervisory Special Agent Winn
was found in the Hudson,
search divers also recovered
the murder weapon.
The registered service sidearm
of fellow FBI agent Ray Nadeem.
When agents went
to take Nadeem into custody,
he drew a weapon to resist arrest
and forced his fellow agents
to kill him in self-defense.
Sadly, we may never know
what kind of mental instability
drove Ray Nadeem
to commit this senseless act.
But our thoughts and prayers go out
to the families of all the agents
who have been impacted by these events.
Press is calling me a liar.
FBI is calling Ray mentally unstable.
Ray's grand jury testimony is sealed,
so Fisk is just throwing up smokescreens
until people forget and move on.
Yeah?
Well, unless Matt figures out
some way to stop him,
he's going to get away with it.
With all of it.
You mean unless Matt kills him.
Shouldn't have warned Mahoney.
If the police have Fisk surrounded,
maybe Matt won't be able
to go through with it.
Or maybe he'll get arrested. Or worse.
Karen...
Look, I'm not saying that I want
him to kill Fisk. I don't want that.
What if it's the only way?
It's, uh... It's not murder
if it's self-defense, right?
Technically, plotting to kill someone is
the exact legal opposite of self-defense.
You know what I mean.
I get it.
Our best shot at taking down Fisk
died with Nadeem.
But yesterday was also a good day...
...because Matt came back to us.
The real Matt.
Yeah, for, like, a minute maybe.
Eventually, he'll come to his senses.
Matt's Matt because he believes that
everyone deserves a shot at redemption.
Except Fisk.
Everyone. It's a Catholic thing.
That's why he doesn't kill people.
If he crosses that line...
Matt will never be able
to forgive himself.
And being around us will just remind him
of who he was and what he's done.
- Yeah, we'd really lose him, wouldn't we?
- Forever, this time.
Hello?
Yes.
Can I ask why?
Uh, no need. I know where you are.
What? What is it?
The FBI wants me to come in.
It's Fisk.
- Yeah. It might be.
- Might be?
Foggy, you're not going down there.
I have a life.
I'm not prepared
to become a wanted fugitive.
Wait, wait, wait. No, just wait.
What if it's a trap
and you don't walk out again? Huh?
Can you run that downstairs?
Mr. Nelson.
Special Agent Poindexter.
You just won me 50 bucks.
Some of the guys
were betting you wouldn't show.
I'm always available to help the FBI,
Agent Poindexter.
In fact...
please smile.
There.
Posted to my campaign web page
and the tens of thousands of
police officers that know that I'm here.
With you. Helping.
Relax, Mr. Nelson.
You're not in any danger.
You'll be very useful
when you're the next district attorney.
Why am I here?
- 'Cause Ray Nadeem was a friend of yours.
- A client.
Sad, the way it all turned out.
Even though he's dead,
I can't answer any questions
that would violate privilege.
I'm not asking you to.
Follow me.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Nelson.
Mrs. Nadeem. What are you doing here?
I came to apologize.
To apologize?
I asked them to call you,
because you were Ray's lawyer.
And I want to fully cooperate
with the investigation of my husband.
What Ray did is...
How could a man I loved
with all my heart...
the father of my son,
turn out to be such a monster?
It wasn't your fault, Seema.
Ray fooled a lot of people.
Nobody here blames you or Sami.
You're still part of the FBI family.
We'll give you the room.
Take all the time you need.
Suck it up.
I'm only doing this because I have to.
- How's Sami?
- He's okay.
With my sister.
I haven't told him yet.
- When did you get here?
- I came as soon as I saw the news.
I didn't want to believe it,
but I know I needed to hear the truth.
I'm so sorry. That...
must have been an incredible shock.
It was.
But I decided it was the right thing
for me to come in and to cooperate.
That was smart.
Totally the right thing to do.
I was hoping you could help me
figure out how I can help the FBI.
And whether or not Ray's
life insurance policy will still pay.
Otherwise, Sami and I
have nothing to live on.
How will we survive?
I'll help you figure it out, Mrs. Nadeem.
Whatever I can do
to help you and Sami get through this.
What do you want?
I'm coming for you, Dex. And my suit.
Where's Felix?
You'll find out soon enough.
I've got some free time now.
Why don't we meet up?
I have a question.
Did you enjoy the feeling you got
when you killed those birdies?
Is that why you're still killing?
Birdies?
The ones you killed with rocks.
I bet it felt good at first, right?
Then it's never the same after that.
What do you think Dr. Mercer would say
if she could see you now?
Can you hang on a second?
I need a tissue for all the tears
I'm crying over my shitty childhood.
Have you heard
from your friend Julie lately?
You wanna talk to Dr. Mercer, asshole?
Keep talking.
What do you think she'd say if she knew
about the innocent people you killed?
I bet she'd be disappointed, Dex.
If she were still alive.
If you...
If you hurt Julie...
Fisk had her killed.
He killed Julie, so he could replace her
as your North Star.
You should stick
to beating on people in alleys,
because you're not
going to get in my head.
You don't have to believe me.
Then again, you may wanna ask
how I got Manning's phone.
Don't know. Don't care.
Julie wouldn't approve
of you killing people, Dex.
Stop saying her name.
You said you got some free time?
You may wanna check out 16 Canal Place.
Why?
If you're showing this to Sami,
I need you to stop the video now.
For everyone else...
My name is Special Agent Ray Nadeem
of the FBI,
and under federal law,
I swear that the testimony
I'm about to give is the truth,
whole truth
and nothing but the truth...
and should be considered
my dying declaration.
I'm guilty of a number of criminal acts,
and I was in no way acting alone.
Wilson Fisk coerced me
and a number of fellow FBI agents
into aiding and abetting
a criminal conspiracy...
to extort protection money
from New York crime organizations.
I gotta hand it to you, Fisk.
You know how to put on a show.
Agents Arinori, Johnson, Markham, Mockter,
O'Connor and Ramsey all took part
and continue to act as Fisk's operatives
under the orders of our boss,
Special Agent in Charge Tammy Hattley.
There may be others. I can't be sure.
But I personally witnessed
SAC Hattley murder Agent Winn
in her kitchen, using my handgun.
No!
And then witnessed Fisk's aide,
Felix Manning,
remove the body and use this crime
and threats against my family
to blackmail me
into cooperating with Fisk.
I'm not making any excuses,
because I aided and abetted
the worst crime of them all.
I personally drove
Special Agent Ben Poindexter
to the Clinton Church...
dressed in a fake Daredevil suit.
I knew at this point
that Poindexter was the killer
who attacked the Bulletin,
and I knew he was going to do
something horrible at the church.
But I let it happen anyway.
So I'm guilty of aiding and abetting
the murder of Father Paul Lantom.
I'm ashamed of what I've done.
But that doesn't change the fact that I
and everyone I just named
are guilty as hell.
Seems...
you need to get this video
to my attorneys.
And don't try and run.
Go to the FBI and pretend like you
don't know anything about any of this.
Tell them I'm a monster.
It's the only way that you and Sami
can get through this.
I'm sorry, baby.
I will always love you.
God.
He knew he was gonna die.
Okay, so...
maybe it won't hold up in court.
But if we put this out there,
it'll make Fisk's life a living hell.
Actually, a dying declaration
is exempt from the hearsay rule.
What?
The court says that a person
who believes that they're dying is...
has less incentive to lie.
Therefore, anything they say is...
You're telling me
this is admissible in court?
Every damn word.
It's the silver bullet to take down Fisk.
Shit. The world has to know.
The world and Matt.
When I find you...
Like I said,
Fisk killed her and we both know it.
- You did this.
- Think, Dex.
Who got Julie the job in the hotel?
Who had you followed
when you were stalking her?
It was all Fisk.
You let him turn you into a murderer.
You think he's gonna let
Julie get in the way?
Why are you telling me this?
'Cause Fisk wants to get married tonight.
And I don't think he deserves
a life of happily ever after.
Wonder what
the bride's gonna wear.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please have your invitations in hand
as you go through the metal detector.
Who does Fisk think he is?
Summoning us here with no notice.
Well, he's the only one who can.
Well, he's really starting to piss me off.
Oh, relax. Here, have some champagne.
You'll live longer.
- This is what we're running?
- Mmm-hmm.
Well, it's official. Yesterday sucked.
Yes, it did.
But today is gonna make it all worth it.
- What's this?
- Look.
My name is Special Agent Ray Nadeem
of the FBI,
and under federal law,
I swear that the testimony
I'm about to give...
Parking's on 53rd.
We're staging the motorcade... Jesus.
Hey there, Lim.
Dex?
That's Agent Lim.
He's one of the good ones.
- What in the hell...
- Do yourself a favor.
Walk away.
...to be a loving
and faithful husband,
in plenty and in want,
in joy and in sorrow,
in sickness and in health,
as long as you both shall live?
Wilson?
I...
Repeat the question.
Do you?
I do.
- And you?
- I do.
Then you may.
...we are so glad you could
come and celebrate with us tonight.
It is my honor and privilege
to present to you for the first time...
Mr. and Mrs. Wilson Fisk.
- Hi.
- Beautiful ceremony, Vanessa.
Thank you for coming.
That was a bold move
to sit me next to the prosecutor
who tried to send me away.
I told him to hold my purse.
That must have been
very satisfying for you.
It was. My tax dollars at work.
You never disappoint.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
we'd like to invite the bride and groom
to the floor for the first dance.
I believe that's our cue.
My name is Special Agent Ray Nadeem
of the FBI,
and under federal law,
I swear that the testimony
I'm about to give...
Everyone's looking at us.
They're staring.
...of criminal acts,
and I was in no way acting alone.
Wilson Fisk coerced me...
My name is Special Agent Ray Nadeem
of the FBI...
What's happening?
...to extort protection money
from New York crime organizations.
Agents Arinori...
Ladies and gentlemen,
this next one's a favorite,
so grab your dance partner
and head to the floor.
You'll handle it, Wilson.
Like you handle everything.
Show them that none of it matters.
Agents down.
Repeat, agents down.
Daredevil is en route to the ballroom.
Sir, there's trouble. Agents are down.
We're under attack.
I'd like to make a toast.
It's Daredevil.
Julie and I wish you the absolute best.
Hold your fire!
- How did this happen?
- Dex knows our security protocols.
That video of Agent Nadeem
is a threat to us.
I'll discredit his testimony
and take care of everything.
- I will handle it.
- Wilson.
I should have never let Dex
get that close to you.
Be angry later. Be smart now.
Listen to me.
We need to run.
You didn't make a mistake marrying me.
I know that. But now, be smart.
For both of us.
Please don't.
Reports of Daredevil attacking the hotel
continue to circulate.
Meanwhile, more and more police
are arriving at the scene.
ESU, you have one job:
Find and stop Daredevil.
The rest of you,
we don't know which FBI agents
- Fisk has in his pocket, so...
- Sure hope this wasn't Matt.
You came back.
Police are on their way up.
Can you shut down the elevators?
- Why?
- So nobody stops me.
It's over.
Run.
- What about you?
- Keep it, please.
I'll meet you downstairs. Go!
Stop.
Stop it, please!
I will never stop hunting Karen Page
or Foggy Nelson.
I will tell the world who you really are.
Wilson.
Vanessa, please go. Please!
You...
You want me to kill you.
No prison can keep me.
You know that.
- Come on, kill me!
- No!
God knows I want to,
but you don't get to destroy who I am.
You will go back to prison,
and you will live the rest
of your miserable life in a cage,
knowing you'll never have Vanessa,
that this city rejected you.
It beat you.
I beat you!
You'll keep my secret,
and you won't harm Karen Page
or Foggy Nelson
or anyone else.
Because if you do,
I will go after your wife.
And I will prove Vanessa ordered
the murder of Agent Ray Nadeem,
and like her husband,
she'll spend the rest of her life
in a cell.
I failed you. I failed you.
No.
Everything that I tried
to build for us...
Vanessa...
today was the happiest day of my life.
All I wanted was you.
Please.
If I agree to your demands, then...
you leave my wife alone.
You leave Vanessa free!
If you keep your word.
Then, it's a deal.
Wilson Fisk, you are under arrest.
I can't move.
He isn't the real Daredevil.
How do you know?
Because he is.
He's alive.
Thank God.
Please, give me a moment
to say goodbye to my wife.
- Did you give one to Ray Nadeem?
- Please.
Please!
Matt should be here.
Well, I'm pretty sure he is.
Last time we spoke,
I confronted Father Lantom.
I was angry.
I'd change that if I could.
If God allowed that, there'd be no future.
- Just people endlessly rewriting the past.
- Yeah.
I think he was trying to tell me that
for a long time.
His last words were, "Forgive us."
Do you think that's possible?
He told me something, years ago,
when this happened, that I never forgot.
See, I was pretty angry at God
and bitter towards his world.
How could a loving God blind me?
Why?
Anyway, he told me...
God's plan is like a beautiful tapestry.
And the tragedy of being human is
that we only get to see it from the back.
With all the ragged threads
and the muddy colors.
And we only get a hint at the true beauty
that would be revealed if we could see
the whole pattern on the other side...
as God does.
Anyway, I've been thinking
a lot about it recently, 'cause...
I realize I've made some bad choices
and hurt people
that I love without meaning to.
You don't always know
when you start down a false path.
No, you don't. And that's my point.
I realize that if my life
had turned out any differently,
that I would never have become Daredevil.
And although people have died on my watch,
people who shouldn't have,
there are countless others
that have lived.
So, maybe it is all part of God's plan.
Maybe my life
has been exactly as it had to be.
You have a generous heart, Matthew.
To see the good in so much pain.
Not always.
In fact, Father Lantom
used to help me with that.
Help me see the errors of my ways.
I could use someone else
to help me with that now...
once in a while.
I'm a nun, Matthew.
Helping is what I was called to do.
Feels like half of Hell's Kitchen
is here today
to say goodbye to Father Paul Lantom.
Seems fair.
He certainly welcomed everyone here,
Catholic or not.
And he expected those of us who were
to, uh, look for ways to do good
in our community.
Not even the kids
got out of that requirement.
I'm sure I'm not the only one
who remembers his "suggestion"
that we give some of our
First Communion money to the poor box.
And that was his way.
To think of the community,
and the, uh... and the individuals in it.
To think in terms of, "What can I give?"
He gave his life, right here
in this church, protecting others.
Standing up to a man who used fear
as a tool to set neighbors
against one another.
If Father Lantom had an enemy,
I would say it was fear.
For me, personally, he spent many years
trying to get me to face my own fears.
To understand how they enslaved me,
how they divided me
from the people that I love.
He counseled me to transcend my fears,
to be brave enough to forgive...
and see the possibilities
of being a man without fear.
That was his legacy.
And now it's up to all of us
to, uh, live up to it.
That was nice, what you said.
Yeah, it wasn't just him, you know.
It was you, too.
You helped me see the truth about myself.
Ouch. That had to hurt.
Well, maybe one of these days,
I'll forgive you, too.
Before my funeral, I hope.
I'm glad you told me, Karen.
About Wesley and your brother.
Yeah.
Well, uh...
I couldn't live with that lie forever.
We're all just trying to do
more good than harm.
And I'd say you're ahead on that score.
I was starting to like the idea
of being married to the DA.
Pretty sure Blake Tower's not married.
Yeah, he'll have to get by without me.
You, on the other hand, are in luck.
The firm will be thrilled
to have you back.
The thing is, Marci...
I'm not sure I want that anymore.
I was afraid you were going to say
something like that.
You're not mad?
We'll talk about it later.
But do I really have to watch you
drive your campaign off a cliff?
Nah. I got that part covered.
...that Wilson Fisk is a malignant tumor.
Well, the State of New York
isn't going to make the same mistake.
Everyone knows his game now.
Fisk won't manipulate the system again.
Excuse me, Mr. Tower.
Mr. Nelson.
I wanted you to be the first to hear
that I'm officially dropping out
of the race for district attorney.
The way you stood up to Wilson Fisk
was an inspiration to us all.
I'm gonna be voting for you.
Thank you.
- Hey there, Matty!
- Uncle Timmy.
- How are those briefs doing?
- Still stapled together.
Attaboy.
Of course, we're gonna
have to buy sunscreen by the bucket.
Better than that rock salt.
Enough with the snow and ice.
We're getting out of here.
I can't believe you're finally doing it.
Guess I'll have to get used to the idea
of Christmas in Tampa. Yikes!
Like I'd miss the grandkids at Christmas.
- Speaking of which...
- Hold that thought.
I need to talk to Theo for a minute.
- You know she ain't giving up.
- You don't have to, either.
Me? I don't even have a girlfriend.
I mean on this place.
Tower's taking down Red Lion Bank.
You talked to him?
He's not going to prosecute a sweet
old couple who got screwed by Fisk.
You, though...
What about me?
If you pay back the loan...
they won't file criminal charges.
That's some fancy lawyering, Foggy.
You're really saving my ass.
Eh. Who wanted to be DA anyway?
You're too good-looking for that job.
Ow!
So, what are you gonna do now?
Drink these.
Good plan.
Is that a whiskey neat?
- For medicinal purposes.
- Mmm-hmm.
You want me to get you your own?
Oh, this one tastes fine.
- Give Matt his drink back.
- Yes.
So, I guess you guys heard,
Special Agent in Charge Hattley flipped.
- She corroborated Ray's dying declaration.
- I did hear.
Hmm.
So, the FBI is getting an enema,
and Fisk is...
- still breathing.
- Yep. Still breathing.
Headed to prison. Again.
Not exactly what I had in mind.
You trust that he'll keep his word?
I mean, I trust that he loves Vanessa.
Long as she's free, he should stay away.
- And if she gets hit by a bus tomorrow?
- Yeah. Well, then we'll cross that bridge.
So, how long you gonna stick around?
Actually, I was thinking
about moving back into my apartment.
Really?
Well, seeing as the bills are paid,
I might as well.
Okay, so hold on.
You're going to move
- back into Matt Murdock's apartment?
- Yeah, yeah.
I just figured he has
a healthier life-work balance.
Hmm?
And... actual friends.
Doesn't have a job, though.
He's kind of a mooch.
Semi-decent lawyer, though.
Ooh... "Semi-decent"? Ouch.
You do break the law.
A lot. And often.
Objection. Sustained.
I have a crazy idea. I need a new napkin.
- Okay. Well, he's writing something.
- Apparently.
What?
Oh, he just wrote
all of our names, didn't he?
How can you know that?
- 'Cause I was thinking the same thing.
- Okay. Okay, guys, I'm not a lawyer.
You're one hell of an investigator.
Yeah, and way more stable
than Jessica Jones.
All right, so what? What does that mean?
We go back to helping people
out of a crappy office,
getting paid in chickens?
I think Theo would let us
work out of here, to start.
At least we'd have a place
to sell the chickens.
So what do you think?
Why the hell not?
To Nelson, Murdock & Page.
- Page, Murdock & Nelson.
- Hang on a minute.
That actually has a nice ring to it.
Doctor, if this fails,
he'll be permanently paralyzed.
T8 and T9 are falling apart.
Even using cadaver material,
reconstruction is hopeless.
I disagree.
The Cogmium steel
reinforcing framework is...
Can't replace
pulverized vertebrae, Dr. Oyama.
The patient knew the risks.
We continue.