Nadeem!
Stay in the car!
Don't shoot! We surrender!
Convict. Don't move.
- Move! Move!
- Get back! Back it up!
I need to make a call.
Lobby's secure.
Straight to the nest! Move!
SAC's inbound.
What the hell happened?
Ambush.
- They were everywhere.
- Do you have status on anyone?
Two agents in surgery now.
We lost five for this shitbag.
- Donovan!
- Stay back.
- We're his attorneys.
- Congratulations. Stay back.
Locate Vanessa.
The Albanians, they tried to get me.
They'll go for her, too.
My client is not implying that
he knows how to reach a wanted fugitive.
And make sure she's safe!
We're good. Get the medic.
- He's fine.
- For me, not him.
Copy that. Shitbag's all yours.
Dex... Hold on.
Check in with the SAC.
We're down too many agents.
The debrief can wait.
You know the deal.
Follow the protocol
and get back here ASAP.
You will be confined
to these quarters.
You'll be monitored at all times.
You are allowed no outside contact
other than your lawyers.
Armed guards will be
stationed outside 24/7.
You'll be safe here.
"Safe." You nearly had me killed.
Good men died tonight.
You will make their sacrifice
worth something.
Or you can shove our deal up your ass.
Hey, convict...
your lawyers are here.
Get dry.
Get dressed.
Did you reach her?
I need these cameras shut off
and a moment with my client.
- Forget about the cameras.
- Kill the cameras till they leave.
Is Vanessa safe?
We don't know.
She's missing.
Oh, God. I don't know, it's been...
uh, three months since I had one.
- See, now, that's bad.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's been about a month for me.
I've been elbows deep in, uh, research,
but it feels like 100 years
since I had a home-cooked meal.
- This is all Uncle Mitchell.
- Please, stop.
Left to my own devices,
we'd be ordering Wo Hop every night.
- Nothing wrong with that.
- This woman does it all.
Not only does she run Proxy Magazine,
she is an expert orderer.
- Stop it.
- No, it's true.
You're amazing. It's like a skill.
Right? You know all the best dishes
on every menu.
You always order the right amount.
Never too much, too little.
It's perfect.
- He'd be lost without me.
- I would.
- Disgusting.
- Are they always like this?
When I was eight,
they renewed their vows on Long Beach
- in front of the whole family.
- No.
Aunt Lily hired one of those planes
that write in the sky.
- Oh, my God. Did you really?
- I did.
- So, how did you two meet?
- Kind of like you guys, actually.
We were set up
by our college newspaper editor.
Oh. Mitchell, did you not tell them?
- Uncle Mitchell...
- I am so sorry. I had no idea.
I had no... I was...
I had nothing to do with it.
You know what?
Uh, we need... We need more wine.
- Really?
- I get it. I'm sorry.
You know...
I knew that if I had actually asked you,
you'd have said no.
Right. See, that's the part
where it gets to be my choice.
I know you meant well, but this...
- You could use some happy.
- I am happy.
Look, I'm not, um... I'm not ready.
All right, well, if you want to leave,
I'll understand.
I'm sure Jason will, too.
So, wait. You're telling me
that you named your cat Ralph?
- Ellison.
- Oh.
Hey! I have a PhD in Am Lit.
He's my favorite author.
"Life is to be lived, not controlled.
Humanity is won by..."
I know this one, actually...
"Humanity is won by continuing to play
in the face of certain defeat."
Is that right?
How do you know the quote?
I was going to be an English major.
Invisible Man would have been
a big part of my curriculum,
but that was another lifetime.
You made out okay.
A revered journalist
with an acclaimed publication.
- Okay.
- Too much, honey.
So, tell me, you ever worry
little Ralph's plotting your demise?
- I take it you're a dog person.
- Absolutely.
I don't know, I like the company.
Shared a room with my brother growing up.
The apartment felt empty till I got Ralph.
How about you? Any, uh, siblings?
- Uh. More wine?
- Um...
Yeah. No, I had a brother, too, but, um...
but he died.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- Who wants dessert?
- That'd be great. Thank you.
Sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah. Ellison.
Uh, sorry.
Karen Page.
- Who in the hell would let out Fisk?
- Don't say his name.
What? Why?
After Ben died, Lily was
inconsolable. They were really close.
And, you know, it turned out that somebody
at my office had been working for him.
We'd gotten to the point where
an hour could go by,
and I didn't have to call
to reassure that I'm alive.
- I understand.
- Good.
Then you won't push back when I tell you,
you are staying away from this story.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can. And you will.
Look, I get it.
I have a history with... that man.
- Makes it a conflict of interest.
- Exactly.
But I also know him better
than anyone else on our staff.
- Doesn't that give me a unique angle?
- It gives you a bias.
Look, it's not up for discussion.
Enjoy the pie.
And, darling, that is not
a dress, that is a disaster.
I worked on it with all
the materials available to me,
and I did the best with the time...
Baby...
What was it this time? Laughing Matt?
Body Matt.
Foggy Bear, whatever happened to Matt,
it's not your fault.
You have nothing to feel guilty about.
Because I have this great life?
Beautiful girlfriend, high-paying job,
expensive suits...
I always wanted a good suit.
I have it all, but Matt's just...
gone.
Maybe you should talk to someone.
It won't bring him back.
But it might help you.
I can't.
Why not?
Sorry. Go back to your brief.
Take a pill.
There's some in the medicine cabinet.
No. No. No.
Lock Fisk up!
Lock Fisk up! Lock Fisk up!
Doesn't make any sense.
Of course it does. God is angry with you.
What are you talking about?
You don't think God knows
you tried to kill yourself?
No.
That has nothing to do with this.
God restored your hearing...
just in time to hear my name
chanted by the crowds.
Just in time to learn, in the long run,
I won, you lost.
Does that sound like God's forgiveness?
No.
It sounds like... hell.
Lock Fisk up!
You'll never keep Karen safe.
- In the end, you'll kill her, too.
- Stop it.
Just like your father.
- And Stick.
- I said stop.
And Elektra.
They all died because of you, Matthew.
I can't believe this.
This is insane.
You're that reporter.
Sorry. Karen Page, Bulletin.
Uh... Sorry, who's in charge here?
That's the genius who got him out.
Agent Nadeem.
Thanks.
Soon as I'm done here.
There's a vigil at the hospital.
Just give Sami a hug for me. You, too.
Hi. Karen Page of the New York Bulletin.
I'm not authorized to speak to the press.
You need to find
Special Agent In Charge Hattley.
But it is N-A-D-E-E-M, right?
And you're the agent
who released Wilson Fisk?
Fisk has not been released.
That's fake news.
He's a cooperating witness,
but he's very much a convicted prisoner
and being treated as such.
Being held in a $20 million penthouse?
Seized by the US Government from some
Wall Street prick convicted of fraud.
Oh. Oh, I get it. Okay,
so what's he having for dinner?
Is it the filet mignon
or the line-caught halibut?
Press area is over there.
One RICO count carries
a 20-year sentence.
Fisk was convicted on five.
Want to explain to me how this is justice?
Jennings, Garcia, Foster,
Leighton, Torres.
They lost their lives,
and they were good agents, good people.
Write about that, Ms. Page.
All right...
get it up there.
- All right?
- Yeah. Okay.
Excuse us. Watch yourself.
Nine-one-seven-four.
Thanks.
Oh. Hey, man, hand me one of those BNCs,
would ya?
Thanks. Dude, I said a BNC...
Yes, I've checked three times.
I have the tickets.
Okay, okay.
I just wanted to be sure.
With this mess outside,
we don't wanna have to come back.
- Do you think we're safe?
- We should check out.
We booked this months ago.
Now we have to deal with this?
We're checking out early.
We are very sorry
for the disruption.
Can we assist you in making
reservations elsewhere?
Do you know who I am?
You know who he is, right?
Just one moment, sir.
Watch rotation.
Sound off.
North entrance is green.
West entrance is green.
Service area is green.
Lobby is green.
So, you're inside. Now what?
Why would they let you out?
Does it matter?
The real question is, when you find me,
what are you prepared to do?
See, if the FBI are protecting you,
that means you cut a deal.
With everything I know
about crime in this city...
the FBI will be eating out of my hand.
- You'll manipulate them.
- You don't know that.
I know you.
Maybe prison has changed me.
Maybe right this moment
I'm giving the FBI information
that will save lives.
While you're here doing what?
Whatever this is.
Wouldn't that be something?
If I became more valuable
to this city than you ever were.
Garcia was the best man
at my wedding.
Word is Andrews will pull through.
If you call probably never going
to walk again pulling through.
That's hard. That's really hard.
And he gets a penthouse.
Shut the cameras off, please.
We need time with our client.
And?
We reached Felix Manning.
Vanessa's safe.
Her bodyguards
relocate her every 72 hours,
and they take precautions
to avoid being tracked.
No cell phones.
It's why they were unreachable.
Where is she now?
A safe house outside Barcelona.
Felix hid her in Spain?
It was her decision.
We strongly advised against Europe,
given the extradition risk,
but Ms. Marianna enjoys the art
and she can be very insistent.
Yes, she can.
But it's too easy for the Albanians
to get at her there.
Call Felix.
Tell him to put Vanessa some place safer.
Some place closer.
"Homicides are down,
burglaries down, assaults down.
I have not accomplished this alone.
The good people of Hell's Kitchen
have said no more.
Together with the NYPD,
we have begun to take
our neighborhoods back.
Reelect me for district attorney,
and let's continue to take our city back.
Together."
How was that?
Too many "togethers."
Sounds like a Beatles' song.
Okay, but is that good?
No.
- Wow. I'm inspired.
- Mr. Nelson.
Mr. Tower, you need to get ready.
I believe a $1,500 contribution
buys me ten minutes.
It doesn't buy you anything,
but I'll give you five.
- Arlene, I said the blue one.
- It had a stain.
The charcoal's the ticket. Trust me.
You have five minutes.
So, what can I do for you?
It's what I can do for you.
The Wilson Fisk case.
I want to provide my complete,
unmitigated, fully caffeinated support.
I'm sorry, the Fisk case?
I know you're doing
everything in your power
to reverse the terms
of that crap deal he finagled.
But you're under-resourced
and I'm over-resourced.
Like, obscenely over-resourced.
All this to say, I'm drafting myself
onto your team for this.
So tag me the hell in.
Maybe just a nod?
- Mr. Nelson...
- Foggy.
I already fought this tooth and nail.
I objected to Mr. Fisk's
house incarceration
on every ground imaginable.
I assumed as much.
So I did some digging,
and if we can open a state case,
we can at least put him back behind bars.
At least for a while,
which will buy us time to build...
It's just not feasible.
I'll do research. Late-night strategizing.
All pro bono, of course. Soup to nuts.
Nelson reporting for duty, sir.
Fisk is cooperating
with the federal government.
There's nothing I can do.
I know you know the difference
between a good fight and a losing battle.
I know that sometimes
they're the same thing.
And you don't know which battle
you're fighting until you're fighting it.
Well, I'm moving on.
You should, too.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go change for an interview.
So that's it? You're just gonna roll over?
No, I'm just gonna do my job.
And your five minutes are up.
Would you care more
if you weren't trying to get reelected?
Watch it, Counselor.
Fisk had Ms. Cardenas killed.
Maybe you don't give a damn,
because she's dead and can't vote for you,
but she was a good person.
She cared about her community,
was braver than both of us put together.
Fisk will hurt more people like her.
She didn't have a voice,
because the people in power didn't care.
You're supposed to be
Ms. Cardenas's voice.
Leave... or I'm calling security.
I'm going.
But I'm canceling my check.
Prison, not a penthouse!
Chow is on the way, guys.
Mickey D's?
You think DOJ is going to cover
$40 tuna melts for us?
Just a coffee, please.
Save me something. I'm up in ten.
Penthouse, please.
It's got the best view.
You should be rotting in a cell.
So you're gonna bring me back to prison?
But you know that won't work.
There's only one way to stop me,
but you're not gonna do it.
Are you sure about that?
In a way, you're my accomplice.
Everything that's happened
since you refused to kill me is on you.
The bodies that I've stacked up.
The ones to come.
- I wonder who's next?
- You have the routing number.
Two million. In euros.
No, today. My client is not a patient man.
You can follow him right to me.
You know you want to.
- May I see your room key, sir?
- Yeah, I got it.
No, I need to see it.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
You can take him. Grab his gun.
Come for me. I'm caged up. Unarmed.
- Sir.
- They gave me, like, three of them.
But you won't.
You can't kill me.
You can't even kill yourself.
You know what?
I must have left it in my car.
Then I can't let you through.
Sure, I...
I'll be right back.
Pharmacy service,
please call station four.
Doctor Brenner, 241.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, boss.
Andrews is back under the knife.
They think they can save his liver.
Good. Good. That's good.
I wanted to give blood, but...
I wasn't sure if I should show my face.
Nobody blames you.
I blame me.
Moving Fisk was my call.
Because I pushed for it.
Because it was the smart thing to do.
Because we signed up to protect people.
And this is what it looks like sometimes.
Think of all the times this won't happen
because of what we're doing.
Not to civilians. Not to us.
Hold on to all the lives we're saving.
They matter...
just as much as the one's we've lost.
Yeah.
Bon appétit, asshole.
It's Special Agent Poindexter, isn't it?
You saved my life last night.
Yeah, we all make mistakes.
I'm sorry for the loss
of your fellow agents.
Losing them to protect someone like me...
must be particularly difficult
for the families and the loved ones.
I'd offer my condolences...
but I imagine it brings them
greater comfort to hate me.
Unless you feel otherwise.
That my words might bring
any positive effect.
If so, please share that,
from what I witnessed,
they were incredibly brave.
Might wanna eat faster, convict.
The meal's over in five.
I owe those fallen agents a debt...
that I can never repay.
But...
I also owe you.
I've known extraordinary people.
But I've never seen a talent like yours.
May I ask you where you acquired
such a skill?
Okay. You're done.
I saved him 'cause it was my job.
What more do you want me to say, Doc?
Forget Fisk. Talk to me about the ambush.
What about it?
Come on, Poindexter,
we both know how this works.
We have to talk
so I can clear you for duty.
It is what it is.
I lost friends today.
And you used lethal force
against multiple suspects.
- Yeah.
- And you're on duty
even though you should be
on administrative leave.
I understand you're trying to do your job,
but if I were wearing a mask,
the press would be calling me a hero.
Instead, I'm sitting here
trying to justify protecting myself.
I'm not the enemy. I'm just trying to...
Look, forget the psych bullshit
for a minute.
Just tell me for real, how are you?
It's hard.
It's really hard.
This isn't the first time
you've used lethal force.
I'm FBI SWAT, Doc.
What do you think a sniper does?
Well, the thing is, Dex...
Can I call you Dex?
The thing is,
events like this exact a toll.
Repeating traumatic experiences
compounds that toll, creating a pressure.
Until one day I go postal? Yeah, I get it.
The point is,
you have to process this stuff.
I process it.
Do you have a support system?
Well, I think
she'd rather be called Julie.
Oh. Well, tell me, how does that work?
She's a bartender.
Professional listener, like you.
She probably gets paid more.
Tell me about her.
We get dinner most nights.
Today's Tuesday?
It's pizza night.
Julie gets broccoli with sausage,
extra cheese.
I tell her about my day.
The good, the bad.
I know it's not healthy
to hold this stuff in, so...
I talk to her.
I tell her everything.
And...
And she doesn't judge me or blame me.
She's just... there for me.
She sounds like a good one.
Yeah, she is.
All right. You are clear for duty.
But I want you checking in with me daily
for a while. Okay?
Yes, sir.
You, uh... You go see your girl.
It'll do you good.
Why did Fisk flip on the Albanians?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You've got the wrong person.
Fisk hated prison. The FBI got him out.
No, no. He could have turned on anyone.
Why the Albanians?
I'm just a lawyer.
What is Fisk really getting out of this?
Is it the Albanians' territory?
- No.
- Is it money?
No.
Why don't you let me know
when you wanna breathe?
Fisk's woman.
The feds will drop
all charges against her.
- No.
- I swear! He's doing it all for her.
And where is Vanessa?
- Where you wanna eat?
- How about the Chinese place?
- Help! Help!
- Over there! Go! Let's go!
Help!
He's an Albanian.
There's an unidentified
assailant in the parking deck,
considered armed and dangerous.
Anyone got a visual on him?
Nothing yet.
Moving to the south side of the garage.
We're in stairwell H,
heading down to parking level three.
We need backup
on parking level three.
Repeat, we need backup
Stop! FBI!
They have families, asshole.
Listen. I'm not here to...
- There he is! Stop! Stop!
- Stop!
Come out with your hands up. Now.
Stay down, man.
Oh, God.
That's it. Let the Devil out.
Felt good, didn't it?
Too bad you still can't get at me.
Not with the FBI protecting me.
I'm going to kill everyone you love,
and there's nothing you can do about it.
Paper goes to bed in 20 minutes.
- You got 15 seconds.
- Okay. It's big.
- Shit. Fisk.
- No, look...
God damn it.
I explicitly told you not to do that.
- I didn't set out to.
- Stop.
Mason saw you at the hotel.
I mean, I know Fisk is important to you.
I know. I don't care. Okay?
I assign the stories,
and I gave this one to Mason.
I wasn't there on that story.
I was there on my story. Kazemis?
Look, I think there's a connection.
What do you mean?
Do you know who used to own
the Presidential Hotel?
- No.
- The Kazemis.
I don't have proof yet,
but you know who I think owns it now?
Wilson Fisk.
- Tell me.
- Okay.
Look, I got a lead.
So the Presidential Hotel is owned
by these nested shell companies.
It's just one company
who owns another and another...
Anyway, I tracked them from here
to the Caymans to Luxembourg.
And this connects to Fisk how?
Because all of those companies,
they're all represented here
in the United States by one law firm.
Donovan and Partners.
Fisk's lawyers.
Okay, keep going.
All right,
here's what I've pieced together.
Six months ago,
one of these shell companies buys
the Presidential Hotel from Kazemi.
A week ago, he tells his family
that he regrets the sale
and announces his intention
to buy the hotel back.
And two days later, Kazemi gets attacked.
Yes. Yes, exactly. Now,
I don't think that timing is coincidental.
I just...
I can feel Fisk is behind this.
Right? I feel it in my bones.
I need two days to get everything vetted,
then I'll have a story that you can run.
- It's excellent. Outstanding work, Karen.
- Thank you.
Really.
Yeah.
- I'm giving it to Mason. I told you.
- What? No, I know, I'm biased.
Of course! Of course I'm biased.
Fisk tried to have me killed.
He also killed Ben,
which makes you as biased as me.
If people see your name
and know your connection to Fisk,
it compromises this paper!
Fine. Give the byline to Mason.
I don't give a shit about credit.
What I give a shit about
is Fisk getting out of prison.
We have to do something...
I have to do something about this.
So don't tell me to back off,
'cause I won't.
You know, it took Ben decades
to become this much of a pain in my ass.
Well, at least you're upright.
Do I even wanna know?
Do you believe people can change?
I'm still holding out hope.
I don’t think we can.
Not really.
I think we come into this world
who we are.
And maybe we get a little nicer.
Or a little angrier.
But we can't change
our fundamental nature.
Well, you'd actually
have to try to know.
I was talking about Wilson Fisk.
So your hearing's really back, then?
Well, what do you know?
Maybe the boss did hear my prayers.
Yeah, or my curses.
Please don't start with Job again.
You gotta admit it's interesting,
though, isn't it?
I finally get my full hearing back,
and the first thing I hear
is that Wilson Fisk is out of prison.
So you're suggesting that God set a
dangerous mobster free just to spite you?
Nah.
Probably just a coincidence.
Because that would be
incredibly narcissistic.
Fisk claims to be helping the FBI.
But they don't know him like I do.
Right. And according to you,
people can't change.
'Cause he's claiming
to have changed over a woman.
I see.
Well, if there's anything
that can redeem a lost soul,
love would have to top the list.
Oh, come on. Even a monster like Fisk?
You're talking to a nun, kiddo.
Love and redemption
are pretty much our sales pitch.
Yeah. Well, I'm not buying.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll stop him.
For good this time.
Well, just be careful
that you don't become the monster.
Foggy.
This isn't real.
It's real.
Hey, Foggy.
How? Where have...
We all thought you were dead.
I'm sorry.
- Does Karen know you're back yet?
- Take a seat.
I'm...
I'm not back.
- Well, I'm 75% sure I'm not hallucinating.
- I'm, uh... not back.
Matt Murdock isn't gonna be
a part of me anymore. Um...
- I'm leaving him behind.
- What?
The only reason I came here
was to warn you and Karen...
that Fisk is out
and you're both in danger.
- Dude...
- I've had a rough couple of months, Foggy.
Questioning a lot of...
The point of it all.
And last night, everything became clear.
I'm going after him, Foggy.
I'm gonna find a way to bring Fisk down.
But I can only do that
if I know you and Karen are safe.
Dude, slow down.
I'm still processing that you're,
like, even sitting here.
I know you're gonna want to get involved.
You and Karen will try and fight Fisk
in some way.
I'm telling you,
I need you to stay out of it
and leave it to me.
No.
- "No"?
- No.
You don't get to show up like this
and say something like that
and expect me to be cool with it.
- You're my best friend, asshole.
- I see I was wrong to become your friend.
I... I put you in danger,
and it was selfish of me.
I can't change the past,
but I can stop making the same mistake.
We're done, buddy. It's, uh... It's over.
There's something
seriously wrong with you.
Yeah, I know.
Stay clear of Fisk.
Tell Karen to do the same.
And I'd appreciate it
if you didn't tell her you saw me.
- Do you even hear yourself right now?
- Goodbye, Foggy.
Matt! Matt!
[door closes
Was it him?
He took out six feds.
He wasn't in a red suit,
but, yeah, it was him.
So the Devil is back.