Let's take some calls
From the request line
Caller number one
Hey, man, what's up?
This is Dominique
From Shady Knoll Trailer Park
What's up, Dominique?
I wanna hear that song
From Lil Jon and Petey Pablo
A'ight
I got that coming right up for ya
Now shout out the radio station
That gave you what you wanted
W boom boom beat, baby!
Luge! Luge! Luge! Luge! Luge! Luge!
Yeah!
- Come on.
- Come on!
- Go for it!
- Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Professor Reed called
my thesis "bromidic."
I had to look it up.
Do you know what "bromidic" means?
- Yeah, it means, like, dull, right?
- Right.
What's your major again? English?
Oh, no, I'm taking kind of a gap year.
- Later.
- Yeah.
Yo, let me get a gram.
Uh... Yeah, that'll be $100.
How about a student discount?
Yeah, that's cute.
Come on, help me out.
I can give you, like, $60.
That's beer money. I don't sell beer.
Okay.
Hey!
Attachment is the root of suffering.
- Give it back.
- Here!
Apologize.
Suck my dick.
- I'm sorry!
- Yeah, I didn't quite catch that.
- God, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- Now he's sorry.
Come on. Come on.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Namaste.
What?
"Namaste."
Shut up. How'd we do?
Thank God for midterms.
Shit.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah, I know. I just... I overslept.
No, no, no, no, I stayed at Rhiannon's.
Okay, okay, relax.
Relax, I'll be there in a minute. Okay?
I gotta go.
Shit, shit.
Okay.
Shit.
Karen?
Comin'.
Sorry, sorry. I'm here.
Hey. You were at Lynch's
picking up pastries.
- Thank you.
- Where the hell have you been?
Sorry, I was at the bakery
getting pastries,
but they're not ready yet.
- Alice says hi, by the way.
- Your brother coulda done that.
I need you here to prep the front.
You know that.
- Yeah, sorry.
- Yeah, it's my bad, Pop.
I had to work the grill,
I asked her to go.
I'm not set up for the day.
I'm drownin' here.
Dad, I did most of my prep last night.
I have to make coffee and set tables.
- But it's all under control, okay?
- Get to it, then.
I got it.
6:01, Karen.
Nice to see you, too.
How's that?
I said your coffee's on me today.
Eggs and sausage?
If it's not too much trouble for ya.
Houston, we have liftoff!
- Sausage and eggs?
- Uh, he wants a BLT today.
Really?
Oh. Ha!
Hey, have I told you lately that you suck?
Yeah, probably.
- Where's Dad?
- Delivery's here.
No, no, no. Sysco already came this week.
Uh...
Gorgeous.
- Thanks, Jake.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna love it.
- Dad?
Ah!
- Hey, what's going on?
- Well, it was time, honey.
How could you do this
without talkin' to me?
Well, I got news for you, kid,
I don't need your permission.
This grill costs $5,000.
How are we gonna pay for that?
Pat Condo says they're gonna reopen
the ski runs real soon.
- We're gonna be swarming with customers.
- Pat's been saying that for ten years.
No, look, Jake...
Jake, we gotta send it back. I'm sorry.
No, we're not. You said you had somethin'
you want me to sign, yes?
Yeah, it's in the truck.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
You'll figure something out, honey.
You always do.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I had to fetch my own coffee.
Well, when you go back for a refill,
I take mine with milk and two sugars.
Karen, honey,
you're starting to remind me of my wife.
I don't like it.
Need anything else?
New eggs would be nice.
Oh, God. Shit.
I'm so sorry. Just...
Are you okay, toots?
Uh, yeah. No, it's just been dry lately.
I'll get you...
Fresh eggs.
- Is something wrong with 'em?
- No, no. I just dropped 'em. Stupid.
You know, studies show
hand-eye coordination improves 110%
when you're sober.
Maybe use less butter,
and they won't slide off the plate.
Thanks.
Hey...
do we have a regular order
set up with Sysco,
or do we have to, like,
call it in every time?
Why? You looking for a career
in the greasy spoon industry?
Figured I could pull more weight,
- that's all.
- Why?
Why would you suddenly
feel the need for that?
I'm trying to steal your position of power
in the family.
You have somethin' to say, say it,
I got a lot...
- Can you stop being a dick for two...
- Okay, you caught me.
Fine. I do drugs, all right?
I'm a big junkie.
I'm just two lines away from giving
blow jobs for heroin on the street.
Thanks for the intervention.
I won't touch it.
- We done?
- That's not what I'm talking...
If I wanna go blow off steam,
it's none of your goddamn business.
- What? What...
- Read it.
No, I deferred.
Yeah, I undeferred you.
I believe the traditional response
is, "Thank you."
No, how... How could you do this?
Because you gotta get outta here, Karen.
Oh, I could kill him.
Well, you can't go to college.
You'd miss me too much.
I don't know, I could just get myself
a college boyfriend.
Name's Ian.
He plays lacrosse, by the way.
Sounds like a douche.
He is. But he's hung like a horse.
But seriously...
you gonna go?
We both know I'm not goin' anywhere.
Nothing's permanent, Karen.
Not even the Buddha.
Mmm.
Fagan Corners is.
Sometimes, I feel like I could
burn that diner down,
and it would just respawn by morning.
Not if you use diesel.
That's good to know.
Well...
It'll come in useful when I can't find
the five grand to pay for that grill.
Your dad needs to stop with that bullshit.
It shouldn't be on you
to take care of him and your brother.
Maybe you should just let
the diner go under.
Yeah, we should.
But it's all he's got left of my mom.
You're trapping yourself
with that guilt shit.
You're way too nice, K.
Yeah, I know.
You know...
if you wanna make some real money,
you could always come
work with me full-time.
- Pay off that grill in a week.
- No.
Seriously. You're good at it.
You and me together, we could
take this thing to the next level.
You could hook up your family
and do shit for yourself.
Every now and then,
we could even go places.
Tibet. Paris.
Anywhere we want.
Sounds good, right?
Yeah.
Mmm!
Like a dream.
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
- Hey.
- What's goin' on?
Dad said I had to come back right away.
I just wanted you here
for dinner, little girl.
You made, uh...
Karencakes. That's right.
We're celebrating.
Come on. Sit down, honey.
We're gonna have dinner like a family.
We won't be able to
once you go off to college, now will we?
- Hey. What the hell did you tell him?
- The truth.
That you can only defer Georgetown twice,
or you'd have to reapply.
- So you're goin' next term.
- God damn it, Kevin. No.
Don't worry about us, Karen.
You should go.
Dad, I'm not goin' anywhere.
Listen, Kevin and I will get by.
Besides that, you know,
it's obvious you're bored here.
It's affecting your work.
Sorry, you have a problem with my work?
Well, you're late all the time.
You go out most nights, running around
with that Todd Neiman loser.
Do you think it's some big secret?
That's none of your business.
And you think
people don't know what he does?
Do you think
that I don't know what he does?
- Dad...
- He's the only person
who gives a shit about how I feel.
- He's a loser.
- Dad, she gets it.
And what you do
reflects back on this family.
You think that I don't want
to go to college?
I can't go to college.
If I leave here,
this place will go under in a week.
We'll be fine.
You just bought a grill
that will bankrupt us.
You know what? I'm... I'm sorry,
but Mom used to do everything around here,
- and now I have to...
- Okay, guys, stop.
No! You have no clue
how to run this place.
- I run the front. I do the books.
- Karen, stop.
- This is ridiculous.
- No, Dad, Dad. You are lost in a fog.
The diner has been failing for years,
and you won't admit it.
You keep clinging to it,
'cause you think Mom's gonna
find her way back somehow.
Well, if she does,
you're not gonna be here,
- so it won't be your problem...
- Yeah, well, Mom hated this place.
She hated this town, you never saw it.
She loved this place. This was her home.
No, she loved you.
That is the only reason she stuck around.
She felt like she was dying here
a long time before she got cancer.
You take that back.
You ever wonder why Mom
kept buying lottery tickets?
For somethin' to hope on
when she went into remission.
You know what she was hoping?
She was hoping
that if she ever got a second chance,
she would get us the hell out of here.
Well, Mom never got to find out,
so let's see, huh?
Put that down!
What do you think?
One scratch, and we pay off all the bills.
One scratch, and we go our own way.
One last gift from Mom.
Don't.
Karen, please don't.
Mom lost again.
We all lose.
Now we know.
Hey. Shh... Hey.
Hey.
- Let's get you out of here.
- Yeah.
Okay?
Where are you going?
- You can't just leave!
- Kevin...
Shoulda asked her
before you sent that letter.
- I'm not talking to you, asshole.
- Come on, let's just go.
You're lucky your sister's hot.
Hey, does Bernie know you sell, Todd?
- Maybe he should.
- What the hell did you just say?
- You heard me!
- Hey, hey! Hey, hey! No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey. I'd go to jail, too.
Is that what you want, Kevin?
Just go inside. Come on, just go inside.
Come on, let's go.
Please, let's go. Let's go.
Just go inside, Kevin. Go.
Babe, take it easy.
- What the hell?
- Shit. Kevin?
You stay the hell away from my sister!
- You're dead, asshole!
- No!
Shit.
Todd, no!
No! Hey!
You get away from him, Todd!
Come on, come on, come on! Get up!
Are you crazy?
Okay. Okay.
Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ.
What's the matter with you?
I was gonna fix it!
I was gonna fix it! You ruined it!
Why? Why would you do that?
Huh?
Because... I already lost Mom.
Watch out!
Kev?
Kevin!
Dad.
You weren't there.
What?
Bernie is gonna say
it was just Kevin in the car.
But...
He's gonna omit...
certain other details.
He said we've suffered enough.
Dad, I...
You'd go to prison.
Thank God your mother
wasn't alive for this.
Reverend Shockne called...
about Kevin's arrangements.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
No.
I need you to, uh...
leave.
I don't want you here, Karen.
Uh...
Hi.
You doing okay down here?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Will it offend you if I say
I'll be glad to be gone?
Sister Maggie called.
She said she'd have some options for you
by the end of the day.
You'll be safe soon.
If you say.
Well, I'm getting ready to say Mass.
Um, you could come up if you'd like.
Uh, no, no. Thank you. I'm not Catholic.
Hell, if you get strict about it,
neither are most of the people
who come here.
That doesn't mean you shouldn't join us.
A little ritual, a little ancient wisdom.
Not the worst medicine
for a troubled soul.
Jesus. Am I that transparent?
Someone once said that everyone
is fighting a battle of their own...
that you can't see.
But sometimes...
Sometimes...
you can see.
Yeah.
Father, what do you do...
when you realize that you've lost?
A man I helped raise as a boy
came to see me recently.
Matt.
I had...
I had a choice of evils.
He blames me for the ones I chose,
for the way his life turned out.
I can't argue with him.
I just have to find a way to live with it.
Yeah, but how do you live with that?
Knowing that you...
that you hurt someone like that?
Well, you have to realize, Karen,
that whatever it is that you've done...
or haven't done...
it can still be redeemed.
Yeah, that's nice,
but I'm not so sure that I believe that.
"Everything will be okay in the end.
If it's not okay, it's not the end."
John Lennon said that.
Who are we to argue with a Beatle?
Do yourself a kindness. Come to Mass.
Karen Page is located
at the Clinton Church.
Keep all NYPD units clear of that location
until otherwise advised. Copy.
There's one more thing
we need to do tonight.
I don't let people know me.
Very few have.
There was one person,
an employee that I let become my friend.
Eventually, he was like a son to me.
James Wesley.
- Yeah.
- I've read his file.
You're like him in many ways.
He, too, was always prepared.
Aware of every detail.
He anticipated my every need.
He disappeared.
He was murdered!
When I sent you to the Bulletin,
it was to discredit Daredevil
and the reporter who helped him
become a hero.
I didn't know at the time,
but Karen Page killed Wesley.
Mr. Fisk, if there's something
you want me to do...
just ask.
I want you to kill Karen Page.
Consider it done.
What does Fisk want with Karen?
He wants her killed.
Well, good evening, everyone.
I just want to take a moment
before the service starts
to thank you all for coming out tonight.
The events of recent days
have been deeply troubling.
Especially for us, here in Hell's Kitchen.
He's downstairs.
There are no cameras in the bedroom.
No, no. God...
How long?
What? What are...
- How long until he gets here?
- Seconds.
If you leave,
I have to tell him you were here.
- He'll triple security.
- No, no...
Getting back in here will be impossible.
You'll never have
another chance like this.
- Where are we going, Dex?
- Just keep going straight.
Institutions we trust have been attacked.
Innocent people have been killed.
Wait for me over there.
Keep the car running. I'll be back soon.
What are you gonna do?
Don't worry, partner. I'll do us proud.
We have been called upon
to question
whether the people we thought
were fighting for us...
were really monsters all along.
We are being told
that we are not strong...
that we are not safe.
You do what you have to do.
Yet... here we are.
Stronger, because we will not accept
that we are weak.
Safer, because we will not be divided.
I am proud of all of you for coming here
despite your fears.
And I am grateful to you, always...
for letting me call myself one of you.
Even when the night is darkest...
Karen Page!
Where is...
Karen Page?
It's locked!
- Go back! Turn around!
- Go back.
All right, hurry up! Hurry!
I'm here!
I'm here. Please...
No, no, no, no, no. Please, don't. Please.
Please, no, no.
Hello, Karen. It's nice to see you again.
No!
No, no...
Matthew...
Matthew, please forgive us.
No.
Matt.
Matt, I can get everyone out.
But you have to get them away
from the nave.
Okay. Okay.
Can you get them out?
Okay, it's over there. Just wait...
Wait till I distract him, okay? Okay.
Hey!
I'm the one you want, right?
Karen?
Oh, my God. Matt. Matt. Matt.
Matt, you okay? You okay?
Hey.
I can't... can't let him leave.
No, no, no.
Oh, shit, no, he's gone.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Matt? Matt?
Matt?