Check-up call.
-Everything is running smoothly over here.
-Smoothly?
Smoothly as in Tokyo being interrogated?
As in you're about to execute Rio?
Berlin, what are you doing?
Professor, it's Nairobi.
Berlin is indisposed.
So from now on, I'm in charge.
Let the matriarchy begin.
If we took a photo of this moment
it could be my last memory
of the Royal Mint of Spain.
Leaving a string of mistakes inside,
a weakened group,
and only one with the guts
to pull their weight:
Nairobi.
What I mean, Professor,
is that this is out of control.
The situation is critical.
Tokyo played Russian roulette
with Berlin tied to a chair.
Berlin turned her in.
And then, Rio deserted
and Berlin almost executed him
like some fucking Vietnamese firing squad.
Helsinki suffocated Oslo.
He killed him?
He was a vegetal.
Helsinki says he would have wanted it.
As you can see,
this is a fucking disaster,
so I have no choice but to take control
until things get back on track!
Ask him what the hell he was doing
with the police.
I was at the house in Toledo,
it was part of the plan.
Professor,
we need to know what situation we're in.
MONDAY 09:00 PM
There are some loose ends,
I'm not going to lie.
HOUR 83 OF THE HEIST
I'd say it was the biggest loose end
of all.
Assistant Inspector Angel
had discovered the Professor.
He had his fingerprints
and was in a coma
waiting to wake up and reveal it.
The Professor was living on
borrowed time.
As was everyone else.
The situation in there isn't
much better from what you say.
Look,
you do what you have to do,
I'll fix things in here
in the meantime.
I'll put the call through,
probably from the tent.
Inspector.
Before I get to the point I need
to clarify something.
What do I call you now?
Professor?
Sergio? Or...
Mr. Marquina?
I'll always be the Professor to you.
That's how we met.
You'll always be Inspector Murillo to me,
even if you become my executioner.
Remember the first time you made love?
Of course. One doesn't forget that.
Well, this is my first time
in the world of crime.
And no matter what, I will always
remember it fondly.
You're an enthusiast.
And this world needs people like you.
I hope that when you get out of prison
you'll help the country progress.
Because the truth is that...
Where did it happen?
What?
The first time you made love.
In a tent.
That's wonderful.
That's a good place for a first time.
The sounds of the countryside,
the lights...
Yes, that was right.
The rest was, let's say...
experimental and...
brief.
Okay, Professor.
I'm calling to inform you
that Silene Oliveira
is going into provisional custody
without bail tonight.
What did she say to make you angry
and skip the 72-hour custody?
She was trying to be smart.
There's something I don't get.
Why do you let go of your people
instead of the hostages?
There have been
discrepancies in the group.
-Nothing else.
-You're against the ropes.
-And you know it.
-I admit you're winning,
but this is only one battle.
It's nothing compared to the war.
He still teases you,
with a riot on his hands?
He's a rock star.
Salva,
how are you doing?
How are you holding up?
Well...
I never thought tying my shoelaces
could be this painful.
Those bruises could use some care.
A nurse.
That's a very suggestive proposal.
I'd love to look after you, but...
It would have to be at my place.
I want to see my daughter and...
I know that's not the most romantic date.
I can't think of a better date.
Okay.
When you spend years
obsessing about something,
that something
is your whole world.
A perfect world.
But now the plan
was not only the Professor's.
It belonged to all of us.
And we were all screwing it up.
For once, the Professor felt weakened.
And crawling into Raquel's arms
seemed like the best refuge.
The only one possible.
Now you're a hostage too.
What's the matter?
They tried to kill me.
They almost did.
Why did they want to kill you?
They turned Tokyo in.
I was going to turn myself in too.
Alison!
Leave her.
She's lost her mind!
If Tokyo shows up,
who knows what could happen.
You heard him, she's been kicked out.
This could actually be good.
-Good for what?
-To get out, damn it!
For good!
Is it that hard to understand?
They have locked up our colleagues
when they had promised them freedom!
Some of us have been truly humiliated.
They've ruined my relationship
and my future paternity.
And regarding the money that they
promised us,
it's all a lie.
A fucking sham!
He confirmed it!
How long are we going to stay
and do nothing?
The thieves are weakened now.
No one can argue.
And if we don't seize this opportunity,
we'll be letting them escape.
We have to finish them off!
Muster up all the dignity, the
courage, the wild animal we carry inside!
We must do something.
I don't know...
steal a gun from them.
What?
What are you saying?
Where are we going to get a gun?
Swapping one of theirs for a fake one.
If you manage
to get one of the fake weapons
you could swap it.
Then one of them will be unarmed
and one of you armed.
Oh, hello, dear.
-Mom, what are you doing here this late?
-Mommy!
Sweetheart.
Come here.
But wait a minute.
Tell me, what are you doing up so late?
I wanted to see you before going to bed.
Me too, baby.
Hi.
Hello.
Why didn't you tell me?
I would've made dinner.
You came for dinner, right?
Yes. Dinner and sleep, actually.
Right?
Are you dating?
Oh, dear.
Well, uh.
Yes, right?
Kind of.
But have you asked her?
Actually, I haven't. But...
we kissed, which is...
almost the same.
Okay.
Come on, Paulita. Let's go.
You have school tomorrow.
No, don’t worry.
I'll tuck her in.
Thank you.
Did you really hit him?
Well...
yes, I did.
It infuriated me
to think he'd hurt you.
I don't like violence.
Never have.
I know it's wrong
and you can defend yourself.
-It's not my bussiness, but...
-Salva.
I'm glad you hit
the jerk of my ex-husband.
I should have done it myself.
Even if it's wrong to say so.
Well...
sometimes what's wrong is...
the only choice.
I'm speaking from experience.
I'm glad you're here.
Okay from now on
I need everybody closing bags.
Non-stop!
You won't mention the lies?
Arturo, drop the Gandhi crap
or you'll eat shit
for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
Besides, I guarantee you
that I haven't lied to anyone.
Nairobi is in charge now.
So everyone get packing!
Nairobi has a heavy hand for a woman.
Berlin, we're sinking.
The most important thing
is to get out of here alive
without making any more mistakes.
You tell me. Are you with me...
or against me?
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe,
-catch a tiger by the toe,
-A tiger by the toe.
Well, I'm going with you, Nairobi.
Until the end.
I'm going to abide by your coup.
And I'll even confess that I am turned on
by the idea of serving a woman
who is a goddess.
You better pray to this goddess,
because she's got your morphine.
Don't forget.
That's the office where they keep
the fake guns.
-So?
-So one of us has to get in there
and take a blank gun.
And which one of them
will you switch with?
Denver.
He's the dumbest one.
-And who will take his gun?
-Must be Monica.
-When he calls her in for treatment.
-And why would she do it?
It's a suicidal risk.
Because that thug shot her.
He's got her in a den
and he took advantage
of her fear and desperation
to screw her a few times.
And apparently now he left you.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
But that's what happens.
Sometimes we want to change our lives.
We get our hopes up.
But no heist man will take you with him.
Fine.
I'll go get the gun.
Do you have copies of the office key?
No.
What is Plan Chernobyl?
Plan Chernobyl is a...
desperate but beautiful plan.
Consists in releasing the cash
in balloons from the roof,
popping the balloons with gunfire
and causing some wonderful rain.
-Calling the media, radio, television...
-Like the Christmas Pageant parade,
but with 50 euro bills.
That's Plan Chernobyl?
Thousands of people picking up the dough,
spreading chaos among the police. Imagine.
A billion euros rain.
Right.
And us vanishing amongst the frenzied mob.
Very nice.
You know the Professor, an idealist.
He cares more about the message
than the money.
And I didn't say it
because we must respect the timing.
Wish me luck.
Mr. Torres, in my office!
Come in, Mr Torres.
Let's see...
could we increase the printing rate?
Well, it's possible.
But it would be very risky.
If it gets stuck,
it would take us three to four hours
to fix it.
Calculate the production rate increase.
Okay, Miss Nairobi.
Mr. Arturo.
Get up, Torres. God damn it, get up!
What are you doing?
None of your bussiness.
Act like I'm not here.
Walk to the door and don't lock it.
I'm sorry, but I'll have to report you.
If they find out I've seen you,
I'm done for too.
Look...
idiot!
I have a gun.
Don't you dare report me
or you'll be the first to go.
Okay?
Excuse me, Mr. Arturo,
but that's one of the fake guns.
You left the bag open.
Listen to me.
Listen because I won't say it again.
When all this is over,
and it will be in a couple of hours,
at best,
you're going to come back
to your crappy job.
And I'll be waiting for you the next day
with a fat layoff and a disciplinary file
that will make you shit yourself.
You'll be fucked up
until you retire.
Okay?
You have three daughters, right?
And two of them
have been unemployed for...
seven years, if I recall correctly.
So it's up to you.
Torres.
-Miss Nairobi.
-What is it?
We would increase production
by two million every hour.
Do it.
And the technical stops
will be every six hours.
Because that's an extra two million.
Very well.
I'll get this off the ground.
Mark my words.
Anything troubling you?
No.
I'm worried it's been the best night
of my life.
Salva.
You've already won me over,
no need to exaggerate.
It's true.
But I wasn't planning on it.
I hadn't anticipated it.
Oh, you hadn't anticipated it?
Do you anticipate everything?
Well, let's say...
I'm a man who...
picks out the clothes
he's going to wear the day before.
A man who became obsessed...
with...
making the best cider in the world.
And...
and I studied it all.
Acidity, fermentation...
Every possible reaction
of each ingredient.
Year...
after year, after year.
And you can get one bad apple...
that ruins the whole barrel.
Salva,
you're really into cider, aren't you?
It was my father's dream.
And...
he died before he could fulfill it.
He...
He wanted to make...
twenty four hundred barrels.
I understand the homage but...
Why don't you make half?
Or half of half,
and then...
focus on your own dreams?
Let's go away.
I wrap up this cider thing in a few days,
and we'll go to the Caribbean.
Well, I...
I don't have the cider,
but I have a mother, a daughter,
-and a heist to solve.
-Well, we take your mother...
and your daughter with us.
Can you imagine raising your daughter
on a sunny beach?
Raquel...
I don't want this to wear off.
I don't want to ignore this...
this desire to feel alive
that I've never felt so strongly.
You would cross the ocean with a mother,
a daughter and a grandmother?
Right now, I would.
I have a plan B.
Damn.
It's so crazy...
that...
I can't imagine myself
doing anything else.
Finish with the heist.
Do what you have to do.
And then we go.
Okay.
Everyone listen up!
We're going to solve this heist
in 24 hours
and get back to our lives.
We've neglected them enough.
Suarez.
Call Chief Sanchez.
I won't let anyone else get killed,
destroyed, or caught.
Nairobi, listen.
Coming as far as you have is epic.
I give you
my most sincere congratulations.
Listen,
I'm going to get you out of there.
Before they catch you all.
Get Lobo and the rest of the UCO here.
What do you have in mind?
I'm starting to think that
the man outside
is the real brains of the operation.
He drew a trail of clues
to lead us to the estate in Toledo.
But I think I know how to catch him.
First, we'll get the hostages
out of the basement.
Thank you. We don't have
enough people to guard the hostages.
Besides, we promised them freedom.
So let them have it.
We'll release them, but give me an hour.
It's a very big spectacle
for such a small audience.
Hi.
I'm going to release 11 hostages,
under one condition.
I want a reporter and a camera
to cover the news from the inside.
Live news feed.
Look,
I'd love to help with your propaganda
but...
I can't force any civilian to go in there.
- You know that very well.
-True.
You're right, Inspector.
You don't have to force anyone.
Just suggest it. I'm sure
many reporters will volunteer
for an interview like that.
-I'll think about it.
-Of course.
Think about it.
But remember I record
these conversations and the last time
you refused to release hostages...
it wasn't taken very well by the public.
But, of course, take your time.
Son of a bitch.
Let's talk about something else.
How can I explain...
-Do you like soccer?
-Oh, yes, soccer.
Professor, in my country soccer is big.
Well, imagine a soccer match.
-Again with soccer?
-Nairobi, listen.
A match in the World Cup.
And Brazil is playing against Cameroon.
-Who wins?
-Easy!
Or rather...
who do you want to win?
I'd say Brazil wins.
But I'd root for Cameroon.
-Cameroon.
-Yes.
Cameroon, for sure.
-Cameroon, all the way.
-Look,
by instinct, human beings always,
always sides with the weaker one.
The underdog.
So if we show the world our weaknesses,
our wounds,
that we are on the verge
of surrendering.
It will produce a...
a shudder.
I think any guy who isn't Brazilian
would go for Cameroon.
-Even some Brazilian guys.
-Or Brazilian girls.
Yes, or Brazilian girls.
Okay, gentlemen. To Cameroon!
How does that soccer chant go?
Cameroon, Cameroon, Cameroon!
Cameroon!
We move on to plan Cameroon.
We'll release the hostages
in the basement.
And we're going to get a reporter
and a camera to record it.
We'll need someone to be interviewed.
And my suggestion
is you, Rio.
I understand your anger,
but we need you.
You can do it without a mask,
you're empathetic.
You think I'll go out on TV?
For Tokyo to see me from jail,
with a big smile,
doing an interview as if nothing
had fucking happened.
Now I'm a hostage.
Don't count on me for anything.
Fuck it, I'll do it.
I'm a natural crybaby,
you can tell just by looking.
You're no crybaby.
You make others cry.
I'll do it.
If I don't have to talk too much,
You could, but no.
No.
I'll do it with a mask.
With a mask?
On a live interview?
What are we now?
ETA?
Jihadists?
No, no.
This interview has to be done
open-faced.
So all of Spain can feel our eyes,
our breath.
So that they can understand the pain
and a little bit of the sorrow.
Right.
You want to do it.
But you know what the problem is?
If there's someone
who I've never seen feel pain or sorrow
it's you, Berlin.
Tokyo's gone.
Rio doesn't want to do it.
Don't look down on someone
who's good at his job, Nairobi.
I can be a good master of ceremonies.
He's right.
He's good at acting.
Very well.
You'll do it.
HOSPITAL BLUEPRINTS
ENTRANCE
An interview in exchange
for releasing 11 hostages.
I don't know.
It's more justifiable.
We'll be criticized on every front,
but we have to accept it.
Let's take the credit
and sell it as a display of transparency.
You can sell it however you like.
But what about the other thing?
The operation you want to set up
in the hospital.
In exchange for what?
On what evidence?
A plate of fresh anchovies?
On the evidence
that they have a guy outside
who keeps messing with us.
Angel caught him,
and they tried to kill him.
-It was no accident.
-Inspector, we all
read the forensic report
on the accident.
And there's no evidence
of an attempted homicide.
Don't forget he was driving
under the influence.
Fine. You want evidence?
Let's set up the operation.
Let me leak to the press that Angel,
the only one who knows who he is,
will wake up from his coma.
And I guarantee you,
before five in the afternoon,
he will be in the hospital to kill him.
But we'll be there
to catch him like cat and mouse.
Are you asking me to fill a hospital
with undercover agents,
like some police comic strip?
We should focus our efforts
on the factory.
What about the reporters?
What if they end up hostages too?
That interview is a smokescreen.
A trick to make us waste time.
Chief. Let's, for once,
be the ones who set the trap.
Can't you do it with ten?
Twenty.
Monica Gaztambide,
you're up for treatment.
Let's go.
If you take off the jumpsuit,
maybe I can treat you.
Can you turn around?
Since we're not together anymore, right?
No problem.
Can I?
Wait.
Now.
How's the wound?
It hurts a lot.
And it stings.
We'll get only one chance.
I want him alive.
No one fires unless under extreme danger.
First thing we'll do
is taking Angel to some place safe.
To do this, we'll set up a room
on a different floor.
Once we've moved him,
we'll leak the news of his recovery.
And the target will soon be on the move.
It will bw essential
that everyone is in position.
I want everyone
to get deep into their role.
This is a very complex operation,
so we'll need extreme concentration.
We'll have access
to the surveillance cameras.
I don't want anyone from security
on the floor.
Not even hospital security.
No police cars in the vicinity either.
We'll roll out the fucking red carpet
into Angel's room,
where Lobo will be waiting instead.
And agent Balmaseda
will take Mari Carmen's place.
They'll be there,
ready for a welcome surprise.
And remember,
we're looking for a middle-aged male.
You'll be 20 agents and he'll be alone.
He won't escape.
Did you do it?
It's loaded!
It's loaded.
Stop packing the bills
and stash what you can.
We're out of here!
Stash them.
Quick!
We're going now. This has lasted too long.
Piece of crap.
Let's go.
Fifth day of the heist.
One hostage
and two officers wounded,
an explosion,
hostages escaped,
and now Channel 6 cameras
are about to enter the place
that the whole world is watching.
Reporters heading for the entrance.
We must remember the historical impact
of this moment.
TV channels from all over
the world are broadcasting our signal...
Cover them until securing entry.
...the first time a TV crew
goes live on...
They're opening the doors.
Attention escorts,
stop at the bottom of the stairs
as requested.
...special at the Royal Mint of Spain.
A crucial moment.
In a minute,
we'll witness something historic
A Channel 6 reporter and cameraman
will enter the site of the heist.
This is as far as the police can go.
From this point on
the reporters will be on their own,
unprotected.
We've never seen such a thing.
All over the country, streets are empty.
Return to your posts.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-I'm Andres de Fonollosa.
Thank you for being here.
Can you put this on, please?
We're already receiving the signal.
We're going live...
-Raquel.
-...inside the factory.
Mr. Fonollosa, I have to ask
why did you allow a team of journalists
to broadcast live from here.
This is a decisive moment
for all of us in here and...
we needed you here
to record it and to make it public.
Please, come with me. This way.
That's Andres de Fonollosa,
a familiar face to the police.
Bank robber, informer, and
convicted for human trafficking.
These are the 11 hostages
that are going to be released.
There they are.
I recognize
Manuel García,
Alfonso Martínez,
and María Cornejo.
Looks like they will let them go.
We're all nervous...
Medical services ready.
...like kids waiting
for the school bell to ring.
I want to thank you all.
For the courage and bravery...
you have shown.
And...
and you, especially.
You and your child.
You've proven
to be a strong woman.
Why have you decided
now,
after five days of captivity,
to release hostages?
Five days?
It's hard to believe it's been
a few days, isn't it?
You see...
We confess
that this is a very hard time for us.
The situation is critical.
We have no other option but to surrender.
That's why you're here.
This gesture is the beginning
of the end for everyone.
Helsinki,
it's time.
You can go.
Thank you.
Snipers ready.
Assault Team 1, keep your distance.
Copy that.
We'll release hostages
in order to negociate
the conditions for our surrender.
Have you decided to surrender?
We are aware that we lost.
Open the doors!
Eleven released. We're watching it live..
They're coming out.
At last, good news at the Mint Factory.
There they are.
It's an exciting moment.
It seems like the heist men are giving in.
But there are more headlines, big ones.
Fonollosa has admitted that
the situation is critical,
that they have no alternative
but to surrender.
His literal words were:
"This is the beginning of the end,
and we are aware that we lost".
I don't know if you've ever seen a corpse.
For some of us it's also a first.
You've come here to tell the truth.
Here it is. This is the truth.
We've been beaten.
We've been defeated.
It's important that you confirm it,
please.
Yes.
He doesn't have a pulse. He's dead.
The hostages who escaped
hit him in the head.
He died within a few hours.
Maybe to the people out there,
this man is just a thief.
But to us,
he was a companion and a friend.
Nobody prepares you for that.
Nobody.
It's one of the reasons why
we decided to release hostages.
Some of us here thought
we weren't going to make it out alive.
But I never thought it would be him.
You mean,
there were people in the group...
willing to sacrifice themselves?
No.
Not at all. We're simple people.
We have gone through hardship
of all kinds.
Like anyone else.
Including terminal illness.
And we have had to
take desperate actions like these
in order to
leave something for our families.
For our loved ones.
As a matter of fact,
I have a degenerative disease
called Hellmer's myopathy.
The police knew it.
That didn't stop them
from spreading lies about me.
I'll tell you something,
I may be a thief...
I have always been.
I've robbed banks, jewelry stores,
I've broken into mansions.
But I have never sold anyone.
I've never sold a woman.
I'm not a pimp
who traffics.
Or rapes minors.
I'm not.
Ask the police, when you leave,
in which files are these cases.
You mean the police have lied
to the public?
The police lie!
They lie to the public!
They've lied to my friends.
They've soiled my family name.
I'm a thief.
But I have every right
in the world not to be defamed.
I have the same right as anyone
to die in peace.
With dignity.
I can't go on. Cut.
Please, cut.
That morning we were
a trending topic worldwide.
People went silent
in cafeterias and in taxis.
Fonollosa says the police are lying.
That they have been lying about his past.
And dares them to come up
with legal files.
We were the Cameroon team
barefoot against Brazil.
And everyone was rooting for us.
We're now going to our news colleagues,
Cristina Saavedra. Go ahead.
Breaking news:
Deputy Inspector Ángel Rubio
could wake from his coma.
He was kept in an induced coma
after a car accident.
The Deputy Inspector
suffered an accident on road M-506
when his car crashed
into a construction booth
in one of the lanes, causing it
to roll over multiple times.
Professor,
did you see us on TV?
Nairobi, I want you all to be one,
like a rowing team.
Tell Rio that, as captain of the ship,
I'll get Tokyo out of jail
no matter what.
Yes, sir. That's more like it!
Put Berlin on.
Berlin.
Me?
Yes, you.
Thank you.
Hello?
Deputy Inspector Rubio
is waking from his coma.
What are the odds of that being true?
I don't know.
That's elementary police work:
saying he's waking from his coma
to lure you in.
That doesn't even work on sitcoms.
And what if it's not?
He's the only one who knows who I am.
The only loose end.
What room did they put him in?
Room 119.
It's a trap.
Yes.
There's a 90 per cent chance it's a trap.
Ninety nine percent chance.
Ninety nine percent.
But are we going to leave
one percent to chance?
No, you'll have to make sure.
And if it isn't a trap,
finish him off.
Enter a hospital
in which, surely, there'll be
50 police officers waiting for me?
Sergio, think, damn it.
You spent half your childhood
in a hospital.
How do you walk into a trap
and not get caught,
knowing that the cavalry
is waiting for you?
That would be
by making the cavalry
run away.
Subtitle translation by Andrés M.