A moment of your attention, please.
Let's see.
As you already know,
we've released your colleagues.
So nobody has been deceived here.
We've kept our promise.
Promise, my ass.
And, likewise,
I swear that the million euros
will be sent to the addresses you gave us.
Lies and more lies.
TUESDAY 03:32 PM
We will also keep that promise.
I give you my word.
HOUR 101 OF THE HEIST
Attention to all units.
-No one gets in without identification.
-Copy that.
Hey, you!
A clown has entered.
-Could be him in disguise.
-Another one is entering the E.R.
What the hell is this?
There are more coming in.
What the hell is going on?
Get those people out of there.
You can't be here. Get out.
GAME ROOM
Who wants a super fun crazy rabbit!
Inspector, they put out
an ad for a fake casting.
Lobo, he might be inside the building.
He's entering the room.
What's going on? Somebody talk to me!
False alarm. It wasn't him.
Inspector, the interview on the TV.
We've verified that there's
no open case against Fonollosa
for human trafficking,
pimping or pedophilia.
Sources say the information leaked
could be part of a scheme
orchestrated by the authorities
in order to reduce
the heist men popularity.
The latest events and
the death of one of the kidnappers
has earned them
the sympathy of the people.
You missed me.
Let go.
Listen,
when Helsinki leaves,
we take action, got it?
Is it the right time?
Monica, I'm carrying a gun.
He has a blank one.
What can happen?
Either you tell him or I will.
I'll do it.
The Professor will try
to free Tokyo.
Where are you going?
Hey!
For fuck's sake.
Where the fuck are you going?
What is this, recess time?
Everyone sit down!
I suggest you sit, buddy.
I'm not in the mood.
You know what?
I feel like breaking some skulls.
And yours is the best one to start.
Try my gun.
Maybe it'll help you relax.
Arturo.
Little Arturo.
You've got a toy pistol
and I've got a bad fucking temper.
-What are you doing?
-A toy pistol?
No.
Doesn't look like it.
Why don't we test it?
I'll give you three seconds
or so help me God...
-Make it one.
-Three.
Two.
One.
Surprise.
Cheer up, Rio.
Because
we can be a family again.
Turn around.
I said turn around.
Bitch.
Come on, quick. Get moving!
They're going to escape.
Who?
The hostages!
Come on. We don't have all day.
Monica, open the door!
Monica, don't fucking listen to him!
He is taking advantage of you.
Don't do it!
Quiet or you'll get shot, champ.
Don't listen to him, open the door
and we'll get out of here.
SECURITY SYSTEM
BLOCKING DOOR
Come on.
What's the matter!?
-It's not opening.
-Fuck!
They must have blocked the door.
It was me.
Get back!
Arturo.
Put the gun down.
Little Arturo.
I know you love movies
but this is getting out of hand.
Another step and I'll shoot him.
I may not make it alive,
but I'll make sure
he never smiles again.
Berlin, calm down.
Open the door!
Okay.
Take it easy.
Let's talk like civilized people.
Let him go.
If you want to get out, I'll help you.
Open the door now!
No one's opening any doors here!
Is that so?
I'll count to five
and then I'll shoot him.
I have nothing to lose
and I don't give a shit.
So it's up to you!
Five, four,
three, two,
one!
How could he have found out?
He had a remote-controlled GoPro camera.
Bastard.
We're trying to trace the signal.
It's no use. It's too late.
We've been deceived again.
But you were right.
That son of a bitch tried to kill Angel.
So Angel must have come pretty close
to get that evidence.
Maybe they even came face-to-face.
Excuse me, but I'm exhausted.
Leave your message after the beep.
Salva, it's Raquel.
I'm going to have a coffee at Hanoi.
If you feel like it,
I could really use someone to talk to.
Antonio.
They left an envelope for you.
-Who?
-I don't know.
It was here when we opened.
What can I get you?
A beer.
How's your day going?
I take it that it's going well.
It's been awful.
I set up an operation
so I could leave tomorrow with you to...
these beaches, but...
it was a disaster.
-What can I get you?
-The same.
Raquel.
Sooner or later, this will end.
And you and I will meet on a beach.
But you have to choose a place.
Okay. I just haven't had time yet.
Let's see.
How about we choose it together?
That sounds great.
-Pick one.
-Such responsibility! Let's see.
Palawan.
Palawan? Let's see.
Amazing.
Where is it?
Palawan it's an island
in the Philippines.
It's southwest of the archipelago,
a little to the north of Borneo.
Its population is 849,000, more or less
and the capital is Puerto Princesa.
Angel must have come close
to get that evidence.
Maybe they even came
face-to-face.
Have you investigated him? I have!
...my fucking job.
...the white sand beaches in the tropic.
You don't like the Philippines?
Yes.
Of course.
Do you mind if I go
to the bathroom for a moment?
Not at all.
Suarez,
one question.
What color was the wig of the clown
that talked to the kid in the hospital?
Orange.
Are you sure?
For your life to fall apart,
doesn't matter if you're in a bathroom
in a heist,
or at the door of a penitentiary.
You see,
that afternoon, the misfortunes
of three women would sync up.
Raquel suddenly understood
that she had fallen head over heels
for Spain's most wanted heist man.
She's one of them.
She's with them. You all saw it!
Monica Gaztambide realized
that she had just become an accomplice,
and that there would be no turning back.
And me...
I kept following the instructions
the Professor gave us in Toledo.
But without any certainty.
Feeling numb.
Like a bottle thrown into the sea.
Not knowing if someone would pick it up.
If they catch you,
twenty four hours after being detained,
you say you want a deal.
That you will testify only
before a judge,
and they will have no choice
but to take you
to the National High Court and
maybe during that travel,
I can do something for you.
There I was,
on my way to the courthouse,
hoping that my guardian angel would know
the route of the van
and save my life again.
It was hard to be hopeful in a van,
prisoner and handcuffed.
But it would have been worse to know that
twenty kilometers from there,
my guardian angel
had just been discovered.
Raquel.
Hi, Alberto.
Have you analyzed the evidence
from the fireplace in Toledo?
Yes. But nothing conclusive.
What do you mean?
They were the remains
of a sports paper
from a couple of days ago.
So I don't know if it's tainted evidence
or if the guy reads the paper on Sundays.
Right.
Hey,
how exactly did the fight
with Salva happen?
Damn it, Raquel,
I told you it wasn't a fight.
He grabbed my neck
in a chokehold and I passed out.
I didn't touch him!
He's a fucking ninja with glasses.
Why are you asking?
No reason.
And you said he provoked you?
Yes.
He said I shared my brains with my cock
and my fists, among other insults.
He wanted to fight. But what for?
I don't know.
Bye.
Alberto.
Nobody touch those trays.
They're off limits for now.
Get prints off them
and crosscheck them with the ones
from the spoon Agent Rubio brought.
-Are you kidding?
-No.
And then get the prints
from the co-pilot's inner door handle.
-But...
-Do it!
Remember, we look for a middle-aged male,
with a beard and glasses.
Hey!
Find out who he is
and what he's doing here.
It was him.
Of course it was.
Do you have a phone charger?
No.
Do you want mine?
It had been him all along.
Always friendly,
always smiling,
always in the right place.
The only civilian
who had set foot in the tent.
Something's up with your daughter.
The stranger
who managed to get past all her defenses.
And not only as a police agent.
Salva.
I don't have a gift as wonderful
as these postcards but...
I'll improvise a surprise.
In the ladies' room.
You go first.
And then I'll go.
Raquel.
It's the middle of the day
and they know us both here.
Salva.
It's the first time
that I'm not wearing a lifejacket
and am diving into the deep end.
Don't tell me
there's no water in the pool.
There's water.
Well...
Go wait for me in there.
Hands against the wall.
-Raquel, I don’t know...
-Hands against the wall!
What are you doing?
Are you carrying a gun?
Why would I have a gun?
Turn around.
Put them on.
-Is this a joke?
-Put them on!
Put them on!
You're under arrest for collaboration
in the heist at the Royal Mint.
You see,
You have the right to remain silent
third time was the charm.
You have the right not to testify
and to be brought before a judge.
And this time she had something
stronger than a suspicion.
She had a grudge.
She felt anger.
She felt poisoned.
Helsinki felt something similar.
But not because of deception,
but for lack of sleep.
He had slept four hours
in the last five days.
Do you know what happens
when you don't sleep?
Their neural connections break down
like a short-circuit.
They stop secreting dopamine.
They stop processing glucose.
And the only information left in the brain
is survival.
So one thing you can't expect
from a guy who hasn't slept in five days
it's patience.
Come on.
Take off your clothes.
The t-shirt too.
I have a wound on my shoulder...
Take it off!
And you try to steal from us.
Shit.
It's what we get for not killing
when we had to.
What will you do?
If I shoot you,
you just die.
You don't suffer.
Now you'll wear two kilos
of explosives strapped to your body.
I'll blow it up,
but you won't know when.
That's a shitload of explosives.
Careful, it could make a real mess.
He has been
a bigger pain in the ass than the police.
Oslo died because of him.
Denver almost died because of him.
With this
we end our troubles.
Right, little Arturo?
If you remove the wire,
it blows.
Don't make sudden movements,
don't sweat,
don't touch yourself.
Detonator.
If I touch
this button,
Your wife won't recognize you.
Minced little Arturo.
Do you have a cigarette?
-Do you?
-Monica, you're pregnant.
I'm pregnant, kidnapped, shot.
And soon accused of...
collaboration in an armed robbery.
Don't think the worst.
Arturo will toss you a line.
He's the father, right?
Which father?
The one who pointed at me
like I was a kidnapper?
Which father?
The one who's head I busted in
with an iron rod?
Maybe my colleagues will help me.
I only screwed up their escape plan,
which I'm sure I'll get tried for.
Why am I so stupid?
What was I thinking?
Come on, give me a cigarette.
Give me a cigarette.
My fetus needs it!
I swear I'll mess Arturo up
before you sit in any court dock.
You won't mess anybody up.
Take it easy.
She's right, they'll put her away!
If we escape and get caught,
she's going to jail.
If we stay and the cops get in,
it's the same.
One way or another she'll do time.
Shit.
I always make the wrong choice.
I messed around with a married man.
I got pregnant.
And then another guy comes in,
shoots me in the leg,
and I go
and fall in love.
You know what we'll do?
What?
You'll come with us.
You crossed the line.
I won't leave you behind. Okay?
-Look, son. Maybe...
-She's coming with us!
She'll take Tokyo or Oslo's place,
end of story!
No, listen.
I'm just the secretary.
I don't see myself running away
from the police or shooting guns.
Or hiding in who knows where, Cambodia.
A country without extradition laws.
I don't.
It's better to stay.
And when the police come, I'll say
I did it because I had
big-time Stockholm syndrome and
that will be an extenuating.
That's what it was, right?
Stockholm.
What?
That sounds nice.
If you come with us, you...
your name could be Stockholm.
I don't know, man!
Get out.
DO NOT CROSS
POLICE LINE
Open it.
Get in.
We were all exhausted.
The lack of sleep,
the stress,
or the anguish of years
keeping a secret that,
in that suffocating environment,
was becoming harder to keep.
And all of us,
sooner or later,
lost control.
Except for Berlin.
He was the only one who stuck
to the resting protocol.
The others
went crazy.
I have tried being nice.
I tried to give you
what you were promised.
To free you from Berlin.
For this to make sense!
After losing what I have lost,
to give this some meaning.
I'm kind.
I've been kind.
And the world
spits in my face.
I have tried
to give you space.
And you fucked me over.
Berlin.
Hey.
It's been over an hour and a half.
Don't you feel like
killing me
while I sleep?
Just a little.
Hey.
You're laughing.
That means you're
not afraid of me anymore.
Let's say the dose of tranquilizers
I'm taking has neutralized me.
If everything works out,
which is
unlikely if I don't take the reins again,
but...
if it does all work out,
I'd like to propose a deal,
a romantic venture.
Within a few days
I'll send you a plane ticket
to a very
distant place.
If you want,
you can come with me.
For a very short time,
a lot of pleasure.
And then,
after it ends,
you get to keep everything I have.
It would be really wonderful
if you fell completely in love with me.
But...
I don't live on expectations
or false hopes.
I have many flaws,
and I know it.
I could settle for
you being
my partner
until the final voyage.
You and me together
until the end.
You don't get it.
What do I have to do to get some respect?
What do I have to do?
Do I cut off one of your ears
and send it to your father?
Or shoot you in the leg
so you can't ever dance again?
That's a great idea!
It is time to be pragmatic.
The utopia
of collaboration
has failed.
Nairobi,
I appreciate you allowing me
to take some time off from my duties,
but...
we're all ready for me
to be back in charge.
All yours.
This is a wonderful moment.
Stand up!
I told you
I was going to protect you,
didn't I?
But I've changed my mind.
It's a lot more practical
to torture you.
In concentration camps,
respect is a given.
Well, here it's going to be the same.
You're going to dig the tunnel
until your hands bleed!
At night,
you may cry in pain
in your cot,
but you will keep on digging!
You'll be on shifts without rest.
Otherwise, an epic punishment awaits you.
Just like your leader.
A man who will kill
if he betrays us again.
Who will kill if he ever
yearns for freedom again.
Whose sweat
kills.
A man of explosive nature.
Now they're going to be scared of you,
Arturo.
Although we've always known
you're "the bomb".
Since you're an outcast,
you'll stay here, secluded.
Helsinki and everyone else, to the tunnel!
Come on, let's go!
Let's go, quickly!
Subtitle translation by Andrés M.