Look, Paula's markers,
with chewed up caps,
like you used to do.
Thanks, Mom. Give me one.
So, on the day of our first date
I arrived 25 minutes early.
I called him and he said
he was heading out right then.
See you soon.
We met
here, at Hanoi.
He walked there
and it only took five to seven minutes.
Pity, for once you land a good guy...
Why do you want to know how long it took?
To know how far away
from the cafeteria he was.
DISTANCE WALKING 5 TO 7 MINS
500 MTS APPROX.
In that time frame he could have
traveled 500 meters at best.
More or less.
his hideout
is in this area.
He took one of these streets
to get to the cafeteria.
I'm sure one of the surveillance cameras
taped it.
I have to narrow it down.
Give me another one.
I'll get the recordings
from that area
to figure out the route he took.
Are you sure of this?
Mom,
I'll find him no matter what it takes.
Be careful, dear.
We have a badly injured man.
Three gunshots in the abdomen
and it's been a few hours.
Where is he?
I don't know how long
before I get him out.
And listen,
the police are tracking me down.
Is it safe for them?
They already know
and they agreed to their part.
Yours would be ten million.
I need abdominal laparotomy gear,
a medical ventilator
and surgical equipment.
Can you get it?
I'll take care of it.
WEDNESDAY
09:36 AM
14 HOURS
SINCE THE SHOOTOUT
Good morning. Inspector Murillo.
I need the footage from the cameras
from October 23rd.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Bye.
Thank you.
Did you find out anything yet?
I'm starting to draw
the route he took to the cafeteria.
Look, that narrows the area down
to this triangle.
If he went to Hanoi this way,
His hideout is very close, in this area.
I have to go out again, mom.
The bulk of the calls were made
from this area.
So the Professor must have
used these streets.
Check the surveillance tapes
from this area.
Get the judge to issue a warrant.
This is headquarters...
I told the kid.
Told him what?
What I did to you.
That I abandoned you
at that roundabout in Martorell.
I went back to that roundabout,
because...
I dreamed that you were
cleaning windshields
at that stop light.
I took the car
and drove.
Hours and hours,
because I wanted to fix
my mistake.
Don't speak.
-Rest.
-I showed your picture
to everyone who passed by.
And now...
your son...
told me he hates me.
Your son
adores you.
No matter what he says
in the heat of the moment.
I know he doesn't hate you.
Well, I deserve it.
I took his mother from him.
No.
No, you did great.
You have a wonderful son.
Strong.
Noble.
And that...
that's thanks to you.
I did what I could, honey...
He came out a little nuts, didn't he?
I have never
been as happy
as the day I met you.
If I have to go to some place now,
I'd like it to be that one.
The village festival.
And dance with you,
together
with the lights.
With the colorful lights.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
-What are you doing?
-Listen!
Do you hear that?
It's them!
-It's them.
-How much is left?
30 or 40 centimeters.
Come on. Let's go!
Hey!
Professor!
We're here!
They're here.
They're here!
Hey!
They're right there!
One more!
Professor!
You're going to get ink on the wall, dear.
Mom,
where are your car keys?
That car hasn't been used
for a long time, dear.
Well, it's about time
we take it for a spin.
Professor!
Denver!
Monica, tell my father to hang in there.
We're almost there!
-Denver.
-We're almost done!
-Go back up.
-What?
-Not now!
-Listen, Denver!
-I'm not...
-Denver!
-What?
Go back up.
You need to go back up, now.
I'm not going back up now.
Denver, stop!
I'm not going back up now!
No!
We're so close, Monica.
I know. Listen.
You have to go back up, now.
Do you understand? Look at me.
If you don't go up now,
you'll regret it for the rest
of your life.
Go up.
Hey!
Let's go.
Come on!
I'm here, papa.
Just hold a little longer
because we're going to make it.
Right, Rio? We're digging like crazy.
We already hear
the Serbs on the other side.
Don't worry.
Dad...
-What?
-That...
That thing I said about
hating you...
I could never feel that for you.
I can't hate you, okay?
It's okay. Don't worry.
You did what you had to do with mom.
But I can't hate you.
Monica.
Yes?
I'll give you 300 million if you keep him.
This guy's a headache.
I brought him here,
But...
now I'm going on vacation.
Of course I will.
Take care of him.
Gentlemen.
I haven't introduced myself.
Agustin Ramos.
And it's been a pleasure.
I love you.
I love you too, papa.
So much.
And I'm not letting you go.
Rio, bring all the explosives
we have left.
I'm blowing up that tunnel.
Don’t.
If you blow the tunnel
you'll bury us all.
But papa...
You have to carry on.
And remember...
-Remember what?
-"No rear-view mirrors".
Alright.
But I don't know if I can...
I love you.
I love you too.
It was for the absence of your lips
That I cried for the first time
And I cursed having met you
For not being able to stop loving you
You, my wife I wished to make
And without love, I searched for luck
I pulled out a gun
And fate brought death
Maria, my life, my love
I promised
That I'd return
But I will not return
I was caught by the police
Maria, my life, my love
I will not stop
Loving you
The hugs that I lost
You will not see me again
All the shops in the area
said the same.
Inspector Murillo has seized footage
crucial for the investigation.
Indisputable evidence
that she's collaborating in the heist.
Activate the intervention protocol.
Immediately.
Gather your best men.
What about the hostages?
And Alison Parker,
or the international protocol?
What about public safety?
Colonel, they have large caliber guns,
entrances loaded with explosives.
The hostages wear jumpsuits
and masks, like the thieves.
Impossible to tell them apart.
It will be a bloodbath and you know it.
And what do you suggest?
Let them get away,
holding hands with Inspector Murillo?
Yes. Let them get out
and catch them outside.
Do you know where
public safety has led us?
You want me to tell you?
To us being the laughing stock.
Not only of Spain,
of the whole fucking world.
The world's newscasts follow this story
as if it were the World Cup.
Do you want to be on TV
with the headline:
"The idiots in the police
let an escaped prisoner re-enter
the Royal Mint factory
riding a motorbike".
A motorbike!
Do you like being the goddamn foo?
Excuse me...
I didn't ask for your opinion.
The government has given
the order to intervene.
They have been in there for 125 hours,
and if by chance they were to escape
it would be a disgrace to this country.
-Excuse me...
-What?
The State Prosecutor's Office
issued an arrest warrant
for Inspector Raquel Murillo.
She is under search and arrest.
Shall we close it?
Just like that?
We should...
say a few words or something.
Our Father who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Thy will be done on earth,
as it is in Heaven.
Thy Kingdom come.
What?
You skipped a part.
After "hallowed be Thy name"
comes "Thy Kingdom come."
What the hell does that matter?
If you're going to pray,
do it right.
You think God is checking
if you're saying it right?
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our debts,
as we also have forgiven our debtors.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
There are moments in life
where you should be able
to have a remote control
so you could stop it.
Even if just for five minutes.
But some things happen
with irreverent obscenity.
And there's nothing you can do.
On the one hand
we had just buried Moscow.
On the other,
we were opening the path to our freedom.
SHOP AVAILABLE
WEDNESDAY
03:35 PM
HOUR 125 OF THE HEIST
-Where is he?
-In the warehouse.
I'm so sorry.
Come here.
The one with the phone.
Hello.
You can call her Stockholm if you want.
It can't be all tears, can it?
Go on then.
Go.
Nine hundred and eighty four
million euros.
Yes.
Colonel, we are ready to go in.
Good.
There's news from the tunnel.
The GPR shows that they are
close to the sewer system.
We have a special operations unit
in the sewers.
Entering the main drainage channel.
Target distance 300 meters north.
Copy that. Standing by.
Suarez.
We'll carry out
this operation together.
We'll use an enveloping tactic,
flanking them to force them into the hole.
In other words, a fucking sandwich.
We'll push them from the inside
so that they come out and
catch them at the sewer bend.
They can't go back for cover.
We've got them in a mousetrap.
Now we have to find Inspector Murillo
and her little boyfriend.
Lieutenant.
Come on, go, go!
-Squadron!
-Sir!
Ready?
Yes, sir!
Everyone moving the money.
-We need to get out!
-Very well.
Assault units are
getting ready to come in.
We'll get on it.
We're already in.
Son of a bitch!
Helsinki this won't be the last
you hear from me, I swear!
When I get out
I'll sue the shit out of you,
for cruelty, torture
and crimes against humanity, motherfucker!
Little Arturo,
we're going to the tunnel.
Your very important mission. Yes?
It was fake.
Stand up.
Slowly.
Turn around!
Now you're coming to the station.
And don't fucking move
or this time I will shoot you.
You know why?
Because I've gone for a little walk
in the countryside
and I've had time to think and I regret
not shooting the biggest son of a bitch
that I ever came across in my life.
Raquel, please.
I'm not killing you
because I want you 30 years in prison.
And there,
you get to ask whoever the fuck you want
what he's wearing.
Don't move.
Don't move!
Stay where you are!
MOSCOW. AGUSTIN RAMOS
DOS HERMANAS. MAY 1, 1964
He was born on Labor Day.
On every birthday since he started
working at the mine he said
all the arrangements
were made for his party.
A good picket.
And the rubber bullets were his gifts.
This year it was real bullets.
I guess if you're born on the wrong side,
you die on the wrong side.
What's your name?
-No, Monica.
-I need to know your name.
Because I'm leaving here with you.
Through the back door,
the tunnel, or holding a machine gun.
But I don't want to be away from you.
And if I have to learn to shoot,
I will.
Besides...
this child...
this child is going to need a father.
Come on, tell me your name.
Ricardo.
This is the Underground Unit,
making our way down the sewers.
-What's that noise?
-Stay still.
It’s the metro. Line 6.
It's right above us.
Proceeding.
Come on, people! Keep it up!
Let's make sure the magic lasts
until the very end!
In there, we'll have satellite
radio and video signal
in order to avoid frequency jammers.
The bomb squad
will open a gap in the cargo door.
300 grams of thermite explosive.
You know what that means.
So Lobo, Ruiz,
you'll provide cover fire, if necessary.
The rest of us will enter in line,
no one stays behind.
Come on, come on, come on!
Gentlemen,
there's going to be a ruckus in there,
so we'll have to be united.
Together!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
The only instructions
are not to open fire if they wear a mask.
Of course, we will open fire
in response to anyone shooting at us.
The only instructions
are that there's no order for any of them
to come out alive.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
We're ready, so let's go get them!
Go, go, go!
Rio,
-Rio, are you there?
-Yes, Professor.
-I encrypted the frequency.
-How long can it take to decode it?
Two hours.
Perfect.
Set the explosive charges.
Pass the intercom to Berlin.
Right away.
Hey.
Come, please.
What's the matter?
I don't feel well.
What's wrong?
I feel pain in my chest.
May be an anxiety attack.
Do you want a tranquilizer?
It would have been easier for me too
if none of this had happened.
It was the only
actual crack
in an otherwise perfect plan.
A plan no longer perfect. You know why?
Because even if this all goes well...
Even if it all goes well, I'll be...
I'll be fucked.
Because I won't ever see you again.
You think it was in my plans
to fall in love
with the inspector?
I don't want to hear more.
You don't want to hear?
Why don’t you want to hear, Raquel?
Because I'm a bad guy?
You've been taught
to see good and bad guys.
But what we're doing
is okay to you when other people do it.
In the year 2011,
the European Central Bank made 171
billion euros out of nowhere.
Just like we're doing.
Only bigger.
185 billion in 2012.
145 billion euros in the 2013.
Do you know where all that money went?
To the banks.
Directly from the factory
to the pockets of the rich.
Did anyone call
the European Central Bank a thief?
No.
"Liquidity injections",
they called it.
And they pulled it out of nowhere, Raquel.
Out of nowhere.
What's this?
This is nothing, Raquel. Paper.
It's paper, you see?
It's paper.
I'm making a liquidity injection,
but not for the banks.
I'm doing it here,
in the real economy.
With this group of...
of losers, which is what we are, Raquel.
To get away from it all.
Don't you want to get away?
Angel is calling you.
Does this mean he woke up?
If he's awake, they're going to...
He'll talk and they will be here
in five minutes.
Okay,
I'm going to answer it.
And you'll speak.
But no nonsense, please.
Please.
You'll answer it
and you're going to verify
if he's awake, okay?
Please.
No, no! Don't answer it.
Don't answer it.
My phone is tapped.
Do you have another one?
Who is it?
Raquel.
Raquel Murillo.
Angel woke up.
He didn't want us to call anyone
before he talked to you.
I'll put him on.
Raquel,
how are you?
Don't worry,
come on.
Take it easy.
Come on, Raquel.
-How are you?
-Me?
So high I can't even feel my ass.
Listen,
I saw on the TV that you've...
you've been replaced in the investigation.
Yes.
Don't tell anyone I woke up, okay?
I need you to come see me first.
Okay.
Colonel, we've picked up a phone call
to Murillo's number.
But there was no communication.
Locate the call immediately.
Get the owner and the antenna.
Now.
You have to let me go talk to Angel.
If I don't go, in 15 minutes
he'll tell the police where you are.
And I can stop him.
-It's your only chance...
-Please.
It's about your perfect plan
not falling apart.
Please, let me think.
There's nothing to think about.
Sergio.
I'm with you.
A minute ago you were screaming
and biting me like an animal.
Can I trust you?
Come.
Come closer.
Subtitle translation by Andrés M.