(wind whooshing)
(high-pitched ringing)
(vehicles passing)
(grunts)
(exhales)
HOSTESS:
Hi.
Welcome to Endless Pasta Week
at Tony Cicero's.
Where the fuck am I?
You're at Tony Cicero's.
No, no.
What fucking city am I in?
Uh, Fort Wayne.
The fuck?
You got a bit of paper,
something I can write with?
A pen, anything.
(muttering):
Ah, fuck it.
(indistinct chatter)
NEWS ANCHOR:
Yesterday, it closed
at ten percent below
its record high,
set last month.
Federal authorities have
initiated a multistate manhunt
for William Butcher
for allegedly murdering
Vought Vice President
Madelyn Stillwell
as well as endangering
her infant son, Theodore.
Law enforcement officials
have set up a tip line
and are urging anyone
with information
regarding the suspect's
whereabouts to come forward.
Police are also asking...
(sniffles)
("Indé-Structible" by Guizmo
playing)
"Boy, girl."
I am sorry.
I do not understand.
All right, I'm off.
-HUGHIE: Where you going?
-Going to meet a contact.
Who?
Someone who can help us find
this Supe terrorist cunt.
Who is the contact?
What is their actual name?
-You'll love it.
-No, I won't.
I won't love it.
I never love it.
I never fucking love it!
Noted.
Not a word from him.
He left us for dead, and now
it's like nothing happened?
You're right.
I am sorry.
Sorry that I trusted this lot
was smart enough
to save themselves like they've
done a hundred times before.
Okay, well, where you been?
Well, technically,
I called him back.
He blew up Madelyn Stillwell.
I told you. She was already dead
when I blew her up.
Oh. Great. Cool.
Totally. We're just gonna
pretend like this is normal?
Like we're fucking lemmings?
Well, who else
they gonna follow?
Right.
(birds chirping)
(grunts)
(laughs softly)
Hey. You know, my dad,
he had a ball
from the '56 World Series.
Signed by Don Larsen himself.
Pitched a no-hitter in Game 5.
Really?
Pretty cool, huh?
Ooh. That's okay. Uh...
You'll, uh,
you'll get the next one.
-Yeah.
-Yeah!
RYAN:
Yeah, I'll get the next one.
(sighs)
Okay.
Ryan. Use your powers.
What do you mean?
RYAN:
Huh.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can. You're my son.
Has anyone told you
what you're capable of?
No.
Well, then it's about time
you found out.
BECCA:
Hey, Ryan? Come on.
Math time, buddy.
Chapters 12 and 13
in your workbook.
(exhales)
Yeah.
Math, yeah. Sorry, I forgot.
BECCA:
It's your favorite.
Be in in a minute, okay?
HOMELANDER:
You know, when I was his age,
I was breaking
the sound barrier.
He can't even throw a fastball.
We thought it was best
that he have
as ordinary
of a childhood as possible.
We?
-Who's we?
-Look,
I just want my kid to be normal.
Well, then,
it's a good thing I'm here.
'Cause my son
is the furthest fucking thing
on this planet
to a normal little boy.
How long are you planning
on staying?
Becca, we had a deal.
A deal that is alive and well
and-and running around
as free as a goddam bird.
So, let's just
try and be civil, shall we?
Did I get 'em right?
There's...
There's no correct
or incorrect answer.
Oh.
What is missing here?
DEEP:
Uh...
Deep, how do you expect to be
welcomed back into The Seven
if you can't be honest
with yourself?
Carol, if I'm being honest,
I don't know
what the fuck you want from me.
(door closes)
Hey, guys.
How's it going?
Can I have a word?
I don't mean to be negative,
but his operating perspective
is functionally nonexistent.
(whispering): I don't think
there's a path here.
Leave it to me.
(tea kettle whistling)
EAGLE:
See, you're just inhibited
by suppressive energy,
that's it.
Just got to realign things.
What is it? Shrooms?
Last time I did shrooms was
at a Goo Goo Dolls concert
with some poli sci chick
from Oberlin.
I guess I'd call it more
of a gateway.
(coughs sharply, chuckles)
Wait.
Are you not gonna drink any?
No. Deep, this is your journey.
STARLIGHT:
Who's revving up the girl power
in The Seven?
Keep watching, WDCS,
Cleveland's first
and best source for local news.
MAN:
Quiet, please.
Going again. On the bell.
-(bell rings)
-MAN 2: Rolling.
Where should I start?
Are you ready
to meet the newest member
of The Seven?
See it here first, WFAK.
KMFT. WDCS.
-WOMAN: Cut!
-(bell rings)
-Quiet please. Still rolling.
She's the newest member
of The Seven,
and she's taking America
by storm.
From Portland to Seattle.
Watch what comes next, KMFT.
ASHLEY:
Amazing.
Do you need to take a break,
or can we power
through the rest?
Let's just power through.
-(camera shutters clicking)
-(cheering, indistinct chatter)
WOMAN:
Hey, over here!
Give us a shot! Gorgeous!
-(camera shutters clicking)
-Starlight! Oh!
-Stormfront, over here!
-Stormfront, show us
what you got!
-We're ready!
-(reporters oohing)
-(whooping and cheering)
-(laughs)
ASHLEY:
Okay, ladies,
we have a big day--
domestic outlets until noon,
ten minutes each,
foreign until 2:00.
Round tables until 4:00,
print one-on-ones until 6:00.
Jesus,
if she vibrates any faster,
-that stick up her ass
is gonna explode.
-(laughs)
-(phone buzzing)
-We really should
be powering through.
We don't have time.
Hello?
What?
When?
Okay. Thank you.
ASHLEY:
We're going positive,
we're going female,
thoughtful but upbeat.
-Where... What?
-MAEVE: I gotta go.
-What? No.
-I'm sorry. Family emergency.
-Is everything okay?
-Maeve,
we've never had three women
in The Seven before.
This is a moment. Girls get it
done. You are not...!
I have a family emergency, too.
PASTOR:
A reading
from the Book of Revelations.
"And God shall wipe away
all the tears from their eyes,
and there will be
no more death."
Today, we say goodbye
to Susan Raynor.
For though her body rests, her
soul lives on for all eternity.
And one day,
you will think of Susan
with joy as well as sadness.
They are two sides of a coin
you will carry forever.
And you are blessed
to have your family
and your friends
to help you carry it.
In the name of Christ. Amen.
(two beeps)
(sighs)
You think you can surprise me?
I literally taught you this one.
Hello, Grace.
You promised
I'd never see you again.
I promised...
not to come to your house again.
A subtle
but important distinction.
I assume
you sent the edible arrangement?
Deluxe Bereavement Bouquet
with white chocolate-dipped
pineapple doves.
Raynor would have loved that.
Oi, where you going?
There are about
two dozen federal officers
in the church next door.
I'm gonna turn you in for the
murder of Madelyn Stillwell.
Oh, come off it, Grace.
You really think I done that?
You really want me
to answer that?
Grace, I know who killed Raynor!
Who?
Okay, well, uh,
I don't specifically,
technically have the answer to
that, but I know how to get it.
We think Vought killed her for
getting too close to something.
Getting too close to what?
Something to do
with a Supe terrorist
smuggled into Jersey
a couple of nights ago,
-and that is where we start.
-(laughing): Honestly,
it's like asking a cockroach
to not be a cockroach.
It's just your nature.
I know what she meant to you,
all right?
We find this terrorist,
and we're one step closer
to finding out who offed her.
I'm not getting back in.
And if I were, which I'm not,
it sure as shit wouldn't be
for you.
Oh, I ain't asking you
all the way back in.
Just dip in a little toe, yeah?
Maybe two.
Not for me. For Raynor.
You never gave a shit
about Susan.
You're only here
because you're desperate,
fucked, and you want something.
All right, fuck it.
Grace? Grace!
Grace, wait, wait, wait. Wait.
I'll level with you, okay?
(exhales)
Just hear me out.
(panting)
(singing along): ♪ I just want
you to know who I am ♪
-♪ I just want... ♪
-MALE VOICE (muffled): Hey.
♪ To know who I am ♪
♪ I just want you
to know who I am ♪
-Hey.
-♪ I just want you... ♪
(music stops)
Eagle?
-Hey!
-(gasps)
In here. Open up.
(breathing heavily)
Bro, we got to talk.
-No, you got to look at us.
-(quietly): No.
Look at us!
(breathing deeply)
(quietly):
Okay.
Remember Melissa Dabrowski,
the kindergarten teacher
you fingerbanged backstage
at the VH1 Educator Awards?
So what?
You were supposed to present her
with Teacher of the Year,
but you bailed while she was
pulling her panties back on.
Yeah, because she laughed at me.
Okay, bullshit.
She just put her hands
on your chest.
You never even unzipped
your suit.
She would have laughed.
Because that's what you do.
You imagine women will laugh at
us, so you humiliate them first.
No, that's-that's not true.
You can't accept your own body,
so you violate theirs.
(stammers)
Shut the fuck up.
(panting)
Hey. Hey. Hey.
(chuckles)
-You can't swim from us forever!
-Let me out!
You shut the fuck up,
you ugly pieces of shit.
I have nothing else
to say to you.
-We won't let you shut us up
anymore, Kevin!
-(whimpering)
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Let me out, man.
Just let me out!
-Eagle!
-(door rattling)
-Let me out, man!
-(slams against door)
Ride it, brother.
(siren wails in distance)
(sighs)
What are you doing here?
Apparently, your work...
still has "Maggie Shaw"
as your emergency contact.
Ah, shit. Sorry.
That's okay.
Where else would I score
this sweet jelly?
(Elena laughs)
I thought it was bad unagi.
Turns out,
my appendix was about to burst.
Well, there are easier ways
to get my attention.
I kept thinking you'd call.
Yeah. Me, too.
-You want me to call your mom?
-(laughs)
Definitely not.
(groans)
Someone else,
like a girlfriend, or...?
Seriously, thanks for coming,
but I'm sure you have
more important places to be.
Hey, you could die
from something like this.
But I didn't, so I guess
you don't need to save me.
Yeah, well, I still want
to see the doctor.
Maeve, I'm fine, I promise.
(Elena sighs)
You know, watching Botched
doesn't make you
-a fucking medical expert.
-(scoffs)
I'll wait a while
and just see, okay?
Can we get this middle chair out
of here, please?
Yeah. Somebody?
Thank you. Thank you.
Can we get the two on the side
just smushed together?
We lost one of them.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: Okay,
resetting; one background.
-All right, people,
quiet on the set.
-Rolling.
Well, Stormfront,
congrats on The Seven.
Are you as excited to be here
as I am?
I don't know!
I don't think so!
(chuckles)
Can you tell us a little
about how girls get it done?
REPORTER 3:
...girls get it done?
REPORTER 4:
REPORTER 5:
...girls get it done?
Let's dish boys.
Starlight, single?
Or, uh, spoken for?
Uh, single, single.
Single.
Uh, single.
Definitely single.
(chuckles)
Tell us how fun it is
to have all this girl power.
-(laughs)
-REPORTER 1:
Can you repeat that but say
"strong is the new pretty"
right at the end?
Do girls make better heroes?
Do girls make better heroes
than boys?
Do girls make better heroes?
Look, uh, no offense.
I-I get you have
your talking points,
but why does it matter whether
heroes have a dick or a vag?
(chuckles): I mean, shouldn't we
all just, you know, be competent
at our jobs?
I-I don't think
girls do anything better.
I think chicks and dicks
are in it together.
(phone buzzing)
Oh, that's me.
(scoffs)
(chuckles):
Sorry, Ashy.
Vought won't let me have pockets
in this thing.
You can see every crease
in my ass.
You can practically see
up Starlight's uterus.
You want to talk
about girl power,
let's talk
about getting some pockets.
(laughs)
Starlight,
your teammate, A-Train,
has been out of the public eye.
-Mm-hmm.
-Vought recently revealed
that he was on a top secret
mission in Kandahar.
Are you worried about him?
(clears throat)
Yeah, of course.
I pray for him every night.
(inhales)
America really is lucky
to have such a brave hero
fighting for them.
What if I told you
he's right behind you?
-(sonic boom)
-Here comes
the A-Train!
What's up?
-Wow.
-All right.
-Yeah. (chuckling)
-(forced chuckling)
-Wow, welcome back.
-Thanks.
Thank you. Mmm.
Stormfront, you know,
it is such an honor to meet you.
-Oh.
-I'm a huge fan.
-Feeling's mutual.
-Don't get up. Yeah, relax.
Relax for a second. Um,
maybe get a chair or something.
♪ ♪
(quietly):
This is crazy.
♪ 30 hitters on my side ♪
♪ Got a little mama in my ride ♪
♪ Then we'll shoot, then
we'll cry, then we'll swoop ♪
♪ Then we'll fly, see the truth,
tell no lies... ♪
STARLIGHT:
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Fan-fucking-tastic.
-That's great.
-(chuckles)
We were really worried
about you.
(plucking strings)
-Do you play?
-(chuckles softly)
Nope.
This is Prince's guitar
from Purple Rain.
When I woke up,
I was just like,
"Fuck it.
I want that shit."
(chuckles)
Shit like what I went through
really gives you
some perspective.
You know?
Totally.
They told me you came by my room
every day to pray for me.
Thank you.
Mm. You're so welcome.
Yeah, I-I think
that prayer really does help.
Anyway...
Mm-hmm.
You should know
that everyone thinks it was
a really good idea
that you called me in
for backup that night.
I mean, what would've happened
if I hadn't been there
to give you CPR?
-(exhales)
-(chuckles)
-That's good to know.
-Mm.
(chuckles softly)
How does everyone feel
about you helping
your traitor fucking boyfriend
escape?
Or maybe you didn't mention
that part.
(chuckles)
Uh, s-- Mm.
Who did you mention
that part to?
♪ ♪
("You're Only Human"
by Billy Joel playing)
♪ You're having a hard time and
lately you don't feel so good ♪
(sighs)
♪ You're getting
a bad reputation ♪
♪ In your neighborhood... ♪
Just had a meeting
with the colonel.
Colonel Mallory?
Y-You saw her?
That's right, Frenchie.
She's gonna help us.
We get her the Supe terrorist,
she's gonna get the CIA
to scrub our records clean,
get the Old Bill off our asses,
get you back to your girls.
HUGHIE:
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
734 Central Ave.,
Newark.
What does that mean?
That's the address she gave me.
It's linked
to the blind bank account
that smuggled
that Supe cunt stateside.
And I'll bet you he's there.
Oh, my Lord.
Ain't you twats lucky
that I showed up, eh?
(exhales)
(sighs)
Melissa Dabrowski was more
than just another fingerbang,
-you know?
-No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
It's not fucking happening.
It's not fucking real.
Ah, the way she looked at you.
She was sweet, smart.
Girl like that,
you could've been happy.
(exhales)
You deserve to be loved.
(sighs)
Don't fuck with me.
You deserve to be loved, Kevin.
But that starts with you.
Don't fuck with me.
Take a look.
A real look.
Go on.
(breathing heavily)
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm the ugly one.
No.
Yes.
On the inside.
You just don't see what I see.
♪ You are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
(cries)
No.
♪ To me ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
I'm not.
♪ You're everything
I hoped for ♪
♪ You're everything I need ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
-♪ To me ♪
(sniffles, shudders)
♪ Can't ♪
♪ Can't you ♪
♪ See...? ♪
DEEP and GILLS:
♪ You're ♪
♪ Everything I hoped for ♪
♪ Everything I need ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ So ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
(sighs)
So, in short, do not waste
your hard-earned cash
on this shitty,
big-titted hunk of plastic
that'll probably end up
in a manatee's belly
when your kid chucks it
in the garbage.
Hey. Um...
I just got to say,
I really like everything that
you've been saying about Vought.
Yeah, okay, cool.
No, I mean...
I agree with you.
You wearing a wire or something?
What? What does that have to...
Look, I mean this
in the nicest possible way,
but I don't need
some fucking Vought Spy Barbie
sniffing around to see
whether I'm a team player.
What? That is
not at all what I am.
I used to be a fan.
But look at you.
You're like the Voughtiest
Vought in all Vought.
I think, uh, cyclops dude's
trying to get your attention.
(quietly):
Fuck.
What happened to your eye?
Oh, Vought is testing
a new volumizing
dry shampoo for eye irritation.
As if you give a fuck.
Here.
I brought you a sample.
Are you kidding me?
I can't take this right now.
I can't get away
from this press junket.
I literally have no pockets.
You wanted the V, here it is.
If you threaten me again,
I'm gonna make sure
that everyone knows
that you're the one who took it.
Uh...
-A-TRAIN: You're tight
with Gecko?
-Hey.
Yeah, it--
From Capes for Christ,
back in the day. Yeah.
Yeah.
What'd you just put
in your boot?
What? Nothing.
'Cause it looked like you
just put something in your boot.
Why don't you tell me
what's in my boot?
(exhales)
Maybe... you shouldn't
be hitting the Cristal
with your buddies quite so soon.
Come on.
Let's finish dick-tickling
these half-wits
so we can finally do
our real job.
Shall we?
BECCA:
All right, kiddo.
Here we are.
Have a great lesson.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll be back in an hour.
I'm gonna go have coffee
with Ms. Bird.
Yeah. Um, thanks.
Bye!
MRS. CROWDER:
Hi, Ryan, how are you?
(engine revving)
♪ ♪
(inhales deeply)
(exhales)
(gulps)
(inhales)
♪ ♪
(seat belt clicks)
Open the door.
Open the fucking door!
Please get back inside the car.
I want to talk to Dr. Park.
Go back inside the car.
Goddamn it, Dr. Park!
Now!
(phone rings)
-PARK: Hey, Becca.
-What the fuck is going on?
I understand this is upsetting.
I was told I would never have
to see him ever again,
that he would never know
about Ryan or me.
That was the deal.
Homelander is quite upset
that this information
was concealed from him.
Corporate has made a decision
not to antagonize him further.
(shuddering)
You need to make him leave.
Because if you don't,
I'm gonna take Ryan
and I'm gonna run,
and you'll never fucking find us
ever again.
I think we both know
that that's not possible.
You have to protect us.
You have...
You have to move us, please.
I'm sorry.
Now that he knows,
there's just no putting the
toothpaste back in the tube.
You should probably
be getting back.
Piano lessons are almost done.
Just keep him calm.
Our best guess--
he'll get bored and move on.
You-you don't know that.
You don't.
Do I get to keep this?
MAEVE:
Maybe.
What will you trade me for it?
I will let you
take me out to dinner.
Right.
I forgot.
We'll need to order in,
keep it low-pro.
Maeve, what are you doing here
if nothing has changed?
(laughs):
Oh, Christ.
The last thing that woman needs
is another nose job.
Okay. We've done
this dance, thanks.
-Elena...
-It's time to go.
(takes deep breath)
Homelander and I went
to this Oscar party
for 12 Years a Slave.
There was this producer,
he swapped place cards
so he could sit next to me.
And he chatted me up all night.
Two days later,
there's a fire in his office.
They found his head
in one room...
and his torso in another.
What are you saying?
I don't want him
to do that to you.
Who?
Homelander?
You think Homelander did that?
The things...
that I've watched him do...
...the things
that he made me do...
If he ever finds out
about you...
(takes deep breath)
Why are you telling me this now?
I don't want you
to hate me anymore.
Cool.
-Thank you.
-(chuckles)
You're welcome.
It's crazy you don't have one
already, actually.
I don't really have anyone
to call, though.
(sighs)
You could call me.
You know, Ryan, um,
when I was your age, I didn't
have many friends either.
Mom says being lonely
makes you know yourself better.
Well...
that's not wrong, I suppose.
Can I tell you a secret?
Man-to-man, you know?
(sighs)
(chuckles)
My dad and I...
we never played catch in the
yard with a World Series ball.
Truth is...
I never had a dad.
Or a mom.
Wait, you... you didn't?
See, sometimes it's hard, Ryan,
being...
(sighs)
superior to every single
other person on the planet.
It's-it's... isolating.
And gods...
should not have to feel
that kind of...
yeah, pain.
Because that...
is what we are, Ryan.
You and me.
We're gods.
Son, we can do anything we want.
And no one can stop us.
Now, that..
that's a good feeling.
A really good feeling.
And now you...
and me...
can share it together.
I...
I-I should probably go
to bed now, you know?
Sure.
(pats Ryan)
I love you, son.
You know, you can say it back.
Um, I...
love you, too.
(sighs)
This is nice.
-Your turn, Mom.
-You need to leave.
Excuse me?
You need to get the fuck
out of my house.
What happens one day
when Ryan asks to go
to a baseball game,
swim in the ocean,
or eat at a Burger King?
How do you think he's gonna feel
when he finds out
that you've lied to him
his whole life?
You think he's gonna be happy
that you kept him
in this pretty prison?
Or...
do you think
he'll fucking despise you?
Hmm?
Let's go ask him.
Don't.
You were right.
I'm not gonna get bored
and move on.
I'm not going anywhere.
So feel free to tell Dr. Park
to go fuck himself.
How about some Jiffy Pop?
(departing footsteps)
Halothane shot.
I only got two of these.
BUTCHER:
Well, we better make it count.
FRENCHIE:
What if it doesn't work
on the terrorist inside?
Then we're
right and well fucked.
Are you okay?
♪ ♪
(grunts)
Shining Light Liberation Army?
The ones who kidnapped you.
You know this man?
What is going on?
Kimiko.
(breath trembling)
(sniffles)
(exhales)
Mouse.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
FRENCHIE:
Boy...
and girl.
Her brother.
That's what she
was trying to tell me.
(panting)
(whispers): Butcher,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's her brother.
♪ ♪
Kimiko!
Wait!
Hey.
You don't know me.
I'm not a sellout.
Oh, okay, cool.
Congratulations.
(chuckles)
Oh, come on,
why do you care what I think?
Maybe...
I want to say everything
that you're saying about Vought.
Maybe I think Vought's...
What? What's Vought?
Oh, my God, everyone is
so fucking stage-managed.
Life isn't actually
a PR strategy.
You can say what you think.
What if it's not safe?
You are literally bulletproof.
What the fuck is gonna happen?
Okay.
Who's the greatest superhero
of all time?
Hmm, Homelander?
No. Pippi Longstocking.
Pippi Longstocking.
She's a nine-year-old girl.
Lived in a house all by herself.
Pet monkey. Could lift
a horse with one hand.
You-you haven't read
Pippi Longstocking?
I guess not.
Hmm.
Okay, well, uh, I used to dress
as her every Halloween,
and all the girls dressed
like Disney sluts
would make fun of me,
and you know what I thought?
I thought, "Who fucking cares?"
Pippi didn't care.
She never cared
about being polite.
Or cute.
Look.
Fuck this world
for confusing nice with good.
Be a bitch if you want.
Be whatever.
Just drop the mask
once in a while.
Feels good.
You can finally breathe.
Oh, and if someone sticks
a dick in your mouth,
bite it off.
Pippi Longstocking
would bite a "D."
That's for damn sure.
FRENCHIE:
Butcher!
Hold on, mon ami.
-Give me your hand.
-Okay.
No. No, Butcher! No!
-Easy, easy, Butcher!
-HUGHIE: The CIA would have
locked him up
in some black box forever,
-and she never would have seen
her brother again.
-Easy.
Both of you, please, not now.
Right.
You...
fuck...
off.
The rest of you, with me.
(objects clattering)
Well, come on, don't piss about.
We ain't got all night.
(weapon cocking)
(panting)
Fuck you waiting for?
Are you telling me
that her family
is worth more to you
than you seeing your own?
No, I'm not.
But Kimiko is one of us.
I'll find another way.
I suppose you agree, don't you?
Since your tongue
is halfway up her ass.
Jesus. It's like
Hughie's infected you both
with a raging case of vagina.
Becca's alive.
What?
She's alive. Vought's
holding her captive somewhere.
-Butcher, if you...
-No.
I'm not stark raving, all right?
I fucking saw her.
She had a little boy
with her. Uh...
The spitting image
of Homelander.
I thought he just wanted
to humiliate me,
show me what he'd done
to my girl
before he gave me the good news.
Then I woke up
three hours later
in a Tony fucking Cicero's.
God knows why.
I got to find her,
and I got to get her
the fuck out of there.
And I need your help to do it.
Are you fucking with us?
I find the terrorist
for Mallory,
she finds Becca for me.
That's the deal I made.
I know what I done t-to you.
All right?
And by rights,
you should tell me to fuck off.
But still...
I'm asking.
When you...
When you disappeared
that night...
I'm sorry.
We were supposed to watch out
for each other
and then you were gone.
Shining Light sent me here.
Put the needle in my spine
and filled me full
of the blue poison.
I should have found you.
No. I'm the big sister. I should
have come back for you, but...
...they made me into...
...a monster.
(chuckles, sniffles)
If that's true,
we're both monsters now.
Did it hurt?
I wanted to die.
Me too.
They had one dose left
and they knew it worked on you
so they figured
it would work on me.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
(sniffles)
(Female crying)
(sighs)
(cabinet opens)
(sonic boom)
Who, uh, who we sexting?
What... What are you doing
in here? Get out.
-Uh, I d... Okay.
-(case unzipping)
Look, you got me.
I'm having a heavy flow day.
It's, uh...
What are you doing with this?
This is not how it looks.
Okay? It's just
a misunderstanding.
Homelander
should have charred your ass
as soon as he found out
that you were fucking Hughie.
Hughie saved your life.
We both did.
Your mistake.
Okay, if you just give me
a minute, I can explain.
You know, I just want you
to think about me
when you're getting the skin
peeled off your face, bitch.
You're not gonna
tell anyone anything.
Who says that I haven't already?
'Cause then I'd already be dead.
You're not gonna do shit.
Why's that?
'Cause you killed
your fucking girlfriend.
That's what you told Hughie,
right? That you killed Popclaw?
You can't prove anything.
Did she suffer?
Did you look
into her big, sad eyes
while you did it?
Fuck you.
Yeah, see, I looked
at the Vought forensics report,
and...
(exhales)
Wow.
All those needles
jammed into her arm
at the same time?
I mean, one of them
actually shattered the bone.
Did you know that? Would someone
really do that to themselves?
I mean, doesn't look
like an accident to me.
I mean,
Vought's happy to bury it,
but, you know, say, if...
Sports Illustrated found out...
If you do that,
I'm gonna take you down
right with me.
And then we'll both be dead.
(scoffs)
Go ahead.
Fucking try it.
I don't give a shit.
(door closes)
(sighs)
These people you were with...
They keep me safe.
They'll keep you safe too.
Or we can go home.
Back to the village.
There is no village anymore.
What?
They came for us.
Who?
The Americans.
This hero came shrieking
out of the sky like a demon.
Destroyed the camp. And all
the villages around it, too.
There were bodies everywhere.
Everyone's gone.
Then we'll go somewhere else.
Back to Japan.
Maybe grandma and grandpa
are still alive.
You don't care?
That the Superhero split
an old woman in half?
That the entire school caved in
with the kids inside?
That babies burned alive
in their cribs
when the propane tanks exploded?
I never wanted this.
But they were right all along.
Shining Light is full of shit!
Shining Light fights injustice.
They stand up for people
without a voice.
They murdered our parents!
This country is an enemy
to the whole world now.
We need to fight back.
Fight with me!
You're the boy who nursed
every mouse who lost its mother.
That was a long time ago.
You're still my brother.
Then... you know
I have to do this.
♪ ♪
(grunts)
(panting)
(grunting)
(Kenji breathing weakly)
(tires screeching)
Are you all right?
Mon coeur!
Well, cheers, love.
At least someone's got
some sense around here.
♪ ♪
(grunts, exhales)
You come between me
and my missus again,
I'll fucking kill you.
(exhales)
(van door closes)
(grunts)
("Psycho Killer"
by Talking Heads playing)
MOTHER'S MILK:
Hey, kid.
Coming?
♪ I can't seem
to face up to the facts ♪
♪ I'm tense and nervous,
and I can't relax ♪
♪ I can't sleep
'cause my bed's on fire ♪
♪ Don't touch me,
I'm a real live wire ♪
♪ Psycho killer ♪
♪ Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa,
fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run ♪
♪ Run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Psycho killer ♪
♪ Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa,
fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You start a conversation,
you can't even finish it ♪
♪ You're talking a lot ♪
♪ But you're not
saying anything ♪
♪ When I have nothing to say,
my lips are sealed ♪
♪ Say something once,
why say it again? ♪
♪ Psycho killer ♪
♪ Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa,
fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Psycho killer ♪
♪ Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa,
fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh. ♪