REPORTER: Federal authorities
have initiated
a manhunt for William Butcher.
SUSAN: It's Vought.
It's a fucking coup
from the inside.
I know who killed Raynor.
Something to do with
the Supe terrorist
smuggled into Jersey.
Her brother.
I just want me wife back.
MALLORY:
Bring Langley the terrorist
and you'll have her.
BECCA:
I was told he would never know
about Ryan or me.
That was the deal.
You need to make him leave.
Because if you don't,
I'm gonna take Ryan
and I'm gonna run.
Superheroes are not born,
but made,
via Compound V.
We got a Supe terrorist
below deck
and shit could go sideways
just like...
(whale singing)
Ah, fucking diabolical!
(screams)
(screaming)
HOMELANDER:
I said he was mine.
STORMFRONT:
You snooze, you lose, Gramps.
REPORTER:
Our newest hero,
Stormfront,
stopped the terrorist
before he could take
more innocent lives.
Communication is everything.
Steve and I had been
dating for two years
when he asked me to marry him.
At the rehearsal dinner,
my dad said
we should look into
a 529 account for our kids.
Steve laughed
and said that was nuts
and that we were
never having kids.
(laughs)
Which was, um, news to me.
Yeah. Long story short, um,
the caterer was totally cool
with everything,
but the Marriott did keep
our deposit on the banquet room.
So... Yeah.
Communication.
("Le temps" by Kaaris playing)
(clatters)
...details are still emerging
about the Supe terrorist
whose senseless attack
on an apartment building
left 59 people dead
and over 100 injured.
His name? Kenji Miyashiro,
a Japanese expatriate
living in the Philippines.
Miyashiro was radicalized
by the extremist group
Shining Light Liberation Army.
Witnesses who caught a glimpse
of the killer
described him as dead-eyed
and unemotional
as he rampaged through
the apartment building...
It wasn't your fault.
Many of the 59 victims
have not yet been identified...
Kimiko, look at me.
...to notify their families.
Look at me.
Investigators have
so far not disclosed
further details
about the attack,
but officials have announced
they will hold a press
conference later this week.
I-I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry. I was just...
(choking)
(panting)
NNC ANCHOR:
No one can debate
that New Yorkers
owe their lives
to the brave actions
taken by Stormfront.
Earlier today,
Stormfront made an appearance
at a New York City park.
STORMFRONT:
How many more people
have to die?
You guys, I have been shouting
up and down
the hallways at Vought,
and you know what they're doing
to stop another attack?
Jack (bleep).
Let's show Vought
what they have to do.
Tomorrow morning,
Vought Square.
(echoing): Be your own hero.
Make your voice heard.
I am counting on you
to show us the way.
Don't let me down.
MADELYN:
There you are.
I was beginning to worry.
(moans)
I've missed you...
...so much.
Are you thirsty?
(moaning softly)
(grunts)
My good boy.
(siren wailing in distance)
I ever tell you about
my recurring dream?
I'm on stage, alone,
at Carnegie Hall.
The audience is made up
of every poor bastard
who got killed
by the superheroes.
BUTCHER:
What are they doing?
Nothing. They're all
just watching me.
Waiting for me to do something.
We hit a dead end on Raynor.
I'm sorry.
Christ, I don't want
to hear sorry.
Sorry's not an option.
We can't have anonymous
skull-exploding assassins
walking around.
What if they hit
the speaker next?
Or the president?
BUTCHER:
Liberty?
You mentioned her before.
Second-tier Supe,
active in the '70s.
She was all over
Susan's private server.
Get Marvin to talk
to this Liberty.
Address on the back.
North Carolina.
BUTCHER:
All right.
We'll see what we can find.
MALLORY:
Wait.
I found Becca.
Or, at least,
our best guess where she is.
Vought facility,
armed to the teeth.
Won't be easy.
We had a deal.
I didn't come through.
Jesus, Butcher,
I'm just giving it to you.
It's my fault you stopped
searching for her.
I put a target
on Homelander's back
and pointed you right at him.
I didn't know Becca was still...
It'd be good to have
one less person
in that audience staring at me.
Hey!
See?
You get disrespected
over and over and over,
that's what happens.
I mean, how much shit
is he supposed to take?
-Everybody respects you.
-(exhales)
Fucking terrorist was my save,
not hers.
It was mine.
What? Now that-that media whore
i-is the face of The Seven?
-No, she's not. No, you are.
-Come on.
And it's not just her,
it-it's the entire team.
-No.
-Yes, it is.
It-It's a whole chain
of weak links.
(sighs)
I-It's very hard
not to take it personally.
-Oh, I know.
-(exhales)
I know.
(shushes)
(grunts)
I'll tell you one thing.
-You wouldn't put up
with this shit.
-Mm-mm.
One little raise of the eyebrow,
and you would've knocked them
-all back in line.
-Yeah.
God, I miss that about you.
You don't need me to do that.
The Seven is your team.
You nurtured them,
you watered and fed them.
-That's-- I did.
-Yes,
and if they can't
respect that or you,
well, it may be time
to tear out the weeds
and start all over again.
(grunting, groaning)
(gasps)
Change back. Change back!
I'm sorry! I can only hold
a shape for so long
before it really hurts.
Change the fuck back now,
Doppelganger!
(straining)
(Madelyn shouts, exhales)
Yeah, it's okay. Come here.
It's all good.
Oh, my little boy. Come on.
Okay.
(panting)
It's okay.
I love you.
You're the most powerful man
in the whole wide world.
And there's nothing
that you cannot do.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Storming an off-the-books
Vought compound alone?
Butcher, how is it possible that
you're dumber than you look?
-Mate, it's Becca.
-No shit.
But win or lose,
you ain't coming back.
Course I am.
That's bullshit.
Look, it's not like Vought's
gonna let us settle down
in Orlando.
We got to get gone
and stay gone.
What about us? Hmm?
We're the Spice Girls, right?
You're in charge now.
Mazel tov.
Motherfucker,
I don't want to be in charge.
Matter of fact,
I don't even want to be here.
I gave up my family for this.
For you.
When do I get them back?
You find this Liberty slag.
See what you can rumble.
You jump through a few hoops
for the colonel,
and she'll help you
the same way she helped me.
She always liked
you more, anyway.
And what about Frenchie?
He's been high as kite for days.
-He won't even notice I'm gone.
-Hmm.
And Hughie?
Kid's a weeper.
Don't want him to get snot
all over me jacket.
♪ ♪
(elevator bell chimes)
Hey, Homelander.
(low thudding)
Maeve begged me
to spare your life.
So I gave you a second chance,
and... you failed me.
What are you talking about?
No more lies.
(screams, grunting)
You go ahead and scream.
As much as you want.
What... what did I do?
I told you
to kill Hugh Campbell,
and you hesitated.
I-I said that we should
go to the police.
You disobeyed my orders
because you're with him.
Fuck you.
Hughie Campbell broke
my fucking heart.
Worse than anyone ever has.
And part of me wants to blast
his fucking face off,
so no, I'm not "with him."
But if you want to kill me
because I'm not a murderer
and I won't
straight-up execute someone,
then go ahead.
So, tell me,
am I lying?
(elevator bell chimes)
You're not lying.
Ooh.
Black Noir. Hi.
Would you like an Almond Joy?
Um, do you mean William Butcher?
-Okay.
-(tapping keyboard)
Well, he was definitely
on the yacht with the terrorist.
Some of his known accomplices
were, too.
We lost him
in these storm tunnels.
So, yeah.
There you go.
I'll keep you posted
when we find them.
Or I can look right now.
Just, uh, run
a facial recognition search.
(tapping keyboard)
Or you can join me.
(birds chirping)
-Hey.
-(chuckles)
-Thanks for coming.
-Hey.
-Oh, you're so bruised.
-Oh, no, it's fine. It's okay.
That was all me?
It's cool. Really.
I mean, you know,
chicks dig bruises.
You know, I was in...
When I was in fifth grade,
I took a tetherball to the face.
And Amy Burtenshaw,
she brought me
Jell-O Pudding Pops
for, like, two weeks.
I'm talking way too much.
I could've killed you.
But you didn't.
Um...
(clears throat)
I got your voice mail.
Oh, God. Can... Oh, God.
Can we just chalk that up
to a-a drunk dial?
I-I'm okay, really,
it's just, uh...
Do you just mind, you mind
-if we just
don't talk about it?
-Okay.
So, we got the Compound V
out there,
and Vought is still kicking,
so we risked our lives
just to make the world
way worse.
Yeah, but no, no, no.
That's not true.
I mean, you know,
these things, they...
Look, Annie, they take time.
(sighs)
How much time?
(phone ringing)
Just...
Sorry, just give me one second.
Um... Hey, M.M.
Raleigh? Like, the one
in North Carolina?
Yeah, okay, okay.
Jesus, I was just asking.
Um, yeah. Yeah.
Um, just pick me up
at, like, 81st
and-and Central Park West.
Okay, okay, all right.
Um, I have to go.
What's going on?
Can I call you later?
(sniffs)
Are you just gonna...
hang out?
Here?
Yeah, I...
I just... I can't go back
to the Tower right now.
Why? What happened?
I can't...
(crying):
I can't do this anymore.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Are you fucking insane?
She can't come with us,
Hughie. She's chipped.
So, I have a second cousin
who lives around there.
I could tell Vought
that I'm going to visit.
HUGHIE:
And we'd be out of the city,
away from the cameras.
I mean, no one would see us.
No. Even her standing here
is dangerous.
Maybe he's right. I...
(sighs)
This is a bad idea.
If we're gonna go knock
on some Supe's door,
don't you think it makes
a little bit of sense
for us to have one of our own?
(quietly):
Look, she's in rough shape.
She needs this.
You mean you need this?
Hey. How you doing? Cool.
-What's up, man?
-(elevator bell chimes)
(quietly):
Oh, fuck!
Don't bullshit me,
-Ashley.
-Shockwave is just here
to talk about Vought for Tots.
I swear to God.
What the fuck is
Vought for Tots?
It's a new fitness outreach
for toddlers.
Apparently,
they're getting obese.
Well, shit, I fucking love
fat kids. Use me.
Oh, good, you're here.
You tell him yet?
Tell me what?
I thought we were gonna have
a strategy meeting.
A-Train, you're out.
Out of what?
Out of The Seven.
You did great, but we're going
in a different direction, so...
you're out.
What the fuck?
You just said
everything was fine.
You're gonna have a whole year
of parades.
Tribute concerts.
You're gonna hit
the talk show circuit.
You're-you're gonna have
your own reality show
on Vought+.
The outpouring of love
and gratitude
is gonna be off the charts.
Oh, this is bullshit!
You used to get
my fucking coffee!
Oh, fuck this. I'm not going.
A-Train... you can't run.
Yes, I can run.
-I just... I-I just...
-Buddy?
(quietly): You think I don't
know what's been going on?
It's your heart.
I doubt you're even cracking
the top 20 anymore,
and that makes The Seven--
me-- look pretty ridiculous.
I do want you to know, though,
this was really hard for me.
Okay?
It's nothing personal.
Uh, we'll always be friends
and, uh...
(sighs)
Et cetera.
Attaboy.
(door opens, closes)
Does anyone mind
if I put on some music?
Yeah.
-STARLIGHT:
♪ Defended by our heroes ♪
-Oh, God.
-♪ You stood among the best... ♪
-You have a really good voice.
(chuckling): You can do that,
like, wavering thing
they do on American Idol.
-Vibrato.
-(changing stations)
-STARLIGHT: ♪ And thanks... ♪
-You've got to be kidding me.
-No. No.
-♪ From the stars. ♪
♪ It was always burning since
the world's been turning ♪
There it is. Yep.
♪ We didn't start the fire ♪
♪ No, we didn't light it,
but we tried to fight it ♪
♪ Birth control, Ho Chi Minh,
Richard Nixon back again ♪
♪ Moon shot, Woodstock,
Watergate, punk rock ♪
♪ Begin, Reagan, Palestine ♪
♪ Terror on the airline ♪
♪ Ayatollah's in Iran ♪
♪ Russians in Afghanistan ♪
♪ Wheel of Fortune, Sally Ride ♪
♪ Heavy metal suicide ♪
♪ Foreign debts, homeless vets,
AIDS, crack, Bernie Goetz ♪
♪ Hypodermics on the shores,
China's under martial law ♪
♪ Rock and roller cola wars,
I can't take it anymore. ♪
Hey, hey!
This ain't no little Vegas
road trip, okay?
Y'all ain't on no date, either.
Just... chill.
I'm not your goddamn chaperone.
(scoffs)
CASSANDRA:
They say if you love someone,
you should set them free.
But that seems crazy to me,
because if you love someone,
you will never let them go.
Never.
Have you heard of
the Lovers of Valdaro?
They were alive, like,
6,000 years ago,
and they were found
in this tomb in Italy.
These two skeletons with
their arms around each other.
That's love.
(laughs)
(softly):
Open up the door.
Bonjour.
You smell like a wet dog.
Oh, you want a drink?
Mm-mm.
Whoa.
Who says I'm alone, asshole?
So... are you gonna
tell me what's wrong?
Or you just gonna
stain my clean sheets
with your sweaty despair?
I tried to kiss her.
Kimiko?
Her brother died.
I wanted to
make her feel better.
You thought a kiss
would make her feel better
or you feel better?
She was in pain.
I wanted to help.
You always want to help.
So?
(exhales)
You think
that by saving her,
you can make amends
for all the people you hurt.
For those children
that Lamplighter burned.
-Okay.
-You don't know anything.
Look, she's not a kitten
up a tree.
Just leave her alone. Hmm?
Let her grieve.
What good does grieving
all alone ever do?
VNN ANCHOR:
And in our continuing coverage
of the recent revelations
over Compound V,
protesters all over
the Middle East
have taken to the streets
demanding...
-Thank you.
-I'll be right back.
(anchor continues indistinctly)
Meanwhile,
at the United Nations,
governments from all over the
world have voiced their anger
at the Compound V revelation.
-Mm.
-Today, Russia and China
referred to the superheroes
as weapons of mass destruction
-and accused the United States
of terrorism...
-Mm.
You two want a room?
You and the doughnut.
Oh.
(laughs)
I'm sorry.
It's just, um,
my mom never let me
have this stuff.
-Hmm.
-It's just-- Weight gain
in our household
was a capital crime.
But my dad, um,
he'd take me to Dunkin'
on the sly.
And he would get me a chocolate
cream-filled doughnut,
and he'd ask me
to tell him about my day.
And he'd... he'd listen.
Baskin-Robbins.
Every Sunday after church.
My pops, he'd always ask
for samples.
Now, this place had 31 flavors,
and that man would taste
each and every flavor
every time we'd go up in there.
There'd be a line
all the way out the door.
People would be mad as hell.
Yelling.
-(laughing)
-Cussing. "Yo, my man,
get your fucking ice cream
and bounce!"
You think that stopped him?
Hell, nah.
He would stand right there
and order another sample.
"Can I please try the Jamoca
Almond Fudge, please?"
(Starlight chuckles)
My ass was so embarrassed.
I'd be sitting there,
wishing the floor
would just open up
and just swallow me whole.
Man.
Course, now I'd give a year off
my life just to be able
to see that man going through
spoon after spoon
just one last time.
When did he...
16 years ago.
To fathers and sugar.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. Are you dry wiping?
Am I what?
Come here.
Listen, any part of your body,
-and I mean any part...
-Mm-hmm.
When you dry wipe,
you're not cleaning anything.
You're just smearing shit
all over your skin.
Here. Got to use wet wipes.
There you go.
-You just carry these
around with you?
-Damn right...
(tires screech)
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, please!
They're hurt!
-They need help!
-No, please. No, no, no.
This is not the time
to be a Supe.
Okay? We're low-key,
not with us here.
-Annie?
-I...
There's a ton of people here.
Okay, that guy,
he's calling 911.
It'll be okay.
Come on. Come on, we gotta go.
-This was a bad idea.
This was a stupid idea.
-Just calm down, calm down.
(indistinct chatter)
(insects trilling)
Any place around here without
a million bloody cameras?
♪ ♪
(short laugh)
(sobbing)
Are you okay?
-Did he hurt you?
-No.
I'm okay, I'm fine.
I thought you were dead.
I stopped looking.
I shouldn't have stopped.
I couldn't call anybody.
I can't imagine
what it must've done to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
No, you've done nothing wrong.
Look at you.
My girl.
Always.
(quiet laugh)
Billy, it's not safe
for you to be here.
(sniffles)
If he finds you,
he's gonna kill you
and you know that.
Fuck him.
I got out of the last scrape
all right, didn't I?
That was a one-time deal.
What did you say to him?
I said if he hurt you...
I would kill myself
in front of Ryan.
And my last words would be,
"Your father did this to me."
He seems desperate for
a relationship with his son,
so it worked once.
Well, it's a good thing
he don't know your tells.
I wasn't bluffing.
I'm gonna get you
the fuck out of here.
Yeah, how?
Over the fence,
the same way that I came in.
No, no.
Ryan-Ryan can't
climb that fence.
Right.
I saw his-his eyes glow.
I thought he might...
Don't he got no powers?
N-No, I-I mean...
Yes, but I'm not...
I'm not raising him like that.
Hey.
There's a garbage truck.
It comes by the house
every morning at 11:00.
I doubt anyone
checks the hopper.
You sure it's not
a fucking compacter?
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay.
Then that's the plan.
Yeah, yeah.
I have to go.
They get suspicious
when I'm gone too long.
(sniffles)
Wait here, I'll be back.
Okay?
(door closes)
(engine starts)
(insects trilling)
Okay, so, we got two rooms.
There's three of us,
so I guess I'll be, uh...
...bunking with M.M., naturally.
Good choice.
(snoring)
(vehicles passing outside)
(phone chimes)
Mmm.
-HUGHIE: Is that an Almond Joy?
-Mm-hmm.
Nobody likes Almond Joy.
Jeffrey Dahmer...
That's it, he's the only one.
This in my top three for sure.
What are your other two?
Mm...
Charleston Chew...
and Bit-O-Honey.
Jesus Christ!
Those are the, like,
three worst candy bars
-in the history of candy!
-(laughing)
That's it, you're-you're sick.
In the brain.
(Hughie chuckles)
Hey, what's up with M.M.'s OCD?
Wait, what-what OCD?
You know, when he changes lanes,
he taps the steering wheel
three times.
He stirs the coffee three times.
The antiseptic wipes-- Really?
You haven't noticed any of this?
No, but wow, you're right.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's just control over things
he can't control, I guess.
-(Hughie scoffs)
-I mean...
I should be the last one
talking about that.
Says the girl who's
just stress-eating all day.
Oh, my God!
-That was... I...
-(Starlight shushing)
Was so good,
that was really good.
I enjoyed that.
It's harder than it looked.
Nah.
I think, you know,
actually, I think I went
the other way with the eating.
I think I lost,
like, seven pounds.
Mm.
I did not have seven to lose.
Well... oh, I sleep
about four hours a night.
I wish I slept
four hours a night.
I mean, I'm too busy
chewing my fingernails
down to the quick.
I don't know, whatever a...
I don't know
what a quick is, but...
Here's one.
(chuckles)
I walk around the Seven Tower
with this...
knot in my gut.
Just wondering
if Homelander is waiting
around every corner to kill me.
It's like living with
a loaded gun in my face.
Do you feel that way now?
(quiet laugh)
(both moaning)
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got it.
(quiet laugh)
But I still want to see you.
WOMAN:
Love is a leap of faith.
Like, my last boyfriend
was obsessed with Ed Sheeran.
Yeah, I know.
But he was obsessed.
"Shape of You," "Galway Girl,"
whole catalog.
So, he asked me
to get one of these with him.
(smacks lips)
Two weeks later,
he broke up with me.
I fucking hate Ed Sheeran.
(insects trilling softly)
(vehicle approaching)
(panting, moaning)
Took you ages to quit.
All them little patches, eh?
(chuckles)
Do you want one?
No.
(short laugh)
The beard's new.
Fancy it, eh?
Eh, haven't decided yet.
How long you been here
for then, eh?
Since I gave birth.
(whispers):
Fucking hell.
(quiet laugh)
How you holding up?
Yeah, you know, you forget about
reading the news or...
going to a restaurant...
smoking pot on the couch
and eating Cheetos.
I just act like, you know,
Carol fucking Brady all day.
It's okay.
You know, Ryan's happy, and...
that's what matters.
You're gonna like him.
He's sweet...
and very smart and...
so kind.
I know you hate kids and all,
but I think that he's pretty...
Oh, no, no, no, I don't,
I don't hate kids.
Just...
I'm not a very good
role model, am I?
How have you been?
(smacks lips)
Oh, you know, all right.
Started a private
security company.
(both grunt)
You know, weddings,
bar mitzvahs...
Bullshit.
Homelander said you were
"a man possessed."
He said you've been chasing
after him for years.
Well, I thought he killed you.
So... yeah.
I've been on a bit of a warpath.
But on the bright side,
I'm sleeping in a basement
beneath a pawn shop
in East Flatbush.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted that for you.
What was I supposed to do?
Hmm?
Let him get away with it?
What was I before you?
Nothing.
And you saved me.
And here you've been,
fucking living in this shithole
for all this time,
and I haven't been here for you.
I'm gonna make it up to you.
I'm gonna make it up to you
from now till the day I die,
I swear to God.
♪ ♪
Is the supervillain threat real?
Hundred percent.
Very real.
But The Seven will protect you.
That's right, right.
Always listen to Maeve.
She always tells the truth.
And we're grateful every day.
On a related subject,
Compound V.
Did either of you know about it
before the news broke?
No. Absolutely not.
Madelyn Stillwell,
she lied to all of us.
Turns out she was a monster.
We're-we're just as hurt
and upset and confused
as everyone else.
Let's talk #HeroesSoWhite.
The numbers are
rather startling.
92% of heroes are Caucasian.
African American, six percent.
Latin and Asian,
each one percent.
Why doesn't Vought
want diversity?
Wow. These are real hardballs,
Maria Menounos.
(weak chuckles)
But check your facts.
Let's, uh, take The Seven,
for example.
We've got A-Train.
He's a black man.
We got Black Noir. He, um...
Well, he doesn't identify
with any race, really,
so... they're covered.
(chuckles)
And... we have a gay hero.
Really?
Who in The Seven is gay?
Queen Maeve.
Mm-hmm. Scoop for you, Maria.
Maeve here is a strong,
proud lesbian
with a beautiful girlfriend,
Elena.
Hispanic girlfriend.
And I, for one,
am so proud of her.
MAEVE:
Where's Elena?
What did you do to her?
She's fine.
What did I do to her?
I set her free.
And you. You've been living
in the shadows so long,
doesn't it feel good
to be out in the sun?
Hold on.
Me and Elena are just friends.
-Oh. Just friends?
-Yes.
Because, see, I heard you two
talking on the phone,
and it sounded
a little more than friends.
So, I did a little digging,
and imagine my fucking surprise.
Okay.
-We had a relationship once.
-Hmm.
Once. A relationship...
"Relationship."
That's such a vague word.
What does that mean to you?
What, long walks in the park?
A shoulder to cry on?
Scissoring each other raw?
I ended the relationship
when I joined The Seven.
When I met you.
Stop fucking lying to me.
I am at my wit's fucking end
with the lies.
We're together.
And you love her?
Hmm.
I see.
Well, best of luck to you both.
Oh, is it so hard to believe
that I want you two to be happy?
And in love?
Honestly, Maeve, I am
really, really happy for you.
(cheering, applause over TV)
And have you seen
Vought's "Saving America" ads?
Don't they make you feel all
warm and squishy and patriotic?
(high-pitched ringing)
Vought wants you
to feel calm and safe
so that you continue to buy
their shitty toys
and drinking
their shitty energy drinks
-and going to see
their shitty movies.
-(booing)
But maybe we shouldn't
feel so calm.
Or safe.
One Super terrorist
has already gotten through.
More will come.
And for all we know,
these maniacs could already have
flown over our borders
and be standing next to you,
just waiting for their chance
to kill us all.
So what are we gonna do?
We're gonna sit around
and cross our fingers
that Homelander's gonna save us
when he's not on Maria Menounos?
CROWD:
No!
STORMFRONT:
Or will we demand
that Vought do better?
(crowd cheering)
That our government do better!
What do you say?
(cheering, applause)
No.
Mon coeur, please.
You will not survive.
CROWD (chanting):
Stormfront! Stormfront!
FAN:
Marry me, Stormfront!
(shouting, cheering)
Let's go home.
(clears throat)
-Hello?
-HUGHIE: Uh,
hello, um...
I'm Hughie.
Is-is there, by any chance,
a woman living here
who used to go by the name
of, um, Liberty?
No.
Okay, we have
the right address, right?
Is that...?
-Please leave.
-Miss,
I'm sorry if my friend
offended you.
But we just want to ask
just a couple of questions.
Just leave me alone.
I took your damn money,
I signed your damn papers,
and I have kept my mouth shut.
You think we're w...
We're not with Vought.
Okay? We...
(laughs)
We just want to learn
what we can about Liberty.
That's it.
Then y'all are just
some damn fools.
It sounds like you know her.
Or knew her.
You're wasting your time.
-Okay?
-Miss, Miss, Miss. Hear us out.
If, after that,
you want us to leave, we'll go.
Go ahead.
My father was a lawyer.
Small-time, very smart.
And aggressive.
When I was a kid, something
happened between my family
and Vought, which I'd rather not
talk about, but it was bad.
Now, see, my dad,
he believed in the law
and that nobody was above it,
not even Vought.
So he went to work.
He got after their asses.
He had one of those...
Remember
those little black typewriters,
manual ones with the keys?
I'd go to sleep at night
to all that noise,
my father banging away
at that thing.
Wake up the next morning,
he'd still be hammering away.
All night.
But see, Vought wasn't about
to let this one black man
put his foot on their necks.
Mm-mm.
So they hired teams of lawyers.
Paid off judges.
But my father never gave up.
Till one morning
I woke up and...
I didn't hear
those keys anymore.
Just found him hunched over
that typewriter, dead at 55.
WOMAN:
I'm so sorry for your loss.
MOTHER'S MILK:
I'm not here for your sympathy.
But I am gonna tell you that
his fight got passed down to me.
And I'm gonna make Vought pay
for what they did to him
and, ma'am, from what I gather,
what they've done to you,
as well.
I mean... it's been 48 years.
What good is dredging
all this stuff up now gonna do?
Honestly we don't know.
But we still need to hear it.
(sighs)
I tried to get people to listen.
(laughs): Lord knows,
so many times, I tried.
But a little black girl accusing
a white superhero of murder
in these parts?
Yeah.
(Valerie sighs)
It was during
one of those summer rains
that you just knew was coming
by the smell in the air.
I was 11 years old,
asleep in the back seat
of my folks' Ford.
My brother Myron,
he was driving.
(tires screech)
MYRON:
What's the trouble, ma'am?
LIBERTY:
Get out.
MYRON:
Hey.
LIBERTY:
Your car was involved
in a robbery tonight.
No, it wasn't. I-I had it.
I don't know nothing
about any robbery.
LIBERTY:
Just confess.
MYRON:
Why are you doing this
to me, lady?
Ain't you supposed to be a hero?
LIBERTY:
I am a hero.
For killing a black
piece of shit like you.
(Myron wheezing softly)
I wanted to go to the police.
But my folks,
they thought it was pointless.
So when that man from Vought,
when he showed up and he offered
us that money, we just took it.
$2,000.
That is what my brother's life
was worth.
Just $2,000.
But y'all have got to promise me
that you won't tell anybody that
I sat here and I talked to you.
Because if that woman finds out
that I opened my mouth,
she's gonna kill me.
Ms. Hunter,
that woman, L-Liberty,
n-nobody's seen her since 1979.
I mean,
she's probably dead by now.
(chuckles):
Oh, no, no.
I...
(mutters softly)
Right here.
That's her. Right there.
That's Liberty.
HUGHIE:
Valerie was just a little girl,
and she said it was raining,
so she could be wrong.
She seemed pretty certain.
Yeah, but if Liberty and
Stormfront are the same person,
then that makes Stormfront,
like, what, like, 70 years old?
-More?
-Yeah, but who knows
what Compound V can do?
I mean, maybe she doesn't age
like a regular person. Okay?
This is the same Stormfront
that just became
-America's favorite
two-fisted Supe.
-Mm-hmm.
And might've popped Raynor's
head for getting too close.
-Oh, my God.
-What the fuck is going on?
I didn't know that
about your dad.
Sounds like he was a real hero.
I thought so, but...
Nah. He's just a man
with a disease.
He passed it down to me,
and if I'm not too careful,
I might end up
passing it down to my...
(sighs)
HOMELANDER:
Who the fuck
do you think you are?
What, you think I don't see it?
Trying to undermine me,
steal my team...
-Hold on a minute.
-Let me tell you right now,
it won't work.
I'm the face of The Seven!
Not you!
Me. I still score higher
in every demo that counts.
18 to 34, 18 to 49, 25 to 54,
they all love me.
Well, congratulations.
I mean, this constant need
to be loved by everyone
is kind of pathetic,
but, um, yay.
Okay.
(softly):
Okay. Calm down.
I clearly pushed you
a little far. I'm sorry.
Look, I'm... I'm just
trying to help.
Really? How?
By taking what's mine?
Let me tell you something
right now:
I built this team
from the ground up,
and there is no fucking way
that anyone
is gonna take it away from me.
You spent $273 million
on that "Saving America"
bullshit,
and I am running circles
around you
with five guys on laptops
churning out memes.
I practically pay them
with Arby's gift cards.
You...
You can't win
the whole country anymore.
No one can.
So why are you even trying?
You don't need 50 million people
to love you.
You need five million people
fucking pissed.
Emotion sells, anger sells.
You have fans.
I have soldiers.
Look, I know that
you probably won't believe this.
I think that you
are the best of us.
are everything we should be.
You just need a little help
connecting with your audience.
You know, change with the times.
God knows I did.
I don't need help connecting
with my audience.
Thank you.
Okay. Well, just know
I'm always here,
door is always open
for anything.
You're late. Where's the kid?
Babe, we got to get in the truck
or we'll miss our chance.
I'm-I'm not leaving.
What are you talking about?
Of course you are.
Grab the kid and let's go.
You don't really want Ryan
to come with us.
Of course I do.
I said I'd take him, didn't I?
And I wanted to believe you.
Then believe me. Now come on,
we've got to get a shift on.
Listen,
if the three of us leave,
you're gonna find a way
to get rid of him.
I know it. (stammers)
It won't be in an obvious way,
and it won't be right away,
-but you will.
-No, Becca, no.
Billy, I know you.
I know you better than anybody,
and I saw it
in your face last night.
I see it now.
He's a billion-dollar piece
of Vought property.
They are not gonna let him go.
You and me, Becca, you and me,
we've got a chance.
Babe, it's Ryan
they care about, not us.
Yeah, and then what?
And then Vought raises him
without a mother, right?
Then we have Homelander
all over again,
then there's two fucking
assholes in this world.
We could disappear, all right?
Just start again,
-start a new family.
-I have a son!
He's a fucking Supe freak.
(sighs)
Fuck. I'm... Listen, I...
I'm sorry, I d...
I didn't mean that.
Becca.
Becca, please come with me.
You were wrong about me,
do you know that?
You put me on this pedestal,
and the truth is,
I never knew how to save you.
You were always
one-one bad day away
from pounding someone to death
in a parking lot.
That's not true.
Billy.
He raped me, and when
I found out I was pregnant,
I went to Vought.
I didn't come to you.
I didn't come to you
because I was scared,
'cause I knew that
you'd chase after him
and you would seek revenge and
it wouldn't be good for anybody.
I love you.
(crying):
But the hate that you carry
and the warpath that you're on,
it started so long before me.
I can't.
Becs, I'm not leaving
without you.
You have to go, please.
Every guard
in this goddamn place
is gonna be here in 60 seconds.
You have to go.
(crying)
-I'm sorry.
-(car engine starts)
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shit.
-Small token of the trip.
-Mmm.
You know, John Wayne Gacy
used to give those out to kids
when he was a birthday clown.
Whatever, I still love them.
Thanks for letting me come.
It was fun
-until it got so horrible.
-Yeah.
-What can I say?
It's my specialty.
-(chuckles)
Well, um,
listen, if you're ever in
the mood for another Almond Joy,
just-just shoot me a text.
(chuckles)
That came out so gross.
I'm sorry.
Hughie.
we can't do that again.
No, no, no, no. No, we can't.
Why, though?
I mean, th... this is...
this is good.
But that's just it.
I mean, we can't afford
to feel good or to feel safe
or to let our guard down.
You can't go through this
on your own.
We're all alone.
That's the truth.
But it doesn't have
to be like that.
Goodbye, Hughie.
I believe the secret
to a great relationship
is to be willing...
to do anything for your man.
Anything.
I'm a feminist,
but I'm also very sexual,
and I don't see that
as contradictory.
What's wrong
with giving pleasure
and receiving it?
Thank you for coming in, Gianna.
Yeah, we appreciate your candor.
DEEP:
Thank you so much.
Anytime. It was really great
meeting you.
Really great.
So great.
Bye.
(chuckles) Her. Gianna.
I choose her.
I mean, she's the one,
no question.
CAROL:
No, she isn't.
Wait, what?
She was, like,
hands down the winner.
It was not even a contest.
It's Cassandra.
Cassandra? The one...
the one with the hair
and the creepy skeletons
hugging each other story?
Yes.
That's your wife.
Oh... But...
but I thought I got to choose.
You do, and you're
choosing Cassandra.
Congratulations.
Yeah, but, I mean, Gianna...
Is lovely. She's lovely. She's a
valued member of The Collective,
but this marriage isn't about
satisfying your base desires.
It's about rehabilitating
your image
and getting you back
in The Seven.
That is what you want, isn't it?
There you are.
I was beginning to worry.
Oh, I missed you.
Are you thirsty?
Want some?
Aw, I want you so bad.
Are you okay?
Would you like me
to be someone else?
I can be whoever you want.
(gasps)
No.
I don't need anyone...
...but myself.
Like what you see?
See how hot you are?
Hmm?
Come on.
How much do you want this?
How much?
I'm gonna suck your cock
so fucking hard,
so good,
and you're gonna look
in your own eyes when you come.
It's not even gay
if it's with yourself, right?
(chuckles)
Oh,
you're so special,
the most special man
on the planet.
Everybody loves you.
Everybody.
Their love
is your strength.
You're pathetic.
I don't need everyone
to love me.
I don't need anyone.
I don't
need you!
(neck snaps)
(body thuds)
(fire crackling)