-HOMELANDER: Freedom...
-(groans)
...comes at a price.
-So, I'm down a point?
-ASHLEY: Nine and a half.
STORMFRONT:
Bad day?
-Goddamn it.
-Hey, I'm with you.
But you know,
there's a way to handle it.
I owe you.
(moans)
Thanks to
the Church of the Collective,
I now know the kind of man
I want to be.
-#BraveMaeve.
-MAEVE: This is Homelander.
He's fucking with me.
I can't protect you
if you leave.
What are we gonna do?
CHERIE:
You think, by saving Kimiko,
you can make amends
for those children
-that Lamplighter burned.
-FRENCHIE: Fuck you.
HUGHIE:
You can't go through this
-on your own.
-We're all alone.
How do you think the world
will feel when I tell them that
you used to be Liberty?
Wow.
("Casquette à l'envers"
by Sexion d'Assault playing)
(whirring)
(Jay and Cherie laugh)
Why are you laughing?
-You're ridiculous.
-Oh, no.
I am not, uh, ridiculous.
CHERIE:
Okay.
-Then you are high.
-Well, beside the point.
-(chuckles) Mm-hmm.
-Point is
I learned everything I know
from those girls.
-The Golden Girls.
-(chuckles)
I was alone in New York,
you know?
Turning tricks.
Begging for the scraps.
Who do you think
kept me company?
The Golden Girls.
3:00 a.m. to 5:00 a.m.,
they lit up
the shelter's shitty TV.
JAY:
And you're not talking
about porn?
-The Golden Shower Girls?
-(Cherie laughs)
-That's disrespectful.
-CHERIE: Aw.
-He's so sensitive.
-(laughs)
No. Those saucy ladies,
they made their own family.
So I did what they did.
You are my Blanche.
-Blanche?
-And Jay?
You are...
-my Dorothy.
-CHERIE: Mm-hmm.
'Cause you're a little gay.
-Yeah.
-(laughs)
-So, you're Betty White?
-Oh,
what a fucking question.
Of course I'm Betty White.
(sniffs)
Now...
Who wants to rob a bank?
Fuck, yeah.
(whirring)
Will it get through my skin?
If it can't, nothing can.
HUGHIE:
Okay, I-I just feel like
I need to say something.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
Stormfront knows I leaked the V.
Yeah, but she hasn't
come after you.
Ye... But that makes it
so much worse.
That means that she has
some fucked-up plan for me.
I need this chip out now.
I understand, Petit Hughie.
And though you've been covered
with entrails of many a person,
even a sea mammal...
it's always harder
when it's someone you love.
-What?
-L'amour.
No, no. No, I don't.
I mean, I-I do, of course.
It's just, it's a platon...
-We're-we're just friends.
-STARLIGHT: Okay,
can we just do this already
before I change my mind?
Please?
-(drill whirs)
-Okay, this is happening.
-Okay.
-Mm-hmm.
-This might sting a little.
-Okay.
(whirring)
-(Starlight shouts, groans)
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Okay. (panting)
Okay.
(Starlight groaning)
Bonjour, my little spy.
-(horn honking)
-(siren wailing)
(panting)
Howdy ho, buckaroo.
(man screams)
Shit!
I think you broke my hand.
(grunting)
What do you want to do with him?
Well, hand him over
to the police,
-of course.
-Well, of course. We are heroes.
That's what heroes do.
-Absolutely.
-But...
-he'll probably just be
released tomorrow.
-Please,
-just take me to the hospital.
-Yeah.
Please.
That's a really good point.
(exhales)
You know,
sometimes it feels like...
like the justice system
just doesn't work anymore.
Everyone always recording
on their phone all the time.
-Mm-hmm.
-It's like you can't even
-do your job anymore.
-Do your job anymore.
-(Stormfront laughs)
-HOMELANDER: Mm-hmm.
Please, just take me in.
Just take me in, please.
(grunts)
(Homelander moaning)
♪ I do ♪
♪ I think about you... ♪
It really speaks
to the deterioration
of good,
God-fearing American values.
Help me!
STORMFRONT:
Oh, what's this world
-coming to?
-Oh, fuck.
(man grunts)
(screams)
♪ And you say you belong to me ♪
♪ And ease my mind ♪
♪ Imagine how the world could be
so very fine ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ I can't see me loving nobody ♪
♪ But you for all my life ♪
♪ When you're with me ♪
♪ Baby, the skies'll be blue ♪
♪ For all my life. ♪
HOMELANDER:
Don't be shy. Embrace it.
STORMFRONT:
Thank... I'm saying thank you.
HOMELANDER:
Well, you're welcome.
MAN:
Let's be honest
for a moment here.
Who is the biggest prankster
on set?
-(chuckles)
-Ooh, I-I just... I don't think
we should get into that.
I don't know, I... No comment.
(laughs)
I mean, he is right.
But, uh, you know,
Black Noir has definitely got
-just the biggest ego.
-HOMELANDER: Such a diva.
They're fucking.
STORMFRONT:
...under that helmet. (laughs)
(footsteps approaching)
Did you get her chip out?
This is where you're living?
Yeah. You know,
it has its charms.
The rats are, like, uh, Pokémon.
-With hep C.
-Oh, God.
Oh, so you're back?
Tired of killing people
for money?
Uh, hi.
Remember me?
(chuckles softly)
Well, well, well.
What have we here?
HUGHIE:
I know what you're gonna say,
but we just took out her chip.
Everything's fine.
Starlight, don't you
just light up a room, eh?
-You're looking well.
-STARLIGHT: Yeah, no thanks
to the .50-caliber round
that you pumped into my chest.
Well, what don't kill you
makes you stronger.
Hmm.
What's she doing here?
Uh, she has a lead
on Stormfront.
STARLIGHT:
I broke into her laptop,
and I got a look at the inbox.
Dozens of e-mails
from Stan Edgar.
Stan Edgar?
And what does Vought's
big slapper have to say?
How they're close
to a breakthrough
at the Sage Grove Center.
It's a psychiatric hospital
in Pennsylvania.
HUGHIE:
Wait, wh-what kind
of breakthrough?
She came in
before I could see any more.
Well, we better have us
a little dekko
at this loony bin, eh, lads?
Starlight,
would you be amenable
to joining us
on this little caper?
You want her to come?
Oh, most definitely.
If shit goes sideways,
who do you think
Vought's gonna go after?
Us or their billion-dollar baby
turned traitor
who just ripped out
her own fucking chip?
Never go
into shark-infested waters
without chum.
♪ Give a little bit of love... ♪
MAEVE:
This is who I am.
Who are you?
Brave Maeve Pride Bars.
Because you can't be proud
on an empty stomach.
(knock on door)
Come in.
You fucking idiot.
You were supposed to call first.
Did anyone see you?
I'm allowed to visit my friends.
Did you find it?
No, sorry. No black box.
But I told
a couple of my contacts
to keep an eye
on the North Atlantic Current.
So, this school of halibut...
I mean,
these guys are, like, rowdy
motherfuckers, right? They...
-Deep.
-(clears throat)
Anyway,
they found some of the wreckage
that drifted up near Iceland.
And they found this.
(exhales)
I mean, I'm not sure
it still even works, but...
You want back in The Seven?
Not a fucking word of this
to anyone.
♪ Here comes the A-Train,
Mr. Fleet Feet ♪
♪ Savin' lives, takin' names,
nice and easy ♪
♪ There ain't no day
like a race day, what ♪
♪ Ain't no love
like a raceway, what ♪
♪ I'm the best to ever do it,
y'all crazy ♪
♪ Make way or you're pushin' up
daisies, bring the heat ♪
♪ Now they're beggin'
for some AC... ♪
Isn't it lit?
Your very own anthem.
(song continues indistinctly)
Yeah, it's dope.
Well, this is just the demo,
of course.
We're going out to Lil Nas X
for the official version.
Maybe you could bust out
Prince's guitar for the video.
I had to sell Prince's guitar.
I'm going 10-1.
Okay.
Ashley.
-What?
-I can't find her.
ASHELY:
Where the fuck is Starlight?
Yo! Here comes the A-Train.
What, what?
(chuckles)
I'm right here, buddy.
Over here.
-Yeah.
-What's up, buddy?
-Good to see you.
-What you doing here, man?
Oh, not much.
Just here to see, uh, uh...
No reason, really.
But, hey, bro, I've been
thinking about you lately.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I see what they're trying
to do to you. Yeah.
Talk about getting ass-fucked
with a soup can.
Am I right?
What do you mean?
I mean, come on.
If anyone knows what it's like
to get bounced, it's me.
Yeah. Did some shit
I'm not too proud of.
Some weird shit.
I'm good, man.
(chuckles softly)
Nike and Under Armour are
already talking to my people,
so, you know,
this is actually gonna work out
to be really fantastic for me.
-Oh, that's great.
-Yeah.
Yeah. Well, then, uh,
I guess you don't need his help.
Or, uh... No, never mind.
Forget I even said anything.
But hey, it's great to see you,
man. Always.
All right.
Whose?
Whose help?
Would you like a Fresca?
MOTHER'S MILK:
Sage Grove, a proud subsidiary
of Global Wellness Services,
which is
a subsidiary of...
I can guess.
Thanks.
Here.
This is what you bought
with your blood money?
No one will believe you're
an orderly with that, you know.
(exhales)
I should go in with them.
They can manage
without one bony, blonde Supe.
You just get them in
and get the fuck back, yeah?
Okay, just...
(exhales)
If anybody recognizes your face
in there, I mean...
Oi, Frenchie.
Don't get caught.
I never do.
(lock buzzes, door opens)
MALLORY:
Weaponized Xanax.
The grenades
you used on Behemoth
during the bank heist.
You got a Supe
activated by rage,
so you simply take away
his rage,
turn him into a cupcake.
Clever.
I don't know what
you are talking about.
And Cold Snap two months ago?
Malchemical a month before that?
You don't know about those,
either?
What is this about?
Armed robbery,
breaking and entering,
aggravated assault on a Supe.
You're looking at 20 to 25,
minimum.
Or you can come work for me.
I could use someone
with your imagination.
Madame...
fuck you.
That's a pity,
for you...
(inhales)
...but even more so
for Cherie and Jay,
I believe?
ADX Florence
is a supermax in Colorado.
They've got the Unabomber,
head of the Aryan Brotherhood--
all the greats.
And your friends, too.
Maybe.
Or... they go free.
But that depends on you.
Right now.
You can't do that.
(chuckling)
Wait.
(soft chatter)
What kind of work do you do?
Hey.
Um...
Come into my trailer
for a second.
I have a surprise for you.
I have to stop by Vought Tower,
see my social guys.
No.
Come on. Blow them off.
-(chuckles)
-Come.
I will be back in 20 minutes.
(quietly):
And then...
I'll let you surprise me
wherever you want.
Ooh.
Yeah, okay.
(clock ticking)
(sighs)
(soft grunt)
Hmm.
(smacks lips)
(sighs)
(insects trilling)
You see 'em?
BUTCHER:
Yeah.
I see 'em.
(exhales)
(flips safety)
♪ ♪
(whispers):
Get in.
♪ ♪
(insects trilling)
(grunts)
Here.
Seriously?
What is your problem with me?
I ain't got no problem with you,
love.
Really? That's why
you won't even touch my hand?
Okay, guys, come on.
Not the time.
You know what? No.
I think
it's exactly the right time.
I think the time
is long overdue.
You know that I hate Vought
as much as you do.
You know that. But it
doesn't even matter to you
because what you can't stand
is in my blood.
-I'm subhuman to you.
-(exhales)
Only good Supe is a dead Supe,
right?
Your words, not mine.
HUGHIE:
That's enough.
STARLIGHT:
You know what?
Underneath all that swagger,
you're just a bigot and a bully.
I know another guy
just like that.
He's got a flag for a cape.
Annie, stop.
(whooshing)
Oh, fuck me.
Hughie, call them. Now.
(line ringing)
(knocking)
Open the door.
We need help.
I have a patient
that needs help.
Hurry up! Please!
What's wrong with him?
Just open the goddamn door!
He's swallowing
his fucking tongue!
(lock clicking)
-What's wrong with him?
-Easy.
(silenced gunshots)
(groaning)
Holy fuck.
(mouse, keyboard clicking)
What the fuck is all of this?
Vought is making
more Supe terrorists?
MOTHER'S MILK:
Who the fuck knows?
Goddamn.
Brother's got a love sausage.
(speaks Russian)
♪ ♪
(keys clacking)
Stormfront is here?
How you doing today?
(high-pitched ringing)
Do you want to show us a little
of what you've been working on?
-(panting)
-Hey. Hey.
You're okay.
You're all right.
It's okay.
That is very impressive, Tim.
That orderly Stormfront's with--
he look familiar to you?
Je ne sais pas.
What about headaches?
Nausea?
No.
Well, that's promising.
I think we are getting close.
TIM:
Ma'am,
can I go home now?
I want to see my family.
STORMFRONT:
Tim, you were admitted
to Sage Grove
because you're suicidal.
You could be a danger
to yourself.
Well, I'm not doing any more
of these stupid pet tricks
until I talk to my sister.
Okay. Okay.
We'll work something out.
(exhales)
(grunts)
(screaming)
(whispers):
Lamplighter.
-That's fucking Lamplighter.
-Shh...
FRENCHIE:
I didn't recognize him
without the mask and the hood.
-Fucking Lamplighter.
We have to kill him, of course.
-No, no, no, no. No, we can't.
-For Madame Mallory.
For her grandchildren.
-Not right now.
First, we got to find out
what the fuck all this shit is.
-Come on.
-Listen, listen.
Stick to the plan, Frenchie.
(phone buzzing)
-Hughie.
-There you are.
You guys okay?
Stormfront's in there.
That ain't all who's here.
Okay, okay. She just left.
Get the hell out. Now.
All right, let's get
the fuck out of here.
♪ ♪
-(panting)
-(alarm ringing)
Hey. Cindy.
Let's be cool.
Okay?
You remember that extra helping
of Kraft Shells & Cheese
that I snuck you?
(chuckles softly)
I like you.
You know that, right?
Who are your friends?
We ain't his friends.
Go ahead.
Fuck his ass up.
CINDY:
You're dressed like his friends.
I don't like liars.
(exhales)
(groans)
Oh, shit...
Let's get out of here!
(creaking)
(murmuring)
(shouting)
-(alarm ringing)
-(shouting)
(lock beeping)
-Hey. Let go!
-(grunts)
(Lamplighter grunts)
Stay the fuck back or I will
burn your skin off, asshole!
Oh, you won't get the chance!
-(pounds)
-Someone help me!
(screaming)
(panting)
(screaming, shouting)
All right, listen up, man.
You can burn us,
but she's a Supe.
All you're gonna do
is piss her off.
So why don't
we all just calm down
and live
through this motherfucker?
(screaming, shouting)
-What's going on here?
-It's a lockdown.
No one's getting out of here,
not even her.
MOTHER'S MILK: There's got to be
an access code.
LAMPLIGHTER:
There is, genius,
at the front door.
And there is no fucking way
I am telling you
or taking you with me.
You do realize there's a whole
army of Supes on the other side
of that door that want
to tear you apart, right?
She... can help.
I'm gonna take my chances.
(grunting)
-(retching)
-(shouting)
(grunts)
(retches)
(shouting, groaning)
(gurgling)
(alarm continues ringing)
Okay, you guys can come.
(alarm ringing in distance)
(muffled screaming)
What the fuck?
-Come on, M.M.
-(line ringing)
Pick up, damn you.
FEMALE VOICE:
Your call has been forwarded
to an automated
voice messaging system.
MARVIN'S VOICE:
Marvin.
-FEMALE: Is not available.
-Oh, hello.
At the tone,
please record your message.
Easy does it, lad.
No trouble from us.
You just stroll on by, yeah?
I don't want them
to hurt me again.
Oh, nah.
N-No one's gonna hurt you, son.
Uh... we're all friends here,
aren't we?
(whooshing)
(electrical rumbling)
(three gunshots)
(Butcher pants loudly)
Hughie.
(Starlight gasps)
(panting)
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
Fine. Uh...
-(gasps) Hughie? Hughie?
-Oh, shit.
Hughie!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No.
Can you cauterize it?
-(Hughie groans)
-Uh...
-Oh, fuck. The kid must have
fried everything.
-I need power.
-Well, you got
a pretty shite superpower then,
don't you?
We got to get him to a doctor.
-C-- Where, how?
-I don't know, but not gonna
just sit here and watch him
fucking well bleed out!
-All right?!
-Okay! Okay, okay, okay.
-Come on.
-(groans)
What about the others?
They're on their own.
(clock ticking)
(clock ticking loudly)
(truck horn honking)
(siren blaring)
Ashley? Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Don't you dare tell me
you haven't found Starlight yet.
(Ashley coughs)
-Here.
-(coughing)
(indistinct chatter)
(truck horn blaring)
(whoosh)
I've been searching everywhere
for you.
What happened to your trailer?
Electrical fire.
How was your meeting?
Sorry. It ran long.
No need to apologize.
All right, well, I got
to go run lines with Noir.
Scene 48 tonight.
Real megillah.
Something wrong?
No. Nothing.
You sure?
Why would anything be wrong?
By the way, I went to the Tower,
and, uh, you weren't there.
No one had seen you.
So you're checking on me?
Wanted to see
how your meeting went.
Hold on.
-Let me...
-Explain?
Come on now.
Why would you need
to explain anything to me?
("Orinoco Flow (Sail Away)"
by Enya playing)
♪ Let me sail, let me sail,
let the Orinoco flow... ♪
Deep, your numbers among women
have been ticking up
quite nicely.
Did you catch
Malala Yousafzai's tweet?
Called you "a sweetheart."
Well, she's the sweetheart.
♪ Far beyond the Yellow Sea... ♪
So, what's on your mind,
A-Train?
Hmm. Um...
Deep invited me here,
so, you know...
Yeah, I don't know. (chuckles)
Just having a really nice lunch,
I guess, here.
And Deep, what's on your mind?
Well, I think A-Train
sabotaged me my entire career.
-What?!
-Well, you do think
you're better than me.
You know, I fantasize about
drowning you
over and over again.
But I mean, I don't want
to feel that way anymore.
I want to be clean.
Oh, boy.
Looks like we got ourselves
a good old Truth Exchange.
♪ From Bissau to Palau... ♪
-Oh, hell, no.
-Please sit down.
No. Look, man, I seen
that documentary about you guys.
It's not my type of shit.
For a man in seven-figure debt,
a heart condition,
and in heavy withdrawal,
do you really think you have
the luxury to get up and leave?
♪ Far beneath the Coral Sea ♪
♪ De, de... ♪
Who told you that?
Huh? Did he fucking
tell you that shit?
No. The church knows
all kinds of things.
But don't worry.
We also know how to be discreet,
especially for our members.
They're gonna give Shockwave
your uniform, you know that?
-Call him the next A-Train.
-No, they can't do that.
Why not?
"A-Train" is a trademark.
You are just another nobody
from the South Side of Chicago.
(scoffs)
Man, fuck you, man!
ALASTAIR:
I can help.
I can get you back in.
♪ Sail away, sail away... ♪
But first... sit down.
♪ Sail away, sail away,
sail away... ♪
-Let Deep tell you his truths.
-♪ Sail away, sail away ♪
-♪ Sail away ♪
-♪ From the North ♪
♪ To the South,
Ebudae into Khartoum ♪
♪ From the deep sea of clouds
to the island of the moon ♪
♪ Carry me on the waves to
the lands I've never seen... ♪
(alarms sounding)
Come on. In here.
(lock beeping)
(chimes)
(alarm continues sounding)
(distant screaming)
It's beautiful.
Oh...
Hey, what the hell is
going on here? Huh?
You all are juicing people
with motherfucking Compound V,
only to burn 'em alive? Why?
Maybe I just like
watching people burn.
I remember you, you know.
You were tailing me the night
that I torched those kids.
So why didn't you stop me?
Maybe you like
watching people burn, too.
File de pute!
-No, no, no, no, no!
-(speaking French)
-(shouting in French)
-Easy! Easy! Easy...
(yelling)
Easy... Come on, man.
(Frenchie pants)
(panting loudly)
Mon Dieu.
And I don't want
to hear no bullshit
about I'm gonna getting tired
of the pussy.
I love this girl.
Like, this is the one.
Oh.
(laughs)
All right, brother.
All right.
-All right. All right.
-Congratulations, Marvin.
Thank you, Colonel.
Check it out.
-It's beautiful.
-(laughs)
Oh, the bachelor party
I will throw you.
What's your thoughts
about transgender strippers?
Strippers ain't really
my kind of Hershey's,
with or without nuts,
but you golf?
Thinking about doing
a golf trip.
Oi.
(chuckling)
(snorts)
(Butcher laughs)
(snorting)
(Mallory coughs)
-What?
-(quiet laughter)
And what the fuck
are you laughing at?
Sorry, mate.
You just look like one of them
poncy baton twirlers.
-A majorette.
-That's right.
A fucking majorette.
(Butcher laughs)
You look good in these.
So here's what happens now.
You're gonna tell us
every single thing
you see and hear at the Tower.
Especially when it comes
to Homelander.
(flame rumbling)
Please don't pretend
like you have a choice.
I look forward to your call.
-Easy peasy.
-(gun safety clicks)
MALLORY:
I don't like it.
You don't back an animal
like that into a corner.
Fuck him.
We own the cunt.
Frenchie?
Don't let him out of your sight.
Oui, Madame.
(birds singing)
Hey, what's the trouble, miss?
Sir, I need you
to get out of your car.
Well,
what are you talking about?
FBI.
Need to commandeer your vehicle.
-Bit of an emergency.
-Jesus.
-What happened to him?
-Long story, that.
-Uh, can I see some ID?
-Left it in me other pants.
Too busy saving this one,
but you can call my boss.
Yeah, okay. Uh, look, I'll...
I can get you... get you guys
to the hospital, but we're out
in the middle of nowhere.
I'm not gonna give you my car.
Have it your way.
Butcher?
(groans)
Don't.
(gun clicks)
-Stay back.
-Whoa! Okay.
-MAN: I said, stay back.
-That's not necessary.
-Let's just talk.
-The FBI?
Yeah, really.
You're not even American.
What, is-is he even hurt?
What is this?
Some kind of a scam?
If I wanted
to boost some wheels,
it wouldn't be a fuckin'
Hyundai, you daft cunt.
This is a stand-your-ground
state. You stay back!
Oh, you can stand
wherever the fuck you want.
-I'm taking your keys.
-Butcher, stop.
Buddy, just put the gun down.
-I said stay back.
-I said... put it down!
(soft click, car engine starts)
(Starlight sighs)
(sighs)
You couldn't just listen to me
and stay back?!
BUTCHER:
Come on.
Cauterize it!
(grunting)
(engine starts)
(Hughie moans)
(grunting)
It won't hold long.
Come on.
(Hughie grunting)
Is this the right time
to go shopping?
FRENCHIE:
One, why not?
And deux...
this is good news.
What do you mean by that?
Some aerated propofol...
some other odds and ends,
I'll make a knockout bomb.
Even for Supes.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Okay.
Why are we still alive?
-Dumb luck?
-FRENCHIE: No.
I mean that night.
We went underground for months.
But you never came for us.
Not you, not Homelander.
Why?
You're disappointed
we didn't kill you?
I thought The Seven
always retaliates, no?
You're nobody.
Not worth it.
You didn't tell them, did you?
Why wouldn't you tell them?
Who says I didn't?
I figured you'd boast about it
to Homelander,
must've been thrilling for you.
I'm not a fucking animal.
FRENCHIE:
Only a fucking animal
would do what you did.
Drop it.
-You murdered innocent children.
-Shut the fuck up.
You watched them burn alive,
crying for their mama.
If that's not an animal,
then what is, huh?
I didn't know!
I didn't know they were
gonna be in that bed.
It was supposed to be your boss.
Then they started screaming.
But it was too late.
So what, are we supposed
to feel bad for you now?
Fuck you.
LAMPLIGHTER:
I don't want anything from you.
But you...
I saw you following me
that night.
And then you disappeared.
I keep asking myself, why...
why didn't you stop me?
Why didn't you?
Good question.
(crowd cheering, clamoring)
All right, all right.
(phone buzzing)
Cherie, this is not--
CHERIE:
He's dying!
-Quoi?
-Jay!
He's ODing.
I-I don't know what he took.
-Take him to the hospital!
-Please, come now!
Come!
Serge, you fucking come
right now.
Cherie!
Hello--
(smacks lips, mutters)
CHERIE:
No.
FRENCHIE:
Come on!
Come on, mon ami!
-(gasps)
-Oh!
Look at me, look at me,
you went out.
Okay, can you sit?
Come on!
Come on, mon ami, come on.
He's okay.
Okay, you stay with him.
-You keep him talking, okay?
-What?
Where are you going?
Don't let him fall asleep.
-What...?
-I told you I have something.
Something more important
than this?
More important than us?
Cherie, I cannot
do this right now.
Okay?
Please, stay with him!
Fine, you want to go...
go.
(crying):
We don't give a shit.
Serge?
I'll be back.
Je te promets.
-(moaning)
-He's burning up.
I'm going as fast as I can.
I appreciate
what you done back there.
Oh, thanks.
Your approval means
everything to me.
And some sarcasm
to stick the landing.
Nice one.
You didn't have a choice.
You know what I was thinking,
when I was looking at him?
"Why'd you pull a gun,
you stupid fuck?"
That's all.
Maybe once I would've
cried over him, but...
now he was just another
person in our way.
No.
-No what?
-No to that
fucking look of quiet respect
or approval or whatever that is.
I don't want it.
We're nothing alike.
Nothing.
(machinery whirring)
You really think
that's gonna work?
I think so.
You know, they're not
trying to make Supes here.
These people are test subjects.
They're trying
to stabilize the V.
Explain.
Infants handle it best,
but adults?
I mean, you saw what happens--
sometimes you get powers,
sometimes you get a freak,
sometimes you just explode.
Vought is trying
to stabilize it,
so that you put the V
in any adult arm,
anywhere, anytime, you get
a solid Supe, solid powers.
Putain.
Okay, so...
a thousand more Supes...
100,000?
Why? Why would Vought do that?
It's gonna fuck up their movies,
their merchandising...
They don't tell me.
They just make me
burn the evidence.
Okay?
My, uh...
my best friend
OD'd and I left
to save him that night.
Why I didn't stop you.
You were at a party.
I was away for 30 minutes.
Came back, you were gone.
Did he live?
Your friend?
Oui.
But I never saw him again,
and...
then, uh, he died
a few months later.
Another overdose.
Are you serious?
Frenchie, wh...?
Why didn't you ever tell us?
What difference would it make?
After all these years, man?
We would've let you
off the hook.
What makes you think I want
to be let off the hook, huh?
(thumping)
(grunting)
Get it off me!
Get this thing off of me!
(thud)
Was that...?
It's okay.
That's his fucking dick.
Don't be so closed-minded.
♪ ♪
I thought you said that shit
was gonna work.
I said I thought it would.
(door opens)
(creaking)
(screaming)
Lamplighter?!
Lamplighter!
I'm here.
I just killed
six subjects out there
like a fucking
teddy bear picnic.
What the hell happened?
Dr. Carlton got
the propofol dose
wrong again.
So Cindy got loose,
freed some of the others.
I'm sure some of them got out
before lockdown.
Where's Dr. Carlton?
LAMPLIGHTER:
Uh, he's in the cafeteria
and the hallway and...
some of the walls.
(indistinct chatter)
STORMFRONT:
Clean up this mess.
I'm gonna go see
if anyone else got loose.
Yes, ma'am.
We need help!
What'd they say?
Just needs a couple of days for
the Cefazolin to kick in, but...
he should be all right.
We don't have a couple of days.
Well, we're gonna have
to risk it.
Jesus.
What?
Just...
it's the kids' shampoo he uses.
I can smell it.
L'Oréal for kids,
strawberry smoothie.
I seen the bottle.
Hateful shit.
And his Axe Body Spray.
Ugh! I mean...
that's how Vin Diesel
must smell.
You know, every morning
he slathers his bum
-with creamy Desitin.
-No.
I fucking swear to God.
He's got rashes down there.
I don't want to know that!
Fucking mental,
that's all I'm saying.
STARLIGHT:
Hmm.
But he really just...
(inhales)
never gives up on you, does he?
Aye.
And he follows you around
like a right little pup.
He's too good for either of us.
Mm.
Yeah.
ELENA:
I'm gonna Postmate Sugarfish.
(shower running)
MAEVE:
What?
I'm gonna Postmate Sugarfish.
-Where's your phone?
-I can't hear you.
Where's...?
Homelander and Queen Maeve.
Oh, my God, they're leaving us.
(screaming)
-WOMAN: What's gonna happen?
-MAN: It's okay, everybody.
-It's okay.
-Hey,
did you say Sugarfish?
WOMAN 2:
Please save us!
-MAEVE: Take these two!
-HOMELANDER: No, no.
-Just these two! Please!
-No! What, so they can tell
the world we left the rest
of them to fucking die?
-No.
-Elena.
-WOMAN 3: Take my daughter!
-MAN 2: Help us!
-You got to help us!
-MAN 3: Don't leave us!
WOMAN 3:
Please!
(crying)
I love you.
(shuddering)
Tell the boys I love them.
(passengers screaming)
I'm gonna show that
to Homelander.
And...
he's either gonna leave us alone
or I'm gonna put it on CNN.
Elena.
This is our out.
I was scared. I...
I know
I should have stood up to him.
I know that.
Elena, I watched
a plane full of people die.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
(exhales)
(birds chirping)
Yeah. Right.
Yo.
Close stitch, but Hughie's okay.
Oh, bien.
Hey,
tell Butcher about the thick
penis around your neck.
(whispers):
Fuck you.
Nah, nah, nah, it's just
Frenchie being Frenchie.
I am sorry.
For a long time,
I was trying to save you.
I thought, uh,
if I did, somehow,
that would make up
for the things I've done.
You never asked to be saved.
You cannot absolve my, uh, sins.
(exhales)
No one can.
I know this now.
So...
I leave you alone.
(vehicle approaching)
Got to go.
(engine shuts off)
(door opens, closes)
MOTHER'S MILK:
Colonel.
Marvin,
where is he?
This way.
Madame Mallory.
Uh, I know I wasn't welcome
at the funeral,
so, all these years, I
couldn't offer my condolences...
Where is he?
(exhales)
Why isn't this man restrained?
No need. I wanted to come.
I don't want to hear
a single goddamn word from you.
(breathing heavily)
(whispering):
I thought this was behind me.
But it's not.
It never is.
(crying)
Then let's both be done with it.
(shuddering)
I know what you have to do.
Do it.
You'd be doing me a favor.
Madame, please.
If I may?
Besides you,
no one wanted him dead more
than me,
but I am begging you
for his life.
I have no choice.
It won't help you.
All you'd be doing
is ending his torment.
You cannot punish him
as much as he punishes himself.
Trust me.
So...
...what exactly
are you proposing we do
with him?
Hey.
I'm so glad you're here.
I want to apologize.
Please, just let me explain.
Flap, flap, flap
goes that little mouth of yours.
You remember you told me
that you don't break easily?
Well, I've been thinking
about that.
A lot.
I will never lie to you again.
I will tell you everything.
(exhales)
Starting with this.
Your grandmother?
My daughter.
Chloe. She died of Alzheimer's
a few years ago.
How old are you?
I was born in 1919.
In Berlin.
Is that you with...?
Heinrich Himmler.
He was a lovely dancer.
And that's Goebbels.
And...
the most important man
in the room...
Frederick Vought.
He gave me the first successful
V injection.
He taught me everything.
And then we fell in love,
and he gave me a daughter.
He made me,
and his genius made you.
Frederick didn't care
about all the fans or stardom
or any of that shallow bullshit.
We are in a war for the culture.
The other races
are grinding us down
and taking
what is rightfully ours,
but we can fight back.
(exhales)
With an army of supermen,
millions strong.
Because that is
Vought's true destiny.
And you will be the man
who will lead us.
You are everything
that we dreamed of.
So I love you
with all of my heart.
How could I not?
Everyone I have ever loved
is in the ground.
And then I found you.
We found each other.
And now neither of us
has to be alone ever again.
And that...
is the truth.
(The Golden Girls theme
playing)
♪ Thank you for being a friend ♪
♪ Traveled down a road
and back again ♪
♪ Your heart is true ♪
♪ You're a pal and a confidant ♪
♪ And if you threw a party ♪
♪ Invited everyone you knew ♪
♪ You would see
the biggest gift ♪
♪ Would be from me ♪
♪ And the card attached
would say ♪
♪ Thank you
for being a friend. ♪
♪ Okay ♪
♪ Word ♪
♪ And ready, set, go ♪
♪ Here comes the A-Train,
Mr. Fleet Feet ♪
♪ Savin' lives, takin' names,
nice and easy ♪
♪ There ain't no day
like a race day, what ♪
♪ Ain't no love
like a raceway, what ♪
♪ I'm the best to ever do it,
y'all crazy ♪
♪ Make way
or you're pushin' up daisies ♪
♪ Bring the heat, now they're
beggin' for some AC ♪
♪ Only place I will lose,
in your daydreams ♪
♪ Ain't no actor, you can get
that action, though ♪
♪ Takin' back my title
like the Alamo ♪
♪ They be tryin' to play me
like a saxophone ♪
♪ But I'm 'bout
to knock 'em down ♪
♪ Like I'm playin' Whac-a-Mole ♪
♪ Y'all won't ever
touch me like an isotope ♪
♪ Presto, yeah,
he's gone in a flash ♪
♪ Skrrt off, zoom,
you all gettin' passed ♪
♪ Leave 'em in the dust
when I dash ♪
♪ Can't be caught, too fast,
Gingerbread Man ♪
♪ Yeah, A-Train,
second to none ♪
♪ If you're lookin' for the
best, I'm the definition ♪
♪ And if anyone play,
I leave 'em under the dust ♪
♪ I'm in love with the crown,
we gonna never split up ♪
♪ I'm-a do it all my way ♪
♪ Pickin' up the pace,
y'all will never stop me ♪
♪ Put me in the wind, fly away ♪
♪ Slipstream, we're takin' off ♪
♪ Why wait? When I'm... ♪
♪ Faster than the speed
of light ♪
♪ Watchin' as your dreams
take flight ♪
♪ As your dreams take flight ♪
♪ I think I should stand
and fight ♪
♪ Then disappear
into the night ♪
♪ Faster than the speed
of light ♪
♪ Watchin' as your dreams
take flight ♪
♪ I think I should stand
and fight ♪
♪ I think, I think I ♪
♪ Then disappear
into the night. ♪