-♪ ♪
-(wind blowing)
(harmonica playing "Piano Man")
(upbeat intro plays)
♪ You're having a hard time and
lately you don't feel so good ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You're getting
a bad reputation ♪
♪ In your neighborhood ♪
(music continues over earbuds)
♪ Don't forget
your second wind ♪
-BUTCHER: Oi. Hughie.
-♪ Sooner or later ♪
-♪ You'll get your second wind ♪
-Hughie.
♪ ♪
(song continues)
♪ It's not always easy to be
living in this world of... ♪
I said, how long
we gonna be sulkin' about
like some poncy
eyeline-wearin' emo twat?
All right, look,
I will say,
I lost me bottle a little bit
when I popped you one.
So, um...
sorry?
There, I said it.
We all square?
(Hughie panting)
-(Hughie yelling)
-MOTHER'S MILK: Hey,
hey, hey, hey!
-Easy, easy, kid. Relax.
-I'll fucking kill you!
Fucking hell.
Kid's stark ravin'.
-(grunting)
-No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, breathe, breathe.
You mind?
-Fuckin' hell.
-Now, breathe.
-Just breathe. Okay?
-Okay.
-Okay. I'm fine.
-All right.
-I'm fine.
-(phone rings)
-BUTCHER: What's the ETA?
MALLORY:
A team's on the way-- they'll
be there in a few hours.
-A few hours?
-I'm a civilian,
I can't just
push a button anymore.
The target's secure?
No one's seen him?
We're three fucking miles
offshore, Grace--
what do you think?
I think if there's a way to
screw this up, you'll find it.
Look, I just want me wife back.
I know.
Bring Langley the terrorist,
and you'll have her.
Hey, you ever hear
of an old Supe called Liberty?
The fuck's that got
to do with anything?
I'm not sure yet.
How's your crew holding up?
Yeah, all good.
Uh, we are having a few laughs
here, I'll tell ya that.
The target is
the girl's brother?
Yeah, so?
You don't think it compromises
her allegiances?
Well...
if it comes to that,
I'll neutralize her.
The compassion you show
your team is truly touching.
(phone beeps off)
It was just
a figure of speech, mate.
(seagulls screeching)
-♪ ♪
-(screeching continues)
(chains jingle quietly)
(door shuts)
(sighs)
You remember in the camp--
you were so hungry
you'd cry all the time
and I snuck into the storage
room to steal you rice?
I took care of you.
I still will.
I also remember the time they
came after you for stealing.
I said no, it was me,
and they broke my hands.
You might be my big sister.
But I protect you too.
We protect each other.
You know...
the Americans will torture me.
-I won't let them.
-(chuckling, sniffs)
How will you stop them?
Hmm?
You have to let me go.
I won't attack anyone.
I won't hurt anyone.
I'm your brother--
we only have each other now.
Please.
I'm sorry.
(door opens)
(door closes)
♪ Boy, you're filthy ♪
-♪ I got what you want ♪
-♪ Boy, you're filthy ♪
♪ I got what you need ♪
-♪ I got what you want ♪
♪ Boy, you're filthy,
stinkin' rich ♪
♪ Boy, you're filthy ♪
-♪ I got what you want ♪
-Thank you.
♪ Boy, you're filthy ♪
♪ I got what you need ♪
-♪ I got what you want ♪
-♪ Boy, you're filthy ♪
-♪ Stinkin' rich ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
I gotta go, man. I'm out.
-♪ When we first started
selling ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
♪ Up in the Bay,
got my pockets so fat ♪
♪ Like the back of Kim K. ♪
♪ I'm-a go ... my whip,
pop my... ♪
-(horn blaring)
-(jackhammer rattling)
-(bus rumbling)
-(siren wailing)
-(gasping)
-(sound fades)
(heart beating rapidly)
(groans softly)
(gasps)
(sound resumes, horns blaring,
jackhammer rattling)
-BECCA: Breakfast is served.
-HOMELANDER: Mmm.
Do you want one or two, buddy?
-Just one.
-Yeah, just one.
You want maple syrup?
-RYAN: Um...
-Yes, please.
A little more.
Mmm.
Thank you. Love it.
(Homelander sighs)
(Becca pouring liquid)
Mm.
This is nice.
-Um, Mama?
-Yeah.
Quiero Raisin Bran, por favor.
BECCA:
Sí.
What is that?
BECCA:
That's Spanish.
Monday mornings
we have breakfast in español.
(groans quietly)
Hey, Ryan.
Do you want to stay in here
and learn Spanish,
or do you want to come
outside and have some fun
with your old man, huh?
BECCA (nervously):
I think that he needs to...
Mom, is it okay
if I go with him?
Yeah, of course it's okay,
right, Mom?
-(rubs hands together)
-Come on.
-Sure.
-(utensils clatter on plate)
There you go, champ.
You guys fucking ready?
Okay, we pan up,
we see Homelander flying
towards Martinez's
Miami mansion.
And Martinez make a run for it.
(as Martinez):
Octavio, vámonos!
Vámonos, mi amigo!
Octavio accelerates
but Homelander
laser blasts out the tires--
bzz...
-Boom!
-(tires screeching)
Martinez gets out of the car,
dazed, looks up...
Homelander.
(as Homelander):
You're under arrest.
Oh-ho-ho.
And he slaps the handcuffs
on Martinez,
the cops take him away,
Homelander turns
to the other heroes.
(as Homelander):
We should work together
more often.
(as Maeve):
You mean like a team-up?
(as Homelander):
Exactly.
All seven of us.
Holy shit.
(sighs)
That is the moment
The Seven became...
The Seven.
Rousing music.
♪ Hans... ♪
♪ Zimmer. ♪
Title card:
Dawn of The Seven.
Cut to black.
-That is amazing.
-Thank you.
ASHLEY:
Wow, I am very impressed.
BOURKE:
Thank you so much.
And, gang,
that's just the teaser.
Look, this is not just
a superhero...
You look like shit.
Had a big night.
And I want to shoot the whole
thing hand-held, right?
very Greengrass, very grounded.
I want to take the audience
and literally put them--
boom-- right there
in the action.
But what's the plan
on Translucent?
That's a great question. Okay,
we're gonna take a stuntman,
put him in a jumpsuit
and just CG him out.
And... fuck,
I don't want to jinx this,
but Lin-Manuel Miranda
wants to do the voice.
-I love Hamilton. Oh, man.
-The world loves Hamilton!
-Oh, my God,
you think he'll do a...
-STORMFRONT: Excuse me.
-I'm sorry to interrupt
this lovefest,
-No, of course.
-I just want to be a part of it.
-Understood.
Um, this... (growls playfully)
-Great work.
-Thank you so much.
This script is a great start.
Really good bones.
Uh, I just have a few headlines.
Yeah, totally.
Listen, we can tweak dialogue
right up to
the day of production.
Yeah, it's not really tweaks.
It's more...
global.
Okay, yeah.
What are we, um...
What are-what are we thinking?
Oh, um, like, uh...
you write all women as either
unknowable Hitchcock bitches
or Michael Bay fuck dolls.
I mean, I get that a lifetime
of jerking off to Transformers
didn't exactly make you popular
with the ladies,
but, um, a little effort
would be nice.
You know what I'm saying?
Um, excuse me,
but I do have two sisters.
Thank you very much.
-Oh.
-And, uh, excuse me,
but Homelander really loves
this script.
-So...
-Oh, okay. Where is he?
(phone buzzing)
STORMFRONT:
Ashley?
Um, okay. Okay. Okay, uh,
just, you know, continue doing
what you're doing.
Um, I just have to get to my...
I have to... I have a...
Uh, I just have to get
to my next thing.
I have a, um,
I have a-a noon...
(breathing rapidly)
Can someone open this, please?!
-ASHLEY: Okay.
-STORMFRONT: Okay!
I got a few more headlines.
-(elevator bell chimes)
-Mr. Edgar.
Sir, if this is all true,
I will get a strategy together
with crisis management and PR.
-We're fine for now, Ashley.
-Sir, is it true?
-What they're saying?
-We're investigating.
Sir, I have to tell you
something.
We have to tell Homelander,
and I have to admit something
to you. I...
You don't have the faintest
idea where Homelander is.
He will know
when I want him to know.
Just keep the rest
of the infants on 99
in check, will you?
(shuddering exhale)
THOMAS ROBERTS:
...and if you are
just tuning in,
we have some major
breaking news.
Superheroes are not born
but made,
in fact created by a chemical
serum, Compound V,
produced and administered
by Vought International...
-(chuckles)
-...the company that has been
the corporate face
of superheroes for decades.
-(sonic boom)
-Now, we don't know
where their superpowers
-actually came from.
-What... did you do?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, come on.
I saw you with the V
in your hand.
Yeah, and you let me
walk away with it, so...
this is kind of on you, too.
If I go down, you come with me.
Pretty sure they'd kill us both.
(sighs heavily)
You don't get it.
You don't fuck with the money.
You never fuck with the money.
We're gonna lose everything--
I mean, cars, houses, bonuses...
There are more important things.
You know, the only people
that say that...
are the people who grew up
with money.
ROBERTS:
...provided evidence
proving Vought has been
administering Compound V
to children for decades.
Our very own reporting suggests
the parents also received
a very generous payment.
-It started when I was nine.
-Now, after the kids
were treated with Compound V,
they were then monitored...
I was at the mall.
And we, uh...
we passed the pet store...
...and I heard the goldfish
begging for their lives.
They were begging.
And after that, I...
The beach, the aquarium,
Red Lobster...
I mean, I thought
I was going crazy, you know?
But my mom said it was a gift.
That I was born this way.
But I wasn't.
It didn't have to be this way.
-I could've been normal.
-ROBERTS: But early reports
seem to suggest the first
manifestation of powers
-can cause fear and anxiety
-(sobbing)
in the affected children,
especially if they are not
carefully guided
through the process.
-(sobbing)
-So far, Vought has refused
to release a statement.
Likewise, Dr. Jonah Vogelbaum,
former C.S.O. at the company,
refusing comment.
He's been in seclusion
since an undisclosed accident
-left him paralyzed.
-(answering machine beeps)
-Uh, hey.
-Is this you?
-Vogelbaum all but disappearing
from public life.
You did it.
We did it.
Um, call me. Call me back
when you get a chance.
-(phone beeps off)
-...on their stock price,
which is already
falling today,
-MOTHER'S MILK: Did what?
-signaling a huge trend
that could be potentially
catastrophic
to Vought's bottom line.
-You did this?
-(newscast continues)
Uh, yeah. S-Starlight did,
mostly, I'm pretty sure,
but I just gave her
an old alley-oop.
(quietly):
Hughie.
Hughie, yes!
-Okay. (laughing)
-Hughie!
Dude, look at what you
fucking did.
-Oh, my God.
-You lads touchin' yer tips?
MOTHER'S MILK:
Look at what the kid just did.
Me and Starlight, but yeah.
-Petit Hughie?
-The fucking kid.
-Mm!
-(kisses)
-Oh, shit.
Yes!
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
-Nice one.
MOTHER'S MILK:
That's all you got?
We've been trying to do
this shit for years.
Vought's finally fucking
going down,
the kid did it,
and "nice one"?
All right, real nice one.
You can't even give me this,
can you?
Not one goddamn win.
I'll tell you what.
When we're all done here,
I'll buy you a nice, big,
family size bottle
of top-shelf lube
and I'll tickle your balls
till you beg me to stop
and even then I won't.
I just won't do it.
But right now, we got
a Supe terrorist below deck
and shit could go sideways
just like... (snaps)
So all of ya, keep your fucking
eyes on the ball, yeah?
(pats arm)
Don't worry about him.
Yeah, fuck him.
You did great.
(birds chirping,
dog barks in distance)
Isn't this great?
-Yeah.
-(Homelander chuckles)
Your mom ever bring you up here?
No.
Nah.
Of course not.
You see, that is why a boy
needs his father.
Hey, I think it's time.
Yeah. You ready?
Um... ready for what?
To jump.
Wait, you can't be serious.
I'm not going to jump.
Ryan, you're my son.
You can fly, just like me.
I-I... I don't want to.
You take a big, deep breath,
you step off
and your body will just
do the rest.
It'll just take over.
But I-I can't fly.
I'll just fall
right off of here and get...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, buddy.
You're gonna love it.
I promise.
I'm nothing like you.
I-I can't fly.
You can. You can.
I promise you can.
(breathes deeply)
Dad, please.
Please, don't make me jump.
(clicks tongue):
Aw.
Buddy.
You called me Dad.
(chuckles)
(Ryan gasps, screams)
(sputters)
-(door opens)
-BECCA: Ryan.
God. Ryan!
Hey. Hey, hey.
What did you do?
It's fine. It's a 20-foot drop.
Relax.
Inhuman fucking monster.
-Come here.
-Don't help him up.
-Let him do it himself.
-Come here. Baby, hey.
Hey, Ryan, I need you
to wake up.
Baby, can you hear me?
I'm right here.
-I don't think he's breathing.
-(laughing)
-He's fine.
-I don't think he's breathing.
-I don't think he's... (gasps)
-(gasps) Mom?
-Hi. Hi.
-Look. See?
-Told ya.
-Hi, sweetie.
Are you hurt? (kisses)
Does anything feel broken?
-Oh, for God's sake, broken?
-Let me see.
Come on, look at him.
There's not a scratch on him.
You know why?
'Cause he's my son.
And you, you... (scoffs)
...you're raising him
to be a pussy.
You don't get to tell me
how to raise my son.
I'm his father.
You don't get to say that
after what you did.
What I did to you...
was give you a son,
that you are raising
-like a little girl.
-(Ryan breathing rapidly)
Let go of me.
-He's mine.
-Get your hands off of her!
(Ryan breathing rapidly)
(rapid breathing continues)
Good boy.
See?
-I told you.
-What?
You're just like me, Ryan.
No, I'm not like you.
I'm nothing like you!
I fucking hate you!
Leave us alone!
Hey, hey, it's okay.
I'm not angry.
-Ryan.
-Go away!
-Buddy, it's o...
-Leave us alone!
Ryan, this is a good thing.
(door opens)
(door closes)
So, um...
These are horrible,
powdered cheese things,
but, um, if you're hungry?
Fuck you.
So you do speak English.
Thirsty?
-(slurps)
-You know,
the way you talk
with your sister...
it's no sign language
I ever seen.
I just want to help her.
I can help her.
Tu comprends?
You understand?
The night our parents
were murdered...
...Kimiko just stopped talking.
Can't talk.
She's never made a sound since.
In the camp,
we were alone week after week,
just the two of us, for years.
We... came up a language
so we could get through it.
(laughs softly)
I-It saved us.
Both of us.
Will you teach me?
(slurping)
(sighs)
(clears throat, sniffs)
(quietly):
Please.
Fuck you.
I think your sister
is very special.
And she loves you very much.
(grunts)
(straining)
(can crinkling)
(groans in pain)
(breathing rapidly)
I don't know anything about
this Compound V monkey business.
If someone gave it
to my little Maeve,
I sure as hell didn't know.
-Bullshit he didn't know.
-(turns off TV)
I remember this one weekend
where he made me do
three mall appearances
and a photo shoot
for Teen Vogue,
all to get the cash for
my braces, which he then blew
at the five-dollar table
at Circus Circus.
ELENA:
Maybe this is what
we've been waiting for.
What do you mean?
They've lied to you from
the beginning, all of them.
You don't owe them anything.
Maybe this is our chance
to leave while we can.
Elena...
if we do that,
you know what'll happen.
I'll call you back.
(phone beeps off,
sets phone on table)
Not, uh, interrupting, am I?
No, of course not.
Great.
It's funny, you know, uh...
...of all the people here,
I've known you the longest.
Yeah.
Sometimes it, um,
just seems like you're
the only person I can lean on.
Yeah, I...
I-I feel the same way.
You do?
Of course.
(inhales deeply)
(sighs heavily)
You...
Oh... fuck.
Life, huh?
(exhales)
(patting hand)
It's crazy.
(sniffs)
Who's Elena?
Elena's an old friend.
Since when do you have friends?
I was just venting
about all this fucking bullshit.
What bullshit?
Wait, you haven't heard?
Where have you been?
(helicopter blades whirring)
What the fuck?
MAN (over speaker):
This is the NYPD.
This boat's been
reported stolen,
and you're all under arrest.
I repeat. This is the NYPD.
This boat's been
reported stolen...
I thought you said this boat
belongs to a friend.
Gather on deck and get
your hands in the air now.
Well, a stranger is just
a friend you ain't met yet.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Don't fuck this up.
BUTCHER:
I ain't gonna fuck it up.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Vought's almost toast,
we're almost home free...
I said I ain't gonna fuck it up,
all right.
-(radio clicks)
-Ahoy, gents.
I am the captain
of My Big Wet Dream.
I'm holding papers,
signed by the owner,
for the lease of this vessel.
So there must be some kind
of misunderstanding...
Look out!
(water splashing)
Get his hands!
(Kenji grunts)
Time to go!
(frustrated grunting)
Hey, what are you doing?
We gotta help 'em.
BUTCHER:
Trust me, they're already dead.
-You don't know that.
-(engine starting)
-We have to try.
-Hughie.
Literally everyone
is on their way here right now.
We stay here, we die, too.
(engine accelerating)
(gasping breaths)
(water splashes)
What?
I wasn't the one
who fucked that up.
(seagulls screeching)
♪ ♪
EAGLE:
I know how you feel.
I'm a freak, too.
Oh, you shoot a fucking
bow and arrow.
I'm amphibious.
Okay, just...
just give me the phone.
Cancel the call.
Postmating Papa John's
isn't gonna help.
How do you know what helps?
You don't know
anything about me.
(doorbell rings)
Let's just recite
the Fifteen Tenets, together.
-(doorbell ringing)
-No, fuck you
and your creepy shit, Eagle.
I'm hungry.
Deep, it's time.
Time for what?
For you. It's your time.
To get back into The Seven.
What?
This came from Alastair himself.
EAGLE:
Holy shit.
Who?
Alastair Adana, the...
the leader of the Church.
He sits in the First Chair.
Cool.
Guys, with everything going on,
I just, I don't think
I can do it right now.
EAGLE:
No, Deep.
This is your journey.
You're ready.
You have been ready all along.
Now, get out there
and be a hero.
My dad always used to say,
"Where there's smoke,
there's fire."
So Vought lied to us
about Compound V.
What else are they lying
to us about?
We're down 68%
in morning trading,
20% in the last 15 minutes.
-It hits 19, start a buyback.
-Yes, sir.
Jesus. What about
the pharmaceuticals?
Pfizer's circling, "dismayed
at our lack of ethics."
BARASSI:
Investor lawsuits,
breach of fiduciary duty,
non-disclosure.
SKILTON:
We have exposure
for fraud, assault,
infliction of bodily harm--
all policy exclusions,
no coverage.
We have two options.
Option one, deny.
High risk, high reward.
But if we deny
and they nail us,
if there is a legit
whistleblower,
there's no coming back.
That's bankruptcy,
criminal charges,
ten to 15 for everyone
in this room.
BARASSI:
Option two, mea culpa.
PRESTIA:
They've called it.
Trading's halted.
(Skilton sighs)
Stan.
We got to put out a statement.
Which one is it?
Stan.
A power drink can, Frenchie?
You're a goddamn idiot.
I was trying to help her.
Where the hell are your mates?
New deal--
you gotta bring him in.
Grace,
we're three miles offshore.
You just crashed
a police helicopter.
Not exactly keeping
a low profile.
All right,
where do you want us to go?
CIA safe house Hazlet.
Be there in 30.
And Butcher?
Yeah?
Please be careful.
I will.
(phone beeps off)
-(tosses phone)
-Fuck me.
(phone dialing)
AUTOMATED MESSAGE:
Please leave
your name and number
-and a message after the beep.
-(beeps)
Hey, uh, Annie, it's me again.
I was just wondering, have
you ever seen the music video
for that Billy Joel song
"You're Only Human"?
There's this kid
and he's climbing up a bridge
and he's-he's gonna
kill himself,
but then Billy Joel
steps out with his harmonica
and tells him stop,
you just have to wait
for your second wind,
and now I-I feel like
I'm-I'm that kid
and I'm gonna drown,
and...
...and thank God
I found my second wind
because it's-it's you.
(sniffles)
You're my second wind.
Um,
look, I know it's exciting,
uh, taking down Vought
and being like James Bond
and everything,
but you've got to be careful,
because that stuff can go
to shit really quick...
and you wind up hurting
the people that...
you love.
Like the way that I hurt you.
Um...
Anyhoo... (sniffles)
...that's all I wanted to say.
Second wind.
(quietly):
Fuck.
Um, okay, thanks.
-Bye.
-(phone beeps off)
(sniffles)
(chuckles softly)
♪ ♪
EDGAR:
I know I don't come up
to 99 enough
and I apologize for that.
But times like this
tend to give us clarity,
don't they?
You and me are partners,
after all.
A symbiotic part
of a larger thing,
a living thing named Vought.
And that's how
we'll get through this,
together, as Vought.
But, sir...
...I got to say...
...we didn't know about
this Compound V shit.
-None of us.
-EDGAR: Is that so?
Well, we're all victims here,
A-Train,
but we'll get to the bottom
of it, I promise.
Right now, catching
this Super terrorist is...
HOMELANDER:
Villain.
Super... villain.
Sure. Whatever.
It must be our priority,
and it changes the conversation.
So you want us
to go out there?
Now?
I mean, we still need to be
prepped by Legal and PR.
(scoffs)
We'll be eaten alive out there.
-There's no time for that.
-MAEVE: Well, I'm sorry,
but I don't think
we have to damage control
your fuck-up.
Hey, guys.
Enough.
We gotta pull together here.
-Thank you, Homelander.
-HOMELANDER: Shh! Not you.
Us.
The Seven.
See, it doesn't matter
who made us
or how we got here,
the point is...
we are here.
Together.
Family.
You guys...
...you are my real family.
This guy...
he doesn't care about us.
We're not his partners,
we're his product.
So who gives a shit if Vought
burns to the fucking ground?
You should think before you
say something you don't mean.
Really, should I?
We are not Vought.
You see, companies,
they come and go,
but talent...
talent is forever.
The world still needs
superheroes,
and that, family,
that's what we are.
So let's get out there
and do what it is we do.
Let's take this cocksucker down.
(indistinct chatter)
Fuck Vought, huh?
I did not see that
coming from you.
Maybe you don't know me
that well.
Maybe I don't.
MOTHER'S MILK:
How far?
A mile, right there.
-What the fuck was that?
-What the hell was that?
(loud thud)
Take the wheel!
(grunts)
-(engine whining)
-We lost power.
Everyone, off the boat, now!
Frenchie, grab the winch.
Come on, let's go,
let's go, let's go! Get in!
Come on, come on!
Let's go, let's go!
-(gun clicking)
-Fuck!
-Go on. Frenchie, start it up!
-Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
♪ ♪
Look, there.
Head for the storm drain.
(whale singing)
Oh, shit.
♪ ♪
(whale groans)
HUGHIE: Butcher!
What are you doing?
Butcher!
(yelling indistinctly)
Stop...!
(whale bellows)
(liquid running)
(whale bellows weakly)
(grunting)
(spits, pants)
(strained grunting)
(gasps)
Fucking diabolical.
(gasping rapidly)
-(grunts)
-Where's Hughie?
-(high-pitched ringing)
-BUTCHER (distantly): Hughie!
Oh, geez.
You all right?
Come on, son.
We got to leg it-- Deep's here,
and The Seven
won't be far behind.
Um, you know what?
Okay, you guys go ahead.
You guys go ahead. I'm good.
Eh? What?
Just gonna sit here and wait,
i-if you don't mind.
What the fuck
are you waiting for?
(sighs)
My second wind.
All right, son.
Come on.
-Come on.
-Get your fucking hands
off of me!
Geez.
All right, fine. Suit yourself.
All right!
Come on, let's go.
(panting)
(grunts)
Whoa.
We can't leave the kid, man.
Pinocchio is staying put.
Have at it.
(squelching)
Ugh.
Hey, kid.
What are you doing here?
(Mother's Milk grunts)
Uh...
(sighs heavily)
You ain't going...
I ain't going.
(sniffs)
They're gonna be here
any second.
MOTHER'S MILK:
Probably.
(liquid dripping)
Asshole.
Yup.
(grunting)
This way.
(quietly):
Frenchie.
-Hey, Butcher.
-(gasping)
Petit Hughie.
Hey, the kid's falling apart.
You know that, right?
Well, what'd you expect?
He's a fucking civilian.
No, no, no, it's not just him.
It's all of us.
Move the feet.
Just move the feet. Come on.
Move.
MOTHER'S MILK:
We're at our breaking point,
at each other's throats,
and you keep pushing us
and pushing.
-It's like...
-Right over the fucking
finish line.
We just need to keep
our shit together
a little bit longer.
Okay?
We hand the cunt over,
and I get Becca
and you get your girls.
-Butcher, Butcher,
-We're right fucking...
-Butcher, Butcher.
-we're right there.
Hughie's not gonna make it.
And you need that kid,
more than any one of us.
He's your canary.
My canary?
You let your canary die,
how you gonna know
when you've gone too far?
Oh.
I mean, what a load of bollocks.
Hell, I tried, all right?
The kid doesn't want
a part of me,
so fuck him.
Come on.
-(flies buzzing)
-(softly): Lucy.
I promise
we'll harvest your blubber.
-HOMELANDER: Jesus Christ.
-(Deep continues indistinctly)
(Deep sniffles)
Deep.
-Homelander.
-Hey.
-What happened?
They killed her.
They fucking killed her, man.
-What?
-I just was trying to help out.
-You know, I got
some intel on the boat.
-Okay...
We started to cut them off
and then, fuck,
they just ran right into her.
I'm so sorry. I was just,
like, gonna try to stop them.
-I tried to cut them off...
-Okay. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
So you're saying th-there's
people with the terrorist?
Look at me. You're saying
they're not alone?
I think so.
All right. Did you get
a good look at them, or...?
DEEP:
Not really.
I was too busy
worrying about Lucy.
Oh, Jesus. Right. Lucy.
DEEP:
But I think they went off
in the storm drains.
Can't be too far.
Uh, who invited you, exactly?
Starlight.
Listen, what I did
was unforgivable.
-Oh, God.
-I'm going to do everything
in my power
-to renew my light.
-Mm.
Not just for you
but for all the female people
-that I've offended.
-STORMFRONT: "Renew your light"?
Did you just fucking join
the Church of the Collective?
-Maybe.
-You're an idiot.
Hey, easy on the religious
persecution, okay, new girl?
Starlight, maybe one day
you can welcome me back
into The Seven, but I know
my road is long and hard.
Are you serious?
There is no fucking way
you're coming back.
There's no need for language.
HOMELANDER:
All right, enough.
We do not have time for this.
Look, I am with you, sister,
but first we have to go get
the terrorist, okay?
All right,
everyone in the tunnels.
-Yeah, everyone in the tunnels.
-Not you.
Anyone gets eyeballs
on the target,
he's mine, understood?
DEEP:
Go get 'em.
Noir.
All right, you...
need to hang back a bit. Okay?
-Okay.
-Still got some work to do
with the ladies,
but it's going to be okay.
You'll be back in no time.
-Really?
-Sure.
One other thing. You, uh,
you ripped your vest.
What?
Your gill is showing.
Cover it up.
It's disgusting.
(grunts, gasping)
-(groaning)
-(heart beating)
(groans)
Come on.
Come on!
(gasping)
(heart beating)
(gasps, moans)
(groans)
-(heart beating rapidly)
-(groans)
You okay?
-(heart beat stops)
-(sighs) Yep.
(chuckles)
I just need a little rehab.
I'll be fine.
(sniffs)
-Yeah.
-(A-Train exhales)
I know you will, A-Train.
(A-Train chuckles)
(footsteps splashing)
(panting)
(approaching footsteps)
You got my message.
Annie, I...
(grunts)
(Hughie coughing)
(Hughie groans,
coughs in distance)
(coughing)
HOMELANDER:
Oh, come on.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
-(gasps)
-This guy?
Again?
-I did not know...
-Shut it.
What, do you got rocks
in your fucking head?
Come here.
All right.
I'd like you to do something
for me, okay?
Kill him.
Uh, n...
Wait.
N-N... he...
-HOMELANDER: He...?
STARLIGHT: He's wanted.
Shouldn't we...
take him to the police?
HOMELANDER:
Yes, he is. Yes, we should.
Kill him.
Right now.
(sighs)
Chicks, right, Hughie?
Oh, for God's sakes.
Come on, it's easy.
Hands in the air,
like you just don't care.
(chuckles)
Kill.
Do it.
More incentive? Okay.
You kill him
or I'll fucking kill you both.
Do it.
("You're Only Human"
music fades up)
♪ ...truly call your own ♪
♪ Don't forget
your second wind... ♪
-Oi. Cunt.
-(music stops)
William?
(laughs):
What a surprise.
Hey.
You know, I had
a great breakfast
with your wife this morning.
Pancakes.
Mmm. Delicious.
Yeah?
Eat this, motherfucker.
(grunting)
(crackling)
(distant horns honking,
car alarms blaring)
Please.
Don't.
Come on, Hughie.
Before that cunt gets out.
Come on.
♪ ♪
Please.
I love you.
-I love you, too.
-STORMFRONT: Hey, guys.
(electrical crackling)
Call the foul!
(kids screaming)
(game continues on TV)
(girl screams)
Dad, no!
(screams)
-BOY: Daddy, you okay?! Dad!
-(girl screaming)
-(electrical crackling)
-(thudding)
(grunting)
(grunts)
-(man screaming)
-(car alarm wailing)
(woman screams)
(electrical crackling)
(grunting quietly)
(grunting)
(snapping)
(screaming)
Aw.
Can't do your magic little hand
thingy anymore?
-How come?
-(sobbing)
(grunts)
(choking quietly)
STORMFRONT:
Open your eyes.
-(chokes)
-Open your eyes.
I like to see the light go out.
Fucking yellow bastard.
(bones cracking)
(Stormfront scoffs)
(whooshing)
I said he was mine.
You snooze, you lose, Gramps.
(sirens wailing)
(quiet chatter)
(baby crying)
EDGAR:
I know the news of Compound V
came as a shock to everyone.
As you can imagine,
this has been a very difficult
day for the Vought family.
Our focus now will be
to learn the truth.
As I said, we are conducting
a robust investigation
into Compound V,
but let me be clear:
I had no knowledge whatsoever.
We believe it was the work
of a small,
disaffected group of scientists
led by former Vought employee
Madelyn Stillwell.
But sadly, there are more
important matters at hand.
Everyone at Vought
sends their thoughts
and prayers
to those families
that were affected today.
Though it is important
to acknowledge
that this tragic event
could have been far worse,
today's attack underscores
just how dangerous the threat
of Super terrorists has become.
And, at a time like this,
America needs its heroes
more than ever.
We live in a dangerous world.
Our brave heroes were already
fighting terrorists overseas,
but now, America faces this war
on a different front:
right here at home.
These enemies
will stop at nothing
to infiltrate our borders
and attack our citizens.
Our superheroes are
the last line of defense.
And today, the death toll
would have been much higher
had it not been for the brave
actions of our newest hero,
Stormfront,
who stopped the terrorist
before he could take
more innocent lives.
(Edgar continues indistinctly)
♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen--
Stormfront.
(crowd applauding, cheering)
(applause, cheering continues)
STORMFRONT:
Thank you.
But we all know
who the real heroes
of this group are, right?
The people you see behind you,
the people who are struggling
every day.
So let's give them all a hand.
(applause)
(applause continues)
(crowd clamoring)
MAN:
Stormfront, over here.
MAN 2:
Stormfront, over here, please!
(applause and clamor continue)
♪ ♪